PEACE AND PROSPERITY
RETURN OUR HOMELAND
- Protect His Majesty!
- Yes!
Qianlong,
the brothers of the Red Flower Society...
will take your worthless life tonight!
- Set sail!
- Aye!
Chan Ga-Lok?
You dare assassinate the emperor?!
You're obviously a Han Chinese,
yet want to be Emperor of Manchuria.
Tonight, I'll take your worthless life,
for the sake of millions of Han people.
Take care, Your Majesty!
Why...
aren't I allowed to sleep well?
- Your slaves deserve death!
- Listen!
Send for the Governor
of Nine Gates, Ordo.
May I ask if this gentleman
is here to buy a sword?
No.
If you're not here to buy a sword,
then what can I do for you?
My master has nightmares every night
and suffers from severe insomnia.
If he's sick,
he should see a doctor.
We're just blacksmiths here.
It's no use seeing a doctor.
My master said,
"just kill the demon in my dreams".
Only then can he sleep soundly.
Who is your master?
My master is Qianlong.
Five days ago, I killed a member of the
Red Flower Society known as Thunderhand.
What?!
You killed Fourth Brother Man?
I found a letter on his body.
I know the Red Flower Society has left
a register in the hands of a swordsmith.
That's right!
I've already sent the register away.
Don't expect to get hold of it!
- That so?
- Let's avenge Fourth Brother!
- Let's go.
- Yes!
Tiger Lei's so rich.
What business does he do in Shandong?
He used to be a bandit.
I heard that he used his money
to organise this sports meeting.
So what if he has money?
What's so great about being rich?
Those who have dirty money
ride roughshod over the people.
After buying up all the fields,
in just three months the land in
Guangdong became too expensive.
Nothing can be done!
The Lord Prefect and Tiger Lei
are in collusion with each other.
How can he not be arrogant?!
(Mandarin)
Miss, let's go.
It seems they all think
really badly of my father.
Miss,
you're only realising this now?
Does anyone here know us?
Don't be afraid...
Let's go quickly, though!
That girl is beautiful.
Let's go have some fun!
- Great...
- Let's go!
Look there,
should we stay and take a look?
Stop looking!
Let's go back quickly!
- Little girl, you out all alone?
- What're you doing?
- Come on...
- Go away!
Let's talk...
- Turns out she's a northern girl!
- She's real pretty!
Don't bully me!
We can speak Cantonese!
Ooh! That's even better!
There won't be any misunderstanding!
Hey, don't bother my sister!
- She's your sister?
- I know him!
He's that guy!
How can he have a sister?
I know you better!
You're the bastard who specialises
in pimping for his boss!
- You talk to us like that?!
- Go on!
Come on!
Fight with our boss?
You want to die?!
- Beat him!
- Beat me up?!
Fighting here?
Want to go to the Ministry of Justice?
It's nothing to do with him!
Hey,
today's my first day on duty.
Can you give me face?
Ask him to give you face.
Outrageous!
Fighting here?
Want to go to the Ministry of Justice?
Sorry...
- No fighting!
- Yeah-yeah...
Sorry!
Hey, kid!
We didn't get to finish our fight.
If you have the guts,
go and join the competition.
Want to compete with me?
Our Master Sing is a gold medal athlete
from St. Joseph's College in Shanghai.
Master Yuk, you don't know how
to play the foreign devils' games.
Are you stupid?
How could Master Yuk not know?
He's so good at martial arts.
Hey, Northern girl!
Your "big brother" doesn't dare!
Hey, don't talk nonsense!
He's not my...
Then make your move!
One foot eight.
One foot eight:
the exact length of a snake spear.
The next one up is awesome.
Three consecutive gold medals from
St. Joseph's College in Shanghai.
Terrific!
- Two feet two, next up.
- A record breaker...
and a reputation well-deserved.
Look at this next one,
he's wearing a long jacket!
No information.
Let's see how he jumps...
- He stuttered!
- Are your feet weak?
Hey, hurry up and jump!
Walking this slowly,
how long will it take you to cross?
- I'll give you a ride!
- Still haven't jumped?
He's jumping!
What force!
He jumped over the sandbox!
How stylish!
Although you're just an ant,
I won't bully you.
Kid, the next event is
a four-man relay race.
I won't lose to you.
Let's go!
The relay race needs four.
- How can we three run?
- What do we do?
Young lady, the next race is a relay
that takes four people to run.
There are only three of us,
can you help?
- Me?
- Yeah.
I'm such a slow runner.
Would you be slower than an ant?
- About the same.
- That's good enough! Come on!
You, first leg.
- What leg do I run?
- You? First leg!
Get ready!
Start!
Hurry up...
Faster...
- I can't do it!
- You can do it!
Hey, get up!
Run faster!
She's so slow, we're gonna lose--
Look at me.
Run faster!
- Whoa! The pigtail's standing up!
- Yeah, the pigtail's vertical!
Hurry up...
Faster...
Hurry up!
Faster!
Wow! He's flying over grass!
The double event champion-youth with
the long-jacket must participate next year.
The three-time consecutive champions
can go back to Shanghai and eat shit!
Miss, thanks for your help.
You have a share in this medal.
I give it to you.
- How about you?
- Pfft! It belongs to Tiger Lei.
I don't want it!
- What's your surname?
- My surname's Chan.
Go to hell!
Hey, why are you hitting people...?
How dare you ruin my face?
Teach him a lesson!
I like nothing more than fighting.
Bring it on!
Come on!
Well?
Still want to fight?
Thank you...
so much for supporting my fight.
Thanks!
What's this fight about?
Who's fighting?
They were fighting.
I've arrested them for you.
- Thanks for your help.
- You're welcome.
- Take them all back!
- Go!
Take them back!
- What is it?
- You're going, too!
- I'm going, too?
- Right!
- I was only helping! Are you serious?
- Get moving...
Hey, wait a minute!
- Hey, let's go!
- What's your hurry?
LEI RESIDENCE
Fucking hell!
Motherfucker! Fuck!
How dare he refuse to sell the
Central Primary School to me?!
Isn't he hitting a louse
on a tiger's head?
Go on!
Tell the Lord Prefect...
to frame him for being a pirate...
and chop off Principal Wong's head!
Yes, Master!
Master, the past few days I've heard many
people outside are dissatisfied with us.
So what if they're dissatisfied?
Am I afraid of them?
Master,
of course, you're not afraid.
However, as the old saying goes:
"When in Rome, do as the Romans do."
If we want to develop in Guangdong,
we must integrate with them, right?
- How do we do that?
- Master, I have an idea.
If Master wishes to settle down
here and make a name for himself,
why not hold a martial arts contest
here for the young miss' hand?
This is very unfair to
Tingting in my opinion.
- Master, you must act decisively.
- Fuck!
As the old saying goes:
"a woman's heart is with her husband."
When a daughter gets married
she won't remember her own parents.
Master, do you think your in-laws
have received any benefits...
from you and your wife?
Fucking hell!
You said what I was thinking!
That's what I'm going to do!
Brilliant, Master!
Brilliant!
Then it's decided.
A martial arts contest for a groom!
JIANGNING YAMEN (COURT)
Master Yuk, we're screwed!
Our names are held in
the Ministry of Justice.
If word gets out, we're screwed!
Right! If my dad finds out,
he'll scold me to death!
Don't worry.
I just scribbled some names.
Your name's Yuen Kwai,
your name's Lau Chun-Wai.
What about you...?
I'm the impressive Wong...
Jing.
Hey,
I'm going back to the store.
My mum'll scold me if I don't show.
- That's all for now.
- Master Yuk...
That white girl's hair is rather
interesting, so curly...
Her glasses are even more interesting,
so dark...
I guess in that case,
I can just paint these black.
Jeez, I can't see anything!
The aim is to look stylish.
Oh, so she's blind!
Proprietress!
Trying to scare me to death?!
You look very stylish
wearing those glasses.
Your voice is very sexy.
Are you here to sell
fabrics or make jokes?
Aren't I taking care of you?
The cloth inside is more expensive.
The cloth outside is much cheaper.
- Which would you like to buy?
- I'll buy one from outside.
- You want one from the outside?
- Yes.
I won't give you credit!
That's right, this one...
- This one?
- Yes, thanks.
How much?
I want to buy...
This much...
Right here, thanks.
- There?
- No, here...
- Just here...
- There?
- Yeah...
Buying it to wipe your nose?
Robbery?!
Hey!
- Hey, this white--
- Your head's white!
- No, Mum! This white--
- Don't be rude!
It really hurts when you hit me!
- Mum, you're so stylish.
- Hurry, go get the scales.
OK!
- Scales?
- My cloth is calculated by the pound.
Why else would you take so much?
You can see it?
I guessed, though I couldn't see.
Would a blind person hit you twice?
In that case,
I paid with those two hits!
Trying to leave?
Eat this!
Shit!
You killed someone, now we're in trouble!
Relax, it's two inches short.
Measure if you don't believe me.
Really?
Measure carefully.
Mustn't let him bleed.
Don't bleed...
Whoa!
Still a long way to go.
A full six inches difference!
The white guy has a deep throat!
He deserves bad luck!
I'm in a good mood today,
we're closing.
Mum, yesterday you closed in a bad mood,
today you're closing in a good mood.
Of course,
your father's coming back today.
How can I be in the mood
to do anything but close?
Mum... I met a girl today
who's very charming...
- and very beautiful.
- Really?
Then take tomorrow off.
Close the store again?!
Master Yuk!
Hey, Master Yuk!
- It's bad...
- What's the matter?
The Lord Prefect's here and he's
talking to the master in the hall.
Shit!
What do you know about it?
I got into a fight today.
Don't worry,
Mum'll stand up for you.
Lord Prefect, fellow citizens...
I must give you an explanation.
Brother Fong,
you truly are a man of principle.
I truly am ashamed.
- When the two of them return, I will--
- So many people here?
Oh, Lord Prefect, fellow citizens...
Give face to this little woman.
Whatever's happened,
I, Miu Chui-Fa will take care of it.
Of course, it's your responsibility!
You... beat the white guy
to look like a pig's head!
- Huh?
- Furthermore...
That cloth you sold me, turns out
it'd been used for wiping the floor!
She thinks my wife looks like a radish!
No matter what,
she refuses to sell cloth to my wife.
Not only that, the other day
she laughed at me for being stupid.
- This is outrageous!
- Speak!
What else do you have to say?
If I'd known about this,
I wouldn't have come home!
"Mushroom", serve the punishment!
Beat me again?
Master, give me face.
Give you face?
You beat the young mistress,
no need to give me face.
Dad, don't hit Mum!
If you want, hit me!
See how your son respects you.
May I ask,
is this the Fong household?
- This is the Fong household?
- Yeah.
Hmph! Turns out your name's Fong Sai-Yuk,
not Wong Jing!
Why do you call him Wong Jing?
This morning he got into a fight.
When I took him to the Ministry of
Justice, he said his name was Wong Jing.
You bastard!
- Does it hurt?
- Ow, that hurts!
I withstood most of it for you,
it hurts me more.
Mum,
Dad doesn't know martial arts.
Why can't you avoid him each time?
Of course, I have to give him face
in front of others, silly boy!
A man's status within
the family is very noble.
Whoa!
Very noble, indeed!
Not going to bed yet?
I don't know how you teach your son.
Even though he's older,
you still protect him.
He's a grown-up now and
needs to be independent.
You're often at work all
day and don't come home.
If my son doesn't keep me company,
who will?
And when you do come home,
you listen to the villagers' nonsense...
and beat me like this.
You don't think of me as your wife,
at all!
Listen to me.
I won't listen.
I won't listen...
"The beauty rolls up the beaded curtain."
He's reciting poetry again.
"She sits,
her eyebrows knitted deep."
"But visible are traces of tears."
"Not knowing who her heart hates."
I can't resist him, I really can't.
He's so stylish.
Why do I get excited for no reason
every time he recites poetry?
Giddy, dizzy, dead...
Was I right about you?
Right.
Then why don't you go to sleep?
"PUNCH THE GUANGDONG PROVINCE"
"KICK THE SUZHOU AND HANGZHOU STATES"
They're clearly treading on us
Cantonese by hanging these out!
Master,
how well written are these couplets?
As soon as they were suspended, you
could see how it stoked the fire in them.
Tingting...
Dad, I don't want to be the
bride in a martial arts contest!
You're not fit to talk to me!
If you keep pushing me,
I'll just leave!
If you keep talking,
I'll beat you to death!
- Fucking hell!
- My Lord!
You're pushing Tingting too hard.
Don't I get a say in the matter?
When I'm talking,
why don't you shut up?
I'm doing all this to win people's hearts.
If I don't,
how will I be able to stand here?
- Don't you get it?
- Understand! I do understand!
- Get one over on that bastard!
- What are you laughing at?
I'm not putting a show for you!
Fucking hell!
Hey, Mum!
You sure you can stand this?
Yes, I'm sure!
- You really can stand it!
- I can!
- So are you ready?
- I am.
Hey, are you sure
you're doing it right?
Is this how white people curl their hair?
It's more like a barbecue!
Yes, all white people
curl their hair like this.
Hey,
curl my eyelashes later, too.
Sure,
I can curl your armpit hair, as well!
How disgusting, you naughty boy!
If your father could see me now...
I wonder if he'd recite poetry to me?
Of course,
he'd even recite English poetry.
English poetry?
I'd get even more excited hearing that!
- Son, how do you recite English poetry?
- I know.
"Wonderful!"
It's wonderful to recite.
- How come you know foreign speak?
- Siu Fong-Fong taught me--
Sai-Yuk!
Hey, your father's here!
Hurry up!
Quickly now!
Hurry and it'll be fine.
- Hubby!
- What're you doing in there?
Hubby, you mustn't come in.
I'll be pretty in a bit!
- Faster now...
- Mum, don't move until it's finished.
- Sai-Yuk?
- Hubby, you mustn't come in yet!
I'll be pretty real soon!
Oh, bugger...
- What's the matter?
- It's on fire...
Why do you look like that?
I can't recite poetry in this mess.
I'm off to study.
I'm going into the city.
Want me to buy anything for you?
I was pretty a moment ago!
Dear fellow countrymen...
I, Tiger Lei,
have just arrived in your noble realm.
It's important that
we all live in harmony.
I arranged this martial arts
contest to find a groom.
Whoever grabs the
embroidered ball will win.
During the contest,
only one foot can touch the ground.
If both feet touch the ground,
you lose.
Whoever can defeat my wife,
Li Xiaohuan...
can marry my daughter,
Lei Tingting.
If anyone during the contest
is injured or killed by my wife,
I, Tiger Lei,
will not be held responsible.
Let me now introduce my wife,
Li Xiaohuan.
Whoa, she's stunningly beautiful!
If she marries me, I'll make sure
she doesn't get a good night's sleep!
- You sure you're capable?
- If not, I'll ask for your help!
Great...
Let's sign up first!
Go sign up!
Those three are of the same mind.
Hey, "Bronze Hammer Six"!
Go tell Master Yuk!
- OK...
- Excuse me, please...
- Where's Sai-Yuk?
- Hitting the books inside.
- I'm going to the dye mill.
- Come back soon.
"Comes in the night - one, two, three;
fallen flowers - four, five, six."
"One, two, three, four, five..."
Six!
Whoa! So many?
Who is it?
Master Yuk, it's just us!
Come outside...
Sai-Yuk.
"Spring sleeps, unaware of dawn."
"Everywhere,
the birds are heard singing."
"The sound of wind and rain
comes in the night."
"How many fallen flowers..."
- Dad, you're here?!
- Sai-Yuk, sit down.
Dad's going to the city now.
How long will you be gone?
I'll really miss you.
Try your best to study well.
OK!
Today's not for studying!
Hey!
What do you want?
Tiger Lei's holding a martial arts
contest to find a groom.
His daughter's very pretty.
- Really?
- Yeah, he actually said...
"Punch the Guangdong province,
kick the Suzhou and Hangzhou states."
Ridiculous!
What a big mouth!
Hey,
what do you think about this?
What do I think?
I should keep studying!
Are you kidding me?!
My dad's inside.
If he found out, he'd beat me to death!
Hey, Master Yuk,
what are you doing up there?
Master Yuk, are you really going to
let an outsider tread on us like that?
Master Yuk,
you'll only be out for a bit.
Two or three gestures will knock him down!
Master Yuk, that's no good!
The Master's here!
OK!
Mushroom!
- Stand in for me for a while.
- I can't!
I won't be long!
Hey...
I have to go to the city with Master!
GUANGZHOU: FRIENDSHIP GAMES
- Master, this time it's bad!
- What is it?
The young miss faked a
toilet break and escaped.
She's gone?!
Fucking hell!
Fuck!
- Come on...
- No! It's no good, Master!
Don't...
I'm not married!
- It's no good!
- What're you looking at?!
How can this be right?
There's no problem, My Lord!
Fok, aren't you a Master (monk)?
You're competing in a groom contest?
Yeah, my secular heart is astir!
If your secular heart is astir,
you must protect your six indriyas!
Dear fellow countrymen...
I had hoped to find a real
hero among you Cantonese,
but I fear it's too difficult.
You're ignorant!
Hooray...
- Who the hell is that?
- You don't recognise me?
One of the Top Ten Outstanding
Youths in Guangdong...
the Invincible Spiritual Boxer,
Fong Sai-Yuk, that's me!
You're just a damn punk kid
who thinks he's stylish.
But is your kung fu good enough?
Test it against my wife
and then we'll know!
Alright!
Xiaohuan, test him!
- Is it you?
- Not me, it's my daughter!
- Let me check the goods first!
- You must get past me first!
Let me borrow your head!
My God!
You tricked me?!
My feet haven't touched the ground!
Don't worry,
I want to play until you drop!
Still waiting for you to try
our Cantonese head pillars.
Ouch, my head!
It hurts!
My neck!
When a woman steps on you,
you get three years bad luck!
Terrific...
Master Yuk, beat her...
- Hey, how many of you can stand it?
- We can stand it!
But I can't stand it!
Strike her down!
Shandong Mama,
better stabilise your horse stance!
Ow, you're standing on my neck!
My head is spinning!
Darling, be careful!
Oh, I will!
Let me borrow your pigtail!
Ouch, let go of my pigtail!
Let it go!
Master Yuk, throw her down!
I'm giving the crowd what they want!
Quick, catch my wife!
They found some helpers!
- Well?
- Don't worry! I can beat them, too!
Be careful, everyone...
Hold tight!
I'll scatter your head pillars!
Six, hold up Master Yuk!
Master Yuk,
you have our moral support...
See, you Cantonese fall
apart when you're beaten!
You fall apart...
- Hey, can you stand it?
- I can stand it!
- We can stand it!
- No worries!
Well?
You only have those two to hold you up?
If not for the six pillars supporting you,
how could you sustain this long?
Fight!
If you win,
you'll be my son-in-law.
Beat her...
Hey, your support reinforcements
are going limp with exhaustion.
Let's fight!
My God, trying to pull my pigtail?!
I'll jab you in the eye!
You asked for it!
I'll kick your shin's weak spot!
- I'll poke your belly button!
- I'll blow up your balls!
- My eye is hurt!
- Six, are you OK?
- I'm fine...
- Come on, Cantonese!
- Six!
- Beat them...
I'll bite your ear off!
Hey... hold on!
Six is getting beaten!
Wait for me!
Grab your pillar!
I just can't stand it!
Master Yuk, don't disappoint me!
When have I, Fong Sai-Yuk
ever disappointed you?
Hammer head!
Propel me up!
Madam!
Don't fall down!
Fortunately,
you grabbed hold and kicked me!
I lost...
Master Yuk,
I'm so disappointed in you!
If you weren't disappointed,
I'd be in despair!
What led you to lose?
You're too good!
I'm not capable of beating you.
Miss, I'm sorry!
I can't marry you.
Kid, can we discuss it...?
Fucking hell!
Guangdong's Top Ten Outstanding Youths
spilling blood on the martial arts stage.
Anyone placing a bet?
Another loss.
There are ten outstanding
youths in Guangdong?!
Is it that serious?
No one would listen to
me unless I exaggerate!
Bet one more dollar for me.
Bet until someone wins.
Then you must look for my son,
Fong Sai-Yuk to show up.
He already did show up,
and got knocked down by someone!
And he calls himself one of
Guangdong's Top Ten Outstanding Youths?!
Seems now, the Fong family will
find it difficult to show up anywhere!
That brat's a real disappointment!
Dear heroes...
Is there anyone else coming up to compete?
If not, that's it for today.
Wait a minute!
There's money to pick up!
Go pick up the money!
Let me borrow your backs!
I'm here now.
Terrific...
May I ask the name of this hero?
And what should I call you,
pretty lady?
Are you bashful?
I'm Madam Lei,
the mother of Lei Tingting.
If you can defeat me today,
I'll be your mother-in-law.
Marry the mother-in-law, too!
Big mouth!
Did you hear that, huh?
Are you interested, huh?
Don't retreat any further,
or you'll fall down.
Who the hell are you?
Are you here to cause trouble?
Mothersucker!
Watch my mouth, its...
Mo-ther-fuck-er!
I'm the mysterious Invincible Boxer
of China, whereabouts unknown...
Fong Sai-Yuk's elder brother...
Fong Dai-Yuk!
Fucking hell!
You brothers have such long nicknames.
You use them to intimidate people,
but is your kung fu real or not?
Why don't you ask Madam
to test if it's real?
What's the big deal about
picking up a bouquet of flowers?
I'll take it!
Good leg skills, Madam.
No better than yours.
Why are you holding my big foot?
Your face is very smooth.
Madam, why are you so nervous?
Thanks a lot!
You weigh quite a bit!
Don't be afraid, I'm here.
Now, if you use a little force,
I'll pull you up.
Come up!
Bouquet!
Be careful!
Sneak attack on me?
Too heavy!
Madam!
Madam, we've come down now.
Are you alright?
I'm OK.
I'm not OK!
She's my wife, do you know that?
Please remember, everyone.
The Fong family is the
real deal in Guangdong.
What about my Lei family?
Don't touch my body!
We're all one family now, right?
I only came to compete.
Find another for your daughter.
You won't marry my daughter?
I don't want to!
Damn it, Kid!
Say that one more time!
Watch my mouth...
Don't-want-to!
Since you won the fight,
you must marry my daughter!
If you don't,
I'll ask the prefect to seize your home!
- Go to hell!
- Hell? Who's going to hell?
Don't touch my face!
Touching my face will leave a--
Give me your finger print.
Then you can't deny your
debt even if you want to!
Stamp it for me!
- Who's grabbing my stick?
- Your mum!
- Wow, Mum! You're so stylish!
- I did this for you!
I had to pretend to be your big
brother to redeem your reputation.
Go get me the chest.
What do you need the chest for?
I defeated Tiger Lei's wife,
so he wants me to marry his daughter!
Now I have to pack and run!
Whoa, Mum!
You're so powerful!
- You gay?
- What?
- Shit, the onslaught is coming!
- So what now?
- Give them a fight!
- OK!
Hang, sweep, split...
Fong Dai-Yuk, here I come!
Fong Dai-Yuk...
Fong Dai-Yuk!
- Search inside!
- Yes...
Go inside, search in there!
I told you to look for them,
not take a peek!
- Find them now!
- Yeah...
Hurry up!
Fucking hell!
Fong Dai-Yuk!
Why're you crying?
- Where's Fong Dai-Yuk?
- My eldest boy's dead!
Dead?
How can he be dead?
The poor bastard died in the street!
Died in the street?
So, where's his corpse?
Cremated into a pile of ash!
Even turned to ash,
I could recognise him.
Let me see.
Really?
You're interested in the ashes?
Mum... here...
OK, then!
Look at the ashes...
Mum, let's go!
Hurry!
Don't go!
- You're a man!
- No shit!
Aren't you a man?
Come any closer and I'll kill him!
Son, what can you do
to him holding a banana?
- Really?!
- It's not a knife?
Eat the banana!
Catch him...
Come down!
Mum!
Go quickly!
Forget me, go quickly!
Won't I be struck by
lightning if I forget you?
I'm coming!
How accurate!
I can't find your elder son, so I'll
take your younger son in his place.
Master, we found Young Miss.
It's God's will...
Buddy, hey, buddy!
Wait for his father to return
from the city for the wedding.
Fine! I'll postpone the wedding,
but now the bridal chamber!
Let's go!
Go away...
Don't get in the way.
Go away now!
Are you kidding us?
Let him go now!
Listen, you lot!
Disappear at once!
If you lot keep making a noise,
I'll arrest you!
Let him go!
- My Lord.
- Master Lei.
- What's happening outside?
- There's a groundswell out there.
I received word...
in two days the Commander of the
Nine Gates is coming to Guangdong.
My Lord, do you have any ideas?
That's easy!
Ask your son-in-law to get
married in front of the crowd.
He can tell them it's voluntary.
That way, everything will be fine when
the Commander of the Nine Gates arrives.
Good!
I'll beat him until he volunteers!
Absolutely not!
We must convince people by virtue.
Then nothing bad will happen.
Right...
Convince people by virtue...
I'm one of the Top Ten
Outstanding Youths in Guangdong.
No reason to lose your virginity to her!
If he touches me,
I'll stab him to death!
Look at her stupid face,
making out she's demure.
I'd rather kick her to the wall!
Hmm...
I'll play a scary prank on her!
He can no longer resist!
I'll scare you to death!
Just try it!
Try and come near!
Whoa, are you kidding me?!
I threw a cockroach, you threw a knife?!
That's going too far!
- What do you want?
- Let me tell you...
You can have me, but not my heart.
I have a sweetheart.
I have one, too!
I won't marry you.
I won't marry you either!
Alright, swear it!
What'll happen if you marry me?
My whole family will die.
- What's this?
- Give it back to me!
It's neither gold nor silver,
just some crappy iron you hold on to.
Are you daft?
Listen to me,
sleep by yourself tonight!
Don't try to persuade me,
I won't go back.
I'm not asking you to go back.
Then what are you doing?
Actually,
our situations are the same.
I was 12 years old when Master Lei
took me to be his servant.
At age 16, I became his concubine.
I'm just the same as you...
Getting married without falling in love.
What's the same?
You were happy enough to volunteer.
I'm being forced!
For the past 20 years,
I thought I was happy.
I married a rich husband,
gave birth to a wonderful daughter.
But since I saw your elder
brother on that stage...
I realised I was cheating myself.
Actually, what I need...
What do you need?
Love.
You can't be serious?!
You like my big brother?
Actually, I know that your
big brother faked his death.
If you see him, could I trouble
you to deliver this letter to him.
Hey,
aren't you afraid of Tiger Lei?
For love,
I'll die without regret.
Madam Fong, I really admire you!
Never expected you could woo a woman!
Actually, my big brother is...
I know you're much better
than your big brother.
It's you?!
- What do you want?
- I don't want anything!
I just want you to know that, I,
Tiger Lei, convince people by virtue.
I don't want you to think I'm
forcing you to be my son-in-law.
We should be honest with each
other and bring out our strengths.
Perhaps we have many common interests?
Us have common interests?
- Right!
- Really?
- I'm not angry.
Convince people by virtue...
Convince people by virtue.
Fucking hell!
Who's making that racket?!
Convince people by virtue.
I must convince people by virtue.
When the sky is bright,
I practise singing!
Beat the gong!
Singing a good folk song
to sell off my wife!
That's great!
Where's your mum...?
It's your mum's fault
for giving birth to you!
Beat the gong,
be strong and healthy!
You're ready to tear this family apart!
Your mother isn't my mum!
Beat the gong!
Singing a folk song sells off your wife!
That's great!
Your mum would've been better
giving birth to a barbecued pork!
When you beat the gong,
you'll be strong and healthy!
I'm ready to tear this family apart!
Your mother isn't my mum!
My mother isn't my mum!
- You've gained weight.
- Really?
I can't help it.
Good food, comfy life.
Have you lost your virginity?
No!
That's good, then.
Why didn't you run away?
I didn't know what your
circumstances were, OK?
If by some chance I did run,
what good is it implicating you?
Besides,
there are so many people here.
They follow me wherever I go.
A truly filial boy.
I've had a thorough look at the place.
I'll come to save you tonight!
After that, we take a torch
and burn down our ancestral home.
The two of us will be "burnt to death",
you get it?
Then we'll go to the city
and find your father.
It cheats them of a generation.
We'll never come back again!
It's all very hush-hush!
- What's wrong?
- Mum, you're so cunning!
Oh, yeah!
Someone asked me to give you this letter.
- Who?
- Your girlfriend!
MR. FONG DAI-YUK
Xiaohuan, tonight, I'm meeting an
important guest with the Lord Prefect.
I may be back late,
you go to bed first.
Mum, I'm being chased by dogs!
Why are you scared of dogs,
stupid boy?!
Whoa!
Did you offend the bitch?
Don't chase me!
My God! It's truly terrible
being chased by dogs like this!
Run faster, Mum!
Did you have to piss off the dogs?
You really are a stupid boy!
This way!
Who are you?
You dare break into Lei Mansion?!
Bite him!
Madam!
Don't bite him!
Dai-Yuk, it's really you?!
That's right, it's me!
Please ask your monkey gang to leave.
We don't want them eavesdropping on us.
Oh, alright...
One, Two, Three, Four
- back inside.
Hurry up...
- Dai-Yuk!
- Don't come any closer!
I'm afraid I cannot bear
the burden of your feelings.
Since I received your letter that day,
I've been suffering the pain
of yearning every night.
I really can't bear it.
I had to come see you tonight.
"The beauty rolls up the beaded curtain."
"She sits,
her eyebrows knitted deep."
"But visible are traces of tears."
"Not knowing who her heart hates."
Madam, this poem was
written especially for you.
He knows how to write poetry.
How stylish!
Hey, there are voices over there!
Madam, I must take my leave.
We will meet again some day.
If you please...
Dai-Yuk...
Madam, are you alright...?
I'm fine!
What are you doing here?
Who asked you to come?
Only fools walk slowly!
It's you?
It's me!
You?
It's you!
Miss Chen, has Tiger Lei captured
you to be his servant again?
Yeah, and you?
Me, too!
I went back to the sports field to find you.
That day I waited patiently
for you at the sports field.
I didn't see you, so I left!
Waited for me?
You really waited for me?
She waited for me!
Do you still want this medal?
You kept it all this time?
There are voices over there!
- Did you find anyone?
- No!
I'm afraid they'll discover us!
I'm going now.
Hey, be careful!
There are many dogs that way!
Will I see Miss Chen again if I leave?
Hey, Fong Sai-Yuk is here!
Hurry up and catch him!
I came to Guangdong this time,
to eliminate the treacherous
rebels of the Red Flower Society.
I received word,
I know they'll show up here.
Therefore, I hope...
you'll notify me as soon as you have news.
Yes, My Lord!
My Lord needn't worry.
Your humble servant will try his best.
My heart has already been
given to the Imperial Court.
My Lord, here's a small gift.
Please, My Lord, accept it.
My son's father-in-law,
there's been an injustice!
There's been an injustice?
My husband returned yesterday
from a visit to the city.
When he didn't see his son,
he took his anger out on me.
Look! He hit me till my forehead split,
and used charcoal to burn my hands!
You see how miserable I am?!
How's that my fucking business?
I fucking beg you, my son's father-in-law...
let Sai-Yuk go home and see him for one day.
That's all, one day!
Just one... day!
If Brother Fong really is missing his son,
he can come here to see him.
Or, move in here with me.
That way he can see him every day!
Huh?
Are you so unreasonable?
Fine! I'll slam myself into a wall,
then you'll get it!
You can watch me die!
Got a wall with a hard edge?
Hurry up and tell me!
Got a wall with a hard edge...?
- I'll slam myself into a wall...
- Co-Mother-in-Law, don't do that...
Master, just let Sai-Yuk
go back with her for one day.
I don't really believe she'll
slam herself into a wall and die.
Let her try it!
Just look at her,
would she really slam into a wall?!
Fine, you can watch me die!
- Dai-Yuk!
- Dai-Yuk?
- Dai-Yuk, Mum's about to die!
- Don't! Master...
- Dai-Yuk, Mum's slamming into a wall!
- You want to convince people by virtue?!
Huh? Convince people by virtue?
That's right...
Take him home today,
bring him back tomorrow.
Thank you, Master!
She's up there!
Mum, is Dad really back?
I lied to spare us!
We'll clear the house, then...
- go to the city and find your father.
- Oh, alright!
He's back!
His expression isn't good!
Stop there!
Were you going to tell me
you're getting married?!
What kind of mother are you?
I'm in the city a few days and you let
our son move in with the bride's family?!
How can I face our Fong family ancestors?
Dad, I...
You shut up!
It's not his fault!
It's... my mistake.
In short, it's all my fault.
I don't know how to teach my son.
I... apologise to the
Fong family ancestors!
I deserve to die!
I'll slam my head!
- I'll slam myself into the wall!
- Mum...
- This time, I'm serious! Let me go!
- Don't... slam your head into the wall!
- I'll slam my head!
- Mum, it's your second slam today!
- Forget it... I have to go out.
- Stop holding me! Let me go!
I'll talk about this with you tomorrow.
What?!
Hey!
I'm... just about to die!
And you're going to leave, huh?
Hey, are you a man or not?
You won't try to save me,
not even from death?
This is for you.
It's a razor for shaving!
He bought it for me.
It's for shaving my leg hair!
Mum, it's raining.
Your father forgot to take an umbrella.
Hurry and bring him one.
Why is it suddenly raining so heavily?
- Be careful!
- This umbrella's leaking! Change it!
- Mum, it's stopped raining!
- Right.
- Someone's making noise in there!
- What?
Alright, don't cry.
Bastard!
Mum, don't be so impulsive!
I don't want to live!
I hope you don't think
it's all meaningless.
There's a child in your belly.
The bastard got her pregnant!
Don't worry.
There's a child in your belly.
It's my responsibility
to take care of it.
- We're all responsible.
- This whore has so many men?!
Dad,
they're claiming responsibility.
Back out while you can.
If Fourth Brother hadn't saved me,
you wouldn't have become a widow.
It would've been impossible for
me to smuggle out this register.
Pfft!
Turns out, Dad isn't having an affair!
He almost scared me to death!
Mum, don't make so much noise!
Who's there?
Come out!
Don't go!
- What's that sound?
- Firecrackers.
- Firecrackers?
- Right!
Look at how your hands shake.
You don't seem to be a
martial arts practitioner.
Why aren't you out on serious business...
instead of rebelling against
the Qing to restore the Ming?
We each serve our own masters.
In your mind,
Qianlong may be a good emperor.
But in the minds of the Han people,
he's not a good emperor.
Hand me the register and you
can enjoy wealth and status.
For my own wealth and status,
I'd be sacrificing so many lives.
Even if I was willing,
my brothers wouldn't be.
And even if they were willing,
my wife would never forgive me.
I'd forgive you!
Boss, I'd definitely forgive you!
So you're selling me out?!
Go on!
Dad!
In my mind,
my dad's a good person.
So, I'll take care of you!
Let's go!
Beat my husband?
I'll deal with you!
Mum!
Hang, sweep, split...
Dad, where's the register?
It's here!
Shadowless Hands.
I said it's "Shadowless Hands"!
Sai-Yuk, hurry and save Lok Bing.
Your Mum can take it from here.
Be careful!
Well, are you alright?
This hero...
help your father protect the register.
Don't worry,
I won't disappoint you.
Then we'll meet again someday.
Take care.
Son, you hold on!
We're leaving!
Don't worry!
Joining a triad society?
I'll interrogate you at home!
That hurt!
Come on!
That didn't hurt!
Didn't hurt?!
Doesn't that hurt...?
That's how my dad beats me!
Let me tell you,
that's how I beat my family dog.
Kid, this is called:
"one inch long, one inch strong".
You're ridiculous!
Mine's called: "concise and forceful!"
Run, then!
Let's see where you can run?!
We'll meet again someday!
Dad!
Sai-Yuk,
is anyone following you?
Don't worry, my ten years of kung
fu practise hasn't been in vain.
Where's Mum?
Another petty argument?
Mum, are you alright?
He's never treated me like this before.
He recited ten poems in a single breath.
Ten poems?
How awesome!
Stop bothering me,
I'm still enjoying the excitement!
- He's just too stylish!
- That's so romantic!
Sai-Yuk!
Dad has now chosen his path.
From now on, both mother and
son won't have a good life.
If I can live a good life alone,
then what about the others?
Even if I were willing,
what good can good times do?
Even if I didn't care,
might others be willing?
And if by some chance the good times
and the others didn't know, then...
Basically, I don't know anything!
Dad's chosen path must be the right one.
I'll definitely accompany you to the end.
Son, I've no idea what
you're babbling about!
But I'll accompany you both to the end.
Since you've made your decision,
we'll move into Tiger Lei's
home immediately.
That's dangerous!
The more dangerous the place,
the safer it is.
Understood.
What? Your whole family
is moving into my place?!
Right.
I didn't want to come at first,
but as my wife says:
Brother Lei is a hero among men.
You've even managed to turn
this little monkey obedient.
I didn't know what to believe,
so I decided to bring him here,
to stay for about a month.
Brother Lei is well-known for
convincing people by virtue.
I do convince people by virtue!
Make yourselves at home.
Stay here until you're convinced.
Miss.
Quickly,
greet your father and mother-in-law.
Hey, go ahead.
Wife, I miss you so much!
I'm not your wife!
She's your wife!
- It's you?!
You're getting thin!
You, too!
That rascal's such a romantic!
He inherited that from me.
Come...
What are you doing?
Hey...
This breastplate is our
Fong family heirloom.
- It's a greeting gift from your in-laws.
- Aren't you going to thank Mum?
Thank you, Mother-in-Law.
Brother, seeing as most of us
are gathered here today,
wouldn't it be best to set a date
for them to get married tomorrow?
Sorry...
No problem...
I convince people by virtue.
Spray by all means,
spray until you're satisfied.
Brother, I don't have any
close friends in Guangdong.
How about asking your relatives and
friends to come join the festivities?
Co-Mother-in-Law,
tomorrow, ask Dai-Yuk--
No problem...
I convince people by virtue.
I don't mind if you
spray my wife with tea.
Admirable...
Alright.
We convince people by virtue.
Everyone, take an early rest.
Many guests are coming here tomorrow.
We must rest well.
Convince people by virtue...
Are you kidding me?
None of your relatives or friends came?
It's just that our Fong family
has a prosperous population.
But as we do business across the country,
more and more branches open.
I wasn't able to notify all my relatives
and friends in time.
You buy groceries at the wet market.
Don't you have friends there?
Dear Father-in-Law, it's just...
Our family grows its own vegetables
and doesn't need to buy them.
Rice, then...?
Rice, too!
We grow our own rice.
Well, then,
the people who shop from you...
aren't they your friends?
Right,
they most definitely aren't our friends!
If they were, would I sell them shrunken
fabrics and charge random prices?
Actually, running our cloth store
is much like running a brothel.
If you're willing to buy,
we're willing to sell.
Everyone has flings,
no need to invest true feeling.
So how could they be our friends?
Am I right...?
Good answer...
Master, the Lord Prefect's here.
Finally a guest has come.
Please hurry...
Don't worry, it's only the Prefect.
It's only the Prefect!
- Brother Lei!
- Lord Prefect!
The Commander of the Nine Gates has come.
My Lord...
- Please...
- Welcome, My Lord.
Hey, in-laws...
let's greet our guests together.
Come... let's go together.
Come on!
My Lord, please...
Welcome, My Lord.
Your presence honours us.
- Welcome...
- This is my son-in-law...
- these two are my in-laws.
- My Lord!
- My Lord, please take a seat.
- Please...
- Goodbye... and good riddance...
Sit as you please.
- My Lord, please sit.
- Please sit.
Why are you three sitting over there?
Come and sit together!
No, I see it's crowded with people.
So the three of us are sitting here.
You're talking rubbish!
Half the table here is unoccupied.
Come over...
Oh, dear!
I dropped money!
- I'll help you find it. Where is it, huh?
- Shit!
Brother Fong,
why are you sitting alone?
Come sit over here...
Where's the money?
I can't find it!
- How long have you been there?
- I-just-got-here!
- Brother Lei...
- Yes?
What's your son-in-law
doing under the table?
What are you doing there?
Come out...
Your favourite meal of
braised pork is here.
Son, you eat up!
Mum,
it's no good for him to see me.
To the right...
He's your son-in-law?
Family Head Lei,
tell My Lord who Sai-Yuk is to you!
He's my son-in-law!
Are you head of the family?
Yes, I'm in charge here.
- Hand over the register!
- Master, watch out!
Xiaohuan!
Mum!
Tingting!
Where's the register?
I'll fight you to the death!
Mum!
Flip over the table as cover!
Quick, let's go!
Xiaohuan...
Master, be careful!
- Go on!
- Yes!
Take him back.
Set fire to their house
and burn it down.
Fucking hell!
Fucking little bastard!
I was letting you marry my daughter,
but you've brought misery
to my entire family.
Master Lei,
our young master didn't want this.
You shut up!
Speak again and I'll kill you!
Let him go,
or I won't be polite to you.
Fucking hell!
You want to fight?
- What do you want?
- Master Yuk, forget it.
Dad, Mum's in real trouble!
Fuck!
Xiaohuan!
- Tingting!
- Mum!
Where's your father?
Xiaohuan... how do you feel?
- Hurry up...
- Go see a doctor!
No need for you to worry!
Don't I know what to do?
Piss off, you!
Don't touch her!
- Don't do this, she's hurt so badly.
- Xiaohuan, let's go!
- Be careful!
- Brother, Guangdong is unfamiliar to you.
We'll take you there.
No need, you couldn't care less!
From now on,
we go our separate ways.
Dad, that's no good.
We're not familiar with
the roads in Guangdong.
Are you coming or not?
Don't come,
and you're no longer my daughter!
Tingting!
Let's go!
Let's go now!
Mum doesn't have any ideas yet.
Don't worry about it.
As long as the register's in our hands,
they won't do anything to Dad.
I'll check out the city tonight.
You be careful!
- Bamboo Pole!
- Who's there?
Sai-Yuk.
Open the door.
Come in!
I've seen notices all around.
They say my Dad's going
to be beheaded tomorrow.
Many people I know were arrested today.
So I came to check you
two brothers were alright.
I'm alright...
What's wrong?
Master Yuk, I've let you down...
You don't have to cry.
What's happened?
They took me and Bronze Hammer Six
in for questioning.
I said, I didn't know you.
So that's why I'm alright.
What about Six?
He blamed me for having
no guts or loyalty.
He refused to disown you
even if it meant death.
So they beat him until he vomited blood.
He was beaten until they were exhausted.
At first, they told him if he kowtowed
three times they'd let him go.
He refused to kowtow
even on the verge of death.
Where is he now?
He was beaten to death...
and hung at the East Gate.
Master Yuk, will you forgive me?
I was so scared!
I won't blame you.
I've already lost one friend,
I don't want to bury you, too.
Who's there?
Hey, what are you doing here...?
I came to collect his corpse.
Who are you to dare collect his corpse?
Fong Sai-Yuk.
Fong Sai-Yuk...?!
You dare to come here?
Aren't you afraid of death?
My friend wasn't afraid of death,
he dared to recognise me.
How could it be that I, Fong Sai-Yuk... am
too afraid of death to collect his corpse?
- Go on!
- Yes...
Six, let's fight side by side!
Kowtow to my friend three times!
Don't blame us...
It's not our fault...
Six, let's go!
You mustn't blame us!
Bronze Hammer Six,
you were a good friend to me in this life.
I hope we can be good
brothers in the next.
Master Yuk, restrain your grief.
Mushroom, Dad will be beheaded
at the execution ground tomorrow.
You're saying that
Master will be beheaded?
I've decided to save him alone.
Take Mum away early in the morning.
Master Yuk,
it's dangerous for you to go alone.
- Don't!
- Say no more!
I've already made my decision.
You mustn't let Mum know about this.
Mushroom...
Don't cry.
Mum's waiting for us inside.
We'll go back in first.
Let's go.
Well?
Any news about your father?
It's alright, don't worry!
Turns out, Dad was rescued by Chan Ga-Lok,
Chief Helmsman of the Red Flower Society.
Really?
Why would I lie to you?
So why hasn't he come back?
Oh, Chief Helmsman Chan said, it's best
for everyone not to concentrate together.
That's why he instructed Mushroom
to take you tomorrow...
to meet him at the Boshui Beach
branch of the Red Flower Society.
Mushroom, isn't there a branch of the
Red Flower Society at Boshui Beach?
You say it!
Tell Mum, then!
Say it!
Right, I went there with Master
year before last.
What about you?
Are you just by yourself?
Chief Chan asked me to take the register
to Mount Longhu and join a Master Chiu.
Isn't there a Master Chiu at Mount Longhu?
Say it!
Why aren't you saying anything?
Say it, then!
Right,
we met the year before last.
We had dinner together.
That Master Chiu,
he's a real nice guy!
Did I get it right?
Right, not a single mistake!
Then, all's well that ends well.
Fucking hell!
You Cantonese,
there's not a good one among you!
They said they'd find
a doctor to cure my wife.
Turns out, they called officers
to come and arrest me.
You Cantonese... are all motherfuckers!
Wife, how are you?
Tingting...
I'm alright.
It's pouring down,
get on board first.
I don't need your care!
I won't get on your boat!
I'm warning you,
don't you come near me in future!
Dad!
Don't you talk to me!
Tingting.
Mother-in-Law's seriously injured.
Why are you so stubborn?
Tingting, get on board with them!
I'll... stay here with your father.
Damn you, asshole!
Saving face at a time like this?!
Fucking hell!
Haven't you scolded me enough?
I only said I wouldn't
get on your boat.
I never said anything about my wife
and daughter not going on board.
Say no more.
Help her up.
Be careful!
- Watch out.
- Be careful...
Don't let her fall!
Be careful.
God!
What the hell did I do wrong?
Why do you treat me this way?
A man with a rotten mouth
deserves to be struck by lightning!
I'll ask you once more:
are you boarding or not?
I'm not...
- You have to hang in there.
- Mum...
Sai-Yuk,
take Tingting out for a while.
I have something important...
to tell co-Mother-in-Law.
Go on!
Good girl!
Co-Mother-in-Law,
I have something to ask you...
What is it?
Where is Dai-Yuk?
Dai... Dai-Yuk is here.
"The beauty rolls up the beaded curtain."
"She sits,
her eyebrows knitted deep."
"But visible are traces of tears."
"Not knowing who her heart hates."
Madam, it's me!
Dai-Yuk!
Are you really Dai-Yuk?
Yes!
We can't be together in this life.
I hope we can be together
in the next life, OK?
OK.
Co-Mother-in-Law!
Mum!
Xiaohuan!
Although you always scold me,
in my heart,
I can't be angry with you.
Once you're my father-in-law,
you're my father-in-law for life.
Once your boat passes Boshui
Beach tomorrow morning...
the officers can't catch you.
Xiaohuan!
Sai-Yuk, remember to come and
join us as soon as you're done.
Master Yuk, take care of yourself!
Damn it, you're crying?
You're crazy!
He's not going to die, he's going
to deliver the register, that's all.
I caught a cold is all!
Say no more, it's time to go.
Dad's waiting for you.
Oh!
- Sai-Yuk!
- What's the matter?
Can you swear an oath?
What oath?
Swear that you won't recognise me as
your wife in future, will you agree?
Why?
That night in the bridal chamber,
you said...
What did I say?
If you took me as your wife,
then...
My whole family would die?
I don't care!
No matter what happens,
you'll always be my wife.
His father used to kiss me like that.
Hey,
did you ever kiss your wife like that?
Forget I said that!
Foul mouth!
Put this on.
What about you?
I have this one.
- You're still wearing that?
- Master Yuk, time to set sail.
Take care.
Sai-Yuk, be careful...
You don't want to go walking!
Ride a horse.
It's faster, you understand?
Also, wear enough shirts,
so you don't catch a cold.
Take some rations...
All of you, take care.
As long as you hand over the
Red Flower Society rebels...
and give me the register,
you won't die!
We Han people won't betray our own.
As long as the Manchus return to
Manchuria... we won't oppose you.
For many years our great Qing dynasty
has united the whole of China.
It's just that you aren't
willing to face reality.
You see,
haven't we ample food and clothing?
Don't we have peace and prosperity?
- You hear that?
- Shut up!
I'll kill anyone who makes a noise.
I'm asking you,
where are the Red Flower Society men?
Wherever there's a heaven and an earth,
there are Red Flower Society men.
How many can you kill?
Fine.
I kill one, that's one less.
Carry out the execution.
It's really so tragic!
Chop!
The register's here!
Terrific!
Today, Fong Sai-Yuk and the Red Flower
Society advance and retreat together.
I live, the register survives.
I die, it dies with me.
Sai-Yuk!
Don't come over,
or I'll blow this up!
Back off!
Retreat!
Fong Sai-Yuk,
you're brave enough, indeed!
Don't tell me you aren't afraid?!
Today, my fate is predetermined!
Hand over the register,
and neither you nor your father will die.
Sai-Yuk...
you mustn't give it to him!
A wise man submits to circumstances.
As long as you hand
the register over to me,
I guarantee you a bright future
and promotion to the nobility.
You stupid dick!
You want to turn me into a traitor?
My Dad would disown me!
My Mum would cripple me!
The people would curse me!
History would revile me!
The country needs someone whose name won't
go down in history as a byword for infamy.
Terrific!
How ambitious!
You have guts.
I admire your kind the most.
If we didn't each serve our own master,
I could discuss heroes with
you today over a cup of wine.
Alright, I'll give you a chance.
If you can beat me before the rope breaks,
I'll help you be a filial son.
If you lose,
you hand over the register to me.
I only used 30% of my power last time.
I think you're a martial arts prodigy.
I had wanted to promote you
to serve the imperial court.
But now it seems,
you won't have the chance.
I'm proficient in many fists.
I had wanted to take you as my apprentice.
But as you bullied my dad...
I can see you won't have the chance.
Lucky I have a breastplate.
Go to hell!
It's yours!
Sai-Yuk, you must go now!
I won't go...
Sai-Yuk, Dad is so happy
to have seen you grow up.
Don't bother about me.
Besides, there are many
important things for you to do.
Even if Dad dies,
he'll be without regrets.
You must go now!
Whatever I have to do,
anyone can do it!
But I only have one dad!
You must go!
Dad,
I want to live and die with you.
- Fong Sai-Yuk, let me help you!
- Mum...
I'll help you, too!
Exert yourself!
FUCK YOUR MOTHER!
Kill them for me!
Husband!
Sai-Yuk!
Mum's here to save you!
Stupid boy!
Trying to get yourself killed?
Think I'm not ready to die?!
Mushroom,
why do you bring my mum here?
I didn't, turns out there is a Red
Flower Society branch at Boshui Beach.
- What a coincidence!
- Yeah...
Master Yuk, your bullshit was spot on!
Don't talk nonsense any more!
Quick, go save my Dad!
I'm ready to die...
You go to hell!
How come I'm not yet dead?
Chief Helmsman Chan!
Husband, are you alright?
I'm fine, let's save Dad!
Dad!
Mum, let's save Dad!
Master, let's go now!
Chief Helmsman Chan,
your reputation is fully justified.
Admirable.
However, my master ordered me
to bring back your corpse!
Flying stinky shoe!
Guided flying spear!
Mum!
Brother Fong,
I'll adopt Sai-Yuk as my godson.
I'll surely teach him well.
Chief Chan,
I'm handing Sai-Yuk over to you.
Thief Chan!
Umm, sorry!
Chief Chan!
Look after my son well, please.
He hasn't left me since he was a child.
Chief Helmsman Chan,
it's time for us to part company.
Godfather,
can I take Tingting with me?
Of course, you can.
Husband,
have you thought it through?
You're really booting
your son into the Triad?
Have you thought it through?
Alright, then...
he should go out and see the big picture.
Tingting, let's go.
Dad.
Don't you bully my daughter.
Take care I don't beat you!
Don't worry,
I haven't the will to bully her.
Be good like me when
you travel the country.
Convince people with virtue,
understand?
Yes!
Dad,
can I beg you for just one thing?
Say it.
From when I was little,
I've never seen you smile.
Let me see you smile.
I'll smile next year!
Sai-Yuk, let's go.
Dad, take care of yourself.
Let's go!
Sai-Yuk, sit steady.
You won't bully me, will you?
"The beauty rolls up the beaded curtain."
"She sits,
her eyebrows knitted deep."
"But visible are traces of tears."
"Not knowing who her heart hates."
Son, your Dad's smiling!
It's really romantic!
I'm so happy!
Sai-Yuk,
haven't you forgotten something?
Catch!
HEAVEN AND EARTH SOCIETY REGISTER:
Chief Helmsman: Chan Ga-Lok
Second Master: Daoist Mo Tsan
Third Master: Chiu Boon-San
Fourth Master: Man Tai-Loi
11th Master: Lok Bing
14th Master: Yu Yu-Tung
Messenger: Fong Dak
Resident Doctor: Wong Fei-Hung
Foreign Language Translator: 13th Aunt
Financier: Beggar So
Recreation: Wai Siu-Bo
Barrister: Sung Sai-Git
Housekeeper: Lui Sei-Leung
Production Managers:
MARGARET WONG & RONALD LAU
Assistant Directors:
LO PO-SHAN & CHAN SHEK
Assistant Martial Arts Directors:
AILEN SIT & KU HIN-CHIU
Theme Song: "Youthful Heart"
Performer: JACKY CHEUNG
Theme Song: "The Book and the Sword"
Performer: ADAM CHENG
THE END