You hear that?
NARRATOR: Tonight
on "Dead Files Revisited"...
Oh, he's pissed now.
NARRATOR:...a second look
at some of Amy and Steve's
most terrifying cases...
Looks like scratch marks.
...new information...
We wanted him out of here.
NARRATOR:
...startling revelations.
You wonder
if they ever will stop.
NARRATOR: First, a return
to Wabash, Indiana...
I don't know how
to make it better.
...where a mysterious portal...
There is a doorway here.
...releases an ancient evil.
They're all **** mental.
Then...
There's something attacking
my wife.
...we travel back
to an Ohio restaurant...
They're all crying
in the corner.
NARRATOR:
...where disturbing spirits...
They deserve
to be punished.
...threaten the living.
There's a female
that he wants to kill.
Did they face their fears...
You guys are definitely
gonna do this.
...or does the nightmare
continue?
In the name of the Father,
the Son,
and the Holy Spirit,
amen.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing's, like,
a monster.
I speak to dead people.
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
I cannot help you
unless I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her?
It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you
stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
[ Echoing ] Stop it.
We uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
WOMAN:
I want to know the truth.
I want to know
what's happening.
Or time to get out.
[ Crying ] I told you
there were ghosts in this house.
When I got the call from Suzanne
and B.J. in Wabash, Indiana,
I knew right away that those two
were paralyzed by fear.
And as soon as I entered
the home to hear their story,
I was determined to help.
Now that I'm here, why don't you
explain what's going on?
Well, we've been having
a lot of experiences here --
myself, my husband,
my three kids.
Okay. Like what?
Give me a for instance.
[ Crying ] Sorry.
It's okay.
[ Sniffles ]
It really gets down deep.
My children
were being severely affected
by what was going on here.
It's hard enough
just to raise kids,
let alone when they're seeing
and hearing things
and you don't have an answer
for them.
We've seen an apparition.
Footsteps, voices.
I just don't want my children
to be scared of their own house.
I don't know
how to make it better.
[ Sniffles ]
AMY: As I pulled up
to the location,
I could already sense
a serious threat,
and it was so overwhelming,
I didn't even
have to walk inside
to know that the problem was
there long before the house.
There is a doorway here...
for -- for dead people.
But I opened it, and it was,
like, endless darkness.
And it's a darkness
that's layers of depression.
These dark, black hands
came out to grab me.
And it wanted to wrap me in it.
Okay, Suzanne, why did you
bring me in this room?
There was a time
when I woke up
in the middle
of the night to a --
what I thought was
a man's voice yelling, "Hey,"
on the baby monitor,
and then she started screaming.
I ran into the bedroom
to get her,
and that's when I walked
into a black mass,
like if you would
walk into blackness.
It's just...dealing
with this every single day
for the past seven years --
it's been very trying.
It just...
is very overwhelming,
and you wonder
if it ever will stop.
AMY: There's a big, solid,
black mass.
And a bunch of people
that are halfway in the walls.
And they're see-through.
Could this maybe
be the portal?
Yeah.
It's been here
for...ever.
A portal typically allows
the dead to pass in and out
of our world with ease.
But that black mass had
a different plan for the dead.
And what about
the -- the big mass?
It's keeping them trapped.
STEVE: Suzanne's home had been
in her husband's family
for three generations.
These days, that's an impressive
track record for any homeowner.
But after speaking
with her husband,
it was apparent that he was
ready to throw away
the family legacy
to protect his kids.
STEVE:
Why don't you tell me a little
bit about what's going on?
The thing that's happened with
the kids, first it was Macy.
She's the oldest,
and when she was about 3,
she started saying that she's
seeing monsters and ghosts.
I thought it was kind of odd,
but now that Andy is 3,
Andy has said
the same thing.
As a parent, you're supposed
to protect your children,
and not really knowing
what's going on
and how to protect them,
it gets stressful.
Are they experiencing
anything else?
In this room,
we had something that would
mimic what was being said.
So, whatever you guys are
talking about, something's...
- Repeating it.
- Like a parrot. - Yes. - Okay.
I want my children
to be able
to feel safe in their home,
where they don't have to worry
about monsters.
AMY:
There is a lady here.
She rules this structure.
This lady -- she is able
to manipulate sound waves.
So she could make noise, noise.
I do feel like
people see her, though.
- Like, the younger people
in the house. - Uh-huh.
It would be, like,
a white mist, you know?
You know, she's
very smothering, you know?
She wants to make clear
that she's a protector.
Why do you say that?
Like --
'Cause she thinks that
the adults here are satanic.
NARRATOR: Next...
She died of a broken heart.
...a lost soul
unleashes her wrath.
She thinks she's here
to do God's work.
And in our second
investigation...
My wife was assaulted here.
...a dangerous presence...
He would like them to die.
...just won't leave.
"Be gone, accursed Dragon."
Amen.
STEVE: After talking
to Suzanne and B.J.,
there was no question
they were terrified.
But all I knew was that B.J.'s
family had lived on the property
for over 100 years
and nothing questionable
happened during that time.
So I had no choice
but to dig a little deeper.
So, Heather,
what were you able to find out
about the property
I'm investigating?
I found that
Maggie and Edwin Williams
were the first
white settlers.
What do you mean,
"white settlers"?
Well, the land was actually
owned by a Miami Indian tribe.
Okay. So what can you tell me
about the Williamses?
They were devout Christians.
They were Presbyterians.
They were active
in their small church.
How many kids
did they have?
They had six.
Did anybody from the family
actually die on the property?
Yeah, actually, Edwin,
the father, he died first.
And about six weeks later,
Maggie died, too,
and here's her obit.
- You're kidding me.
- Nope.
And according to this,
she died of heart disease.
Well...allegedly.
What do you mean,
"allegedly"?
Well, I think she died
of a broken heart.
AMY: This religious lady,
she has this depression
from losing her family.
I think because
her husband died.
She's alone.
She was alone.
I think she feels like
she failed.
I think she'd like
to raise the kids.
The religious woman had
completely lost sight
of right and wrong.
And although her intentions
of caring for the children
now living in the house
may have been good,
her methods to make that happen
went too far.
She thinks that the reason
why she's still here...
[ Sniffles ]
...is to do God's work.
She's talking
about somebody having
or they've had
or they're gonna --
gonna have
a near-death experience?
That'll bring them
closer to God.
STEVE: Heather had mentioned
the land around Suzanne
and B.J.'s home was once
Native American territory.
After working with Amy
this long,
I knew it was a lead
I had to follow.
So I tracked down a member
of the local tribe,
and his account of what happened
to his people
can be summed up in one word --
"tragic."
The property
I'm investigating,
the Miami tribe actually
owned it at some point.
The first person
it was ever allotted to --
his name was
Poqua Godfroy.
He was a son
of the last war chief,
Chief Francis Godfroy
of the Miami Indians.
What can you tell me
about Poqua?
Poqua, he had a temper.
He used to drink
quite a bit.
He was living
in a time
where their land
was being took.
The 1938 treaty with
the United States government
called for the removal
of the Miamis
from the state of Indiana,
and it shows them putting
the Miamis at gunpoint.
They took them
and moved them
750 miles away
from their homelands.
And a lot of them perished
after they got there.
Did Poqua
die on the property?
He fell off a horse,
and they said he broke his neck.
Okay.
Okay, that, like --
This shouldn't be here.
Ah, we've got a griper.
Native American.
She doesn't like it.
She is pissed
about this building.
The ground was sacred
to Native Americans.
AMY: The Native American woman
showed me
that what was once
their holy land
had actually become a prison
for the dead.
The people go and bury
their dead people there,
and it brings them back,
but they're all **** mental.
This isn't good.
And their suffering was all
because of one entity.
And it's because
of that black mass thing.
How do you think
the living
might experience
this black mass?
A definite feeling
of intimidation.
A sense of overwhelming dread.
Fear.
NARRATOR: Coming up next...
She's felt that you guys
were satanic.
NARRATOR:...what happened
after the investigation?
We had some challenges.
AMY:
Leave these people in piece.
Leave this place.
You are not welcome here.
STEVE: Amy, I want to introduce
you to B.J. and Suzanne.
When we walked in to meet Amy,
it was very surreal.
We've been waiting for answers
for seven years,
and we finally
are gonna get some.
They have
three beautiful children,
and two of the older ones
are experiencing things.
Inside the house
was a female,
and she is very,
very religious.
Her husband died.
She has a huge amount
of depression
surrounding his death,
and she also felt like
she let down her children.
The first white settlers to live
on your property
were a young couple,
Edwin and Margaret Williams.
He died at the age of 40
of pneumonia.
Oh.
Five to six weeks later,
she dies.
Her emotion does spill out
into the house,
which is really
severe depression.
[ Voice breaking ]
Several years ago,
B.J. had a really bad bout
of depression -- very bad.
B.J.:
That was a bit of a shocker.
I went into
a pretty deep depression
when my father passed away,
then I had
one of best friends die.
It gave me validation that Amy
was for real.
And it took a couple of years
for him to come up out of it.
That really triggered
something for me.
B.J. went through
a really hard depression,
and I always wondered if it was
something else,
because it was totally
out of character
for him to be like he was.
[ Clears throat ]
She's always
watching you guys.
If people do see her,
it would be more
like a white mist.
The kids are seeing
this white thing.
- Do you think it's her?
- Yeah.
She actually wants to protect
the children.
She's felt that you guys
were satanic.
She feels like she is here
to lead you to God.
That's her mission,
and she feels the only way
she can do that with you
is a near-death
experience.
This religious woman may not
agree with the way we live
and the way that we believe,
but it's our house
and our family,
and she needs to go.
STEVE: So, how'd the rest
of your walk go?
I came into contact with this
Native American lady,
and she was just going off
about how this was,
like, once sacred ground.
And now it's become
very tainted.
Now, your land was owned
at one time by the Miami tribe.
Actually, your property itself
was owned by a guy named Poqua.
He did not like
the white man whatsoever.
When the government came in,
they basically
took the Miami tribe
and shipped them off
to Kansas.
It makes sense.
I saw about 20 people.
They weren't bad in life,
but now that they're dead,
they're twisted.
And they're being held
by a huge black mass.
And now I'm thinking
it might have been Poqua.
SUZANNE: Both my girls
have talked about monsters,
and if I asked them
the question,
"What does it look like?"
they would say, "black.
It's all black."
When I went
into the basement,
there's a pathway
that the dead can use
to come in and out
of your house.
These dead people
can be dangerous
and have
very bad intentions.
And I did sketch
a scene of it.
One of these walls
had, like, a pathway.
Halfway out of the wall
are two men.
SUZANNE:
The sketch was disturbing
because how do you stop
all these different people
coming and going in your house
that aren't welcome?
I think that
a lot of the dead here,
they kind of get
sucked in the pathway.
I mean, are these
the people that are...
talking to my kids?
Yes.
They're going to go for them
because they're so open.
To think that Poqua or something
from our basement
could be trying to get
my children was very scary,
and we wanted to know
what we could do
to keep it from getting worse.
STEVE: Big question is,
are your kids safe here?
So, the first thing
I want you to do
is to find a deacon
who can do a blessing
for Margaret,
the pious woman
and tell her she can go now.
The second thing
is to seal the pathway
with tar-water
and brick dust.
Now, the last thing you need
to do is deal with Poqua.
You're gonna have to go
to the Miami tribe,
and you're going to ask them
to send a medicine man.
STEVE:
Will this get rid of him?
Yes.
So, once they do all this,
will these guys be able
to raise their kids here safely?
So, when Amy left,
the activity really increased.
The kids were
seeing things daily,
and the noises in the house
were just unbearable.
DEACON: Leave those who live
in this house in peace.
The deacon came in,
and he did a house blessing.
DEACON: We wish for you
to enter into the light
for all eternity.
Leave those who live
in peace, amen.
SUZANNE:
And then I went to the basement
and took the tar-water
and the brick dust
that Amy had given us
and sealed both sides of
the pathway as she instructed.
We had some challenges
getting the Miami tribe here.
The first shaman
got very, very sick
and put into the hospital
and never came.
The thought did cross my mind
that Poqua could be interfering.
Fortunately, the tribe was able
to send another member
to come help us out.
WOMAN: We ask the spirits
to leave this place.
SUZANNE: She started off by
burning sage through the house.
We cleanse this home.
Let them have their home.
B.J.:
She was almost in a trance
as she was walking around
blessing the house.
WOMAN: We ask the spirits
to leave this place.
SUZANNE:
Then she went into the backyard
and started the tribal ceremony.
WOMAN:
Leave these people in peace.
SUZANNE:
We don't know what happened,
but when she came back,
she informed me that Poqua
was seen running away.
Leave this place.
You are not welcome here.
Now that everything's done,
things in the house
have been quiet
and the kids are not having
any experiences.
I think there will always
be a concern
that things might stir up again,
but only time will tell
that everything we've done
for the children
is gonna make it better.
AMY:
I know the cleansing process
has been extremely stressful
for Suzanne and B.J.,
but the most important thing
is they've taken back control.
And now they have the tools
to keep their home
a safe environment
for generations to come.
STEVE: I'm sure that owning
a restaurant is hard work,
but for our clients at the
Jury Room in Columbus, Ohio,
their business
had gotten dangerous.
Unexplained activity in
the place was so out of control,
the owners were considering
shutting down.
But the moment
Amy and I walked in,
their luck started to change.
STEVE: So, Harold, you sounded
really concerned on the phone.
What's going on?
My wife and I just bought
the restaurant.
And recently employees
have started reporting
seeing apparitions,
seeing things moving around
on their own.
When we were given the keys
to the restaurant,
we were told that something
was here.
But it wasn't until we opened
the doors
that things began to happen.
A restaurant is
a dangerous enough place
with fire, slippery floors,
knives,
and that's without malevolent
forces threatening my staff.
Harold, I got to ask you,
what would you do
if Amy told you
you got to get out?
I hope that's not
the answer.
We have everything tied up
in this restaurant.
There's too much
going on.
AMY:
Walking into that restaurant,
it was like a wave
of negative energy
smacked me
right across the face.
You hear that?
[ Wood creaking ]
Stomping up and down.
And it's him.
I think it's a shadow man.
AMY: I've always been open about
my fear of shadow people.
It's something I've dealt with
my entire life,
and to start an investigation
this way was very disturbing.
He attaches to people.
He's been here before.
And he wants everyone out.
Looks like scratch marks.
NARRATOR: Next...
Just was this really violent
push to the ground.
...the dead fight back.
Oh, he's pissed now.
STEVE: The owner of the Jury
Room had serious concerns
about what was happening
to his restaurant,
and once I got him talking,
it was apparent
that his biggest fear
was not being able to protect
the love of his life.
My first experience came
when we opened the bar.
I was standing
under the bar here,
and one of the pictures
fell off of the wall
and hit me squarely
on the head.
But the breaking point
was when my wife
was assaulted here.
We were bothered enough by what
was happening to the staff,
but the most frightening
episode for me
was when my wife
experienced a force
which pushed her to the ground.
That's when it began to turn,
and I became
very, very concerned
and worried for my wife.
There's something here
attacking my wife,
and I feel helpless.
AMY: So there's this one guy,
and he doesn't like to be here.
[ Scoffs ]
He's very annoyed
about the shadow man,
who he cannot stand at all.
And he ****
throws a fit about it.
This is, like,
a long-standing feud.
**** gonna go down.
Like, he's had it.
The conflict
between the angry man
and the shadow person
had escalated
from a feud into an all-out war,
and when the dead go to battle,
sometimes the living end up
in the line of fire.
Is he gonna
do something?
Well, that's what
he's threatening.
Like, he's trying to touch them
or push them or punch them.
Oh, he's pissed now.
STEVE: Harold's wife had spent
most of her adult life
working behind the bar,
so to say she's got a thick skin
was an understatement.
But seeing how her experiences
were starting to chip away
at that tough exterior,
I understood why Harold
was so worried about her.
Since we've been
in here,
a lot of our trusted
employees
have started to complain
about things,
and we don't have
answers.
What do you know
about the building?
This building is --
is 200 years old.
And -- and we know stories about
the history of this place,
but we don't know
what's true.
ELIZABETH:
There's a lot of legends
and, sort of, history
about this building,
and we knew that it was haunted.
But it struck us more
of something interesting,
historical,
but things really seemed to take
a quick, negative downturn,
and it was scary.
You got pushed?
Yeah, the door was open,
and I felt this push,
uh, on my back.
I basically fell forward,
like, onto my forearms.
It was scary.
It just was this really violent
push to the ground.
And nobody
was in the hallway?
Nobody was in the hallway.
It happened so quickly.
- It was very strange.
- Okay.
The shadow man -- he doesn't
like the living people.
He says they're just as bad
as the dead people.
Can you describe him?
I have to look
into the shadows.
Holy ****
I'm trying to get
into his head,
and he doesn't like that.
AMY: Shadow people are all
about mind control,
so I decided to fight fire
with fire.
And what I ended up discovering
was that the shadow man
was a phony.
So this man isn't actually
a shadow person?
No.
He's a dead person,
but he looks like
a shadow person.
He does follow people.
He's, like, stalking them.
He would like them to die.
STEVE:
In addition to housing one of
Columbus' oldest restaurants,
the building also had several
business offices.
So, I decided to knock
on a few doors,
and what I wind up finding out
was that the things upstairs
were even worse.
Did you ever
experience anything?
I was downstairs
in the conference room,
and all of a sudden I could
feel, like, a burn on my arm.
And when I pulled up
my sleeve,
you can see the scar
on my arm.
Looks like scratch marks.
So, is there anything else?
There's a young girl.
I feel like she's, like,
trying to get my attention.
It's almost like
you can hear her,
and she's, like,
really sad.
But I feel like she died
a very tragic, sad death.
AMY:
There's a lot of sadness.
[ Whispering ]
I don't like it back here.
[ Normal voice ] There's
something very bad up here.
There's quite a few of 'em
he's got trapped up in there.
A few of what?
[ Whispering ] People.
[ Normal voice ] They're
all crying in the corner.
He says, "Don't pay attention
to the ****
crying in the ****
corner."
Can you take me through
what happened?
NARRATOR: Next...
WOMAN: Within two minutes,
he's dead on the street.
NARRATOR:...Steve unearths
a grisly murder.
Would she have
gotten hung?
STEVE: Without question,
the Jury Room
had a colorful past,
and years of rumors made it hard
to distinguish fact
from fiction.
But there was one lead
I couldn't ignore.
At one time,
the building was a bordello,
and a confrontation
between one of the prostitutes,
Frances Miller,
and a potential john
ended in bloodshed.
Can you take me
through what happened?
It's the end
of March, 1859.
3 guys in their 20s,
friends, meet up.
They've been drinking
way too much,
and they're gonna go off
to the bordello.
There's dark things
coming up from the ground,
from the floor.
There's these men that are
coming up from the floor.
They're trying to come up
from the floor.
You have these
intoxicated young men,
which one of them,
Paulus Ruprecht,
he's definitely gonna get
his way into the bordello,
even though
it's past midnight.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
What's wrong?
People are yelling.
Now, what
about Frances Miller?
So, it's not unusual
to think
that she has to take the matter
into her own hands,
pick up a gun,
and scare him off at least.
AMY:
There's blood on the floor.
Why is there blood
on the floor?
Because there was
this murder.
She turns him away.
Then he says, "I'm gonna kick
down the door."
And at that point,
she's definitely threatened,
and she shoots him,
And within two minutes
he's dead on the street.
He's like,
"Well, now you've got blood
on your hands, too ****"
STEVE: By most accounts,
Frances Miller's actions
were justified,
and many women in her situation
might have done the same thing.
But back in those days,
women in her line of work
had no rights whatsoever.
And according to a local author,
the case against Frances
ruined her life.
This Frances Miller trial,
what can you tell me about it?
Well, uh, I can tell you that it
started in the mayor's court.
Lorenzo English.
He was mayor of Columbus.
And he presided in mayor's court
over the witness testimony.
And then transferred it
to the common pleas court.
Okay.
What was her defense
in the case?
Well, her defense is that Paulus
was banging down the door
and threatened
to kick it down
and enter her bordello
establishment.
So her claim was
self-defense to shoot the guy.
And what winded up
happening?
Well, uh, she was tried
for first-degree murder.
And, um, she was convicted
of manslaughter
and sentenced to 11 years
in prison.
Now, had this guy, English,
done her trial,
would she have gotten hung?
Mayor English
was very, very strict
and a very, very
religious man,
It's my belief
that he would have
really thrown the book
at this woman.
The shadow man,
he's really pretty powerful.
Religious man, very.
Oh, I'm just getting
bits and pieces.
Huh?
He doesn't want me
to get into his mind.
Aah.
AMY: Even though
I'd already proven
that I could see through
his shadow person disguise,
the dead man continued
to try and block
my attempts to connect with him.
But once I broke through,
what he showed me
was absolutely disturbing.
AMY: Somebody's saying,
"And they deserve
to be punished,
"because...
"They were all, uh,
"evil, uh,
"doing very bad things,
uh, like,
against, uh, God."
Is he, like, the threat?
Yeah, I mean,
he can hurt you.
He hurt me. Yeah.
I think he can do that
to others. Yeah.
Do you think he wants
to kill the living here?
Yes.
NARRATOR: Next...
I saw him
coughing up blood.
...the shocking reveal...
There's a female
that he wants to kill.
...and the clients...
We wanted him out of here.
NARRATOR:
...struggle for survival.
I cast you out,
unclean spirit,
along with every satanic power
of the enemy.
STEVE: This is Harold
and Elizabeth.
They bought the place
a few years ago,
and they've had trouble
ever since.
Going into the reveal,
we knew that Amy
was gonna find something,
but what we did hear from her
was much more than we
would have ever imagined.
STEVE: This is Brenda,
and she had a pretty frightening
incident happen to her.
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
AMY: The first person
that I encountered
was a very, very sad,
lost woman.
She was hysterical,
um, crying.
Wow.
I sense her.
I don't see her.
She's just very sad,
and she died
a very tragic death.
Well, back in the 1850s
there was a bordello
run out of the building.
The woman that ran
the bordello here,
her name was Frances Miller.
She shot and killed a young man
who was attempting
to get into the bordello.
She was sentenced to 11 years,
came out, and her life
was basically destroyed.
Could that sad woman you
encountered be Frances miler?
Yes.
ELIZABETH: As a fellow
female business owner,
I can absolutely empathize with
Frances Miller, why that happened.
She was defending her staff.
She was defending her business.
So the next conscious
entity that I encountered,
he's in his 20s.
He is a braggart.
He hates
the depressed woman.
I saw him
coughing up blood.
Well, it sounds like the guy
that Frances Miller murdered.
He was 26 years old.
His name was Paulus Ruprecht.
He was treating the women
like they were animals.
He also has an issue
with the living,
because he wants the place
for himself.
Right now I know
that he can touch and push.
Back towards that office
I was actually pushed
pretty -- pretty violently.
Definitely a forceful push.
He's, like,
at the end of his rope
with the other
dead people here.
Will this guy get worse?
Oh, yeah.
He wants to trash the place.
ELIZABETH: My whole life, I've
waited on people like Paulus,
just an obnoxious,
drunken bar customer,
and I didn't want him
in my bar,
and I certainly didn't want him
harassing the women
who worked here.
This is my business,
and I built it up,
and this man wants
to destroy it -- no way.
So, the next entity
I see is this shadow person.
But it's actually
a dead person
who is projecting that image
around him.
He was an extremely
powerful person.
He was very religious.
He felt the people
who were here
were doing things
against God.
There was a mayor here,
Lorenzo English.
He was very religious
and rigid.
He presided over
the witness testimony
for the case
for Frances Miller.
Do you think the shadow being
is this guy Lorenzo?
Yes, I do.
Why would he be here,
though?
He didn't get to do what
he wanted to do to her in life.
ELIZABETH: We didn't know why
Lorenzo English would be here,
but we knew that our staff
had seen a shadow person
and we knew that
he was bothering them.
And then the fact
that Amy saw him
made us certain that we wanted
him out of here.
I was, um, finishing up
some paperwork,
and all of a sudden
I felt this, like,
burn go down my arm.
STEVE: She still has
the scarring from it.
Oh, my God.
I think he probably did
harm you.
- This guy?
- Yeah.
There's a male
that he wants to harm,
but there's a female
that he wants to kill.
So I did something a little bit
different with my sketch.
I sketched him
attacking me.
AMY: He'd probably be
about 6'3".
You can see, like,
his arms,
and there's bricks
on the floor.
STEVE:
Take a look at this.
ELIZABETH:
He's grabbing at you.
AMY:
What I wanted to show
is what he's capable of doing,
like causing pain.
HAROLD: Seeing the shadow figure
attacking Amy in the drawing
really brought home
that this force
could do that to my wife
and to my staff.
That was scary.
STEVE: Is there any way
that Harold and Elizabeth
can save the restaurant
and save lives?
I was initially concerned
about the shadow man,
because he does have
a lot of power.
But he's just a dead guy,
so with him, his main weakness
is his religion.
Using the religion is
bringing in a man of the cloth
to do a blessing
of the entire location.
Once you do this,
there will be no dead
that can enter this place
and no dead that remain.
And you guys
are definitely gonna do this?
HAROLD: While I'm not
particularly religious,
Amy's the expert.
When she told us that a priest
would get rid of the spirits,
we trusted her.
ELIZABETH:
We had to come in late at night
with the priest to face this,
and we were frightened,
but we knew we had to do it.
PRIEST:
I arrived at the restaurant
and began the normal routines
of a blessing for a building.
Heavenly Father,
we ask for your blessings
on all those who enter the door
in the name of the Father, the
Son, and the Holy Spirit, amen.
Didn't feel bad at all,
but when I went
into the basement,
there was a feeling
of a heavy presence,
had a very dark tone to it.
ELIZABETH: It got really cold,
and the lights were flickering.
It was unlike anything else I've
ever felt in this restaurant.
PRIEST: At that point,
I felt it necessary to move
from just a simple blessing
to an exorcism.
I cast you out,
unclean spirit,
along with every satanic power
of the enemy.
ELIZABETH:
The priest's energy changed.
Be gone and stay away far
from this creature of God.
He became more aggressive.
The blood of the martyrs of all
holy men and women command you,
"Be gone, accursed dragon."
ELIZABETH: There's more prayers.
There's more holy water.
It was scary.
In the name of the Father,
the Son,
and the Holy Spirit,
amen.
When everything was finished
and things settled down,
we finally all felt
just at peace.
HAROLD: Now things have gotten
much better.
We haven't had
any more experiences here,
and the future looks bright
for the Jury Room.
AMY: When dealing
with powerful entities,
sometimes the only way
to get rid of them
is by taking extreme measures.
But now that the sins of
the past have been absolved,
Harold and Elizabeth should take
comfort in knowing
that their customers and staff
have nothing to fear.