I really, really hope they don't live here.
I seen my son in the air
by the back of his shirt.
This poltergeist has some juice.
I understand it was a shootout, though.
They opened fire and
three deputies were killed.
This thing is, mm, not good.
I never been through this. I
never experienced this before.
He says, "I'm gonna get ya."
It's like somebody's
into some dark [bleep].
You're mine you can't escape.
My name is Amy Allan.
What's happening?
I see dead people.
It seems like a devil.
I speak to dead people.
He's pissed off.
And they speak to me.
I felt real fear.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I think she's being murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Serial killer pops in my head.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
Nobody believes me.
It's my job to reveal them.
- You think there's still bodies there?
- I do.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
You got problems. I got news for you.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
This is our house, whether
they like it or not.
Or time to get out.
This is their house...
the house of the dead.
I'm in Florida City.
It's about 45 minutes south of Miami.
I got a call from a married couple,
Tracy and Travas.
The family's so scared by
what's happening in the house,
every night they grab their three kids,
and they huddle in the same room
together till the sun comes up.
It broke my heart listening to their story.
I'm really hoping Amy
and I can help them out.
Since Amy can see two worlds,
this one has to be free
of any leading information.
Family photos, trophies and personal items
can influence her findings
so it's important I
cover or remove them all
before she begins her walk.
Oh, boy.
Hmm.
Right away, there were, like,
several dead people on
the other side of the door
piling up on each other,
desperate to get out.
So, there's something going on here
that's preventing them from leaving.
It's like somebody's into
some dark [bleep], I think.
I do get something with witchcraft.
Now, Tracy, when we spoke on the phone,
you sounded pretty bad.
Tell me again exactly what's going on.
There's a lot of different apparitions,
a lot of touching, bruises...
attacks.
How long have you guys been livin here?
It's been a year now. Why'd you move?
Just so my kids could have their own room.
But seems like I've moved
here to live in a one-bedroom,
because they're too afraid
to sleep in their own room.
Now, who exactly is living in the house?
My husband,
my daughter... she's 13...
my son Travis, he's eight years old.
And the baby, he's two.
Okay. You told me on the phone
you did a blessing on the house.
Yes, I have.
When I first came, the
landlord actually told me
that she's been saging the house.
Why would the landlord tell you that?
At the time when I moved in,
I didn't think about
it when she told me that
because I was just so
excited to be in a home.
So, I continue saging the house.
It seems like everything
just got worse after then.
It's not right what's going on here.
There's [bleep] going on all over here.
This is insane.
I'm seeing this woman and
this man who lived here.
They're inviting dead
people to come home with them
and trapping them.
Either someone in this house now
or someone who used to live here
is messing around with dark magic
and is calling out to the
dead, but I don't know why.
I really [bleep] hope
these people are not here anymore.
I'm angry right now.
I really, really [bleep]
hope they don't live here.
What else is going on?
Mood swings.
What kind of mood swings?
What are you talking about?
I could be one moment cooking
and being happy and laughing,
and then all of sudden, I
just get into being angry.
I'm just so mad,
and I get very abusive to my husband.
I really have to, like, leave the house.
When you leave the house,
are your moods better?
Perfect. I'm happy.
You on any medication
that would cause this?
No.
It got real bad where my relationship
with my husband is really going down.
We were like love birds.
We were together for 13 years,
and it's like now, there's
times that I don't want
nothing to do with my husband at all.
Sorry.
It's gotta be tough for
him too, I would think.
It's real tough, and he doesn't walk away,
'cause he knows it's this house
that's making me act like this.
This is not me.
There's also really intense and big energy.
I'm thinking it's some type of poltergeist.
This person is not mentally well.
I think it's the person
practicing dark [bleep].
I would think that people who were here
would feel this panic.
It's really fear, but you feel it like...
anxiety.
I'm, like, literally shaking.
So, what's going on in here?
We all sleep together here.
My son, the babies, stays
in this room with us,
because they're too scared to
be in the rest of the house.
I actually had my son that
was lifted off the floor.
He was in the air.
I seen my son in the air
by the back of his shirt.
What happened?
My husband got off the
bed and he fell completely.
So, whatever had him let go?
Yes, and he was scared.
We were all scared.
And what about you? Anything with you?
Yeah. I wake up with bruises
on my legs like I've been hit.
Just on your legs?
Yes, just on my legs.
This is just something small.
This is when the bruises
are already just going away.
Yeah, but you said the
kids sleep in bed with you.
Sure you ain't getting kicked by the kids?
No, no, no, no. I'm a light sleeper.
What happened?
I just keep getting touched on.
So, you're getting touched right now?
Yes, while I'm talking to you.
Every time I keep telling you
about something that has happened in here,
somebody keeps tapping me on my back.
I'm getting mad.
I'm starting to get upset about this now.
Wow.
This poltergeist has some juice.
Person's praying. I see
the back of her head.
She's got her hair pinned
kind of like mine...
pinned up, brown.
She gets smacked by the poltergeist.
Smack.
What all can this poltergeist do?
Slapping, hitting, pushing,
shoving, holding people down.
I see her again, beat up by this energy.
Someone's feeding it, for sure.
Getting scared now.
Let's go outside.
Just had to get out of there. I'm sorry.
No, no, listen, I'm gonna try my hardest
to figure out what the hell's here.
That's one thing about me...
I'm real hard on the inside
and the outside, but
this, it makes you weak.
So, Travas, this is your son's room?
This is Travas and DeSean's room,
but they won't sleep in here.
They're too scared to sleep in here.
That's sad, actually.
Now, I was talking to your wife,
and, I tell you, the
stuff she was telling me
that's been going on
here is really concerning.
Everything was good, but
moved into this house,
and all of a sudden, like,
everything just went chaos.
She's, like, a totally different person,
like, anger... like, straight mad, angry.
And she wasn't like that before?
No, never like that.
Never.
We almost got a divorce.
Geez.
Now, what makes you
think this is paranormal?
It's got to be.
We had a perfect marriage for so long
till we moved here.
Tell me about some of the experiences.
If I am watching TV and
I'm sitting on the bed,
I've seen, like, a shadow
right there by my door.
As soon as I turn, you
see the shadow just leave.
- What kind of shadow? What's it look like?
- A dark shadow.
Okay, what, does it
stay there? Is it quick?
- What's the story?
- Nah, it's quick.
When you get ready to, like,
look that way, all of a sudden,
it goes down the hall.
Okay.
When I was talking to your wife,
she was talking about
all the physical things
that are happening to her
and how things have changed.
She wakes up with bruises and
everything. What about you?
I don't have bruises,
but, one day, I was dozing off in my bed,
and I woke up, but I'm,
like, stuck... can't move.
My eyes open, but I
can't say nothing or move.
Wow. So, what'd you do?
I couldn't do nothing.
There's nothing I could've
did until I popped out of it.
It let me go, and then I wake up...
neck pains, like, before I
go to work in the morning.
My back be hurting.
I never been through this. I
never experienced this before.
How are living like that?
It's hard, man. It's hard.
There's this weird, dark thing.
It's [bleep] weird looking.
It's about this big... like that.
And it's like shades of black and gray.
He moves around here a lot.
In this hallway, he's focused on this male.
What do you mean?
He drains his energy.
He possesses him, so
he jumps into his body.
This dark shadow creature
has destructive ways of
interacting with living people,
and I see that it's
targeting a man in this house.
It pretty much tortures him
and makes him feel
trapped inside of himself.
And when he does that,
he causes extreme pain.
Do you know what it wants from him?
Death.
Yeah, this thing is not good.
Sweetheart, how old are you?
- I'm 13.
- 13.
Okay, why don't you
tell me what's going on?
What have you experienced?
I see shadows.
It moves real quick,
and it's black and tall.
Where exactly do you see it?
Sometimes, I will be laying in my bed,
and I'll just see it go
right past the hallway.
- Can you see through it?
- No.
Okay.
There anything else?
Voices...
Just hear a lot of people talking at once.
Okay, does it sound like
they're talking to each other
or they're trying to talk to you?
I can't say because
they're all talking at once,
so I can't hear what they're saying.
Okay. How are you sleeping at night?
I got to force myself to go to sleep.
I put my headphones in and listen to music.
Okay, and you keep that on all night?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, are you afraid right now?
You seem a little, you
know, like, a little tense.
They don't want me here.
Okay.
There are people outside,
and I did see people down the block
that were, kind of, walking up...
Mostly men.
And they are out of it.
It looks like, you
know, a bunch of zombies.
How many?
A lot... about 20, 25.
I do hear them.
I think this person hears
them talking outside...
mumble, mumble, mumble.
This bothers this person a great deal.
This person is really good
at pushing things out and blocking things,
but there's still this overwhelming fear.
They need to just get the [bleep] out.
I know Hurricane Andrew
devastated southern Florida.
In fact, back in '92 when it happened,
I came down here to
help in a rescue effort.
I reached out to a local newspaper reporter
to see if Travas and Tracy's
property was affected.
He said I should come meet with him.
Well, Ken, thanks for
meeting me. I appreciate that.
So, I know my clients'
home was built in 2004,
but what was there back in
'92 before the hurricane hit?
It was a mobile home park.
Okay.
Here is an aerial photo
that shows just how bad the damage was.
It was like a war zone.
Wow.
I just drove past this water tank here,
so this is real close
to my clients' property.
So, what was it like when the storm hit?
It was extremely intense...
Gusts of more than 200 miles per hour.
It was one of Florida's worst disasters.
It mangled cars, planes, boats.
At the time, it was the costliest hurricane
to hit the United States... $26.5 billion.
It virtually changed the face of Florida.
How many people actually died in Florida?
Andrew killed a total
of 44 people in Florida.
- Okay.
- And that included 26 people
directly as a result of the storm.
How did they die?
People were hit by tree limbs.
They drove their cars into high water.
One man actually got crushed
in his home by the high winds.
It was like a squadron of heavy bombers
flew overhead and just unloaded.
Right.
I don't get what the [bleep]
these zombies are doing.
Some of them look like
they've been eaten...
Like, legs are missing, and they're a mess.
They drowned, I think.
I know that, you know, they
pretty much died together
and somehow, they know enough to seek help,
or they're drawn to the energy here.
Very bizarre.
I reached out to the current
owner of Tracy's property
and some of the former tenants,
but nobody would talk to me.
So, since I was striking
out with the living,
I started looking into the dead.
After making a few calls, I got
in touch with a local professor
who tells me one of the
original owners of the land
ended up getting destroyed by it.
So, Dr. George, if I'm
standing on my clients' property
back in 1910, what would've been there?
It was a wilderness...
Flooded heavily during the
rainy season in the summer,
mosquitoes galore at all times.
It was the most desolate place imaginable.
I mean, who owned the land originally?
Well, the land down there,
it was owned by the Tatum brothers...
Four brothers who were big-time developers
in the Miami area.
- Okay.
- Men of means, men of standing.
In fact, here's a
photograph of one of them.
This is Smiley Tatum.
Heavily educated, he was
educated in the subject area
of chemistry of all things.
Here's his wife Florie. You
can see she's high society.
Very well educated, too.
So, now the Tatums that
bought all this land,
did they live on it?
No, not at all.
They lived in the more
settled areas of Miami
in beautiful homes.
You get a sense of the wealth they had.
These are like small mansions.
So, what the hell were
they trying to develop?
Well, the Tatum brothers
wanted to sell land,
and they needed to get
people to buy that land,
and so they sent some of
their people on their payroll
up to Detroit, hoping to get...
Actually hoping to create
a colony of physicians
who would move from Detroit
to this desolate place.
And they sold them this land sight unseen,
because their salespeople
are just so wild in the
way they describe the place,
"This is the Garden of Eden."
Okay, so let me get this straight.
When they came down here,
they thought they were gonna be
moving into, like, a place
that had infrastructure already?
Yeah, infrastructure and, you know,
more as a planned community,
but that's not what
the Tatums had for them.
Okay, now, on the phone,
you mentioned the land
destroyed the Tatums.
What did you mean?
They prospered for the
next decade and a half.
Through the first half of the 1920s,
there's a huge land boom.
And then the boom collapses in '26,
and they lose almost everything.
Wow.
She lost it all too.
When they lost everything by
the second half of the 1920s,
Florie becomes just a regular person,
and they're hurting.
They're straining to get by.
There's an elderly woman,
this kind of creepy chick.
Like, what I'm seeing,
like, a lot of animals,
like snakes and there were fish.
Like, I'm seeing a lot of wilderness.
Even the land looked wild.
But it belongs to her
so I'm a little confused
as to where the [bleep]
this woman's house was.
I don't know if she had four houses,
or she's, like, putting
it on four houses here.
So, this is where the old
lady likes to chill about.
Extremely wealthy, powerful woman.
She is physical,
and she is attached to...
a female in the house.
So far, I know my clients' property
was owned by greedy land developers
and then devastated by Hurricane Andrew,
but I need to see if there's anything else.
Searching through the archives,
I discover a deadly shootout
on Travas and Tracy's land
between cops and four bank robbers.
This property's really
turning out to be a magnet
for pain and suffering.
I've placed a call to a local police chief
who says what happened will
definitely help my case.
During my research,
I came across an article about a shootout
between the cops and some bank robbers
that actually started in your jurisdiction.
What can you tell me about it?
On September 15, 1916,
these crooks by the name of the Rice Gang
did a bank robbery here in Homestead,
and they jumped into a stolen car,
and they headed to the Everglades
near your clients' property.
What happens next?
A posse was formed by Sheriff Dan Hardie,
and the next night, they went
down looking for these guys.
Okay, so now what happens?
I understand there was a shootout, though.
Yes, they opened fire on three deputies,
and three deputies were killed.
Do we know anything about who they were?
One of the cops that was
killed was Allen Henderson.
He gets shot nine times in the back.
What about the other guy?
Well, the second guy
who was shot was brother.
- His brother?
- His brother, William Henderson.
He was shot once in the leg.
Both of them died at the scene.
Who was the third cop?
The third cop was Charles Williams.
He was shot five times, as well,
and he died the next day.
The shootout happens.
Do these guys at least get shot
at the scene, the perps, or do they flee?
- What happens?
- They flee into the Everglades.
They were there for
approximately two weeks.
Eventually, two of the
subjects were killed.
Okay, so how does that happen?
One of them was killed by
civilians stealing supplies.
Another one of the guys drowned.
So, what happens with the other two guys?
Well, Frank Rice and Hugh Alderman,
they were apprehended
and charged with first degree murder.
Matter of fact, I have a article here
from the local newspaper.
Did they go to trial?
Yes, they did, and when they went to trial,
they were convicted of
second degree murder.
As a matter of fact, one of the guys, Rice,
he was paroled after nine years.
The other guy, Alderman,
went insane while he was in prison
and eventually transferred
to Florida State Hospital
where he spent the next
53 years until he died.
Everybody sees him in this hall.
Sees who?
He's the dude who is
possessing the other guy... the living one.
I'm starting to catch quick glimpses
of what this dark shadow
man was like in life,
and I'm seeing that he was
a very disturbed person.
He was captured.
He was a prisoner.
He was...
murdered or executed.
The living one, I think he went somewhere,
and he brought this home.
I feel like this guy entrapped him somehow.
And so this dead guy
felt, "I was finally free,
and you trapped me, so I'm gonna get ya."
During my walk, I saw
a group of dead people
gathered outside of a
young woman's bedroom.
I'm meeting with the sketch artist
to describe this horrifying scene.
On the other side of the window,
there were several dead men.
Their clothes were all in tatters,
and I saw a person on the bed.
They had their hands on
their head, on their ears.
Is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to meet Travas and Tracy.
Now, they're a married couple.
They have three beautiful kids.
They have been living
here for about a year.
This is a photo.
Basically, since they
moved here, their lives
have been turned upside down.
The kids are nothing but sad and scared.
They want their happy life together.
They had a great marriage.
Now, they're talking about
possibly getting divorced
because of all that's going on here.
They wanna know what's here,
how to kick it the hell out,
and get back to their normal lives.
Now that Amy knows a little
bit about what's going on,
I'm gonna ask her to
tell us about her walk.
As soon as I walked up to the door,
there were a bunch of dead people
on the inside of the house
that were piling up on the door,
wanting out.
And when I came in,
I saw a female
who was a part of a couple that lived here
who was messing around with magic,
calling out to the dead,
trapping and collecting these dead people,
and what they left here
was this ridiculous energy.
And honestly, I didn't
know if it was you guys
or someone who lived here prior.
But seeing you, it seemed
to be an older female.
Well, when they got the
place, the woman that owns it
was saging the place when they got here.
Yes.
Wow.
Now, if she was saging,
then something was going on.
The other thing that I saw
pretty much as soon as I walked in
was a poltergeist.
A poltergeist is created by a living agent
by the electrical charges that
they send out into the air.
It's just a mass of energy.
Now, I don't know if it was
the previous family who created it,
but anyone who's having
emotional issues can feed it.
In the master bedroom,
I saw someone praying,
and this thing smacked her upside the head.
It's a pretty powerful thing.
Well, one of the other
main reasons we're here
is because Tracy's being attacked at night.
Tell Amy about that.
Well, when I wake up in the morning
and I look down,
my legs are just covered with bruises,
like if somebody kicked me, beat me.
Matter of fact, here's a photo.
That's the bruises she would get.
Oh, my gosh.
Now, you also got held down in the bed.
Yeah.
I was dozing off, and all of a sudden,
I just felt something
just, like, hold me down.
I couldn't say anything. I couldn't move.
I couldn't say anything, but eventually,
It let me go.
And it's not just you.
I mean, you saw your son getting picked up.
- Mm-hmm.
- Travas Jr. here.
It was the middle of the night,
and all of a sudden, I
heard him, like, gagging,
like something had him
by the back of his shirt.
We got up, and...
And he just fell, just...
Wow.
What else did you get?
So, there's this older lady that I met.
Whoever she can scare the
most is where she'll go,
and she is attaching herself
to a female in the house.
You know, making this
female feel out of control,
making her feel anxiety,
causing outbursts of rage.
Well, since they moved here,
Tracy's personality has done a 180.
I just get to a point
where I dislike my husband.
I just hate him.
I want to hurt him.
There's just times that I just
don't even wanna be with him.
They bad, bad mood swings.
And I know this is not me.
She wasn't never like this, never.
Till we got here.
Now, the woman you're talking about,
did you get anything else on her?
Well, one of the reasons
why this woman's here is
because she believes this land is all hers.
She was, like, very well
educated, very wealthy,
and she owned a lot of land,
but what I saw was just all, like, wild.
But it was weird because I saw her,
like, in four houses,
so I'm a little confused as to
where this woman's house was.
There's only one woman
that fits that description
that actually owned big
chunk of the land here.
Her name was Florie Tatum.
Her and her husband Smiley,
who were very wealthy, very powerful...
You mentioned they owned
a lot of houses, right?
She actually owned four homes in Miami.
Wow.
So, they lived large.
Now, they bought up about
26,000 acres in this area,
and this was nothing
but wilderness back then,
but their plan was to make a
big profit developing the land.
So, they set out to get people from north
to get out of cold weather in Michigan,
that, "You're gonna come live
in paradise, beautiful paradise."
When they got here, it was a swamp.
What goes around comes around.
In 1926, the real estate
market here crashed.
Florie wound up losing everything...
her money, her standing,
her whole way of living.
Now, do you think that might
have been the woman you saw?
Yes.
So, this is the woman
that's attached to her?
Oh, my gosh.
I'm so mad at her.
Did you see anything else?
I saw this thing in the hallway,
and it was like this black blob.
This entity, I think,
had initially attached
to a male in the home.
I do think that people can see him.
I got that he was alive at one point.
He was either murdered or executed.
He was captured. He was a prisoner.
And I saw something about a firing squad.
That was all that I got about him.
Now, this is not so obvious for me,
but I got one thing I
came up in my research,
and it was a shootout between
cops and some bank robbers.
It happened in September of 1916.
The gang called the Rice Gang,
it was two brothers and two other guys.
What they did is rob a bank in Homestead,
which is less than a
mile from your property.
Then when they fled there in a stolen car,
they wind up holding up by that water tank
that's literally a quarter of a mile
from your property here.
Well, you said a firing squad.
The only thing I can think of
is that the cops got ambushed.
When they showed up,
these guys all came out
and started shooting at the cops
and three cops got killed.
Two of the cops were brothers.
Do you think it's anybody that
was involved in the shootout?
No.
And why not?
Because it goes much further back.
Okay, so this happened in 1916.
You're talking how much further back?
Like the 1700s.
Oh, okay.
I think the living couple
that was into dark magic
brought him here.
He was in a cemetery,
and these people trapped
him, brought him here,
and he's pissed because
he was finally free.
And he's lashing out
'cause he feels trapped.
I think the living person would
experience great deal of pain,
especially in the neck.
My neck hurting right now.
My neck stay hurting.
He learned how to
possess the person's body,
so he knows how to jump people.
And what does he want
to do with the living?
What does he want to do to them?
He wanted to kill him.
Sounds like you guys called
us just when you needed to.
I think so, too.
Yeah.
There's another thing going on here.
Outside was this group of dead people
wandering down the streets.
There was about 20, 25 of them out there.
To me, they looked like zombies.
Some of them, like,
their legs were missing.
Some of them looked half eaten.
All of them died together,
and I thought that they looked drowned.
Do you have any idea
where you're actually at,
like the area?
- No.
- Okay.
It was August 24, 1992.
Hurricane Andrew devastated
Homestead and Florida City,
which is where we are now.
Take a look at what their neighborhood
looked like after the storm hit.
Wait, this is here?
Yes.
Wow.
175-mile-per-hour winds
plus 200 mile per hour gusts.
Now, you said about 25 people.
Mm-hmm.
In Florida, 26 died the
day of the hurricane.
Another 18 died as a
result after the hurricane.
This was like ground zero for where it hit.
Wow.
I just can't believe
they're all still here.
That's very upsetting.
I did do a sketch of them
talking to someone in the
back bedroom over here.
And that's what she does.
I did do a sketch of them
talking to someone in the
back bedroom over here.
And that's what she does.
So, this supposed to be Rosario?
It's a female that I saw
with dark hair in her teens.
This sketch explains a lot to
me about what she was saying.
Broke my heart listening to her.
That's why she wears
her earphones at night.
They don't let her sleep,
so she'd rather sleep during the day.
You need to speak with her.
She's scared, this kid.
She's really scared.
I promise.
It's scary.
I was expecting y'all to tell me something,
but not at this extreme.
Well, Travas and Tracy,
now you know what's here
and what's ripping your family apart,
and the big question is can you stay here
and eventually be a loving family again?
For the answer to that, I'm
gonna turn it over to Amy,
see if she can help you out.
You have a lot of random dead people
that were unfortunately
collected and trapped here.
You have an elderly woman
who's attached herself to you.
There's a dead male influencing
a lot of people in the house,
and you also have a poltergeist.
There's also the victims
from the hurricane.
The first thing would be a curandera
is going to be contacted.
What the hell's a curandera?
They're healers traditionally
found in Latin American culture.
They will utilize various methods
like burning candles,
burning incense, using stones.
The first thing they're gonna
do is remove the attachments...
the dead lady and any of the dead
that would follow you anywhere.
The second thing is they're going to move
on all of the dead, including
the hurricane victims.
- Ah, that's great.
- So, that's awesome.
The third thing is they're
gonna clear the home
of all the residual and
current emotional muck.
So, it's a person that could
cover anything that's here.
Pretty much.
Okay, yeah.
Got chills.
I know this was a lot, though, tonight.
You guys got hit with a...
Wow, it's a lot, yeah.
How soon after they come through here
and do their thing will
they see the difference?
- Oh, immediately.
- Yeah?
- Oh, yeah.
- Well, that's what's up.
Yeah.
It feels like a lot has
come off of me, a lot,
'cause I really thought I was going crazy.
I thought I was going insane.
Yeah, we was on our urge
of, like, splitting up.
But it's just... at the end of the day,
she's still my wife, you know.
You're gonna take Amy's advice?
- Yes, I am.
- Okay.
How 'bout you? You
feeling good about what...
- Most definitely.
- Okay.
You know I am.
I was shaky earlier.
I'm still a little shaky,
but at least I know.
- You feel better, though.
- Yeah, exactly.
I feel way better.
That it's not the end.
Tracy and Travas need to follow my advice
if they wanna fix their relationship
and get rid of the evil that's
tearing their family apart.
I believe that once they find a curandero,
they can begin healing
and lead a peaceful life.