There's up to 50 dead people down in here.
I wake up with my heart racing,
scared to death.
That creature... I don't think it's good.
For a small town, it was scandalous.
He's like, "I just want to make them bleed."
I don't like it at all,
and I want it to stop.
What are they doing down here?
This place is, like, insane.
"You're mine. You can't escape."
My name is Amy Allan.
What's happening?
I see dead people.
It seems like a devil.
I speak to dead people.
He's pissed off.
And they speak to me.
I felt real fear.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I think she's being murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Serial killer pops in my head.
And I know every person,
every house, has secrets.
Nobody believes me.
It's my job to reveal them.
- Do you think there's still bodies there?
- I do.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
You got problems. I got news for you.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
This is our house...
whether they like it or not.
Or time to get out.
This is their house, the house of the dead.
I'm in the small town of Leslie, Michigan,
about a half-hour outside of Lansing.
Amy and I got called in
by a woman named Michelle.
Now, she told me on the phone
that whatever's in the house
is attacking her and her daughter.
She begged me to rush over
because she thinks she's
running out of time.
Before Amy arrives,
I do a complete sweep of the house.
What's common in most homes,
like family photographs,
can influence her findings.
So it's important I remove them
all before she begins her walk.
Oh, boy.
The living people here...
It feels like they're, like,
weighted, weighted down
because there's too much...
death here.
This house is just really dark,
really bad with crazy,
with people acting out
and doing bad things.
It's not...
It's not good.
Michelle, I'm glad I'm here,
'cause you sounded really
concerned on the phone
about what's happening.
Things have been going on
in this house for years.
We've seen apparitions.
We hear footsteps.
Then the last couple years,
it has become extremely physical.
It's attacking my daughter and I,
scratching us, leaving bruises.
Wow.
Who lives in the house, exactly?
My husband, my 16-year-old daughter,
and my 17-year-old son.
This is your daughter that's
being affected by this stuff?
Yes.
As a mother, it absolutely eats at my gut.
I would do anything to protect her,
but if you can't see something,
then how do you stop it from happening?
With all this going on,
how you dealing with it?
Well, we're not dealing with it well lately.
As soon as we walk into the house,
it's like a switch.
The mood will absolutely change.
You'll go from, you know,
being in a great mood
to being completely angry,
and I've definitely been sick a lot
since I've moved into this house.
What kind of sick we talking about?
My daughter and I both get
debilitating headaches,
and I've had several surgeries.
I've had shoulder surgery.
I've had a hysterectomy.
I lost a baby in this house.
Wow. I'm sorry to hear that.
This house is beautiful.
I mean, why don't you just move?
Somebody would buy it.
I love this house.
I've put my heart and soul into this house.
I've been praying for, you know,
when you guys get here
- that you're really able to help us.
- Okay.
Someone's panicking.
Um, there's a woman.
Living. She has long hair, brown.
She's got something wrong with her heart.
It's just...
a [bleep] mess, man.
She's so scared.
[Bleep] She can't breathe, man.
Okay, so, what's going on in here?
I have physically been
attacked in this room.
I receive scratches.
I actually have a picture
that I took last week.
Wow.
Do you remember scratching yourself at all?
No. And it's happened in
this room several times.
Geez. Amy's gonna want to see this.
You mind if I hold onto
this for a little bit?
- Sure.
- Okay.
Now,
do you have anything else going on in here?
I will hear footsteps
coming down the stairs,
and shortly after, a shadow will appear
walking down the stairways
over there to our basement.
I would describe it like a man,
but as a black mass.
I know it's taller than I am.
And you're not on medication
or anything like that?
No, I'm not on any medication.
You drink at night before you go to bed?
- No.
- Okay.
I wake up with my heart racing,
like, scared to death.
Okay.
Whoa.
What?
There's a really big shadow person here,
a shadow being. It doesn't even have a face.
Really tall, really...
big.
I don't like it. I-I don't think it's good.
It's, like...
trying to make me follow it up the stairs.
It's, like, crawling oddly down the hall.
And it's climbing the ceilings
and climbing the walls.
And it's like this on the ceiling.
You know what I'm saying?
Man, it gets...
It gets bad at night. It gets bad at night.
Thing, like, tortures her.
No sleeping, no sleep.
So, what's going on up here?
I will see the shadow man
roll right across my ceiling over my bed.
Okay. Kind of like the shadow
guy you described downstairs?
- Exactly like that.
- That's bizarre.
Is anything else going on?
The other thing is,
I have repeated nightmares.
And when I wake up from these dreams,
I will have bruises on my thighs
in the shape of fingerprints.
You okay?
Um...
it just reminds me of the times
when I was sexually assaulted as a child.
I wasn't aware of that. Okay.
I was attacked in a very brutal manner.
I was chased around by a babysitter
who would strip naked,
and he would chase me around the house.
And most of the time,
I would hide under the bed
until he would drag me out by my ankles
and physically assault me, so...
I don't like it at all,
and I do want it to stop.
It's like you're reliving it, I know. Okay?
I told myself not to cry.
It's not easy to talk about.
How often did this happen
when you were younger?
This happen one time?
No, I was left with him
on several occasions.
This guy ever get arrested for this?
No, he did not.
He committed suicide as a teenager.
Okay. All right.
I'm sorry.
I know. It's gonna be all right.
You'll be okay.
Mm, this woman again...
Something happened to her.
What?
I don't know. Like, she was
physically abused or something.
And, like, because of that experience,
like, maybe she's just opened,
'cause this person has abilities.
There's, like, this creepy guy.
And this woman in particular...
She's aware that he does bad things.
Do you know when he's from?
Not that long ago.
He's focused on...
the suicide?
I think he killed himself,
and I think he would like to
make others kill themselves.
His endgame...
is death.
I was talking to your wife.
What your daughter and her
are both going through,
that would drive me to
want to shoot somebody.
I do. I do want to shoot somebody,
but there's nobody to shoot, Steve.
Have you had any experiences here?
Yeah. I was outside here with my son, Lucas,
building him something.
I put my circular saw down to my right.
And Luke's eyes opened up.
And at that point, I looked,
and the saw had levitated.
It went through my tennis shoes
and cut off my three middle toes.
- You're joking.
- No, sir.
You know, Dan, looking at this,
I've had friends that have
hurt themselves pretty bad,
and they never want to
admit they made a mistake.
I'd tell you if I made a mistake.
I've looked at it a million times.
I didn't place the saw down on my own foot.
Is it possible you dropped it down,
and it bounced off of something?
No, I set it down.
You set it down? Because I'm very cognizant
of this place and how people
have gotten hurt here.
We had the leading tile guy in
town cut his thumb off here.
Numerous contractors have
been hurt while working here.
This creepy guy...
He's like, "I just go in the ground,
and I just want to make them bleed."
He's very disturbed.
He creeps.
He's a creeper.
I see him, like,
coming up behind a living dude,
and then his head is, like,
right here, you know?
The dead dude's face is right here,
And he turns, you know?
And he's, like, whispering...
you know? And...
this gets inside the living dude's head.
He tells him what to do.
What does he tell him to do?
I think kill himself, you know?
Holy [bleep]
What?
There's probably up to 50
dead people down in here.
Who the [bleep]...
you know what I'm saying?
Has 50 [bleep] bad dead people
in their house in the middle of nowhere?
What are they doing down here?
Wow. Something's wrong with
these [bleep] people, man.
This place is, like, insane.
So, Shayna, I was talking to Mom,
and I really wanted to
sit down and talk to you,
'cause she told me
whatever's happening in the house
is happening to her and you.
- Mm-hmm. - So I just wanted to
hear from you what's going on.
I'm being scratched and bruised.
This just comes out of nowhere?
Yes, I wake up with it.
So, where else have you been scratched?
On my face.
- On your face?
- Yes, and I have a picture.
Wow. There's nothing sharp in
the bed or anything like that,
- like a zipper or anything, like...
- No.
A pillowcase or anything
that could've done this?
- No.
- Okay.
Now, what else is happening to you?
I see a shadow man in my room every night.
He can appear close to my bed,
but he's, like, this black figure,
and he's, like, tall,
and he's just pitch black.
He's darker than the night.
So, it sounds like you're
experiencing a lot.
- I mean, anything else happening?
- My door.
It's either the bathroom
door or my bedroom door.
I'll shut it,
and I'll lock it so I feel safer,
and it will shake it and pound on it
and try to get in. It'll push on it.
Sometimes, I wake up at night,
and it will be happening.
What do you think it is?
I think it's the spirit that
shows himself as a dark man.
- That's frightening stuff.
- Yeah.
The shadow thing tries to get in here,
but it can't.
When the door's closed, it can't get in.
Door's very important.
That creature...
- shadow...
- It's there?
Yeah, he's...
This is his area.
He likes it over there by the window.
There, he crumples up.
Like, he gets all hunched,
and he just... He waits, He waits.
Then he'll crawl out the
door and crawl down the hall,
you know, and go [bleep] with people.
He might be [bleep] crazy.
I don't doubt Michelle's
testimony for one minute,
but one thing that's nagging at me...
I'm wondering if the traumatic
event in her childhood
could be making her relive that nightmare
night after night after night.
It might not be paranormal at all.
Maybe it's psychological.
I'm heading over to meet with a psychologist
to see if that's possible.
Dr. Sivyer, thanks for meeting me.
I appreciate it.
So, I have a client who was
molested as a young child,
and she seems to be having
reoccurring nightmares
duplicating what happened to her.
- Okay.
- Is that common?
Generally speaking,
on post-traumatic stress disorder,
one of the things that can manifest
is called flashbacks,
where they're reliving the traumatic event
over and over again.
Okay. Now, here's the weird part.
She's actually waking up with
the bruising from an attack.
Individuals that suffer from
borderline personality disorder,
they sometimes cut themselves
or bruise themselves.
What would I, as an investigator, look for
in a person to see if they're
that type of personality
to do that to themselves?
They have a hard time with their emotions.
They like a lot of attention
directed towards them.
Yeah, that doesn't describe this woman.
- She's the total opposite.
- Okay.
This is the weird part,
if you could help me out with this.
- She has a 16-year-old daughter...
- Okay.
Who's having the same type
of nightmares every night...
All right... same bruising.
It could be that her mom has explained
these events over and over again,
and they're seeing the same things.
Could those dreams possibly cause bruises?
There's no clinical
evidence that I'm aware of
that bruising and scratches
just manifest themselves.
So, I'm seeing,
like, this living woman.
I feel like she feels like
she's losing her mind.
I want to say it's stress,
and I want to say it's due to her abilities.
But it's [bleep] her body up bad.
This might be what's affecting her heart.
It's debilitating.
It's becoming debilitating for her.
I'm confident that
Michelle and Shayna's bruises
are not self-inflicted,
so I need to look for an explanation
of what's going on in this house.
So I'm hitting the books
at the local library.
Searching old property records,
I find the original owner is
a man named Lafayette Peek.
Turns out,
he suffered a lot during his time,
losing three children
all under the age of 1.
I'm heading over to meet
with a local genealogist
who says those deaths
were just the beginning
of the family's tragedies.
Lafayette Peek and his wife, Harriet,
purchased the property in the 1860s.
And along with his brother, Theodore,
they ran an apple orchard.
And you can see their
property here at the top.
The three kids dying,
I guess that's not uncommon
back in those days,
but you say that was just the beginning
of his problems. What'd you mean by that?
In addition to Lafayette's children dying,
his brother,
Theodore, and his wife, Sally,
also had five children,
and they lost three of those children,
as well.
He does not take this very well.
He definitely had a mental
breakdown of some sort.
He was wandering through the streets.
He was shouting and screaming
and disturbing the neighbors.
His daughter filed a
petition with the court,
asking him to be declared insane
and committed to the
Kalamazoo State Hospital
for treatment.
What happened to him? Did he get committed?
He did not. So one of his
daughters petitioned the court
to, in fact, have him
released into her custody.
And so he went and lived with her
until he died of a stroke
several years later.
Well, that's kind of a sad
story for this guy...
all this death around him,
and then he goes crazy.
Unfortunately, that's not where it ends.
I also located several other individuals
related to the family,
but not necessarily by blood.
They were neighbors who had
various forms of mental illness.
That's odd. So it wasn't...
You know mental illness can
run in families, but...
It seems to have run in this neighborhood.
I see this man.
I think he lived here,
and I think he's mentally ill.
This person feels crazy.
This house...
It's caused people to go insane.
Oh, I'm getting really pissed. Aah.
This is a mess with the people here...
big-time mess.
During my research,
I came across something
else that caught my eye.
There was a huge legal battle
over Dan and Michelle's property.
And when I called a local historian,
he said it involved betrayal,
death, and insanity.
When I contacted you, you said there was
a lot more to the story.
It's quite an involved case.
The property was owned
by John and Maria Stitt,
and between the two of them,
they had a daughter named Rosa.
Okay.
Well, John was not the
most faithful of husbands.
And after about 20 years of marriage,
Maria had decided she had enough.
And in 1887, she filed for a divorce.
In that same year,
John is sued by one of his neighbors,
Albert Blackmore,
for alienating his wife's affections.
- So, he's going after this other guy's wife?
- He is.
Okay.
So, how's that work out?
They settle out of court financially.
And then he would marry
Elizabeth Blackmore,
And she has adopted an
African-American child
who's 14 years old by
the name of Etta Mecklin.
And it's not much time goes by,
then rumors are circulating
- that John is now having
affections for Etta... - Okay.
- The 14-year-old.
- This guy's a real piece of work.
And then his wife,
his current wife, Elizabeth,
in 1898, develops liver and breast cancer.
- Okay.
- She passes away in 1902,
so that leaves Etta and John in the home.
John passes away within a few
weeks of his wife's death,
and he's found in Etta's bed.
Here's an article.
The big thing is,
John willed most of his estate to Etta.
Wow.
For a small town, it was scandalous.
What happens next?
This is where the lawsuit begins.
His biological daughter
really felt slighted...
- Okay...
- and contests the will.
Rosa felt that her father
was so overcome with passion for Etta
- that he rewrote his will.
- You had mentioned on the phone
there was a little bit of insanity.
I guess that came...
talking about him being under her influence?
- That's what it seems.
- Okay, so, how'd it work out?
Well, in the end, Etta won the case.
Really?
Rosa appealed this on two occasions
and lost on appeal both times.
This image I'm seeing
is really strange.
This is that weird [bleep]
creature thing...
crawling oddly down the hall.
Like, I don't know what this
[bleep] thing is, really.
I can't figure out
what this shadow creature
is or where it came from,
but I know that it's been
here for a very long time,
and its goal is to torment living people.
- Does it interact physically?
- Yes.
It makes people kind of [bleep] crazy.
I encountered many entities during my walk,
but two stood out the most...
first, the creepy guy
who's whispering to a
living man in the house.
It was in this room.
His eyes are kind of roundish.
Seemed to have lighter-colored hair.
And what about the second
person that you saw?
He had dark hair,
and he looked like a corpse.
Next, I described
the shadow creature
tormenting a living woman.
She had long hair. Late 30s or early 40s.
And there's this thing in the hallway.
Its skin is really smooth,
a gray/brown kind of color.
Coming down the hallway,
it actually had to be on all fours,
because it's so large.
Amy, is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our findings
to each other and our
clients for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to meet Dan and Michelle.
This is their home.
They're raising their two children here.
This is Lucas, who's 17.
This is Shayna, who's 16.
Now, things are pretty bad here
because Michelle and Shayna
are being physically
and emotionally attacked
every night.
The family's put their heart and soul
into this home, as you can see,
and they really don't want to leave.
So now that Amy knows a little
bit about what's going on,
I'm gonna ask her to tell us about her walk.
When I got here, I entered the house,
and it was extremely chaotic energy,
especially in the basement.
Like, when I went down there,
I saw all of these dead people.
There was about 50 of them,
which was very shocking.
The scary thing is that
all of those dead people are all negative.
There's not one good person in there,
and that was horrifying.
And one of the things
that also seemed to be a
constant throughout the walk
was the feeling of people thinking
that they're losing their minds,
that they're going crazy.
You guys do experience pretty
bad mood swings, right?
- Yeah.
- Absolutely.
We'll be happy and just loving.
We love... We're a strong couple.
And we come in the house,
and the energy just zaps us,
and we'll start fighting immediately.
You come in, you know, it drags you down.
Mm-hmm.
So, during my research of the property,
it turns out
there's a long history of mental illness
associated with the land here.
Back in the 1860s,
the original owners of your property
were two brothers...
Lafayette and Theodore Peek.
There was a little bit of
bad luck with this family.
Both brothers had five kids.
Both brothers lost three kids.
But it got a little bit worse for Theodore.
Apparently, he went nuts...
walking up and down the streets,
talking to himself,
disturbing the peace, screaming,
to the point where his daughter
tried to have him committed.
So, I got the paperwork on that.
The thing is, there's been other cases
of neighbors in the area going crazy, too.
There was another guy that lived
here by the name of John Stitt.
Apparently, this guy was a womanizer.
He had an ex-wife.
He had a daughter. Has an affair
with his neighbor's wife.
He winds up marrying her.
They adopt a little, 14-year-old black girl,
and it was a rumor that he winds up
having an affair with this kid.
She's 14 years old.
Oh.
You know, a little bit crazy.
Yep. That all makes sense.
When I made it over to
the foot of the stairs,
I saw a woman with long, brown hair,
and she was panicking.
I could feel her fear.
She felt extremely overwhelmed.
Somebody that's living?
This is a living person, yes.
The thing is, is that...
the home is so filled with dead energy,
it can negatively affect the body.
And in this person in particular,
I was getting that she might
develop some type of heart issue?
I actually had
a period of time...
which I didn't think it was important,
and I didn't mention it to anybody...
that I was literally blacking out.
And I had to go through
a bunch of heart tests.
And they told me at the time
that I had neural myocardial syncope.
Okay.
That is very common with sensitives.
And unfortunately for mediums,
we can attract things that
aren't particularly good.
You think she's maybe sensitive?
Mm-hmm.
I think the house is full of sensitives.
What else did you see?
One of the other things that
I got was this female was,
at some point in her life,
abused by a male...
and is having a very difficult time
letting that experience go.
I'm sorry, sweetie. I didn't want to
have to bring it up at the table.
You know, could you just share with her
what happened when you were a kid?
When I was a little girl,
between the ages of 3 and 4,
I was left with a male babysitter
who sexually abused me on several occasions.
He used to strip naked in front
of me and chase me around.
And he has since committed suicide.
Why'd you have that big reaction like that?
Uh...
I ran into a person in the basement,
and I referred to him as "The Creeper."
He's very disturbed,
and he attempts to make the living here
do bad things...
make them feel like they're going crazy.
He did not die that long ago,
and I did get that he killed himself.
Well, once you told me that
you thought he committed suicide,
I made some calls.
He went into a parking lot
with a car, broke the tail pipe off,
turned on the heat, windows closed,
in the end of August,
and was found dead.
And the caveat to the whole thing...
He'd just came home from babysitting.
Now, do me a favor
and tell Amy about the attacks every night.
One of the same nightmares
that I have every single night
is that I'm being chased.
You know, I try to, like,
defend myself in the dream,
and I've woken up with fingerprints,
bruises on my thighs.
Wow.
And I get scratched.
My daughter came to us and shared with us
that she felt like somebody
was trying to assault her,
and she has woken up with...
Similar bruises.
Oh, my goodness.
And they're unexplainable.
They got photos.
This is Michelle with some
scratches on her chest area.
There's their daughter, Shayna,
with scratches on her face area.
Wow.
Now, I spoke to a psychologist
just to get a grip on the whole thing,
and you having the nightmares
is totally explainable with the PTSD.
Yes, absolutely.
But the bruising and scratching don't add up
- based on the profile she gave me.
- Okay.
I did do a sketch with the creeper guy.
Take a look.
The sharp nose and the cheekbones...
He definitely reminds me of him.
The strange thing about him is,
I don't think he's the one
harming the women here.
He had very bad intentions
towards the males in the house.
He's trying to plant harmful thoughts,
telling the males in the
household to commit suicide,
wanting to drive them insane.
That's his main goal,
which is very concerning.
He'll never be successful.
Do me a favor and
tell her about the blade
that landed on your foot.
It was on September 11, 2005.
I sat the saw down carefully,
and the saw levitated,
came over my foot,
and chopped off three of my toes.
- Whoa.
- He had a picture of it, too.
Oh, my God.
There is something else that's here
that might be doing the major damage.
The first time I saw it
was when I was about to go up the stairs,
and it was just pitch-black and huge.
It had no face, just kind of a mouth.
It's, like, crawling oddly down the hall.
It's like this on the ceiling.
You know what I'm saying?
So, I did a sketch of a scene.
Take a look.
Sorry. It's really not a good situation.
So, I did a sketch of a scene.
Take a look.
Sorry. It's really not a good situation.
We see a shadow every night
come across the stairwell to the basement...
and it is completely dark.
You cannot see through it.
But is the purpose for watching us?
What is it trying to do?
This thing is extremely old...
never been human.
And it's been wreaking
havoc around this area
for quite some time.
It's caused people to go insane.
Could that explain what happened
to the Peeks and the Stitts
that lived on this property at some point?
Absolutely, yes.
From a Christian standpoint,
you would call it the devil.
There are many of them all over the world,
and they are much more powerful than demons.
Is it this thing that's
giving her all the bruises?
Yes.
Whatever it is that scares you,
whatever it is
that will harm you,
it's going to provide it.
So, this guy here... Did
this devil bring him?
I think it's highly likely.
I'm really worried now.
If this is something
that we can't get rid of,
how am I, you know,
ever gonna be free of that?
Now, Dan, when we spoke,
you said you'd do anything
- to protect your family.
- Absolutely.
Now we're gonna see what it's gonna take
to protect your wife and your daughter.
For that, I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
If you stay here,
there's gonna be a lot
of things you need to do.
You have the devil.
You have the creeper.
You have the 50 dead people.
You would have to hit
everything simultaneously.
So I would recommend a
minister and a Wiccan.
Basically, you would have this
Wiccan priest or priestess
do a clearing and a banishment.
You would have the minister do a blessing.
What they're going to do
is push everybody out.
But... you ain't gonna
get rid of this devil.
So, you're saying the devil
would still be inside their house?
No, they would push it
outside their property line.
But it's not gonna keep him
out of the neighborhood?
Mnh-mnh, no.
It's always been here.
So, now, once the Wiccan and the minister
come in and they do what they need to do,
how do they keep the dead away from here?
What I would suggest is, once a week,
you go out... And you can put a mixture
of salt and holy water
in just a regular spray bottle...
Going around and spraying the perimeter,
and then
spraying all of the window
ledges and all of the doors.
Be very surprised if anything
happens inside the house
once you guys are doing all of this.
As far as your abilities are concerned,
I would begin with
finding an online or
in-person meditation workshop.
I would also recommend therapy for you.
I'm kind of disappointed
in myself right now
that if I brought a lot
of this about my family.
You can't blame yourself
for what happened to you in the past.
This thing was here before we got here.
That's true.
You can't help your family
until you help yourself.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I'd do anything to help my family.
What are you gonna do?
We're gonna take Amy's advice.
We're gonna take her advice
and do everything as a team.
As long as you do all of these steps,
the safest place will be this house.
I really hope Michelle
and Daniel follow my advice
and deal with the evil that's
terrorizing their family.
With the help of a Wiccan and a minister,
they should be able to free themselves
of the darkness living inside their home.