Probably a lot of different deaths,
a lot of violent deaths.
It just seems like it's
getting worse for everyone.
He says, "Those [bleep] got to go."
He shoots himself with the same rifle
that killed his stepdaughter.
That's a twist.
Someone said, "That's the room of death."
My son whispered, he says,
"That's a bad guy."
Would you say they're a threat?
Something wiped everybody out.
"You're mine. You can't escape."
My name is Amy Allan.
What's happening?
I see dead people.
It seems like a devil.
I speak to dead people.
He's pissed off.
And they speak to me.
I felt real fear.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I think she's being murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Serial killer pops in my head.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
Nobody believes me.
It's my job to reveal them.
- Do you think there's still bodies there?
- I do.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
You got problems. I got news for you.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
This is our house...
whether they like it or not.
Or time to get out.
This is their house, the house of the dead.
I'm in Sumpter, Oregon.
It's a small mountain town about
two hours from Boise, Idaho.
Now, we got called in by a couple
that live and work in a B&B in town.
They want to turn the
business over to their son,
but the activity's gotten so
violent and physical lately,
they don't know what to do,
and they're worried.
They sound scared and
desperately want us to find
a way to keep the B&B in the family.
Before Amy arrives,
I look for any leading information.
Photographs, antiques, and personal items
can influence her findings.
So it's important I
cover or remove them all.
When I'm done, the location will
be ready for tonight's walk.
There is a lot of physical pain here.
My whole head hurts a lot,
and there's a lot of dead people here.
They all died horribly
and I would say violently.
Barb, I'm glad to be here.
This is beautiful place,
but you got a problem here.
Yeah. We love the place.
We've had it for 17 years,
and we've always had little things happen,
but it just seems like
it's getting worse for our guests,
for everyone.
Now, Barb, as far as activity goes,
what are we talking about?
We hear noises that we can't explain,
things are moved,
people feel sick.
And now it's getting really physical.
People are being touched.
I'm just concerned, you know, because we...
Like I say, it's our home first,
and you want to be happy in your home.
And then when we have people come in,
we want to feel that they
are safe and secure here.
What do you know about the
history of the building itself?
That it opened in May of 1900
as Sumpter General Hospital.
- So this was a hospital?
- Mm-hmm.
That was what it was built for.
Okay.
You're looking to retire and
turn this over to your son,
- is that right?
- Yeah, that was the idea.
And he's got two little kids.
I just...
I want to make sure that
they're safe when they're here.
- How attached are you to this place?
- I love it.
I guess we just really thought,
"Oh, that building just needs to be"...
"Needs some love and attention."
What the hell?
There's quite a few dead women here.
They seem to be from a while ago,
maybe 1890...
like 1905?
One of the ladies is the representative
and head honcho of these other four women.
I don't know why they got stuck here.
They didn't die all at the same time.
There's a man.
Mm.
He doesn't look good. He's a little old man.
He's mean. He is ornery.
Ow.
He definitely can make
physical contact with people.
He's pinching and poking.
I don't like him.
Okay, what's going on in here?
We keep hearing loud bangs,
like an encyclopedia,
heavy book being dropped flat
on a wooden floor.
And we'd get up. We were in bed.
We'd get up, and we look all around.
We don't see anything that made a noise.
And what about guests?
No, there were no guests.
Well, this is a B&B.
You sure nobody came in
to try to get a room?
There wasn't anything.
I mean, we both looked.
Anything else in this room?
Yes. One day,
these doors were propped
open like they are right now.
Okay.
I'm in the other room,
hear a noise, come out here,
and this picture is lying facedown
right here on the floor.
It would have had to come
up and over and down.
Okay, so when you...
It was just a couple minutes before,
you saw the doors like this.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
And that picture was...
Was lying facedown right there.
Now, any guests?
No guests.
So nobody else was in the building?
No one.
I can't even figure out,
unless it fell and came through here,
but even that's pushing it.
I can't even figure out how to debunk that.
Now, have any guests had issues
with things moving on their own?
A lot of guests have experienced that.
Their glasses. Okay.
Kick their shoes off here
and find them over there the next morning.
That's bizarre.
The old man, he's tired of these women.
He's trying to keep them out of the house,
but it's not working,
and I think he really hates the lead one.
They've had fights,
and it's affected their environment.
Some objects moved or thrown.
And, like, the electricity
definitely was affected in those situations.
I spoke with your wife.
Mm-hmm.
And she was telling me
about some of the things
you got going on here.
It seems like you got a bit of a problem.
The increased activity in
the last couple of years,
especially in the last few months,
has given me some concern.
Has it hurt business?
In recent months,
there have been three or four times
where, in room six,
somebody has sensed
that somebody had crawled
into bed with them.
And in one case, I had a young lady up there
who said the next morning that,
whatever it was,
was breathing in her ear,
and it startled her.
She woke up, and she yelled.
What if that had been
somebody that had a bad ticker
and was fairly old, you know?
What kind of experience are
you having in the house?
Electrical problems drive me crazy.
Lights going on and off by themselves,
timers going off.
What about the wiring?
Wiring's all brand-new.
Have you seen anything else,
heard anything else?
Yeah.
A friend of mine and I
were here in the kitchen,
and looking up here...
and I can only see it from the knees down...
something or someone came down the stairs.
There wasn't anybody in here,
and the back door was locked upstairs.
Okay, so you guys go up there
and check it out, though?
- Yeah.
- Nothing.
There's nobody there.
Amy once in a while will tell people this...
"You got a serious problem
that's gonna get a lot worse.
You need to get the hell out of here."
What would you think if you heard that?
Blood, sweat, and tears for 17 years
have gone into this place.
Yeah, so it would be really
hard to just walk away from it.
Okay.
Can the living see this angry man?
Yes, and he looks creepy.
His face is a horrible mess.
It's like if he took ash
and was trying to re-create his face.
Ohh, I feel dizzy.
I don't feel good.
He's hurting living people.
So, Brian,
I was taing to your mom and dad,
and your mom was expressing concerns
about your kids being here.
Do you have the same concerns?
My son comes here,
and he's seeing imaginary people,
and he doesn't see them at my house.
He even refers to them as "the bad people."
Putting him down for a nap,
and he points over at
the chair in the corner,
and in a very different voice,
he says, "That's a bad guy."
Needless to say, it was just ominous.
So what about you as far as experiences go?
I have had one.
I was in my room,
and the bed that I'm on started shaking.
I actually thought, "Oh, earthquake?"
Jumped off the bed, looked, still shaking,
and nothing else in the house was moving.
Well,
how big of a shake are we talking about?
I was getting moved,
so it was like, you know, moving.
- That hard?
- Yeah, yeah.
So, I know your mom's got cats.
I literally looked to see if there was,
like, a cat that crawled up underneath,
and there isn't even a space under there,
so it's not possible.
I don't want it around.
I don't want my kids around it.
I don't want to have to
talk about that with them.
I don't like it in here.
These women come in here,
and they're all dressed in black.
I don't like them back here.
They're not the same as
when they're downstairs.
These women are creepy, man.
This could be what the old
man was talking about...
But I think him trying
to get rid of these women
might ultimately not be such a bad thing.
He very much has the attitude of,
"This is my house." You know what I mean?
"And those [bleep] got to go."
Kari, I understand
you're actually staying in the
hotel tonight in this room.
I am.
Okay, is this the first
time you're staying here?
No, I've stayed here two other times.
Kari, have you had any experiences
while you've been here?
I've seen a woman about three times.
The first night I stayed here,
I woke up, and there was a woman.
To me, she just looked like a
black figure walking around.
So I fell back to sleep,
and I woke up to turn over on my bed,
and there was that same dark figure
actually sitting on the side of this bed
and looking into the mirror
and brushing her hair.
Were you boozing that night?
Were you drinking?
No.
Okay, so you said you saw her three times.
When was the third?
The third was actually last night
when I stayed in this room.
- Last night?
- Yeah.
I was looking up towards the wall,
and the next thing you know,
there's a skeleton face.
You're just frozen.
You don't know what to say,
or you can't scream.
You can't do anything.
Why do you come back?
It brings up curiosity.
You want to come here and see
if anything's gonna happen.
I doubt that anything is gonna happen to me.
They've been busted in
this room, the ladies...
Like, somebody waking up in here
and catching them doing [bleep] to the,
you know, person.
'Cause I keep seeing this
one thing over and over again.
Like, them surrounding the
bed with the people in it.
And they would definitely have that feeling
of, like, they couldn't move,
they couldn't talk,
they can't breathe.
So it sounds like you're experiencing a lot.
I mean, anything else happening?
Since I got in this house,
I just felt drained.
I got, like, physically ill.
Describe what you mean by ill.
Like, you felt like you were
just about ready to throw up.
When I got into his room, I just felt tired.
I felt like I had just been drugged.
You can hardly breathe
when you get into here.
And the women are definitely
feeding off of any living people around.
They move through, like, in a pack,
and then they just kind of feed.
They're definitely taking
energy away from living people.
How would that affect the living?
If the person woke up while
the ladies were doing it,
then they would feel like
they couldn't move and stuff.
But if they don't,
then they would feel really awful.
Would you say they're a threat?
Mm-hmm.
If you were exposed to this consistently,
you'd probably have a heart attack
or develop severe issues.
This is a small town.
It only has a couple
hundred people living in it,
so it didn't take me long to
track down a local historian.
She tells me that Jay and Barb's B&B
has a long and dramatic history.
So, you had mentioned that the
building I'm investigating,
that's now a B&B, had a dramatic history.
Yes, it has.
And my client thinks it
opened up as a hospital.
- Is that correct?
- Correct.
JB Stoddard, and there's a picture of him,
he and his wife, Esther,
bought the property in 1899,
and then they built a hospital,
and it opened in June of 1900.
And it operated as a hospital until 1917.
Now, do you know anything about this guy?
He was definitely a very smart businessman.
He was born in Utah,
and he and his family were
in the lumber industry there,
and he came here, started a mill.
Most of the buildings in Sumpter
were built with lumber from his mills.
Now, did he own the hospital
the entire time it was open?
No, he sold out in 1903.
He sold to a couple of the
doctors who worked there.
Okay. All right.
Now, what eventually happened to him?
He passed away in 1925.
There's a copy of his death certificate.
He died of dementia. He was 68.
This grumpy old man confuses me.
I think he owned this at one point.
Do you get an age for him?
He's... Gosh, like 70s.
Doesn't look like he died very well.
Skin and bone.
Definitely mentally unsound.
He's very frail.
Maybe he has Alzheimer's or something.
You blink, you go through this town.
Why would they build a hospital here?
At that time, this was quite a metropolis.
There were about 4,500 people here.
Really?
Here's a picture that
shows Sumpter at its peak.
It shows the wood streets,
the Capital Hotel.
Then going up the street, that's the school.
Okay, this white building here?
Right.
And then next to it is what
was the hospital at that time.
We had all kinds of miners
and then all the supporting industries
that go along with that.
Okay, now,
what kind of mines we talking about?
- Gold mines.
- Gold.
Yes, so there were cave-ins,
crushing injuries, and those kinds of things
where a hospital was definitely needed.
Now, did the townspeople use the hospital,
as well?
Yes, they did.
There were people that had
all kinds of injuries...
burns from house fires, horseback injuries,
flu epidemics, moms having babies.
So that hospital covered everything?
Absolutely.
Oh, God, the head pain is ridiculous.
Ridiculous, ridiculous.
Do you know what it's from?
Well, people being hit in the head.
I don't know what's happening.
There's been a lot of loss here, you know...
women having miscarriages.
Uh...
What?
There's a big old blood stain on the floor.
I can't make it go away.
How large is it?
It's pretty [bleep] Somebody bled out.
Quite a lot of people,
quite a lot of different deaths,
a lot of violent deaths.
Who the [bleep] knows what happened there,
but there is something there.
There's someone throwing up a lot, crying,
and they're dying 'cause they're sick.
Ow.
You said the hospital
closed down in 1917. Why?
There was a fire in August of 1917
that destroyed nearly all of
the business area in Sumpter.
Wow.
I'd say 99.9% of the businesses
and quite a few residences
were destroyed.
And then this shows the
destruction after the fire.
Wow.
Those were two of the
bigger buildings in town,
and it just totally destroyed them.
Did the B&B I'm investigating get hit?
No, it didn't.
It was right on the edge of the fire.
Now, do we know how it started?
It started at the Capital Hotel,
and the it spread quickly
'cause of the wood streets.
Oh, geez.
Did people die in this fire?
There is one article that speaks to the fact
that two miners were killed.
Okay, so the fire happens in 1917,
and it stops being a hospital,
so what happens after that?
It became the Masonic
Hall in 1918 until 1973.
After the fire, the town never recovered.
It's really strange because I...
I see it more crowded.
It looks different.
Like I'm actually seeing more of a town,
I guess.
Okay.
There's like a wooden, like,
sidewalk or something.
Like, they're just kind of showing me,
like, things were good,
and then, uh...
a few things happened to stop that.
What do you mean?
Something wiped everybody out.
So far, I've got a town
that was nearly wiped out by a fire
and a property that was once a hospital
where countless people died,
but I need to see if there's anything else.
Searching through the archives,
I discovered the hospital's first patient
is a miner named Fred Kane.
Turns out, he went crazy and
brutally murdered a 4-year-old
before turning the gun on himself.
Obviously, I want to know
more about this case,
so I've called a local police chief,
and he agreed to look into it for me.
Well, Chief Lohner, thanks for meeting me.
I appreciate that.
The Fred Kane murder case,
you were able to look into it for me.
What were you able to find out?
I found that Fred Kane,
he was a miner up in the Sumpter area.
He actually had went to that hospital
that you're investigating
back on June 12th of 1900.
He was actually the first
patient of the hospital
after being kicked by a horse
up at the Montezuma Mine.
So, this is before the murder.
It is.
A few months later, on September 19th,
up at the family cabin
where Fred Kane lived with his wife, Naomi,
and her 4-year-old daughter,
his stepdaughter,
a young gal by the name of Ruth Toney,
Fred... He took his Winchester
rifle and left the residence.
And when Fred came back into the cabin,
he fired a round from his Winchester,
and that actually shot through Ruth
and entered the body of Naomi at the time.
The child is dead instantly by
every report that we could find.
- Okay, what happens next?
- Fred picked up a club,
and he started beating Naomi with the club,
and then, all of a sudden,
he stopped beating her,
and he looked at her, and he said,
"You got blood on your dress."
So this guy's a whack job.
You know, see, there had been no
indication of any mental illness
with Fred Kane prior to this occurrence,
but he obviously was suffering
from some type of mental delusion
at the time if you believe Naomi's accounts.
Now, what does she do?
She told him that there
had been another assailant
in the residence that had shot her
and that's where the blood came from,
and she said he just ran out into the woods.
And so Fred took off out the door.
She then fled the cabin
as soon as he was gone,
and she went to a nearby
cabin where she was located
by two workers that had been in the area.
He came back to the residence,
saw Naomi was gone,
saw the child lifeless on the floor,
and he set the cabin on fire.
And in the meantime,
he takes off and runs
to his brother's cabin,
which is just a short distance away,
lights it on fire,
and the report indicates
that he shoots himself
with the same rifle that
killed his stepdaughter.
Geez.
He shoots himself in the chest,
but he actually survives.
He ultimately ended up at
Sumpter General Hospital
just two hours later
after Naomi had been admitted
to the same hospital.
Okay, so both of them wind up in
the location I'm investigating
but when it was a hospital?
Correct. Both with gunshot wounds.
Fred ultimately died of his
injuries on October 10th.
Okay, now, what happens to Naomi?
She ultimately was
released from the hospital,
and she ended up up in Portland,
where she actually died
exactly six years to the day
of the original shooting.
She died on September 19, 1906.
She was 35 years old at the time.
Kind of the irony on this, with the theory
that Fred was insane at
the time of the shooting,
was that she died by what
the medical examiners report,
the death certificate states
is a general collapse,
the contributing factor being insanity.
You're kidding me.
No.
Well, that's a twist.
There's a couple of the
women who are extremely depressed.
Like, if they were still alive,
they would be suicidal,
you know, that's how depressed they are.
One of them lost her whole family,
and she still feels that,
like, it happened that day.
She can't move beyond that loss.
I encountered several
dead people on my walk.
But the woman surrounding
a man asleep in his bed
had me the most concerned.
There's about five women who
are at the foot of the bed
staring at this man.
And at the center is a dominant female.
She has dark brown hair, dark brown eyes,
thin, arched eyebrows.
She has a high-collared,
black, very plain dress on.
Is this what you saw?
Yes, that's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our
findings to each other
and our clients for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to meet Barb and Jay.
They're a married couple,
and they live and run this place
as a B&B for the last 17 years.
They've always had activity,
but recently, it's gotten out of control.
They're looking to pass
this on to their son,
who has two beautiful children.
Oh.
The problem is, they're really not sure
if it's safe to keep this
business in the family.
Now that Amy knows a little
bit about what's going on here,
she's gonna tell us about her walk.
This was a really difficult walk for me,
feeling, you know, really physically ill.
Actually up there... top-10 worst.
Wow.
There's a lot of sickness here.
As soon as I got out of the car,
it was like chaos ensued,
and a lot of, you know,
dead people were freaking out.
A lot of them that I encountered
outside had died horribly.
Necks were broken,
heads were just bashed in.
And the head and the neck pain
that I felt out there from them
continued all throughout the walk.
And then I went upstairs
and saw a lot of sickness.
I saw a woman who had a miscarriage,
a huge bloodstain on the floor,
and then another woman
in one of the bedrooms
who seemed to be very ill.
Like, sweat and vomiting and all of that.
You know, that's an easyone to answer.
This building was built in 1900
but not as a bed-and-breakfast.
It was built as a hospital.
- What?
- Yeah.
Oh, my gosh. Oh.
The thing was,
it operated as a hospital from 1900 to 1917.
Back in that time,
there was 4,500 people living here.
Okay, okay.
This was a mining town.
When you talked about head injuries
and all this other stuff.
So these guys were killed by cave-ins,
explosions.
I got a stack of articles
talking about all these
injuries that happened here,
and they were all brought to this hospital.
Matter of fact,
this was the hospital for the whole town.
Oh, that makes sense.
A mining town would explain
probably the physical injuries.
And this being used as a
hospital explains the illness.
So, what else did you get?
There are about five or six women.
They kind of travel as a pack.
They're definitely from around 1890, 1905.
One of the women was all dressed in black
and seemed to be mourning.
She definitely seems to be
the leader of the group.
They all died at different
times from various illnesses.
Does that make sense
'cause it was a hospital here?
Well, now it does, yeah.
Let me ask you a question
about the women that are here.
Do you think they can be seen?
I definitely think that the
main lady presents herself.
Jay, tell her what you saw that day.
Well, I was in the kitchen,
and out of the corner of my eye,
glanced up here on that staircase,
and something came down,
and I could see its legs
from maybe the knees down.
What did the legs look like?
Shadows.
Mm-hmm, okay.
There were two women from this group
that were extremely depressed.
The living would probably
feel this depression
because it's so thick.
One of the women lost
her whole family at once,
and she can't get over it.
She seems hopeless and lost,
crying all the time,
suicidal, even though she's dead.
She lost her entire family in one day?
Yeah.
Now, there's one woman that comes to mind
that ended up here when it was a hospital
that had a very traumatic experience.
Her name was Naomi Kane,
and her husband, Fred Kane,
was actually the first
patient in this hospital
when he got kicked by a horse.
Now, on September 19th that same year,
Naomi was holding her 4-year-old daughter
from a previous marriage in her arms.
Fred came into the house with
a rifle and shot at them.
The bullet went through the baby,
killed her,
and then went into Naomi.
Somehow she escapes and gets
taken to the hospital here.
Fred, in the meantime,
lights the house that they lived
in on fire and shoots himself,
but he survived.
Somebody found him,
and they brought him to this hospital,
as well.
He wound up dying about three weeks later.
Six years to the day after the shooting,
she dies at the young age of 35.
The official cause of death
on her death certificate says
general collapse from insanity.
How do you die from insanity?
I think she committed suicide, to be honest.
That's what I'm thinking, too.
Seems to fit.
Do you have any sense that
she may be one of those women?
Yeah.
Then I met this interesting character.
He was in the back over here.
That's their bedroom.
He kind of was throwing attitude,
definitely grumpy,
kind of crotchety older man.
He was probably in his 70s.
He felt like this place belonged to him,
so I was thinking he either
owned it or he lived here.
He definitely didn't have a good death.
His face was not in good shape.
And then, he, like, runs up,
and he starts, like,
pinching me and poking me.
Barb, can you explain to Amy
what your son and your grandson
experienced in one of the rooms?
Yes. He was putting him down for a nap,
and so he was lying on the bed with him,
and the grandson pointed at a chair,
and there wasn't anybody in the chair,
but then he said, "That's the bad guy."
You mention you think he owned the place?
Yeah.
Well, the original owner is a guy,
James Stoddard,
that had businesses in town with the lumber.
He had this place for like three years,
and he sold it to some doctors.
He knew they needed a hospital here,
and he built it.
You said the guy was in his 70s.
This guy died at the age of 68.
You mention he had a horrible death.
This guy actually died from dementia.
So more than likely,
this is the guy, the same...
- Sounded like it.
- Sure seems like it.
Yeah.
- Mischievous, yeah.
- Mischievous old codger.
Yes.
Mm.
It doesn't surprise me that
this man is still here,
as the dead often come back to the place
which had the most meaning in their lives.
There's a lot of stuff going on
between him and the dead women.
He does not like them at all.
He said that this is his house
and that those [bleep] need to go.
There's been about five or six times
where him and the main
lady got into a fight,
and I saw, like,
physical things happening around them
because of this exchange.
Specifically, I saw,
like, electrical issues.
And this is only when they're fighting.
That explains a lot of things, right?
Yes, it does.
Upstairs, the TV going on and off by itself,
lights going on and off by themselves.
There's nobody to turn it on.
And does this happen often?
- Recently, yes.
- Last little while.
We really don't want anyone
to just get frightened to...
I mean, to have a health issue because of...
You got a legitimate issue here.
Initially, I didn't like the older man,
and then I went upstairs
and saw the women up there,
and it was a very different story.
Are they different women, or...?
No, it's the same women.
Up there, what they were doing
was taking the energy from the living.
Yeah.
And they just all stand around the bed
and literally are just, like,
almost breathing it in.
The main woman does know what she's doing.
And she's doing it to sustain herself.
I spoke to one of your guests
that was staying here that night I was here.
She said she just felt like the whole energy
just got sucked right out of her.
We've had guests on more than one occasion
that have sensed somebody
sitting on the edge of the bed,
crawling into bed with them.
That's exactly what's going on.
I did a sketch
of what people may encounter
when they're in the bed.
Yeah.
That's really frightening.
I mean, anybody that comes here... the kids,
the grandkids...
I don't want them to be
afraid to go upstairs.
I did do a sketch
of what people may encounter
when they're in the bed.
Yeah.
That's really frightening.
I mean, anybody that comes here... the kids,
the grandkids...
I don't want them to be
afraid to go upstairs.
I don't want to be afraid to go upstairs.
You know, it would be nice
if the family could continue
to come here and live here
and be happy and safe...
Mm-hmm.
...for them to love this
place as much as I do.
Your son Brian told me
a story about the bed.
Mm-hmm.
He was awake in bed,
and, all of a sudden,
the bed started to shake.
Okay.
When he described it to me, I mean...
It was shaking.
That could be her.
She's strong, and she can be
very physical and very forceful.
If somebody irks her,
she definitely will let them know.
But if you're exposed to that consistently
over a long period of time,
it can cause serious
illnesses and heart issues
and things like that.
Wow.
You know, you don't want to
pass something like this on
to your son and grandchildren.
No, I wouldn't do that until
this issue is resolved.
How do we stop her?
We want to put a stop to it.
Well, guys,
I know this has been a lot tonight,
but at least you know what's going on.
The big question is,
can you stay here safely
and pass it on to your
family like you want to?
For that answer,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
Okay.
So, first off, there needs to
be a pastor who's brought in,
and this individual needs to do a blessing
and needs to tell the women
and the other lost souls to go.
And this needs to be a
direct order from him.
It needs to be firm.
What this will do is,
all of the women will leave,
and the older man will leave.
The second thing is,
you need a person who is a Reiki
master and does home cleansings,
so that's a healer,
to come in and do a cleansing
of the whole location,
and that's gonna get rid of, like,
all of the residual illness and trauma
that's been kind of absorbed here.
And that'll get rid of all that stuff
that's here with the hospital?
Yeah.
You look like you feel like...
I am so relieved.
Are you gonna take Amy's advice?
Yes, yes. Absolutely.
It's got to make you feel good
you could keep this place in the family now.
Yes. Absolutely.
It's a happy cry.
It won't be easy
removing the layers of dead
inside this location.
But with the help of a
pastor and a Reiki master,
the dead will be set free.
And I believe Jay and Barb
can pass down their bed-and-breakfast
to future generations.