The guy in the black is bad.
He's always been bad.
I became obsessed with this place.
They think I'm insane.
He can induce fear.
Her attachment to the
place is a little spooky.
61-year-old male who hung himself
with a belt in the closet.
Oh, my God.
I never say I own the place.
I say the place owns me.
They're saying,
"Can't you get us out of here?"
I think that he harmed many women.
"You're mine. You can't escape."
My name is Amy Allan.
What's happening?
I see dead people.
It seems like a devil.
I speak to dead people.
He's pissed off.
And they speak to me.
I felt real fear.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I think she's being murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Serial killer pops in my head.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
Nobody believes me.
It's my job to reveal them.
- Do you think there's still bodies there?
- I do.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
You got problems. I got news for you.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
This is our house...
whether they like it or not.
Or time to get out.
This is their house, the house of the dead.
I'm in Santa Paula, California.
It's about an hour North of Los Angeles.
I got a call from a
19-year-old named Gabriella.
She tells me her parents, Rosanna and Tom,
live in and run a historic hotel.
Gabriella says the activity there is so bad
she won't step foot in the place.
She even sent me a video
that's got me really concerned.
It just only hurt our
family by owning this hotel.
It has this very negative, dark energy.
I really worry about their mental health.
It just really freaks me out.
I reached out to Tom and Rosanna,
who agree the hotel is
ripping their family apart.
They say if we can't help them,
they may lose everything.
Before Amy arrives,
I look for anything
that might influence her findings.
This hotel has a lot of
artwork and historic photos
that have to be covered or removed.
When I'm finished,
the location will be
ready for tonight's walk.
During my opening, I saw a cemetery.
There are adults crying... men and women.
There are about a dozen
little wooden crosses.
And I hear, "The children all died."
I feel really sick.
Like, I can't, like, breathe.
I think there's something in the air.
There's something in the air.
Oh, boy.
This is not good.
Rosanna, your daughter Gabriella
got in touch with me,
and she's really concerned
about what's happening here
and what happened to the family.
Gabriella has always voiced the fact
that ever since we bought the place,
she feels like she lost her parents.
Okay, so, do you think she's right?
Yeah, she's right.
Okay.
10 years ago, I came here
and I saw this building that was beautiful.
But it was in such disrepair,
I told my husband,
"Let's do something about this building.
This building needs help."
So, I convinced my family.
It was my idea, my project.
And my family really resents that.
I became obsessed.
Geez.
Now, who exactly lives here?
This is my daughter Aisha,
my husband, Tom, and there's myself.
Gabriella's in New York.
New York, yes.
And this is our home in Malibu.
We had the most beautiful, spacious home
on an acre overlooking the
most beautiful beaches.
- So, this is where you lived before?
- Yes.
And I understand you still own it,
but you rent it out.
- Yes, we do.
- And how long have you guys been here?
Six months.
So, if you wanted to go back there,
you can go back there.
I don't want to be rude,
but I think you're a little insane, myself.
I don't have the strength
and confidence to leave.
I think this place needs me.
At the same time,
it's destroying your family dynamics.
Yes. I'm very torn.
What's some of the overall things
that people are experiencing?
We get people that wake up
in the middle of the night
saying that they can't sleep here
because they feel that their bodies
are being pulled to the floor.
Contractors running downstairs and saying,
"We just saw these children
running down the hall
and then they went into a wall."
There are people who hear
their names being whispered,
like, "Steve."
Wow.
But also, people are jumpy... more anxiety.
And the intensity between my
husband and myself increased.
Everybody's, like, ready to snap.
How's your relationship
when you're not here?
Much happier.
So, why don't we just move out of the hotel?
I'm, you know, scared to leave it
because I don't know what would happen
if I ever thought of
selling it or leaving it.
How would it punish me?
There's something here that I don't like.
It's kind of making me anxious.
Like, that kind of
rock-in-your-stomach feeling.
Like, the fear is just disgusting.
Like I'm stressed out.
I feel very stressed out.
I feel like something bad's going to happen.
I've been resistant to coming up here.
I get a creepy feeling here.
I can't even send my employees
up here by themselves to clean.
I always have to assign two
or with the maintenance guy.
- I mean, they just won't do it by themselves.
- Okay.
Now, this doesn't look renovated.
Eight years ago.
This was the last floor
that we were finishing up.
And we put this place up on the market.
- Okay.
- We did that a lot.
We renovated buildings and
then put them on the market.
My husband and I went on a trip.
And when we were on this trip,
we got the call from hell
saying that, "Your building is on fire
and we don't know if we're
gonna be able to save it."
Oh.
Wow.
It was just growing all over.
It was right about this area.
Anybody get hurt?
Nobody got hurt, thank God.
Now,
what makes you think this is paranormal?
This is the irony of the whole thing.
The fire was exactly $1.3 million of damage
and we were insured $1.3 million.
Like, it's trying to say to you,
"Hey, don't go anywhere."
Now you know why I have PTSD
from thinking about
putting it on the market.
This place has abandonment issues.
It doesn't let me go.
Okay.
Someone's yelling.
Someone... some female's saying,
"Oh, can't you get us out of here?
Can't you get us out of here?"
People running.
There's people running.
There was something like a
fire or something because,
um... you know,
there was a bunch of people here
and then they're all trying
to get out as quickly as possible.
You describe how this place
emotionally changes you when you come in
and how, basically, you're obsessed with it.
But have you ever had an
actual paranormal experience?
Well, there was one time
when I was going to a room.
And I was gonna use the restroom.
And it was in an area that was isolated.
And as I closed the door,
I noticed that the doorknob had moved.
I thought for a second
maybe my husband was trying to scare me.
Then the doorknob fell to the floor.
And I thought, "Oh, my God."
I started hitting the
door and yelling for help.
I became like a crazy, psychotic woman.
And how long were you stuck?
About a half an hour.
They found me just devastated, just sobbing.
Okay. Now, it's an old building.
So you sure the doorknob just didn't,
like, fall out?
Well, I understand what you mean.
But I saw the doorknob move.
This place is telling me who's in control,
that there was an energy or presence there
that I had to respect,
and that they were in control.
And that's why I never say I own the place.
I say the place owns me.
And you really believe that.
Mm-hmm.
'Cause there is something here.
Okay.
I see this guy
walking down the hallway.
He wears all black.
Yeah, ooh.
Ooh [bleep] me.
Yeah, he doesn't like women, for sure.
Yeah, the guy in the black is bad.
He's always been bad.
He definitely is saying, you know,
that he's dealt with women like me before.
What does that mean?
He's like, "I've taken those [bleep] out."
Well, Tom, I was talking to your wife
and she explained what's going on here.
You went from oceanfront
Malibu beach house to this.
It's night and day.
I mean, it is culture shock moving here
and moving to this
environment and this dwelling.
She also mentioned she's become
obsessed with this place.
Would you agree with that?
Yeah, it's one of the few things
that she says that I'll
agree with completely.
I'm surprised she admitted that.
Her attachment to the
place is a little spooky.
Do you believe in this stuff at all?
The answer is, I didn't.
- Have you had any experience at all?
- I've had experiences.
What have you experienced?
- Well, there's two distinct episodes.
- Okay.
The first one is I was brushing my teeth
and behind me, right here,
I heard somebody make this really weird,
menacing sound.
- So, I just whip around. There's nobody there.
- Right.
I ran. I had the toothbrush in my hand.
I had toothpaste dripping down my mouth.
I ran into the bedroom where Rosanna was.
It takes a lot to freak me out like that.
Tom, you said you had two incidents.
What was the second one?
One of the doors to an
upstairs room was locked.
And this was a room
that was not supposed to
be occupied by any guest.
The door was locked from inside.
We're concerned.
We're thinking there's a guy in the room.
He's not supposed to be there.
He's a stranger.
What's going on there?
I removed the door.
And I look around.
Nobody's in the closet.
Nobody's in the bathroom.
And the windows were locked from the inside.
I'm freaking out.
I start looking in vents.
There's an air conditioning vent,
but it's like this.
Check under the bed?
Yeah, looking under the bed,
but there's not even spaces.
There's nothing over there.
Everything's locked from the inside.
And that, to me, was even more eerie
than the thing that happened to me directly.
And if somebody says,
"Do you believe in ghosts?"
all I can say is, "Hey,
these things happened to me
and I can't explain them."
Do you think it's dangerous?
I think it could be. I think it's potent.
The guy in the black,
he's very physical.
Always, like, messing with people,
like, touching, touching, touching.
It's very distracting, very annoying,
and I'm sure very
frightening for many people.
Hmm.
Yeah, I think this is him
because I feel that same...
weight, that same fear.
Now I know what made me so anxious
when I first walked into the hotel.
It's this man in black.
His presence terrifies the living
and he enjoys watching them suffer.
He definitely knows how to induce fear.
He's saying that he can really harm people.
Aisha, your mom feels
that you guys are really upset with her.
We are.
She's obsessed.
The dynamic of the family
was very much disrupted.
I almost felt like she loved this place
more than me at one point.
So, you're living here for how long?
On and off for like 10 years.
Why'd you bring me into
this particular room?
Well, out of all the rooms,
I would say this is
probably the most active.
Recently, the curtains just started moving.
There was no wind.
The window wasn't open.
You have A/C in the room?
We do, but it wasn't on at the time.
And it was like 2:00 a.m.,
no A/C, windows closed,
and I look over and the curtains
are just dancing back and forth.
Okay, was it a windy night,
anything like that?
- Maybe a draft underneath the windows?
- No, no, no.
Now, let me ask you a question.
Would you stay in this place alone?
No, I couldn't.
This room specifically, there's an entity
that I think doesn't like
it when there's people here.
It's kind of like invading its territory.
The one tall, dark guy, like,
he doesn't want us to be in here
'cause this is his pad.
He doesn't like it when people are in here.
What does he do?
He makes it, like, weird, like,
loud and disturbing and shocking.
He's crazy.
So, I'm thinking, like,
the TV comes on full blast
or, like, an alarm goes off.
"Just get them out."
He's constantly touching me,
so I don't like that.
He's showing me, like,
he actually can hit people.
I see, like, he's choking women.
You know,
like I'm seeing this woman laying in a bed
and he's pinning her down
and he's, like,
punching her across the face.
I didn't think I'd have much trouble
digging up history on
an old hotel like this,
so I reached out to a local historian.
And she gave me more than I bargained for.
She says Tom and Rosanna's property
was the scene of a brutal murder.
Mary Alice,
you mentioned on the phone when we spoke
that there was a violent incident
that took place before
the hotel was even built.
Yes.
There had been a shooting on Main Street
which had been initiated
by this outlaw Joe Dye
who challenged a man for
having an affair with his wife.
The man's name was Herman Haines.
Joe Dye actually shot Herman Haines
on Main Street in 1886.
Mary Alice, the hotel, I know where it's at.
I saw Main Street.
So how far do you think the shooting was...
It was about a half block away.
- That's it?
- Yeah.
Now, did Joe Dye go to jail for this?
He did.
In fact, I understand he turned himself in.
But he was acquitted on self-defense.
Wow.
So, what kind of guy was Joe Dye?
He was a known outlaw
from Arizona and Southern California.
He was known to be very mean
and very violent and a high temper.
Nobody messed around with Joe Dye.
This guy's got that crazed look on his face.
Everybody was scared to death of him.
He even had notches on his
gun as the number of victims.
- He had several victims?
- Yes.
16 years before he was in Los Angeles
that he killed his boss.
Geez.
He also shot a dog of
some adversary or client
that he didn't like just to
prove that he meant business.
The guy in the black is not good.
I think he's from way back,
like 18... something.
Definitely a transient...
traveled all the time.
I'm not sure why the man in black is here,
but I can see that he's a coward
who shows himself as a shadow man
so he can terrorize living
people inside this hotel.
I think he killed prostitutes, mainly.
He definitely strangled his victims.
Occasionally, he'd have to shoot them.
So, when exactly was the hotel built?
The hotel was built in 1911.
- Mary Alice, you mentioned there
was another incident? - Yes.
Quite a few years later in 1969,
this woman, Ferry Banister,
was the manager at the time.
Okay.
And she was awakened in
the middle of the night
by somebody yelling and pounding on a door.
And so she, of course, went upstairs
to see what was going on.
And she came across this
young man just having a fit,
yelling he couldn't find his key.
So, she went down and
picked up the extra key
and brought it back.
And he beat her up and stabbed her.
And here is the article.
- He fled.
- Okay.
And witnesses saw him drive away in a car
and he was later arrested.
And what was the reason
for this guy stabbing her?
I don't think they know.
She's taken to the hospital.
She survives.
Is she alive today?
She died in 2004,
so she died an elderly woman in her 90s.
Ow.
Like, there's people fighting.
Some... and there's some
kind of fighting happening.
I feel like somebody gets stabbed.
[Bleep] It hurts.
I feel like it's a knife.
I think it's a woman.
I feel like it caught her off-guard.
She's trying to get away.
You know,
I just see hands and feeling all this pain.
You all right?
Ow.
So far, I've got a family
that's been torn apart by obsession
and a property that's
been the site of violence.
But I need to see if there's anything else.
Digging through the archives,
I find that Santa Paula was devastated
by one of the worst disasters
in California's history.
But the headlines don't say how
it affected my client's hotel.
I'm heading over to meet with a local author
who says she's got information
that will definitely help my case.
Well, Peggy, thanks for meeting me.
I appreciate that.
I came across this article about
the St. Francis Dam disaster.
What can you tell me about it?
On the night of March 12, 1928,
it was just a few minutes before midnight,
the St. Francis Dam burst
and it released 12.4
billion gallons of water.
The flood wave was 140 feet high.
This is what the dam looked
like before it burst.
And this is what the dam
looked like after it burst.
Wow.
Five hours and 27 minutes
after the dam had broken,
the flood wave finally swept
out to sea 54 miles later.
It came right through here.
It came right through the
Santa Clara River Valley.
Look at it now,
and this is what it looked like afterwards.
By the time the flood
waters reached Santa Paula,
it was water and equipment
and trees and mud and bodies.
- Oh, geez.
- It was dreadful.
What kind of a body count we talking about?
The official body count was about 500.
Geez.
But a lot of people think that it would
have to be higher than that... 600, 700,
more.
Do we have any idea what the death toll was
for Santa Paula itself?
Well, approximately at least 200.
Where I'm investigating, Glen Tavern Inn,
was that affected by this?
The first floor received damage.
- It was on high enough ground.
- Okay.
So, the Glen Tavern Inn became a refuge
for families that lost their homes,
that were trying to locate the
bodies of their loved ones.
Now, do they know what
caused the thing to burst?
They used shoddy building materials.
It was probably greed on
the part of Los Angeles.
Okay.
The floor is wrong here.
There's like this sinking,
like it's going down,
like a hole or something is here.
There's a lot of commotion here.
The floor was wet.
Something about the carpet was wet.
The carpet was wet.
There's a lot of arguing over this.
You know, the guys are like,
"This is gonna mess everything up
if we don't fix this right now."
The other men are kind of like,
"Well, we don't really care."
It's all about money.
I've already got a lot of history
on Tom and Rosanna's property,
but it turns out there's one more thing.
A local sheriff tells me
he found a recent death
that didn't even make the papers
right on the hotel grounds.
Well, Sheriff Dean, thanks for meeting me.
I appreciate that.
You said you actually found
a death in the location?
Yeah,
we actually did some checking and found
that there was a suicide
back in 2007 that occurred.
This is a copy of the coroner's report
from the suicide.
He was found in the
apartments just to the rear
of the guest rooms at the Glen Tavern.
61-year-old male, Henry.
So it said he hung himself.
What are the circumstances? Do you know?
He had been living at the hotel
and his family hadn't heard
from him in a couple days,
so they actually called
the keepers and said,
"Hey, would you mind going
and taking a look and check?"
They used the pass key
to go in and found him.
He could have been there
for one or two days.
Do you know what the circumstances were?
Did he leave a note or anything?
Or was it just one of those...
Really wasn't much out of the ordinary.
They did notice several 20-ounce beer cans
that were in the trash.
It appears he tried to hang himself
with a belt in the closet.
It looks like he wasn't
successful the first time
and found another belt and, unfortunately,
was successful on the second attempt.
I just hear the word "mad man".
And I see, like, a guy in the corner,
like, hunched down and balled up.
And he's like...
He'll get up on the desk or the bed,
you know,
and he's like constantly writing, writing...
scratching and writing on the walls.
I think this guy was probably schizophrenic.
I think he killed himself.
I saw several dead people on my walk,
but the man in black
poses the greatest threat to the living.
I'm meeting with a sketch artist
to describe how he appeared in life.
He was on the thin side,
between 5'10 " and 6'1".
I would say that his features were sharp.
He had a longer nose than usual,
very dark eyes.
Is this who you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I
finished our investigations,
it's time to reveal our
findings to our clients
and each other for the first time.
Well, Amy, I'd like you
to meet Tom and Rosanna.
They're a married couple
that own this place and
they actually live here.
Now, you know how most of our
clients can't afford to move out?
They actually can.
I want to show you where they came from.
It's a Malibu beach house.
Problem is, Rosanna's gotten
obsessed with this place.
It's taken over and she refuses to leave.
The activity's bad here
and it's tearing their family apart.
Matter of fact, here's a photo of everybody.
They have two daughters... Aisha, Gabriella.
There's Tom and Rosanna.
Aisha actually lives here.
But Gabriella got so fed up
with this place, she left,
went as far away from here as she could.
So, Rosanna wants to know
if it's safe to stay here
while the rest of the family
wants you to talk her into leaving.
So, now that Amy knows
a little bit about what's going on,
I'm gonna ask her to tell us about her walk.
I was overwhelmed walking in.
I got initially
a lot of different types
of residual impressions.
The first one was when I
was on the second floor
and I kind of felt like
a fire had taken place.
I was seeing all the people running,
but I didn't feel like anybody died.
We had a fire in 2005,
and it was on the second and third floor.
It was a serious fire,
but nobody was injured.
Okay.
I actually have a photo of the actual fire
when it was happening.
Wow!
Now, this is the strange part.
They were insured for $1.3 million exactly,
right?
- Mm-hmm.
- It cost exactly $1.3 million to fix that.
Now, this is after renovating the place.
They were getting ready to
sell it and then this happened.
Okay. Wow.
The other thing that I got
was when I walked into the lobby.
I saw the floor sinking and,
like, the carpets were wet.
There was water,
and there were several men talking.
One man was saying that if all of this
wasn't cleaned up and fixed,
it would cause a mess.
Another man was saying
he didn't really care,
that he didn't want to waste the money.
It seemed to be a pretty
stressful situation.
Back in 1928, March 12th, to be exact,
St. Francis Dam gave way.
The Glen Tavern itself,
the only damage it received
was the first floor...
water damage.
Okay.
The rest of the town got hit really bad.
Now, the dam itself was
35 miles East of here.
But when the dam failed,
12.4 billion gallons of
water came rushing out.
The water got as high as 140 feet,
actually swept its way through this town.
They estimate 500 died,
at least 200 died that lived in Santa Paula.
Now, the other thing is everybody
that survived that flood
wound up in this hotel
at some point, you know, to seek refuge.
Makes sense now. Okay.
What else did you see?
When I was on the second floor,
there was a suicide
I got of a male who seemed
to be schizophrenic.
He was, like, crawling on the ceiling
and he was, like, writing on the walls.
And I got that he hung himself.
Back in 2007, you guys actually
owned the place at the time,
a guy by the name of Henry,
he hung himself in the closet using a belt.
He had, according to the
coroner's report I read,
alcohol abuse.
He'd been drinking heavily.
Why he killed himself, we don't know.
- We remember him very well.
- Yeah, we remember him.
And he was a very nice guy.
What floor did you say this happened?
It's an outside area.
There's like two rooms.
That's correct. That's where it happened.
It's the exact spot where he hung himself.
That's right above our room.
Oh, wow.
I'm surprised that you
found out about Henry.
It was not in the papers.
I get information most people can't.
Anything else?
In several places throughout the hotel,
I would suddenly feel this intense fear.
It would feel like a rock
just fell right into my stomach.
And then I would get really anxious.
I definitely thought that living people
would feel this sensation.
- She feels all those things.
- Mm-hmm.
I get that terrible pit in my stomach
and I don't know what it's coming from.
It's like this horrible thing,
like an impending doom.
Just...
Rosanna, do me favor.
Just explain to Amy about
the dynamics of the family,
how obsessed you really are with this place.
I feel at home. I love this place.
But my family, they don't like
the fact that I love it so much.
They're kind of jealous, I think.
That scares me.
It sounds like you want to stay here forever.
And that sounds strange.
It sounds obsessive.
Our kids had complained ever
since we bought the place
that it was causing us to
behave in unnatural ways,
that something seemed to happen to us here.
This is supposed to be temporary.
I like it here.
What can I say?
I love it. It feels like home.
I know. Sorry.
Tell them sorry.
Is there a reason she
may have a draw to this place?
Is she like a sensitive, maybe?
Actually, I think she might be
drawn here for a different reason.
Some people,
they'll just be attracted to locations
where they were in previous lives.
They feel this strong pull and
it feels like they're home.
- And they don't know why.
But I've always felt that way.
Why would you come back? Seriously?
Because I like it.
And that's kind of an example
of how those situations can
become kind of unhealthy.
And it's become our life.
It's become kind of all-consuming
for our whole family.
The feelings that you've
had of anger and anxiety
are mostly caused by one entity.
And I met him on the third floor.
Hmm.
One of the rooms up there
is very much his area.
The room was 308.
He'll do whatever it
takes to keep people out.
He very much dislikes women.
You know, like I'm seeing
this woman laying in a bed
and he's pinning her down and he's, like,
punching her across the face.
He's not a good person at all.
Now, 308's your most active...
It's one of the most active, yes.
That's where you get most
of your customer complaints.
About two weeks ago, a man came downstairs,
just threw the key on
the front desk and said,
"You guys didn't tell me this was haunted."
He stormed out of here. He was so mad.
She got locked in a
bathroom down here one time.
Explain that to Amy what happened.
I was in a bathroom inside of
a room that has no windows.
As I close the door,
I saw the doorknob move.
And then the doorknob fell to the floor.
Oh, wow.
And I started hitting the door
and screaming louder and louder.
And before you knew it,
I was in complete hysteria.
And then finally,
housekeeper happened to go in that area
and heard me screaming.
It was the scariest time of my life.
Now, is this something that this guy can do?
It's something that he
could and would probably do.
What I was able to get out of him
was that he was a transient.
This was back in the late 1800s.
And he is just a very,
very, very nasty person.
I do believe that this
male was a serial killer.
He killed women, mostly,
and they were prostitutes.
His preferred method was to strangle them,
but occasionally he did
have to shoot people.
Now, I don't know about
anybody killing prostitutes,
but there's one guy that I
came across during research
that might have fit the bill,
especially the time frame...
the traveling, killing people.
It's a guy, Joe Dye.
Not a good guy.
He killed a boss of his in Los Angeles.
He actually killed another rival's dog
to let him know he meant business.
- He shot and killed a dog.
- Oh.
Apparently, he had notches on his gun
for the amount of people he killed.
- Well, you mentioned he hated women, too.
- Mm-hmm.
Back in 1886, he was married
to a very beautiful girl
here in Santa Paula on a ranch
and he used to go away a lot for work.
When he came back on one trip,
he had heard that this one guy,
Herman Haines,
might be taking up with his wife.
Joe Dye, about a half a block from here,
put a bullet in his back
and the guy lived for
three days and then died.
I got a photo of him.
- He's a crazy-looking guy.
- Ew!
- Those eyes.
- Wow.
Now, do you think this is
the guy you might have seen?
I don't know.
You can look at the sketch and tell me.
Take a look. I mean...
Hmm.
They don't look like the same person.
I don't know about that.
If you put a beard on him...
Oh, yeah. Maybe.
Well, whoever this guy was,
what does he want with these guys?
What he wants is to continue
being the way he was in life.
So, he wants to kill women, really.
What do you think about all this?
I do know that there is something here,
but I also feel that there's
a lot of protection...
a lot of good.
And if there is bad entities,
I'm sure that the good
ones will knock them out.
You think as long as you
respect the building,
it's gonna treat you well and protect you?
Oh, no, no.
Mnh-mnh.
You think as long as you
respect the building,
that it's gonna treat
you well and protect you?
Oh, no, no.
Mnh-mnh.
I do have more compassion
for what my daughters are saying.
I think Gabriella would be very
happy to hear you say that.
I think you're right.
I know that you're right.
Well, you know what?
We know what's going on in the hotel.
But the big question remains,
is it healthy or safe for you to stay here?
Or do you need to leave?
For that, I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
I do think that you had a past life here.
You have a connection here
and, unfortunately, in this situation,
you have deceased individuals here
who have a connection with you, as well.
And they're going to try to keep you here
and manipulate you and blind you
and bring that other person that they knew
more and more to life in the present day.
But that was then and
that was another lifetime.
And this is now and this is your life now.
And you need to move forward, not backwards.
So, what I would like you to
do is bring in five mediums.
And there are three types of mediums.
And I would like one of
each of them to be present.
So, there's a mental medium,
a physical medium, and a psychic medium.
The other two can be of any discipline.
So, they would do two things...
clear the residual energy
from this place and also move on
as many of the deceased people as they can.
Following that, you should really consider
selling this place and walking away.
The dead are going to be whispering,
"Don't leave, don't leave, don't leave,"
and try to change your mind.
Will they let me go?
It's about you letting them go
and letting this building go.
Keep that in your head as a mantra,
you know,
"I'm leaving, I'm leaving, I'm leaving.
"You're not gonna ruin my marriage,
"not gonna ruin my
relationships with my family.
This is my fricking life now."
I can see the possibilities
and I could see where I possibly can go.
But I'm torn because it's
like there's two people
and I feel that other
force coming within me,
like, saying, "No," you know?
That my identity is here.
I do believe that I can do it,
but it's gonna take a process.
There's too much wiggle
room in that approach.
You just have to make a decision.
Let's say she moves everybody out
and she doesn't leave here.
Is her past life gonna consume her?
Yes.
I can see that happening, yeah.
I'm making myself and my family stuck,
you know?
Because it is so beautiful and it...
Let someone else take care of it.
You've done your time.
I really hope Rosanna follows my advice
and leaves her past life
in the hotel behind.
I believe if she does that
and embraces the present,
she and her family will be free
of the obsession tearing them apart.