"This is the room, the room of death."
I can't have that in my home.
I can't have that going on.
It scared me to death.
It's coming after this kid.
I love my family. I will fight for it.
This is dark and bloody ground here.
It could hurt her.
I'm worried for the safety of his kid.
He says, "They broke my bones."
This is a mess. This is so messed up.
"You're mine. You can't escape."
My name is Amy Allan.
What's happening?
I see dead people.
It seems like a devil.
I speak to dead people.
He's pissed off.
And they speak to me.
I felt real fear.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I think she's being murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Serial killer pops in my head.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
Nobody believes me.
It's my job to reveal them.
- Do you think there's still bodies there?
- I do.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
You got problems. I got news for you.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
This is our house...
whether they like it or not.
Or time to get out.
This is their house, the house of the dead.
I'm in Fort Barnwell, North Carolina.
It's a very small town about
two hours outside of Raleigh.
Amy and I were called in
by a woman named Laura.
She says things are so bad in the house,
she's ready to pack her bags,
grab her 2-year-old, and leave.
The problem is, her husband
wants to stay and fight.
She told me she's running out of options
and we're her last hope.
Before Amy arrives,
I look for any leading information.
This house has a lot of
artwork and family photos
that need to be covered or removed.
When I'm done,
the location will be
ready for tonight's walk.
Oh, boy.
There's a big problem in one of rooms here.
There's a lot of dead people there.
And they can't see each other,
but they can see the living.
So, whenever they see living people,
they all jump on them.
They want out of there.
It's like a way station
for the dead or something.
Whatever it is, it's a problem.
Well, Laura, you sounded like
you were ready to pack up
and leave when we spoke.
So, what's going on?
Pretty much as soon as we moved in,
we noticed small things started happening.
And it's gotten to the point
where it started to get
a little bit more aggressive.
And as a parent to a 2-year-old,
I can't have that in my home.
I can't have that going on.
Why don't you just move?
I don't want to be here.
But my husband's
grandfather built this home,
so he will not leave.
- He's refusing.
- Refusing.
I want to protect my daughter,
but I love my husband as well,
and I don't... You know?
- I can't just leave.
- Okay.
So, what are some of the
things that are happening?
Electronics do crazy things.
Things have moved on
their own across the room.
People physically touched.
People feel like they're
being watched sometimes,
and there's things my 2-year-old has said
that has been very shocking.
She's been in her room and
been talking to someone,
and my husband's gone in there and just,
"Who are you talking to?" "The man."
- Really?
- Yeah.
How'd you feel when she said that?
I was petrified.
For her to just come up
with that out of nowhere
was very strange to us.
It seems to be drawn to her.
What the hell?
They're thinking that they're seeing,
like, a shadow person.
Who's "they"?
The living people here.
And there's a kid, definitely a kid.
And it's very aware of the kid.
And it's, like,
the way it's moving is very... like this...
To, like, grab the kid.
And, uh, there's, like,
stuff coming off of it.
Like, it has all this stuff
dripping off of its body.
What do you mean?
It almost looks like, like, um, tar, or...
you know, some kind of liquid.
What the [bleep]
It's coming after this kid.
This is where I kind of had
my final breaking point,
and why I wanted to call you guys in.
Okay.
I was actually sitting in the living room,
and I heard a very... very odd noise.
And when I walked around the corner,
I came through here,
and this playroom door had opened.
And it was shoving all
of this out of the way
so that this door was completely opened
against this wall.
Okay. So, you hear...
Mm-hmm.
I mean, I can't even really
do it without pushing it.
Yeah.
So, you got dogs?
Yes. They were going bananas.
But were they the ones that
caused the door to open?
No, they were all sitting on my lap.
We were just watching TV.
And you're sure nobody broke
into the house and then split?
I got a gun out and did a whole
walk-through of the house.
Now, do you get anything else in this room?
Sometimes people have felt watched
in this area of the house.
What areas are we talking about?
Well, that bathroom.
I won't go in.
Geez.
I just don't like it at all.
- So, it's uncomfortable.
- It's very uncomfortable.
Creepy, yeah.
All right.
There's also a male here.
He likes the bathroom.
It makes him very happy.
It doesn't make any of
the living people happy,
but he likes it in here.
Why?
I think most of them feel, like, a presence.
Everything they do, they're being watched,
and it makes them feel uncomfortable,
like somebody's...
somebody's standing behind them.
For some reason, the dead men I'm seeing
are projecting themselves
as shadow people...
but they're not.
They're just conscious entities.
There's a female who
definitely sees this guy.
She has dark hair. It's fairly long.
Like, say she's washing her hands,
he'll, like, suddenly be behind her.
It just is constant,
and she hates it.
So, what's going on in here?
There's one time where I was here by myself,
sleeping right here.
And I just kind of felt and heard, you know,
someone kind of smoothing out the comforter
and, you know, tugging on the edge.
Really?
Did you see the blanket being tugged?
No, but I definitely have heard it,
and I felt it.
I probably would've been swinging at the air
if I would've heard something like that.
No, I think, um, at this point,
there was so many little
things that had been going on,
where we had just started
to almost, in a sense, ignore it.
- So, you got numb to everything
that's been happening. - Mm-hmm.
After we had our daughter,
we kind of couldn't turn a
blind eye to things anymore.
Well, picking on an adult is one thing.
Mm-hmm.
Picking on a baby is another story.
And even with all this,
moving's not an option for your husband?
He just feels, you know,
"This is my home, and I'm staying."
Ah
What?
This room is the way station for the dead,
and all of the activity
is tormenting a woman who lives here.
If the dead are around,
this woman gets horrible pain in her head.
It's because of her ability.
I think she can hear people
talking to her,
whispering to her.
They're coming out of the bed.
Touching, touching, touching.
It's, like, messing with her mind.
You know, "Hey!"
You know, "Hey, I'm here."
If she's around this room
all the [bleep] time,
it could hurt her in the long run, you know?
How?
Feeling, like, defeated. Defeated.
There's no hope. There's no hope.
So, Chris,
I was talking to your wife,
and she says there's no way you're leaving.
Correct.
I love my family, but this is our place.
I will fight for it.
She told me that you may not be so serious
about what's going on here.
I mean, is she accurate about that?
In a way, yes, and in a way, no.
I do write things off.
Okay, what are we talking about?
Me and my wife were in our bedroom,
asleep, and it was after
4:00 in the morning.
TV just came on.
I mean, it had to scare the hell out of you.
Absolutely.
Okay.
- And there was nobody here?
- No, no one here.
Anything else?
I've been touched, physically.
I stood up out of the recliner one night,
and just plain as day,
felt someone touch my shoulder
and felt like they shook it a little bit.
It wasn't a muscle spasm,
it wasn't drinking or anything like that.
It happened.
- You got a 2-year-old here.
- Yes.
A baby girl.
Yes.
And can you imagine her being
touched like you were touched?
No.
I take it seriously,
because I take my daughter's
welfare seriously.
If it wasn't for her,
we wouldn't be talking.
Okay. Uh, well, that being said,
what do you know about any
history on the property?
My grandfather built this house in '74.
His great-grandfather
purchased this property.
Wow. Okay.
- So, your family's been here a long time.
- A long time.
And there was a very major
Indian war fought here.
These supposedly have been repurposed
from Fort Barnwell from
the Tuscarora Indian War.
Wow.
This is my family's legacy.
I'm gonna fight for my house.
I'm gonna fight for our legacy.
There's this old person.
It's a man.
This person, I believe, is a former owner.
He seems to know his way around here.
He's still very sick from
whatever he died from,
which was a long-term illness.
Like, he possibly has a little dementia.
And...
there's some kind of
race thing going on here.
He's desperate to stop it,
but he's not okay to do that.
He can't stop time enough
to stop the things he did.
So, Amy, I was talking to Laura
about the stuff going on here.
She says you guys have been
friends since high school.
Right. We've been friends
for a really long time.
So, I assume you spent
time here in the house.
Well, I used to.
Last time we were here,
terrifying things happened,
and we haven't been back since then.
Okay. Tell me the first thing.
I woke up in the middle of the night,
and those curtains over there were moving.
It was like someone was standing behind it.
What about the windows? Were they open?
No, they were closed.
Did you have the fan or anything else on?
No, there's nothing that could explain it.
So, what else has happened?
Early that morning,
my husband was going hunting,
and I thought that he was
sitting on the corner of the bed
putting his boots on.
And this edge dipped down,
and I looked over and
there was no one in here.
Now, when you felt this thing on the bed,
I mean,
how much pressure are we talking about?
I mean, it was like a grown
man was sitting on it.
I don't know that I'll
ever feel safe coming back
- with a child.
- Really?
Do you think Chris is taking it too lightly?
I do. I'm worried for the safety of his kid.
So am I. That's why I'm here.
I think he should take it more seriously,
before other things start happening.
Uh, there's been bad incidents in here.
Something lives in the closet.
I don't know what this is.
I don't know why it's here.
I just see something
coming out of the closet,
and, uh...
laying on someone
so the person can't move or anything.
Someone says, "Well, this is the room,
the room of death."
Chris told me he thought his house
was built on the site of some Indian wars.
I'm on my way to meet
with a local author who says it's true,
and those battles were some of the bloodiest
in North Carolina history.
So, Doc, what you said on the phone,
my client was right.
There were Native American
wars on the property.
All around it...
very serious wars back in the early 1700s.
Okay. So, what exactly happened?
What started the whole damn thing?
Settlers came in and took land.
That meant less land for Indians.
They're being abused by the settlers.
Indian women would be raped,
and men murdered.
There's also a vibrant
Indian slave trade by 1711.
They'd just grown fed up
with what was happening.
And for a three-day rampage,
they were attacking all these plantations,
these farms, killing men,
women and children,
also killing black slaves, too.
Okay. And this is all around
the property I'm investigating?
Yes.
So, how many did they wind up killing?
Well, about 140 people are
killed in the three days.
They are taken totally by surprise.
In fact, one settler who survived said,
"It's people that we knew.
We see smiling faces,
and then they attacked us."
How brutal was it?
A lot of them are hatcheted,
knifed, and often, their bodies
were put in, like,
positions of prayer in some cases.
We also have stories of pregnant women
having the babies ripped out.
Some of them are impaled.
I mean, this is pretty brutal right there.
What the [bleep]
There's, like,
people all lined up against the wall.
They're all fresh, like, fresh corpses.
They're all white. Quite a few women.
All I can get is, like, they're running.
I don't see what the [bleep]
they're running from.
I feel like it's unexpected.
I think it was a normal
day to start out with,
and then this sudden panic,
and then running,
running for your life.
And then they're here like this.
These are all people
this happened to that day
and probably didn't have a good burial.
I'm curious about the white settlers.
What happened with their bodies?
They complained about,
"We can't bury our dead
"until the wolves are eating our dead
and the vultures are eating our dead."
People were too afraid to
leave those fortified houses,
and the Indians kind of
go back to their villages
to wait and see what's gonna happen.
They're expecting a response.
So, North Carolina calls
on South Carolina for help.
They send Colonel John Barnwell.
He goes to this place called Core Town,
and he turns it into Fort Barnwell.
My client believes the
bricks from his fireplace
came from Fort Barnwell.
Well, it's possible.
So, what happens next?
John Barnwell,
he's willing to sign a peace treaty.
And so the Indians said,
"Great, we'll sign one."
Over 400 Indians show up,
men, women, and children.
They're expecting to sign a treaty.
And then, at a surprise moment,
Barnwell and these militia attack.
About 50 Indians are just killed right off,
and most women and
children are then enslaved.
This is dark and bloody ground here.
I don't know why
they're all stuck in
the wall here like this.
How many?
About 18.
They can't move. They can't speak.
It feels like something bad happened,
whatever.
They all die right...
They're all together like this,
and why they're kind of, like, bound...
Like, this would be a binding on the dead...
is very [bleep] weird.
Someone put some sort of
spell on these dead people.
They can think and see,
but they are all stuck together,
unable to move or communicate.
I want to say that they were
put together even after death.
This is, uh...
terrible.
With hundreds killed
during Native American wars in the 1700s,
my client's land has seen
more than its fair share
of death and violence.
But something tells me the
tragedy didn't end there.
Digging through the archives,
I find a local farmhand
burned to death in the 1940s.
Turns out he worked
for my client's great-great-grandfather.
Fires are always suspicious,
and I want to know more
about the worker that died
on Chris and Laura's property.
I'm heading over to meet
with a history professor
who's looking into it for me.
I found out during my research
that my client's great-great-grandfather
had a farmhand who burned to
death right on the property.
What do you know about
this guy and what happened?
William Loften was a farmhand
who lived on Hugh Lane's Farm in the 1940s.
He was a World War II veteran.
Okay.
And when he returned from the war,
he went back to work on the farm.
So, what happened?
March 14, 1949...
Sometime in the night, he was asleep.
The house caught on fire.
His wife came home to
see the house collapsing.
Geez.
I have a death certificate,
and it says that he died from extreme burns.
Okay. Do they know what might
have caused the fire then?
What the newspaper, the Sun Journal, says
is that the fire was started
by a stove that overheated.
Now, Kate, according to the
article I came across,
it said five black farmhands
were killed within a week from burning.
It sounds suspicious to me,
'cause when you read the article,
right away I'm thinking there's
racial undertones to it.
Was the Klan active back in
'49 in the Fort Barnwell area?
Well, there were pockets of Klan activity,
but there wasn't anything
that indicates that it was suspicious.
So, Kate, looking at this case,
as far as the victim goes,
it's a fire that can be
easily made to look accidental
and be a crime, or just accidental.
I mean, I don't think we'll ever know.
It's something to think about.
Those corpses are
still kind of in the wall.
Yeah, they're bound. They're bound.
I don't think that any of these people
deserve to be like this.
But that shadow,
it thinks that they do
deserve to be like this.
But this is the same person
that the kid was seeing?
Yes. He's saying, "Oh, you know,
'cause they're white people,
then that's why you're siding with them."
He's crawling.
So, he can't stand up
because it hurts too much.
He says, "They broke my bones."
Do you know when he's from?
It feels more recent to me.
It doesn't look like he died very well.
It was at night, but also warm.
This is uncomfortable.
This is a mess. This is so messed up.
So, we've got brutal Indian wars
and a worker who burned to
death on my client's property.
But one other thing caught my attention
while I was doing my research...
a murder-suicide that involved one of Chris'
ancestors.
I'm heading over to meet a historian
who says it's a case of obsessive love.
I came across this article
during my research,
and it looks like a
distant cousin of my client
was involved in a murder-suicide.
This guy Lonnie Lane.
Now, do you know anything about this guy?
He was a young man. He was born in 1879.
When he was 20 years old,
he apparently began a
relationship of some sort
with a young girl named Glennie Sauls.
This was in the spring of 1899.
But she was only 14 years old.
Her parents objected to the relationship
because of the age difference,
so they basically forbid him to see her.
In March... March 24, 1899,
he apparently went to her house
while her parents were out of town.
And they were seen leaving the house
and going on a walk toward the woods.
Okay. So, what happens next?
They're not seen for the
rest of the afternoon.
And when nightfall comes,
people become concerned
and they begin to search for them,
and their bodies are found in the woods,
both shot in the head.
So, here's one of the articles that appeared,
and it gives
the details of their relationship
and what may have happened that afternoon.
There's been some speculation
that he wanted to propose marriage to her
and that she may have rejected him
and then he just couldn't
deal with that rejection.
And the speculation was that
he had shot her and then
turned the gun on himself.
This guy who's always in the bathroom,
I think somehow he's
related to the living here.
He had said that he died outside.
He has something that's,
like, hanging off of him.
Like, if it's moss.
I don't think it was a good death.
During my walk, I saw a group of dead people
trying to get the attention of the living
in the master bedroom.
I'm meeting with an artist to
describe this horrifying scene.
There's two people sleeping in the bed.
There's a bunch of dead people,
like, holding their legs...
Four on one side and
like three on the other.
Is this what you saw?
Yes. That's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
finished our investigations,
it's time to reveal our findings
to our clients and each other
for the first time.
Well, Amy, I'd like you
to meet Chris and Laura.
The activity here is pretty bad,
up to the point where
Laura's ready to pack up her bags and leave.
Now, this property has been in Chris' family
- for generations.
- Okay.
So, he does not want to leave,
no matter what.
But one thing they both agree on,
they're worried about
their 2-year-old daughter,
and that's why we're here.
Now that Amy knows a little
bit about what's going on here,
I'm gonna have her tell us about her walk.
There were a couple of individuals
who initially showed
themselves like shadow figures,
but they're not.
One of them loves the
bathroom because it's quiet.
It's like his sanctuary.
And there was a living woman
that I saw that he keyed in on,
and she had dark hair.
And he's standing right behind her.
And one of the things in the bathroom
was this sense of always being watched.
When we first moved in, I hated the bathroom
I hated it.
Like, the first two years we lived here,
I wouldn't go in there.
Interesting.
And, uh, my daughter,
she'll stay in that bathroom.
She's mentioned talking to a man before.
She has mentioned
talking to a man before.
Wow.
Okay.
Now, do you know
anything about this guy,
who he was in life?
Well, he was about 6 feet tall, thin.
He indicated that he died outside.
He had something kind of hanging off him,
like a moss or a mold or something.
I got that this was not a good death.
I kind of think that he was murdered.
It does bring to mind one story
that took place right near here,
and it involves a distant relative of yours.
His name was Lonnie Lane.
He was 20 years old.
He got involved with a 14-year-old girl,
this girl Glennie Sauls.
Now, her parents were not happy
about them being together.
They didn't like the idea
of the age difference,
but one day in March of 1899,
the parents were away.
Lonnie came to Glennie's house.
They both left and walked into the woods,
never came out.
They were both found later,
one shot to the head each.
Here's the article from it.
So, when she said the moss,
the only thing I'm thinking
was they were in the woods.
They did die outside.
I've heard of
Lonnie Lane in our family.
- Really?
- Yes.
I didn't know about this.
That's one of the people
that's presenting themselves
- kind of like a shadow person, but it's not.
- No.
Okay. So, who's the second guy?
I walked in, went into this
area by that door in the hall,
and he was, like, covered
in, like, a black ooze, oil, tar substance.
And he was actually
interacting with a child.
And the kid was freaked out.
And it's, like,
the way it's moving is very... like this...
To, like, grab the kid.
It's coming after this kid.
I did get that he was black,
and he hates white people.
I also got that he died outside,
and it was nighttime.
And one word that I was hearing was "warm."
"Warm"
All right, well,
there was an incident where a guy got killed
on this property back in 1949.
He was a black guy. He was 35 years old.
His name was William Loften.
Now, Loften was a tenant farmer
for your great-great-grandfather Hugh.
Now, you had mentioned
that he died at night.
- You heard "warm?"
- Yep.
On March 14, 1949,
his house caught fire,
and he was burned to death inside the house.
This is the guy's death certificate.
Now, the official cause listed is burns.
Police say it was a stove
that caused the fire,
but what I found odd,
there was article that says
"Fifth Negro Burns at Farm."
The historian said there was
Klan activity here at the time.
There was.
But a fire like that's easily
done to make it look accidental.
Mm-hmm.
When I walked in the living room area,
I look at the wall,
and there was about 15 to
18 corpses standing upright.
All of these people were together,
and for some reason, somebody bound them.
What does that mean?
Someone at some point put a spell on them.
So, they can see everything that's going on,
but they can't speak and they can't move.
Who would've been in the
house that would've bound...
Well, that's the thing.
The other part of what I got was that
most of these people were female.
They were all white.
All of them seemed to have
died at the same time.
I saw it was, like, a nice day.
All of a sudden, everybody's running.
I know that they were
running for their lives.
Something was done with their bodies.
Like, I don't know if it was a mass grave,
desecration.
That sounds spot-on
for something that happened
here 300 years ago.
In 1711, the Tuscarora Indians went,
basically, nuts
and started attacking everybody and killing
'em,
'cause the white settlers that were here
were stealing from them.
They were raping their women.
So, they decided to attack
them in a three-day rampage.
They killed 140 men, women, and children.
They mutilated the bodies.
They ripped babies from
pregnant women's stomachs.
Oh, my goodness.
So, now, they were so scared
they couldn't even go and
get their bodies to bury 'em.
So, after this attack happened,
North Carolina decided to
reach out to South Carolina
for help.
They sent a guy named Colonel John Barnwell.
So, what Barnwell wound up
doing is setting up a fort,
Fort Barnwell, right near here.
So, what he did was try
to sign a peace treaty
and said, "All right, come to the fort
and we'll sign this treaty,
and everything will be nice."
So, 400 Native Americans came,
thinking it was gonna be a celebration.
So, they came with kids, women.
Barnwell attacked.
They weren't expecting it.
50 of them died right away,
and the rest,
they basically took into slavery
and sent them down to South Carolina
to be put in the slave trade.
Matter of fact, see this fireplace here?
That was built from bricks
that was from the fort that Barnwell built.
Oh, gosh.
My grandfather built this house.
- Your grandfather built this house?
- In '74.
Wow. Okay.
Well, I wasn't sure if he lived here or not,
but I saw this elderly
man in the living room.
He was very attached to this location,
and I got that he died
from a long-term illness.
The other thing was there were things
that happened that he felt responsible for,
that had possibly led to some deaths,
and it involved racial issues.
And he was like, "It's all my fault."
So, I don't know if the illness affected him
or if he also had, like,
a little bit of dementia
or something like that,
because he's very lost, very confused.
You're talking of my grandfather.
He had Parkinson's,
and he had a lot of dementia.
Okay.
This was his dream home.
Take that.
This was his pride and joy.
Sorry.
But why would he blame himself
for the racial tension, though?
Yeah, I'd really rather not talk about it.
Some of these people
that would be brought into this
are still living,
and I don't want to hurt feelings.
No, no, no. It's totally understandable.
But you are talking about my grandfather.
This is crazy.
Anything else?
I went into the master bedroom,
and I saw a living woman there...
thin, dark hair.
And she looked defeated.
She was sitting on the side of the bed,
like [bleep]
I got that she's having a lot of pain,
really bad headaches.
In that area, a whole bunch
of dead people came out.
They can't really see anything,
but they can see living people.
And I saw two people in the bed
and the dead people surrounding
them and touching them.
They were trying to, you know,
get people's attention.
You were telling me about it
happening in the master bedroom.
Mm-hmm. I remember laying in bed,
and it was just, like, fluttering
over the end of the bed,
like, maybe smoothing it out,
pulling the corners down.
Okay.
But you've been grabbed.
Definitely.
It was just, like, you know?
Like, "Hey, I'm here."
Wow.
Well, I did do a sketch of what I saw.
That looks like you in the bed.
I don't like it.
You okay?
I did do a sketch of what I saw.
That looks like you in the bed.
I don't like it.
You okay?
I have countless times sat on that bed
and cried on that bed
and just been like. "[bleep]"
Like, "Why did I move out here?
But what do they want? What do they want?
They don't want to be here anymore,
because they're stuck.
And the female in particular has abilities.
And so the dead are very attracted to that.
And they want help,
and they don't want to be here anymore.
I mean, did you have any idea?
I knew it was me.
Deep... I knew...
in the back of my head, it was me.
I knew it.
I didn't want to say it ever, out loud,
but I knew it.
So, now, what's got me
concerned is the baby.
The baby sees stuff and talks to stuff.
I'm 100% positive of that.
I'm 100% positive of that,
and that's the only
reason why y'all are here.
Well, when we spoke,
you said you'd do anything,
short of selling this house,
- to protect your family.
- Correct.
Okay. So, now we're gonna
find out what it's gonna take.
So, I'm gonna turn it over to Amy
and see what she's got for us.
So, there's a few steps,
and it'll take a little while.
What needs to be done first
is a male who's black who's also a medium
needs to come in and make contact
with the male that's in
the living room area.
He needs to talk to him and listen to him
and work with him to move him on.
Then, the second day, he needs to come back
and deal with the master-bedroom situation,
which he needs to seal.
When he's doing the sealing,
the last thing I do want him to do
is to use tar water at the end.
This is something
that completely negates
the space for the dead.
So, there will never be another dead person
that comes in that room, ever.
After that,
a shaman needs to be
contacted from the tribe.
Tuscarora tribe.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
So, they need to come and do a release
for the people that are trapped in the wall
'cause they are the only ones
who can undo what they did.
Once that's done,
the elderly gentleman, your grandfather,
will leave of his own accord
'cause he'll feel good.
So, now, what about her
abilities and the baby?
Her bedroom is going to be
completely sealed forever
from any dead coming in.
What happens if one day your
daughter comes to you and says,
you know, "All this stuff is happening."
Would you want her to close up?
Yeah.
You guys won't know until
she's a little bit older
if she's going to be open
or if she's going to close down or repress.
So, it's kind of a waiting game right now
to see which way she's gonna go.
So, I want to ask you straight out,
are you guys gonna take Amy's advice?
Absolutely.
Okay.
100%.
Okay, good. I'm glad to hear that.
Yeah, I want this house to be ours...
me, her, my daughter's.
I'm concerned for Laura and Chris,
as the dead within their home
pose a very serious danger.
But I believe if they follow my advice,
they'll remain safe and
live a peaceful life,
keeping their home in the
family for generations to come.