It hurts to be in here.
I don't know how to protect my family.
If you go in that barn,
you're gonna die.
I hate this house.
I love my house, but I love my family more.
Ow!!
This is worse than a prison.
That's very, very, very bad
and there's blood.
I think that the living
are caught in a war zone.
"You're mine. You can't escape."
My name is Amy Allan.
What's happening?
I see dead people.
It seems like a devil.
I speak to dead people.
He's pissed off.
And they speak to me.
I felt real fear.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I think she's being murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Serial killer pops in my head.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
Nobody believes me.
It's my job to reveal them.
- Do you think there's still bodies there?
- I do.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
You got problems. I got news for you.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
This is our house,
whether they like it or not.
Or time to get out.
This is their house, the house of the dead.
I'm in Chester Springs, Pennsylvania.
It's an upscale community about
40 minutes outside of Philly.
Amy and I were called in
by a woman named Carol.
Now she told me the activity
in her dream home is so bad
it's ruining her health and
tearing her family apart.
She got real emotional on the phone
and begged us to come out.
She says we're her last hope.
Before Amy arrives,
I look for anything that
might influence her findings.
This house has a lot of family photos.
Once they're covered or removed,
the location will be
ready for tonight's walk.
I think I'm feeling, like, sick.
I have a fever.
Hot and cold at the same time
and heart's pounding.
I'm also getting this woman.
I think she causes...
sickness and, um,
extreme nausea.
But she always is moving
all over the [bleep] place.
She literally looks like a [bleep] blur.
And she likes to move things around.
Redecorating is what she thinks she's doing.
And she's very strange-looking.
She has spider arms and spider legs,
and then her head is more... just,
like, a skull.
She's scary and she scares people.
Uh, so, Carol, I'm glad I'm here.
You sounded really upset on the phone
and it sounds like you're
going through a tough time.
Yeah, I called you in
'cause I really need help.
I'm concerned for our physical safety,
emotional safety,
and I don't know how to protect my family.
Now how long have you lived here?
12 years.
Now who lives in the house with you now?
My husband and my son.
My daughter, who's in college,
used to, uh, be here.
And the older daughter
lives about 20 minutes away
with her daughter.
Now tell me what's going on in the house.
Noises, things being moved around,
seeing shadows,
and I definitely think
it impacts how you feel.
Within the first year of living here,
I ended up getting sick...
uh, fibromyalgia,
chronic fatigue, migraines.
You seem to think it has
to do with the house.
I think it can all be tied in.
Doctors, when they would test,
would say I look great on paper.
Okay, 'cause to look at you,
you look healthy.
Why don't you just move?
It's our home, and I don't wanna leave.
But I'm very fearful for my family,
for my kids,
and my grandchild.
The living, yeah, they totally see her,
the woman from outside.
I think they see her, like...
- like if the light was shining on her...
- Right.
and then there's a shadow.
Oh, she's goes [bleep] nuts in here, man.
She really makes you not feel good,
and the thing heart and the...fever.
You know, she just does... it's terrible.
She has too much energy.
What does that do to the living?
Probably give you a heart attack. Mm-hmm.
Okay, Carol,
so why are we up in this part of the house?
Upstairs here is when I
first came face-to-face
with a black mass.
Came up to about my waist level.
I came up on it from behind,
and the top of it turned
around and looked at me.
Okay, have... have you seen it again?
I've seen a shadow figure.
I think it's the same thing.
It's just in a different form.
More like a male adult, around 6-feet-9.
Now is anything else going on?
One of the things is that
the door will just close on its own.
You're talking about these doors right here?
Just...
- outta nowhere?
- Yes.
Do you hear it?
No. You don't hear it closing,
you don't hear it latching shut,
but it's closed.
Okay. Now what about it being on a tilt?
This is not off-kilter or anything?
No. It has a latch handle,
so you think you would hear it.
Like that. You'd hear that.
You would hear that.
I can't explain it.
Well, that's gotta scare the hell outta ya,
you turn around and see the door closed.
Yeah, I don't sleep very well.
There's somebody else in the house, uh,
that the woman from outside doesn't like.
Uh, and I think he kinda
torments her a little bit.
He is...
always looking for her
and won't let her alone.
She says that dude is up the stairs.
He's like a bull in a china shop.
He's not aware of, you know, his strength.
He's like, you think about a door,
and a door slams...
and then all the [bleep] doors slam.
But it's not like he meant to.
Do you know how he might
appear to the living?
I think they see him a
like a big black mist.
They might see him, like,
hovering over them,
like, lurking in the corner.
He's like,
"I'm trying to take care of that [bleep].
I'm trying to [bleep] control her ass."
Uh, he says that she
causes all the problems.
All the problems. Not him. It's her.
Sure as [bleep] wants to break things.
She doesn't wanna [bleep] be here anymore.
She's tired of the [bleep]
crazy-ass guy who's here,
[bleep] tortures her.
Uh, so she gets out occasionally.
Uh, but then, you know,
she ends up back here,
and then there he is, and she's upset.
Okay.
You had an experience here?
Yeah.
At one point, I did have horses. Okay.
So to help with, uh,
mice that come in with the food grain,
I had purchased some cats.
And to keep the wildlife out,
we would put cat food in a container.
And to make sure they
couldn't get into that,
we put a cinder block on top.
Okay, what happened?
One time, my son came out to feed the cats.
One of our cats was dead within the bin.
Inside the bin?
And the cinder block was on top.
Okay.
He must've been shocked when he saw that.
Yeah. Me, too.
It just floored me.
Is there any chance the cat
jumped in before he closed it
and didn't see the cat and
maybe suffocated this thing?
It's not a real deep food bin.
All right, so he would've seen the cat.
He would've seen it.
Well, I got news for you.
- If that's supernatural, you got a problem.
- Yeah.
I know you got issues here,
but what are you...
what are you trying to get out
of the investigation we're gonna do?
I need to find out what's going on here
for the safety of my family.
I think whatever this entity is,
it can impact people's personalities,
like the behavior of Kelly in the past.
- Kelly's your daughter?
- Kelly's my daughter.
What are we talking about?
What kind of behavior?
When we moved in here,
she became just atrocious...
the things that she would say
and her physical violence against me.
It was almost as if
it wasn't even my daughter
saying the things she was
and doing the things she was.
But why do you think that's paranormal
and not just teenage nonsense?
Well, because when she then
moved out of the house...
we actually asked her to
leave because her personality,
the way she was acting
jeopardized my marriage,
jeopardized the rest of
the children in the house.
Okay.
And when we asked her to leave,
then she's done a complete turnaround.
Really?
No more explosive outbursts.
It's completely different.
I'm feeling that same woman.
Something, uh, she, uh...
She has been saying,
"Oh,
don't go in there 'cause you'll all die!
You'll all die!"
She's saying there's
something in here that's, uh,
not good.
It's done harm.
She thinks that no one
can take care of this.
That's very, very, very bad.
It's been here a long time.
This thing is, uh...
a blob.
It came...
like a snake
that, uh...
may be influencing people.
Because it talks to them?
It's made a lot of people...
angry.
It can make you do bad things.
But it does... it causes damage.
A lot of damage.
I don't like it in here.
It hurts to be in here.
So, Rob, I was talking to your wife,
and, uh, it was upsetting listening to her.
So, uh, how you taking all this?
It's been very stressful.
I'm an engineer, so, you know,
I believe in science
and I look for facts and I look for proof.
Things just kept happening
and happening that
I really couldn't explain.
It's very disconcerting,
and especially because of
all the different kinds of
things that have happened.
Have you had any experiences
while you've been here?
I've heard footsteps.
Laying in bed,
I've heard things outside in the hallway.
Now the footsteps... you sure it wasn't
- one of the kids walking around?
- Yeah.
Positive?
Yeah. Sure. Positive. Absolutely.
Okay, so now anything else happen to you?
I had an episode where I
woke up in the morning,
took a shower, and my back burned.
And I felt to the back,
and I had scratches on my back.
And my wife said,
"You have big gouges on your back."
And she actually ended up
taking a picture of 'em.
This is your back? That's my back.
Show me where these scratches would've been
and how you could've did it.
It would've been...
like...right here.
I- I mean... And I would've had to,
essentially,
- just do like that.
- Oh, I see where it was.
It was, like,
right into the meaty part of my back.
It is possible? Yeah.
But it's kinda pushing it
that you did it yourself.
I mean,
it's almost like you were in a straitjacket.
What do you think is going on in this house?
There's some sort of...
uh... haunting.
You know, I love my house,
but I love my family more.
And I'll... if I... if I need to move,
I'll move.
She's pissed. Oh, she's pissed.
He keeps saying he doesn't
mean to hurt anybody.
I think he, like, cuts people.
That's what sh... wait.
I think that's what she's saying.
So who the [bleep] knows who's cuttin' who?
I'm caught in the middle of a war
between the dead man and woman.
Both are telling me
completely different stories,
and it's impossible to know
who's telling the truth.
He's like, "I'm the one trying to protect."
He tries to stop her from
doing her crazy [bleep].
He's more... worried about her,
because she physically effects the living.
That's what he's trying to stop.
He feels like the problems he causes
are far less than if he was not here
and she was running amok.
So, Kelly,
I'm glad I got a chance to speak to you.
I was talking to mom,
and she told me you were having a...
kind of a tough time in this house.
I hate this house. Hate it.
It's just negative.
But she thought that
whatever's in this house
definitely influenced you.
I think it had an influence.
We were always just at each others' necks.
Even the little mistakes would
turn into a total blowup.
- You got violent.
- Yeah. It was bad.
Sometimes you just get so mad and,
like, black out
and not really be able
to put 2 and 2 together
about what just happened.
Let me just ask you.
Do you think it was the house
and what's in this house that did it to you?
Or do you think it was just
you were being a pain in the ass teenager?
Um, 100% believe with everything in me
that there is something here.
She's telling me everything that she does,
uh, to people.
She kind of harassed
someone that lived here.
There's a young girl... teenager, I think...
that she didn't have respect for her mom.
She had very bad thoughts
that were not good, pure.
She really, really hated her.
And she...
kind of really let her have it.
What did she do?
She kinda always jumped her a lot.
And it would make the kid very sick.
I think she kinda possessed her.
Why'd you wanna meet me in this room?
This actually used to be my first room here
when we first moved in,
and this is where I had my
first experience in the house.
Okay, what was that?
Uh, actually, this door right here.
Um, very first night we had moved in,
um, just, like, banging and knocking.
Now are we talking about like...
banging like a person was doing it?
As if there was
literally somebody stuck on the other side
trying to get through.
So...
Like that.
Exactly like that.
I'm 51 years old.
That would scare the hell
outta me if I heard that.
Yeah.
I don't have an explanation for it.
Anything else?
Most recently, my daughter actually was,
like, pushed down the stairs.
Legs went over her head,
and she landed on her head.
I... of course, like, complete shock.
Freaked out.
I was bawling my eyes out.
I wouldn't want her to
experience the things I have.
I worry about that every day.
He's not really aware of the space,
you know, around him.
Indirectly, I think he could hurt people,
like by trying to move them out of the way.
I think that the living are...
kinda caught in a war zone.
Some cases I've gotta do a lot of digging
before I find a death on the property.
Not this one. Took one phone call.
I'm on my way to meet
with a sheriff who said
there was a murder right inside
of Rob and Carol's house.
Turns out there was a homicide
in the house I'm investigating.
Yes. Andrew Fedyck was killed in the house
in January of 1939.
So now what do we know about
this guy Andrew himself?
Andrew and his Bessie
were Austrian immigrants.
They moved into the house in 1929.
They were the parents of
five girls and one boy.
Andrew was a farmer,
and he was known to have a drinking problem.
The night of the homicide,
Andrew came in, and allegedly he was drunk
and had been drinking for several days.
And he was very abusive and boisterous and,
uh,
angry with his wife and
whoever else was in the house.
And, uh, the son, Michael, came in.
And when Michael came in,
it's alleged that his dad
came after him with a knife.
- Okay, so now how old was Michael?
- Michael was 19.
Now I do have a picture of Michael.
A struggle ensues,
and Michael is able to disarm his dad.
But at the time,
then his father turned his rage
toward Bessie, his wife.
She picks up a 12 gauge shotgun.
She gives him a warning.
In fact, she gives him several warnings
and asked him to back off.
He proceeds to come after her,
and she shoots once and
hits him in the chest.
I do have a copy of the death certificate
declaring him dead that night,
with information that he
died from a shotgun blast.
Okay. Homicide, murder by gunshot wounds.
I have the newspaper account.
It was headline news.
The newspaper report
said an autopsy performed
revealed that 156 pellets
of the shotgun shell
had pierced his chest.
So, sheriff, did she get arrested for this?
That night, she's taken into custody
and she's charged with both
homicide and manslaughter.
She's released on bail,
and three months later,
she appears in front of a grand jury.
- Okay.
- She alleges self-defense.
The grand jury believes that
and they don't indict her.
Did they have a relationship in life?
Yes. I'm gonna say she knew
him when she was alive.
I don't know if they were related.
With all this fighting going on,
it's hard to know
how this man and woman
knew each other in life.
But one thing's for sure...
they can't stand each other in death.
She seems afraid of him some,
thinking that he can do [bleep] to her.
Or has done [bleep] to her, you know.
I don't know if he, like,
beats her up or what,
but she tries to get the
[bleep] out of the way.
I am seeing a... it's a funeral.
A wife shoots and kills her husband,
and a grand jury does not indict her.
That just seems odd to me,
especially because it's 1939.
I'm heading over to meet
with a professor in Philly
who'll look into the case for me.
Well, Dr. Ruchti, thanks for meeting me.
I appreciate it.
My pleasure.
All right,
so the reason I asked you to help me out
was that I found it odd,
especially as a homicide investigator,
that this woman did not get indicted
for murder charges.
Steve, it is a really interesting case
for the time period, given the fact that
the status of women was subordinate to men
during that time.
And... and that's why I thought it odd
that she didn't get indicted... Right.
'cause I figured, it's 1939.
There was no domestic violence
laws on the books yet.
No, there absolutely was not.
In fact, domestic violence wasn't even
part of our language at that point.
We just called these things "family feuds."
Well, it had to be pretty compelling
'cause I'm assuming
that it had to be an all-male grand jury.
Absolutely.
When you think of somebody as unequal to men,
less than men,
you might think of them as childlike,
not making the same decisions
that you would make.
And they're... looking at
her as if she was a kid.
- And how do you indict a kid?
- Right.
Maybe this grand jury just thought,
you know,
"Well,
she just didn't know what she was doing.
Maybe she lost her mind."
We still see some of this still today,
the argument that women are...
are crazy or irrational.
So, I mean, what's your opinion on it?
- What do you think about it?
- I think it's very clear
that she was being abused by
her husband severely over time.
She's trying to protect herself.
She's trying to protect her children.
And did not want to hurt or
harm or even kill anyone,
let alone her husband,
but felt she had no other choice
because he was coming for her.
He's like, "She was really angry."
I think he...
privately disliked her.
He thought she was nuts.
Yeah, she's done some bad things.
He gets angry at her.
He says that she's crazy.
So far,
I've got a family being terrorized
by unexplained activity
and a property that's been
the site of a homicide.
But there's gotta be something
else that can help my case,
so I'm at the local library.
Searching through old records,
I find a scandal
involving brutal mistreatment
of kids at an orphanage.
Turns out it's right next to
my client's original property lines.
I called the local historian,
and she says it was a scene of neglect,
abuse, and death.
Well, Dr. Giesberg, thanks for meeting me.
I appreciate that.
So the article I came across, uh,
mentioned scandal and abuse in an orphanage
not far from the property I'm investigating.
Uh, what can you tell me about the place?
It opened up, um, in 1868 on the property
of a former Revolutionary War-era hospital.
Oh. Okay.
And here's a photograph
of the school in 1870.
The orphanage in Chester
Springs was one of 35
- operating in the state of Pennsylvania.
- Wow.
Now the article I saw was
sometime in the 1880s.
So when did the scandal actually break?
There were a series of articles, actually,
- published in the 1880s...
- Okay.
uh, reporting abuse at the schools.
- Here are a couple of examples here.
One of these talking about,
uh, kids getting, um,
you know, water tortured
so they can confess to
pulling a prank at the school.
Another one, um, alleging, um, sexual abuse
- at the schools.
- Okay.
This is another article
that was published in a national newspaper
that talked about the
kids not being provided
with adequate food or clothing,
uh, children being neglected
without medical care
and dying in their cells.
- This is worse than a prison.
- Oh, yeah, sure.
The news stories, um,
reported deaths at many of these
schools in... over the years.
So what happens next?
This becomes a political hot potato.
So all the abuse and all
this is still going on?
- That's right.
- All right, so what happens?
So around 1906, um,
the Chester Springs, uh,
Civil War Orphan Home
is finally closed.
Here's our article talking
about its last commencement.
Okay. Did anybody go to prison?
Or was it just basically
"you're out of a job now"?
These guys mostly just lost their jobs.
- That's it.
- That's right.
There's, like, some...
boys?
These guys are, like, beating up this, uh...
you know, they're kids, though.
They're kids.
They're beatin' the [bleep] outta this guy.
Beatin' the [bleep] out of him.
This is bad over here.
Ow!!
Ohh.
Whoa, that hurt.
Somebody lost their hearing.
His whole body's on the ground.
I think he's dehydrated.
And there's blood.
He's young. He's young.
He's, like, a kid.
Oh, that [bleep] hurt, man.
I think he's delirious.
During my walk,
I was caught in the middle
of a feud between a dead man and woman.
I'm meeting with an artist to describe
how their battles affect the living.
Dead lady is kind of on the wall.
And she's weird. Very strange-looking.
She pretty much has a skull for a face.
And there's a dead man across the room,
screaming at her.
The living lady is freaking out.
Amy, is this what you saw?
Yes, that's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our
findings to each other
and our clients for the first time.
Well, Amy, you're sitting across from, uh,
what I consider a family in crisis.
Uh, this is Rob, that's his wife Carol,
and this is their daughter Kelly,
their oldest.
Now Kelly doesn't live here anymore.
And these are their other two children.
This is Heather, who's away at college,
uh, and this is Kyle, who's...14 now?
- 14.
- Yep.
He still lives here.
You should know that the
activity is so bad here,
it's ruining Carol's health,
and it's basically tearing the family apart.
And they told me that
we are their last hope.
So now that Amy knows a
little bit about...
what's going on here,
I'm gonna ask her to
describe her walk for us.
When I first got here,
I encountered a female.
Her energy is just... off the charts.
She's absolutely in constant motion.
She looks... strange.
Her face was basically just a skull.
Her arms and legs were extraordinarily long
and kind of spiderlike.
Definitely one of the...
the major things that I got from her
is that she can make the living by sick.
She... latched on to me.
I was sweating and I felt, like, the fever.
And I felt like I had, you know, a flu.
Oh. This is the...
one of the main reasons we're here,
because your health has deteriorated
since she's moved in.
Now you look at her,
she... she looks like the epitome of fit.
- Right?
- Mm-hmm.
And even the doctors, on paper, say you...
there's nothing wrong.
I look great on paper.
But I just feel pains... migraines,
random pain, sometimes out of the blue.
Interesting.
And what about severe anxiety,
hyperactivity,
then feeling extremely drained?
- I would say that's...
- Kelly has a lot of anxiety.
that's actually more Kelly.
That sound right, Kel?
Yeah.
It's just hard to hear it.
The living should not be at all
interacting with this female
because her energy is so severe
and there's so much death
entangled in her energy.
At one point, I almost had to stop the walk
because I felt like I was gonna
have a [bleep] heart attack.
Carol gets these intense
chest pains from time to time.
Told Rob about 'em. He took me to the E.R.
Well, that's a smart move.
So it is a real threat
because she really can induce that.
Wow.
So that is making me very nervous.
Now would the living be able to see her?
Yes. They would see her
like a brown misty thing.
I've seen it as the mist now.
I've seen it as a, like,
2 to 3 foot mass upstairs,
and I've seen it as a shadow figure walking.
Wow.
The other thing was,
the woman was talking about
torturing this... this girl.
Uh, she was saying it was because
she was disrespectful and
didn't have any manners,
so she was trying to teach her a lesson.
She kind of looked like you.
Yeah.
Those words hit it right on the head,
I'd say.
Yeah, our relationship deteriorated a lot
for several years...
- Mm-hmm.
- once we moved in here.
And a lot of times,
Rob would... it made it difficult
because he would ask
perhaps what I perhaps did
to set things off with Kelly.
Do you feel like she was
being kind of different
or overly controlling or
overly aggressive with you?
Obviously,
you guys are being influenced like crazy
by her.
And it affected your marriage as well, right?
The whole thing?
Un, during that time,
it affected the entire family.
It came to the point
where you guys actually asked her to leave.
Or basically told her to leave, right?
I didn't want to do it.
I- I love my daughter,
but it was overwhelming.
Here, baby.
Thank you.
Neither of them could figure
out a way to not escalate
from the smallest argument to a big,
gigantic...
nuclear war.
And as the dad,
I was caught in the middle of it.
It's just scary to think that, like...
something you can't explain
or you can't really see,
you don't know what it is,
can affect you that way.
Mm-hmm.
So one of the things
that this dead woman was indicating to me
was that...
she's being tortured by
another dead person here.
This deceased male,
she absolutely hates him.
I saw him standing at the top of the stairs,
by the master bedroom, just watching me.
I could hear doors slamming.
He does this.
That happens a lot.
The other thing... um,
you would also see him
as a large, black mist.
And she came back and was
saying how she hated him.
She's like, "He scratches people.
He's worse because he scratches people.
He torments me."
He's calling her a liar.
She's calling him a liar.
You know,
I don't know who... who to b... who to believe.
Well, your walk is nailing
about everything that's
going on in this house.
Rob, do me a favor
and just tell Amy how you
think you got these marks.
One morning, I came out of the shower
and I turned around, and Carol said,
"You've got big scratches on your back.
How did that happen?"
Could this thing also bruise?
Like, cause bruises?
Yeah. And the feeling of being shoved,
pushed, pulled,
you know...
does that resonate with you?
Tell Amy exactly what happened,
because the way you described
it to me did not sound normal.
Mnh-mnh.
Lila, my daughter,
we were going down the stairs
on that side of the house,
and it literally looked like someone, like,
put both hands, like,
on the back of her shoulders
and shoved her down, and, like...
she, like,
flipped and landed on her head on the stairs.
I... completely lost it.
That is probably coming from her.
- It explains a lot, actually.
- A lot.
Yeah, a lot.
Well, these two dead people
really hate each other.
Unfortunately,
you guys get caught in the middle,
and some physical trauma is
caused by them inadvertently.
I had a-a sketch artist draw
kind of an example of a situation,
specifically in the master bedroom.
Oh,..
Holy crap.
It's creepy.
Kinda makes you feel sick.
Now how would they feel
with them two fight...
the two dead fighting...
Just like when I'm... like, they would feel,
you know, unsettled, uncomfortable, anxious.
It would kinda explain why I don't...
I don't feel at rest.
I'm never comfortable.
I always feel like there's eyes on me.
Mm-hmm.
Now did get anything from
when they were alive?
They somehow knew each other
when they were both alive.
He always... felt that she was a bitch,
that she was very mean to people.
But, you know,
she definitely has a fear of him
because he beat her when she was alive.
Well, listening to
everything you had to say,
I kinda have an idea already
who you're talking about.
In 1929, Andrew and Bessie Fedyck
moved into your house with their kids.
Andrew was a laborer and rumored
to be a pretty bad drunk.
There is evidence that suggests
that he may have been
pretty abusive as well.
On January 3, 1939,
Andrew came home drunk and
got into an altercation,
and his son came home... Michael.
And the fight he got into
with his son escalated
where Andrew had a knife
and tried to attack his son.
Michael was able to get the knife away,
and Andrew turned his rage
towards his wife Bessie.
Now she picks up a 12 gauge shotgun
and begs him to stop.
He continues coming at her...
and she fires one round...
12 gauge shotgun...
into his chest.
Wow.
That happened right here in this house.
I have his death certificate here.
Now this homicide was front page news.
I actually have an article
about what happened.
Bessie was immediately arrested.
She testifies at the grand jury,
and they don't indict her.
Self-defense?
Yeah, basically.
You know,
in my experience working domestic violence
for over 20 years on the streets,
this is not something that just happened.
This was abuse going on for years.
This may sound just ridiculous,
but I was actually hoping
that there was something...
factual that could explain
a lot of this nutsy stuff that's going on.
I'm just shocked,
and that they're still fighting
and it's still happening
and they're still influencing people.
So anything else?
Just a quick question.
I mean, did you spend a
lot of time in the barn
or around the barn when you were younger?
Um, yeah, 'cause we had horses.
Okay. I got it.
Okay.
There's something else that's
also influencing this area,
and... and that might have something to do
with what happened here.
I was drawn right to the barn,
and the dead lady actually wrapped her...
her arms around my waist and pulled me back.
And she's like,
"You don't wanna go in there."
And she goes, "You know,
if you go in that barn,
you're gonna die."
I did feel very unnerved.
She was telling me that, um,
there was something in the barn, uh,
that has done a great deal of harm,
that it absolutely was not good.
What I saw was like this small black ball.
And then I saw it, like,
kind of go into, like, a snake form.
It did then take the shape
of a very solid kind of shadow person,
but it's not a shadow person.
What I would call it is a demon.
It did take the shape
of a very solid kind of shadow person,
but it's not a shadow person.
What I would call it is a demon.
The thing is, is that by you being, like,
so out there all the time,
like, it's something
that could've absolutely
influenced your behavior
and could've taken over slightly even.
Uh, it is something that could
have influenced these people.
Not feeling good about
what's going on right now.
No.
It's like Grand Central Station for evil.
Its mission here is to destroy
as many people as possible.
Now do you think the demon in the barn
was attached to Kelly?
- Yes, I think it was.
- You do.
Well, Lila spends a lot of time by the barn.
Al the time. She loves following the cats.
I think I'm in shock.
Well, guys,
your family's been plagued with questions
for years now.
Why have you been so sick, Carol?
Why did you act out, Kelly?
And, Rob, you know, why you got scratched.
At least you have answers now.
But the big question is, can you stay here
in a calm, peaceful environment
and live your lives happily
and have you granddaughter
come over and be safe?
For that answer,
I'm gonna turn it over to my partner Amy
and see if she has a resolution for us.
There are several things that you need to do
in order to make this a safer environment.
So in order to remove the
demon in the barn area,
I would like there to be a
Catholic priest who comes in.
He's going to do an exorcism
of the barn and the property.
He does need to make a very firm statement
that he is not including
the removal of any dead people
from this location.
So my hope is that he actually
gets rid of this thing,
but he may not.
Uh, he may just get rid
of it from your property.
The next day, I want there to
be a physical medium that comes
to remove the deceased male
and female from the house.
It could take several days,
uh, for it to happen
just because there's going
to be a lot of arguing
between the medium and probably
both of the dead people.
Now with all that said and done,
will she start feeling better and...
Yes. The difference will be insane.
It'll be a huge, huge difference.
We're all highly motivated
to move all this on.
It'd be so nice to be able to come home
and feel like it's a home,
because I don't have that feeling.
It's nice to have some answers.
Kinda gives you some closure
to that chapter of your life.
I really hope Carol
and Rob follow my advice
and deal with the entities
terrorizing their family.
With the help of a priest and a medium,
they should be able to free themselves
of the darkness surrounding their home.