They're acting like they're still alive.
Whatever's going on here
really needs to stop.
It was a devil or a monster.
"I have seen a ghost."
There's no question in my mind
that there's something evil there.
The dead don't rest here.
His body was completely
mutilated and half-eaten.
I don't know how they're
not killing each other.
"You're mine. You can't escape."
My name is Amy Allan.
What's happening?
I see dead people.
It seems like a devil.
I speak to dead people.
He's pissed off.
And they speak to me.
I felt real fear.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I think she's being murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Serial killer pops in my head.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
Nobody believes me.
It's my job to reveal them.
- Do you think there's still bodies there?
- I do.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
You got problems. I got news for you.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
This is our house...
whether they like it or not.
Or time to get out.
This is their house, the house of the dead.
I'm in Warsaw, Indiana.
It's about 40 miles west of Fort Wayne.
I got a call from a guy
who runs a hotel in town.
Now, he says he was a lifelong skeptic
until he bought the place
about eight years ago.
He says activity's so bad,
he's losing employees and customers.
It's his dream business,
but he says if me and
Amy can't help him out,
he might have to shut the place down.
Before Amy arrives,
I look for anything that
might influence her findings.
This hotel has a lot of
artwork and historic photos
that have to be covered or removed.
When I'm finished,
the location will be
ready for tonight's walk.
There's a lot of dead people here.
They're acting like they're still alive.
I'm talking, like, about 50 people here.
Do you know if these
dead come inside at all?
Yes, they do.
They,
um... they can come and go as they please.
The dead don't rest here.
Well, Dan, I'm glad I'm here.
Um, when we spoke on the phone,
you sounded like you're at the point
where you're almost ready
to close this place down
because of the activity.
We're having trouble
with employees being scared at night.
- Okay.
- I've had several quit.
Customers not staying.
So, give me an idea
of what people are experiencing here.
- What's going on?
- Knocking on the door.
Things moving off the shelves.
I've heard of people getting touched.
This seems to be worse
the last couple years.
Now, how long have you had this place?
Eight years.
This is a three-story building.
Now, I see the restaurant
here on the first floor.
What else you got going on?
On the second floor, we have a sports bar,
and on the third floor,
we have seven hotel rooms.
Okay. So now, when you bought it,
did you know it was haunted?
I did not.
I dismissed a lot of it.
What changed your mind?
I was standing at the edge of the bar,
happened to look down at the floor,
and I seen a black fog go across the floor
and then just come up and then schoo,
just gone.
What do you think's going on?
Not sure 100%, but the last two years,
there's a lot of... lot of bad things.
Sounds like you could lose the business.
Maybe.
Met a lot of people here,
lot of good friends,
- like to keep 'em here.
- Right.
Okay.
What people are seeing
is kind of like a ghost
but with a black sheet on it.
Everybody thinks that it
was a devil or a monster,
but it's a person.
He goes under, uh, in the ground,
and he's, like,
always kicking, uh, the floor.
Then he was showing me, like,
spinning the structure.
Obviously it doesn't spin,
but I think structurally, you know,
it has issues all the time
because he's kind of [bleep]
with the whole thing.
This thing that's under the ground
causes a lot of the stuff
that's happening here.
And I would think that most people
probably are also thinking
that there's some kind of poltergeist,
but it's not.
He's in his little hole,
and he projects his energy
and affects the surroundings.
What's going on in here?
We have a lot of things
moving around in this kitchen.
We're concerned about that.
For example,
the broom going across the room.
The bartender...
There was nobody in the kitchen at the time,
and the bartender heard a lot of noise...
Okay.
Came out and saw the broom
is in the middle of the floor here,
and she knew that the last
time she walked out there
she saw it on the wall back there.
Okay. Nobody was in the kitchen?
- Nobody was in the kitchen.
- Okay.
So now,
has anything else happened in this place?
Yes. The day that I purchased the building,
I walked through the door,
walked past the dishwasher
and stopped for some reason
and took a glance at it,
and it just squirted me in
the face twice real quick.
We had some, um,
more issues with plumbing with faucets
going on and off.
Lot of things that seem, like,
to try to disrupt the
business it seems like.
He has a lot of energy.
It'll affect everything structurally,
you know, like, water, uh, plumbing.
It's a lot of him. A lot of him.
Can you describe what he looks like?
And he's, like, squished himself out,
'cause he's in the ground, you know,
and, uh, just has his legs,
which are always kicking.
It's very strange.
So, Leslie,
thanks for taking the time to talk to me.
You've been working here for a while?
About 17 years. Bartender and waitress.
I've heard about all the
things that are happening here.
Um, what about yourself? Any experiences?
Quite a few.
I had somebody tap me on the shoulder.
Okay. Where were you?
I was at the computer station.
No one was around me.
You're sure about that?
Yeah. There was nobody there.
And anything else?
I was leaving one night
and saw someone standing on the third floor
in the window in the hallway.
Okay. Was it a guest?
No. There were no guests that night.
I'm the last one here,
and I know if the hotel
rooms are rented or not
because we're the check-in.
Okay. Describe the man to me.
Tall and broad-shouldered, dark suit.
A suit?
Yeah, like, old-fashioned suit, bowler hat.
Okay.
Now, Leslie, you've been here...
What? Almost 17 years.
I mean, how you dealing with this?
I mean, why do you stay?
I love the place,
but if I felt a definite threat, I would...
I would probably not be here.
There's a male here.
He is a workaholic.
He's always moving around.
He's always working.
Uh, I think that they do see him.
Mostly it's just solid,
normal-looking person.
I think the,
uh... workaholic doesn't like people up here.
He's mad.
Came right to the door and was like, "Aah!"
Oh, lordy.
He hates this [bleep]
Oh, damn. Oh, geez.
Okay. He's freaking the [bleep] out.
He's yelling, "Get out of here!"
You know, "Leave me alone!"
He invokes such rage in people.
I don't know how they're
not killing each other.
Now, how long did you work here?
About four years. I bartended.
I was talking to Danny.
He said a lot of the employees
quit over the stuff that happened here.
What was the feeling like
for you when you worked here?
I would experience fear
almost as if I was a child again
locked in a dark bedroom
with demons under my bed
and monsters in my closet.
That's how bad it was?
What about experiences? Have you had any?
Yes.
When I was closing the bar,
I witnessed a shadow
that actually resembled
a man directly behind me,
and it was, like, 7, 8 foot tall.
What did you do?
I was in shock.
I didn't really know what to do,
and from that point,
- I was just, like, "I have seen a ghost."
- Geez.
- You have anything else?
- Yes.
I was working in here,
and I was pushing in the barstools,
and I got to about this barstool right here
and as I went to push it in,
it almost just moved for me.
Show me what happened when
the chair moved on you.
Okay.
I put my foot on it and grabbed here,
and then I went to push it,
and as I went to push it,
it was almost, like,
it just moved for me so gracefully.
All right. Now, these are heavy.
They're not...
Right.
These aren't light.
I mean, you got to push it.
I can't even try to debunk that.
I just really feel like
there's something here.
The workaholic, he's pissed off.
I mean, he's doing things with the chairs.
I feel like he has pushed
living people definitely.
You know, he's like, "This is my space."
"Get out of the way, 'cause here I come."
And definitely they got to
feel this [bleep] energy,
like, it is so intense.
It is so directed.
I just feel like massive amounts of tension,
the heart, you know, just [bleep] pound...
Like, I'd almost think some people,
they can't [bleep] breathe here.
Now, Kathy, I understand
that you actually worked at
the hotel for a little bit.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
I worked there for about six months,
but I've been a customer for about 15 years.
Now, did you stop working there
because of what was going on?
That was a very big part of it.
Yeah. I read the signs.
You know, somebody was warning me
about something, so, um... Okay.
Now,
what kind of things are we talking about?
When I was a patron sitting
at the bar one evening,
um, I turned,
and I saw two apparitions in booth one.
Okay. How do you know they were apparitions?
I said to the waitress,
"You've got people in booth one?"
And she turned and said,
"Kath, there's nobody there."
So it couldn't have been
a mirror reflection of anything?
No. There's no mirror anywhere near it.
- Near it.
- Nope.
Anything else?
One full moon night, the bar was closed,
and looked up, and on the third floor,
I saw a man in the middle window,
and it was like he was looking
up and down the street.
You know,
you're the second person to tell me that.
What'd he look like?
He had a fedora,
so he kind of resembled a gangster.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Would you recognize him
if you saw him in a photo or a sketch?
I believe so. Yes. Mm-hmm.
Anything else?
When I was working and
I was doing the dishes,
- I was by the, uh, sink...
- Okay.
And I felt a tug on my apron.
Was anybody walking by you at the time?
No. No.
'Cause I looked around,
and there was nobody around me.
So you've had a lot of experiences there.
What do you think is going on in this place?
There's no question in my mind
that there's something evil there.
The workaholic likes this floor.
He is, like,
putting pillows on people's faces.
He does not like, um,
drug addicts and whores.
His thing of, you know,
getting the people [bleep] up,
and he's smothering 'em.
He's trying to kill 'em
with the [bleep] smothering 'em to death.
Somehow made it look like a heart attack.
Makes me feel very
uncomfortable and panicked.
There's some talk he may have killed someone
after he is dead.
Dan and his
employees didn't know much
about the history of the Barbee Hotel,
so I'm at the local library
to see what I can find.
Searching through old records,
I find a man named Joseph Plu
who used to live on my client's
property in the late 1800s.
Turns out he was accused
of a brutal double murder
at his neighbor's house.
I've called on my old friend Butch Barile.
He's a local retired detective.
He said he'd dig into the case for me
and tell me exactly what happened.
February of 1887,
I come across an article,
this kid Joseph Plu who got
charged with a double murder
right on the property I'm investigating.
What were you able to find out?
Joseph Plu lived on your client's land
with his grandparents
next to a Henry Dunham,
who had hired Joseph Plu
to work and help him on his farm.
So, what kind of a crime
scene are we looking at?
What happened?
So, it was, uh...
it was a pretty grisly crime scene.
Henry, he had a 20-month-old baby,
a daughter,
and her throat was slit ear to ear.
The other victim was Henry himself.
Okay.
He was found out in the yard
with several stab wounds
and, uh, it's thought that hogs got to him.
His body was completely mutilated
and half-eaten, literally.
I see, like, somebody's face being [bleep]
I feel like it's a male.
He's, like, very much in pain right now,
and he can't breathe.
Ow!
Something... got hit in the head,
maybe, here.
I know there's a few people.
There's more than one.
I think he's just in his death state.
There's so much pain in my head.
Oh, my God.
So what happens next?
A neighbor happened to be
walking near the property,
found him laying there,
went inside the house and found Lucy Dunham,
Henry's wife,
who was just barely clinging to life.
She also had several stab wounds
and... and severe head injuries.
So now, at the time,
Plu lived on my client's property,
and I'm assuming now that
'cause she survived,
she identifies him as the perp.
She identifies him, but also she knew
there were two other people there,
but she couldn't identify either one of 'em.
Now, there's a lot of rage in this case,
and what would motivate this kid,
Plu, to do this?
My understanding is that
there was a lot of animosity
between him and the wife.
- Okay.
- They'd have some confrontations
and some problems.
- He didn't really care for her.
- Okay.
In fact, I think they'd had some problems
with Mr. Dunham arguing over,
you know, over pay.
Joseph Plu, he had some... some cash on him.
He had $90, my understanding was,
and I think some of it
had bloodstains on it.
Okay.
You and I both know that this
is not the type of murder,
especially with this baby
that you commit over $85...
No... or whatever money.
No, not at all.
It was, uh, some, you know,
severe hatred involved.
Wow. Okay.
There's a dead lady.
She's, like, hanging on.
She's, like, hanging on to my leg.
She's, like, being dragged across the floor.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
She, like...
I don't know what the
[bleep] happened to her, man.
She got [bleep]
I think that somebody killed her.
There's a couple of men around her.
I feel them.
She knew one for sure.
Why is my friend doing this?
Someone says it's a brutal
assault with a little knife.
I feel like someone got stabbed.
Uh...
Okay. So now, Plu gets charged.
Does he get convicted? What's the story?
Plu does get charged and gets convicted,
and he, uh... he takes a life sentence.
All right.
So, does this kid end up
dying in jail or what?
No. So, what happens is he
ends up serving 29 years.
Henry Dunham's wife comes back and says
that she can't confirm for
sure that he did do it.
After 29 years.
After 29 years,
so he gets a pardon and he gets out.
Wow.
And this is Plu 29 years later
when he gets released.
Now, how old is Plu when he gets out?
He's 53.
All right. So he get's pardoned.
Do they look at anybody else as a suspect?
No.
It's still, for all practical purposes...
- Unsolved?
- ...unsolved.
This dead guy,
someone's calling him derogatory names.
What do they say?
They're saying that he's gay and stuff.
What are you shaking your head about?
I don't understand how this
could be such a violent place.
It's too much.
Makes me feel very
uncomfortable and panicked.
I feel very, very sad, like I want to cry.
One of the first things I do on a case
is reach out to local historians.
Usually I don't turn up too much,
but in this case,
a local genealogist tells me
that the man that built
Dan's hotel has a wild story
and I'm definitely gonna want to hear it.
Well, Beth, thanks for meeting me.
I appreciate that.
You mentioned on the phone
that the guy that originally built the hotel
on the property I'm investigating
had an interesting story behind him?
Yes. His name was Henry Hover.
He was a farmer.
This is a photo that we
found when he was farming.
He... you can see he's at
the end of the photo here.
Okay. So, how does he go from being a farmer
to building a hotel?
He started amassing that property in 1880,
and it took him 17 years,
but in 1897, he got the hotel.
These are the photos of
the hotel that we have.
He... he just stuck to his vision.
Okay. So now he has his dream hotel.
What happens?
Does he live there happily ever after?
I mean, what's the story?
No. Henry just has one
tragedy after another.
1897, the year the hotel's built,
he loses a son Ira who's sick.
He dies of unknown causes.
In 1901,
his wife loses a child in childbirth.
The biggest tragedy happened in 1902,
when he lost his 3-year-old son, Elmer,
to an accident.
Elmer is playing in the hotel.
They work there. They live there.
He's trying to climb on top of a bean sack
to get up to the counter.
His foot slips and his
little chin hits the counter,
and broke his neck.
Within 20 minutes, little Elmer is gone.
So what happens after all this?
He runs into financial trouble,
and in 1906, sells the hotel for a loss.
Okay.
He dies at the age of 68
after being confined in bed
for a year from tuberculosis.
- You're kidding me?
- Nope.
So what happened with the hotel?
It burned down in the 1920s,
and the hotel you see today is a rebuild,
but it looks very similar to the original.
I want to say that he... owned this place
or was in charge of this place,
um, or thinks he is still.
The workaholic guy?
Yes.
Do you know anything about
what he was like in life?
He's, like, between 55 and 60.
He came from a... a hardworking background,
and he feels he did well
until this happened.
He's still acting like he is working.
He just goes and he just
does what he did every day.
That's what makes him feel comfortable.
Beth mentioned that Dan's
building ended up burning down.
Obviously,
I need to find out exactly what happened.
I'm heading over to meet
with a local firefighter.
He says the cause of the fire
is still a mystery to this day.
Well, Chief, thanks for meeting me.
I appreciate it.
So now, the expert I talked to said
that the hotel I'm investigating
burnt down in the '20s,
- and you said it was true.
- Absolutely.
August 18, 1921,
the fire completely destroyed the hotel.
Okay.
This is one of the articles.
What was the story with it?
The fire started in the attic area
and then it went
and it slowly started to
burn across the attic.
Okay. Now, what about casualties, anything?
It's my understanding
that there was roughly 50 people there
when the fire started, and not a one of them
suffered an injury or a death.
Okay.
So, they were able to get everybody out...
- Yes...
- before the building collapsed.
All right. So, do we know, Chief,
exactly what even started the fire?
The articles I've read said
spontaneous combustion.
There was no electrical wiring in the attic,
so they ruled that out
and they went to spontaneous combustion.
All right. So, in your opinion,
though, what do you think?
I don't know that we'll ever know.
There's been a lot of
things that have happened.
It's kind of crazy.
There was a fire, but I don't know
if it was actually this structure
or if there was another structure.
It's residual, but it happened.
I saw several dead people on my walk,
but the workaholic is
the most advanced entity.
I'm meeting with an artist
to describe how he appeared in life.
He's probably between
55 and 60 years of age.
He has a very thick, full head of gray hair.
His nose has been probably
broken a few times.
Yes. That's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our
findings to each other
and our clients for the first time.
Well, Amy, I'd like you to meet Dan.
He is the owner of this restaurant/hotel
for about eight years now.
Activity here is bad and it's getting worse,
and it's hurting his business
and if it keeps going like this,
he's gonna have to shut the place down.
Leslie here has worked here for 17 years?
She's had ton of experiences,
and I kind of think she's
numb to it at this point.
Now, Kathy lives directly across the street.
She's been here for 15 years.
She actually worked in the
restaurant for six months.
She thinks that whatever's here is evil,
and that Dan and his
staff could be in danger.
So, now that Amy knows a little
bit about what's going on,
I'm gonna have her talk about her walk.
So one of the first things that I got
when I got out of the vehicle
was that there had been a fire here.
I was smelling it and tasting it,
and I felt like people were
breathing in the smoke,
and I didn't know if it was this structure
or a structure nearby.
Well, you hit that pretty much on the head.
Now, the hotel opened in 1897.
It was opened up as the Hotel Ormond.
But back on August 18, 1921,
the building caught on fire.
It started in the attic.
They tried dousing it out,
but you know what?
They had no shot.
Now, nobody died in that fire,
but there were 50 people
staying here at the time,
but they all got out safely,
and I have an article here about it.
Now, two years later, the hotel was rebuilt
and that's the building we're in right now.
That makes sense.
One of the first conscious entities
that I encountered was on the first floor.
Um, so he was really strange,
because what I saw him doing
was, like, burrowing under the ground.
And he's, like,
always kicking, uh, the floor.
Then he was showing me, like,
spinning the structure.
I think structurally, you know,
it has issues all the time
because he's kind of [bleep]
with the whole thing.
But what I saw as a direct result of that
was causing issues with, like, plumbing
or electricity or things breaking.
Dan, the first day in this place,
you had issues with the water, right?
Yes. As I walked in and
walked past the dishwasher,
and stopped and turned and
looked at it for some reason,
and, um,
it squirted me right in the face twice.
I mean, you've been here the longest.
Long time.
So, as far as the structural issues,
has this been ongoing?
Yeah.
I mean, some of it you chalk
up to it's an old building.
But we have a lot of electrical glitches
and computer glitches.
That happens a lot.
Interesting.
Okay. So what else did you see?
During my walk, I came across
a couple of murder scenes,
and one of them involved
a female in the bar area.
So I walk over there
and this woman, like,
grabbed on to my lower legs
and was, like,
dragging herself on the floor.
She was beaten.
There were three men that
were involved at least.
She knew one of them most certainly.
I kept hearing, like,
while all this chaos is going on,
like, the guys were laughing.
It was excruciatingly painful.
The next murder victim I encountered
was a male outside
who was stuck in his death state.
I started feeling like a
really sharp pain in my chest,
and so I think he was stabbed.
And I'm hearing these men clearly,
like, yelling at me,
like, horrible, really awful things.
And I think there was some
kind of issue with him
where these males might have thought
that he was a homosexual or
something of that nature.
There was a double murder
that had strong connection to this place.
It happened in 1887.
A guy by the name of Joseph Plu lived here.
Now, I got a photo of him.
Now, he lived next door to
a guy named Henry Dunham.
And now, Henry lived on the property
with his wife and 20-month-old daughter.
So he needed to hire somebody
to work on the farm for him,
and he hired this guy.
Now, on February 7, 1887,
this is when a brutal crime takes place.
Henry was stabbed repeatedly.
They find Henry in the barn area outside.
He's stabbed to death
and his body's mutilated
because he had hogs on the property
that basically went to town on him,
and they ate him.
Now, inside,
his 20-month-old daughter was also murdered.
It was pretty brutal.
She was cut from ear to ear,
practically almost right to the point
where her head was cut off.
His wife Lucy was stabbed
several times and beaten,
but she survived actually.
This is where it gets interesting.
She told the cops that
there were three attackers,
and one of them was Plu.
She's like, "Yeah.
It was him and two other guys,"
that she couldn't identify.
He's the only one that gets charged.
29 years later, Lucy comes back and says,
"I'm not sure Plu was at the crime scene."
This is after the guy's
in jail for 29 years.
So why would she retract that?
Your guess is as good as mine.
It's still a mystery to this day, this case.
This is actually a picture
of Plu when he came out,
29 years later.
This is, uh... this is him.
Did you know about any of this?
'Cause you seem upset about it,
and I know it's a terrible story.
When she spoke about the woman,
um... I've gotten feelings about,
uh, a lady, um, that was, uh, raped
and... and murdered.
So I felt it.
You know, it was, uh,
by more than just one person.
Her spirit had came through me
and talked with me
and, uh... um, she... she's,
like, telling me
that she was forced to retract that.
Oh, interesting. Okay.
Well, let me ask you a question.
Do you think she has abilities?
Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yes, I do.
It seems to me that she wants people
to know exactly what happened.
She wants, you know, the truth to be told.
I think it was him.
They raped her.
All right.
So what else happened on your walk?
One of the people that I encountered,
he seemed to me to be
the most physically
present dead person here.
And he came off very much
as like a workaholic,
but when I went upstairs, very different.
He was like, "Get the [bleep] out of there.
This is... this is my... my space."
One of the ways that he
sometimes shows himself
is as a tall, shadow-type figure.
Now, you've seen a guy
in the window upstairs, though, right?
- A tall guy?
- Yes.
And when I've seen him,
he was just, like, looking down
each side of the street as to see if he...
he's looking for someone,
like a lookout-type of a guy.
Mm-hmm.
You saw it leaving work
one day when nobody's here.
Yeah.
There was nobody in the
building when I left.
Mm-hmm.
Did you get any sense
of who this guy might have
been when he was alive?
He worked his whole life
to do well for himself,
and he felt like he did do well for himself.
I thought that he either owned this place
or was in charge of this place.
And, uh, he thinks that he's still...
- Running it...
- running it.
Uh, I got that he was
between 55 and 60 years old.
His moods seemed to be
very drastic ups and downs,
ups and downs.
And he's still like that.
Well,
it makes me think of the guy Henry Hover
that originally built this place.
Now, he was a hard worker,
he was a workaholic.
He was a farmer.
In 1880,
he started buying little pieces of land.
Took him 17 years to buy the
property and build this hotel,
which was his dream.
I have the only known photo of this guy,
and it's not a very good one.
You mentioned he was an emotional wreck.
Well, he lost his son Ira at the age of 6
from unknown causes from what we can tell.
1901, his wife lost a baby boy at birth,
and then in 1902,
the biggest tragedy happened
to this guy, his 3-year-old son,
Elmer, fell off a bag of beans.
He was playing in the hotel,
and the fall broke the poor kid's neck.
And he basically died about 20 minutes later
after they found him.
To make matters worse for this guy, in 1906,
he comes into some hard times financially
and has to sell this place at a great loss.
Now, did you get a good look at the guy?
Yes, I did.
And I had a sketch done of him.
Okay.
Take a look at this.
The sketch looks exactly
like this man right here.
Looks just like him.
- This sketch you did looks just like Plu...
- Right.
The more I'm looking at it.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah. It all makes sense. Okay.
- This sketch you did looks just like Plu...
- Right.
The more I'm looking at it.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah. It all makes sense. Okay.
It matches, like,
the murder that he did on that guy,
the things he was saying.
Yeah. It totally makes sense.
So do you think this guy Plu
is the guy that you ran
into on the second floor?
- Yeah.
- Okay. 'Cause it makes sense.
And the second and third floor for sure.
Yeah.
So how'd this guy Plu make you think
he was the workaholic on the top floors?
Because there's so much
residual information,
I feel like he's able to,
you know, almost disguise himself
within all of this information that exists.
The third floor, the second floor,
and the underneath,
I think is all the same person.
Okay. So, the guy that you encountered
- that's kicking the fl...
- Yeah.
- Making the pipes burst.
- Yes.
The aggressive guy on the
second floor we think is Plu.
Yeah.
And the third floor guy... Which is Plu.
- Is all the same guy.
- Yeah. It's all the same guy.
But now it seems to be
getting more physical.
So you think this guy
wants people out of here?
Yes.
I see this guy taking pillows
and putting them over living people's faces
and trying to kill them,
but he's made it look like a heart attack
or things like that.
So he's capable of killing living people?
Yes.
He'll, like, target people he doesn't like,
like drug addicts and homosexuals.
You know, Kathy,
earlier you mentioned to me that you're gay.
Is it okay if we talk about that?
Yes.
Now, is it bothering you that
he might have been targeting you
because of your lifestyle?
Now it is.
I think he was targeting
me not only because of that
but also the fact that I was able to connect
with... with the lady,
and so I'm thinking he's like,
"Not only is she gay,
but she also can communicate
with these other spirits,
and now I'm... I'm threatened."
Dan,
when you said it was getting worse here,
you weren't kidding.
Well, Dan, we know one thing for sure.
Kathy was right. This place is dangerous.
But the big question is,
can you make it safe for your
employees and your guests?
For that answer,
I'm gonna turn it over to my partner, Amy.
The first concern I have
is that I think some of the
activity might get... bad,
and I don't think he's going
to be happy about the fact
that all his cards are on the table.
I am very nervous about
how he's going to react,
so I definitely would suggest
that people not stay here
until it can be dealt with.
I'm certainly shaken.
All right.
So how do we get rid of this [bleep]
It needs to be, like,
a massive hit against him.
I would like there to be a psychic knower
to come with two male mediums,
and they all need to work at the same time.
The psychic knower is
going to be taking care
of the residual that's here,
and the mediums are going to be dealing
with the conscious dead that are here,
and there's a lot.
And I want two badass male mediums,
very aggressive, very strong.
Why?
He'll get intimidated a little
and he needs to be intimidated.
Also, I don't want any other
living people in the building
when they're doing this,
'cause I also feel that
they could be attacked.
All right.
And now, once that's done,
the things will be okay here?
It'll be very quiet, void of everything.
It'll feel very, very, very different.
I'm just... I'm... I'm thinking
that I'm gonna miss this place for a while.
Once this [bleep] out of here,
she'll be safe to come back.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Yes.
Thank you.
So you're gonna take our advice, I assume.
Absolutely.
Can't wait to get rid of him.
It won't be easy removing the dead man
wreaking havoc on this restaurant/hotel,
but I believe if Dan follows my advice,
the evil here will be banished,
keeping Dan and his employees
and guests safe from harm.