[ Gasp ]
NARRATOR: Tonight on
"Dead Files: Revisited"...
That's never happened
before.
NARRATOR:...A second look at
some of Amy and Steve's
most terrifying cases.
You got to get out of here.
New information.
It was like hell's bells
in here.
NARRATOR: Startling revelations.
Is this gonna be something
that somebody dies from?
NARRATOR: First, a return
to Forester, Michigan...
I feel like I'm being kicked out
of my own home.
...where a sinister presence...
She's **** nuts.
She's totally lost it.
...stalks the living.
I feel it watching me at night.
NARRATOR: Then...
Something bad happened
in there.
...we travel back to
Buchanan, Virginia..
I've actually been choked
before.
...where the dead...
The floors
are covered in blood.
...hold the living hostage.
She wants the house
demolished.
NARRATOR: Have these desperate
families faced their fears?
So, are you guys gonna follow
Amy's advice?
...Or does their
nightmare continue?
I summon the muertos
in this home.
Go into the world of ancestors.
Be gone!
It's really bad in here.
My name is Amy Allan.
Something is not right.
I see dead people.
This person might have been
a serial killer.
I speak to dead people.
You get those chills.
And they speak to me.
He is darkness.
He is evil.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
I think she broke her neck.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
Are you telling me the truth?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I think the devil
is down here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who the hell
would do this?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
Who is he looking to kill?
We uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
You need to get out of here
right now.
Or time to get out.
It was, like, endless darkness.
STEVE:
When a mother in Forester,
Michigan, asked for our help,
it was a plea I couldn't ignore.
She and her husband
had their share
of unexplained experiences,
but when activity started
affecting their children,
that's when things got serious.
STEVE: So, Chrystal,
what's going on?
We have been experiencing
noises, voices.
Objects have moved.
Shadows.
I feel like it's
progressively getting worse.
CHRYSTAL: It's one thing for
my husband or myself
to experience things,
'cause we're adults.
We know how to process it,
but little kids don't.
So, when they started telling me
they were seeing things,
I became concerned, like,
we should probably
take care of this.
Chrystal, why is it
so important for you to stay?
I am attached to this home.
I inherited it
from my parents.
They were making the house
in a bed-and-breakfast.
So, obviously,
it's emotional for you.
[ Voice breaking ]
It's very emotional.
I feel like
I'm being kicked out.
[ Inhales sharply ]
Kicked out of my own home.
AMY:
As we arrived at the location,
my whole body felt tense.
Just an hour before,
I'd had a disturbing encounter
while preparing for my walk.
And now I was really nervous
about what was waiting for me
inside that home.
There's this guy,
and all of a sudden,
like, I was him.
That's never happened before
in an opening,
where I was...the dead person.
So, I was pushing him out,
but I couldn't, so I stopped.
- Stopped the opening,
you mean? - Yes.
As a rule,
I refuse to let entities
take control of my body,
but that man's energy
was strong,
and honestly, I didn't know
if I could fight him off.
I'm getting a sharp pain
right here.
Uh...
Getting a really sharp pain
right here.
****
One day, I heard a door slam
upstairs.
[ Door slams ]
Literally the foundation
of the house shook.
Wow.
Now, was anybody upstairs?
No.
I felt like it was
a power struggle
between whatever was here
and us.
Like, they were trying to take
over the house,
and I just -- I don't want that.
I just want it to be gone.
Well, Chrystal.
Amy can turn around and tell you
you got to get out of here.
You got to be prepared
for that.
It's my mother's dream
to make this place
a bed-and-breakfast,
and I want to continue on
with that.
So, there's a girl right there.
She's not happy.
She likes to play games.
In my opening,
I saw this hallway,
and all the doors were opening
and closing at the same time.
Dead people have nothing
but time on their hands,
and that girl had grown bored.
So, the way she decided
to entertain herself
was to mess with the living.
Do you know, like,
why she does that?
She likes to mess around.
She's **** nuts.
She's totally lost it.
STEVE: Chrystal was worried
about their family's safety,
but firm that they stand
their ground.
Her husband, Mike,
on the other hand,
looked to me like he was
ready to walk out the door.
All of a sudden, I see
this big, black, massive shadow
just go right across
my dining-room wall.
Did it freak you out at all?
Yeah.
I didn't even know
what to do.
But after talking
to their oldest daughter,
it was clear
that whatever was in that house
was tearing that family
apart.
So what about yourself?
I just wake up in the middle
of the night sometimes.
I feel like
I'm being watched.
I get an eerie feeling.
So, what do you think
is watching you?
I have seen
a tall, black shadowy person.
The first time I had seen it,
it kind of caught me off guard
'cause I had seen it
out of the corner of my eye.
After that,
it was hard to sleep at night.
I felt like something evil
was in my room,
and my emotions were just being
toyed with.
I never see its face.
It's just like
a black blob.
I've noticed my parents' moods
have changed, as well.
So,
it's affecting everybody?
- It's affecting everyone,
not just me. - Okay.
I feel bad in this room.
I don't like it.
I feel dark.
Like, corners
are really, really bad.
[ Sighs ]
So, there's two
of these very tall, dark,
solid, perfectly round things.
Do you know if they can interact
with anybody living?
I feel like they can, yeah.
They're trying
to get something.
[ Gasp ]
NARRATOR: Next...
Here is
her death certificate.
Steve cracks the code
to a mysterious death.
She wouldn't have lasted long.
And in our second
investigation...
I'm in, like,
a lot of pain here.
NARRATOR:
...Amy is under attack.
Are you afraid of her?
I'm not really allowed
to talk about it.
STEVE: Our client, Chrystal, had
mentioned a rumor
about a local woman
who had died.
At first, I didn't think
too much of it.
Chasing urban legends usually
leads straight to a dead end.
But allegedly, this went down
right across the street
from her house,
and digging a little deeper,
it turned out
that this tragic story
was much more than just
an old wives' tale.
My client mentioned a legend
about this girl, Minnie Quay,
that killed herself.
I need to find out from you
if it's true or not.
Oh, it's true.
Here is
her death certificate.
Suicide by drowning.
So, what can you tell me
about her?
You know, Minnie
was a 15-year-old girl
who was boy-crazy.
She fell in love
with a sailor.
She would
secretly meet him.
And her parents found out.
And they forbade her
to see this sailor.
When the shipping season
reopened again in April,
she found out
that he was lost at sea.
She was devastated.
And so, on April 27, 1876,
eyewitnesses said that
she walked down the length
of the pier
and jumped into the frigid,
icy water of Lake Huron.
Now, are we talking about
the pier a few hundred yards...
...from the house
I'm investigating? - Correct.
It's painful
to jump in icy water.
And once the core temperature
begins to drop,
the systems begin to fail.
AMY:
I'm just hearing this woman.
There's a woman crying.
During a walk, sometimes
I just have to let the dead
lead the way around the house.
And in this case,
they guided me out of the house
and across the street towards
the water.
It's just a girl.
To be honest, part of me wished
it were possible
for me to jump in there
and help her.
The girl who's sad is lost,
and then this woman's
yelling, yelling, yelling
for her.
Lots of people are yelling.
I can't -- I can't reach it.
I can't, uh...
breathe.
I think she's dying.
STEVE: As I combed through
the archives,
I uncovered a series of
mysterious deaths in Forester.
Strange enough, they all
came back to one name --
Harrison Cooper, the man
who owned Chrystal's property.
And once I sat down
with a local genealogist,
I learned that piece of land had
death written all over it.
STEVE: I came across
the name Harrison Cooper.
And I know he lived in
the property I'm investigating.
He lived there
with his wife, Elizabeth,
and they had a daughter.
- Her name was Emma Jay.
- Okay.
And then the fire of 1881
wiped out everything.
A week after that,
Elizabeth had a heart attack
and died.
So now, Harrison
is left with his daughter.
Oh, geez.
Now, how does he move on?
What happened?
His daughter Emma
and her husband lived with them.
Then, in 1903,
another tragedy struck.
Emma gave birth,
but the baby was stillborn.
- Now loses a grandchild.
- Yes.
There's a woman crying.
Real, real, like, sobbing.
She's sobbing.
And then somebody says,
"Well, the baby died."
It's horrible.
She's holding the dead baby.
She's, like, petting it.
And then she's got blood
all over her dress.
This lady, she's fading.
But she doesn't want
to fade away.
For that woman, the memory of
her infant's death
was the only remaining part
of her humanity,
and even though it pained her
to focus on that moment in time,
she just wasn't ready to let go.
She actually doesn't want to
because she likes
to be around those memories,
even though they're bad.
So she's trying to hold on.
She doesn't want to leave.
NARRATOR: Coming up...
Is he dangerous?
What happened after
the investigation?
I was prepared
for the worst.
It is time for you to go.
Move forward to the light.
STEVE:
Amy, this is Chrystal,
Brittany, their daughter,
and Mike, her husband.
CHRYSTAL:
The night of the reveal,
I didn't know
what Amy was gonna say,
but I was prepared
for the worst.
Chrystal's mom had
a dream of turning this place
into a bed-and-breakfast,
and she'd like to do the same.
I went across the street.
and all of a sudden, I felt
like somebody had just died.
I'm feeling this girl,
and I'm hearing this woman
calling,
"Where are you?
Where are you?"
And when I came
back into the house
there was a girl,
and she was very much
the black sheep of the family.
Who does that sound like?
Yeah. Minnie Quay.
Huh?
It was a town legend
that she killed herself.
She was 15 years old.
She threw herself in the river...
...because she was in a relationship
with a merchant sailor. - Oh, man.
But the father
was very strict.
He thought this sailor
was beneath her.
She was capable of having
physical interaction.
And she likes to get reactions
for her behaviors.
One time the door slammed
upstairs
so hard the whole house shook.
Oh, my gosh.
It's the girl.
Could that be Minnie Quay,
the same girl?
I think
it very well could be.
CHRYSTAL: This has been told
to us since we were kids.
And to be perfectly honest,
I actually really don't care
if she's here,
but she needs to behave.
If she's causing issues,
then yeah, she needs to go.
When I went upstairs,
I heard this woman sobbing --
really crying.
I heard someone say,
"Well, the baby died."
I saw blood all over her.
Ah, geez.
This guy, Harrison Cooper,
when he moved to this property,
his daughter, Emma Jay,
she wound up
having a stillborn baby here.
The baby's probably buried on
the property.
So you're saying
you think that it's Emma?
It would seem like it.
CHRYSTAL: I just felt sad
that Emma was still here,
trapped here, and grieving over
the loss of her baby.
That's when I knew we needed
to do something.
So I'm doing my opening,
and there's this man
that came into my body
and meshed.
What did he look like?
A big guy, very husky.
I've seen a man.
It's a dark shadow.
[ Sobs ]
Are you okay?
Yeah? All right.
[ Sniffles ]
- Is he dangerous?
- Yes.
Say, you're sleeping.
The distinction
between reality and dreams
can get blurred.
She's having nightmares.
I do.
BRITTANY: When Amy said
that she had seen a man,
it caught me off guard because
I see a male figure,
and I got upset because
I was almost happy
she had seen the same thing
so she could tell me
if it was dangerous.
I went into a room
with a pink bed.
Then I'm looking,
and I see these two dark things
in each corner.
They're very tall,
and I felt like
they were trying
to reach something
or someone.
[ Sobs ]
I see it.
I've seen it watch me
and my mom in the doorway.
[ Sniffles ]
And I feel it
watch me at night.
I did sketch what I saw.
It's these
two black things.
They're looking
at whoever's on the bed,
and they're
on each side of the room.
Now...
does this look similar
to what you saw in the doorway?
BRITTANY: Yeah.
These things
can make you feel sick
and dizzy and nauseous,
and this one is sadness.
So it's making us
feel like that?
Oh, yeah.
So, when you're seeing
the dark mass
bopping around the house,
I think that's the man.
- Harrison Cooper?
- Yes.
And then this one is aspects
of the woman who lost the child.
That's his daughter.
Yes.
Okay.
And what they want to do is,
they want to grow.
What happens if they grow?
These guys
can cause a lot of harm.
These things feed off
of the living person's energy.
- Me, or my parents, too?
- Yeah. You.
CHRYSTAL: I didn't really know
how scared Brittany was,
but she turned
completely white.
It's creepy.
Who wants that in their house?
Nobody wants to be told that the
people that used to live here
are still lurking around
and watching you.
The big question is,
is it safe for you to stay,
and can you fulfill
your mom's dream?
Well, the first thing
is that you do need a medium
to come back
and help to move Minnie on.
After doing that,
that medium needs to go up
into your room
and deal with
this funky emotional energy
that needs to be contained
and removed from the house.
The other thing
would be for you
to go ahead and sleep
in another area of the house.
I won't sleep in there.
I wouldn't sleep in your room.
Now, you're gonna follow
Amy's advice, obviously.
[ Swing creaking ]
CHRYSTAL:
After Steve and Amy left,
it was like hell's bells
in here.
The lights were turning on.
We were hearing strange voices.
The activity was so predominant,
it was awful.
Coming from
a religious background,
you're really not supposed to
mess around with this stuff,
but I knew that I needed to call
another medium in
to do what Amy said.
I don't think Brittany
really felt comfortable
with the medium here.
I was relieved that there was
something that we could do,
but this is really scary,
and I didn't want to be here.
She just didn't know what
to expect, so she opted out.
Minnie, I need to speak
with you.
CHRYSTAL: The medium came in
and burned some herbs
and offered Minnie flowers
as a way to get her to leave.
There is nothing for you
in this house but darkness.
It is time for you to go.
Move forward to the light.
And then we went in
Brittany's room
and asked the spirits
to leave.
There is no reason to be
in this home of darkness.
There was a little part of me
that thinks this might not work,
and that we're going to be
dealing with this forever.
There is nothing in this house
for you.
It's over 100 years,
it's time.
Go to the light.
As the medium was clearing
the house,
you could feel a release
in the presence.
You could almost feel the fog
lifted from the home.
Now that the medium
has come and gone,
I feel comfortable being
in my home for the first time.
CHRYSTAL:
Things are well here.
Brittany is sleeping in her bed.
And I feel relief in my own home
and comfortable.
I just hope now that my family
can move forward
and live peacefully and happily
in our house
and continue on with
what our plans are
in opening
the bed and breakfast.
AMY: I understand Chrystal's
concerns about their future.
After what her family's endured,
it's going to take time
before they'll feel comfortable
in that home.
But now that the dark energy
has been removed,
I'm sure it won't be long
until Chrystal can carry out
her mother's dream.
STEVE:
Whenever I think about our
clients in Buchanan, Virginia,
I get a heavy heart.
All that couple wanted to do
was raise their family in peace,
but the odds were
stacked against them.
And the deeper Amy and I got
into their case,
the more I questioned
whether or not
this was gonna end with
a positive outcome.
STEVE:
You know, Tysha,
this kitchen
doesn't look lived in.
What's the story?
The activity in the house
just became outrageous,
and it just became too much
for our family,
and we decided to build
a modular house three years ago.
Did it get better
when you moved over there?
No, not at all.
What happened while
you were living in this house?
We have everything from, like,
seeing apparitions and noises.
I've actually been choked
before.
TYSHA: Things are just
amplifying to a point that,
I don't even want to know
what possibly could happen.
Honestly, I'm just afraid
that it's gonna be something
that somebody dies from.
On the phone, you said this
was affecting your health.
Yes, sir.
My pain
was just so amplified,
I was getting to where
I couldn't function at all.
Oh, geez. All right.
Did you and your husband
ever consider
moving off the property?
Financially, it would be
impossible for us to move.
And I would never be able
to do that.
- It would break my heart.
- Okay.
AMY:
As we drove up to the location,
I started to feel
a bit panicked.
We were
in the middle of nowhere,
yet there were dead people
everywhere.
That's not normal,
but then again, nothing was
normal about this walk.
This place is really busy.
There's, like, a ton of ****
people around that are dead.
Like, how many?
I would count, like, 15 people
that were walking by.
There's a lot of pain
and despair here.
I think something bad
happened in there.
It could have killed me.
NARRATOR: Next...
She's not
a very tolerant person.
NARRATOR:...the battle of
Amy's life begins.
Are you afraid of her?
I'm not really allowed
to talk about it.
STEVE: Our client, Tysha,
had reached the end of her rope.
She was convinced that something
in her home
wanted to harm her family,
and neither of us knew it
at the time, but she was right.
This is probably
the worst place.
I just do not
come down here.
I have terrible feelings --
just dread,
sadness, pain.
We were told, actually,
that slaves were kept down here,
as well.
TYSHA:
Ever since we moved down here,
there has been so much activity
in the basement.
I had contacted everybody
from an ordained minister
to the Native American people,
and even other different
paranormal teams,
and nobody could just
get to the bottom
of what was actually going on.
Have you ever seen anything
down here?
I've seen apparitions.
Yes, sir.
I've seen a man
and he just kind of
walked across the floor
and just disappeared.
- All right, you know what?
Let's get the hell out of here. - Okay.
I see a lot of black men
who are dead, who are lined up,
and somebody's
throwing water on them.
Like, just throwing water
on their bodies.
That was a sight
I'll never forget.
Just another awful reminder
of how cruel humanity can be.
And while I tried to stomach
what was happening around me,
the person in charge
started to make her move.
In particular, there's
a woman -- a black woman --
who's splashing the water
on them.
I don't think there are people
here who like white people.
Like, "Get out."
[ Door creaks ]
MATTHEW:
Could she be dangerous?
I think so.
STEVE: Tysha had a list
of encounters a mile long.
So many, that you might think
she blames everything bad
in her life on the paranormal.
But after seeing how the events
in that house
had also traumatized
her husband,
I think any doubts about Tysha
were put to rest.
So, what have you experienced
up here?
Well,
we put all new drywall in,
and we had it
stacked up against the wall.
And it started to shift
over onto me.
And it all came down
and smashed me down.
That's a lot of weight.
And excruciating pain.
And my son had walked in
right as that was going on.
Could have killed me.
It could have killed him.
TROY:
I was scared for my family.
If you're in a situation where
something could happen to you
or your kids, that's the worst.
I mean, I've got scars
on my body to prove it.
Well, I'm hoping that
we can get some answers
to what's going on.
Yeah, before something bad
happens to one of the kids.
Okay.
AMY: A black woman
hates me so much.
[ Sighs ]
I'm in, like,
a lot of pain here.
Very, very, very painful.
Are you afraid of her?
I'm not really allowed
to talk about it.
Why can't you talk
about it?
She has
a way of preventing it.
To this day, I'm still amazed
at what happened.
On rare occasions, the dead
will take control of my body,
but never my mind.
But with that woman,
I didn't have a choice.
She says, basically...
that she's given warnings.
What kind of warnings
has she given?
Like, there's been some kind
of physical abuse
towards the adults.
Like, hitting,
making them feel pain suddenly.
She's not
a very tolerant person.
[ Chuckles ]
TROY:
I was relaxing on the sofa,
and I seen
a big, big mist right here --
a blackish-colored mist.
And I've seen that same mist
throughout the house.
Do you ever think about
just moving?
This place had been in my family
for so, so long,
and I've fought tooth and nail,
to keep the property.
And you have
the two boys you want to...
...pass the property on to?
[ Sniffles ]
Now, what are you hoping for
at the end of the investigation?
Just to get
straightened out.
[ Sighs ]
Figure out what's going on.
[ Sniffles ]
- [ Voice breaking ] I need a minute.
- Okay.
NARRATOR: Next...
Sickness and death.
That's it.
NARRATOR:...the home's
disturbing past is exposed.
The floors
are covered in blood.
STEVE: Without question, Tysha
and Troy's home had a dark past.
Back in the 1800s,
it was a working tobacco farm
and home to at least 60 slaves.
And the owner, Nicholas Burks,
should have been thrown in jail
for the way he treated them.
But according
to the genealogy records,
it turned out that Mr. Burks was
nothing but a hypocrite.
What do you make of
the five or six young kids
with the same name
as the plantation owner?
It was more common
than people like to think.
One of the five children is
someone who's mixed race,
and that suggests that he was
the plantation owner's son.
- Now, was it consensual?
- Not necessarily.
Is there any way
of figuring out
who might have been
the mother of this kid?
There is someone.
- It's a woman named Louisa.
- Okay.
And she was 45 years old
the same time that he was 18...
...listed together,
so the age range works. - Okay.
And they were also recorded
as running away
during the same period,
possibly together.
Now, what kind of a woman would
even take a risk like that?
A brave one.
The domestic slave trade
was at its height.
So, she witnessed a huge export
of her family and friends.
The risk of being separated
from her son
might have been enough
to make it worth leaving.
AMY: There are so many emotions
with this black woman.
She is just showing me, like,
that the only good thing in life
were -- were children.
That was the only thing
that made her happy.
She didn't want
anybody else to be here,
so she did things to try...
to set that in motion
when she was alive.
After my last encounter with
the woman,
the thought of even being
in the same room as her
was absolutely terrifying,
but I had no choice.
My job is to get answers
for my clients,
even if that means putting
myself in harm's way.
[ Sighs ]
What's going on?
She doesn't want me
down here.
I'm in, like,
a lot of pain here.
STEVE: After the Civil War,
slavery might have ended,
but the tragedies on
that property kept piling up.
And the more facts I uncovered,
the more I couldn't help
but think
that any person who lived
in that house was cursed.
Nathan, what were you able
to find out
about this guy,
Starke Robinson?
We found out that he was
a plantation owner.
And, in 1870,
he buys the property
that you're investigating now.
Now, I also noticed through
the paperwork, he had some loss.
Yes.
His wife, Ellen, in 1871--
she died of complications
that occurred during childbirth.
Not long after,
Starke marries
her younger sister, Elizabeth.
Okay.
And then
she lived until 1904.
Starke actually ended up
outliving
7 of his 14 children.
Four died in childbirth.
So, this guy Starke
kind of had a rough go.
Mm-hmm.
AMY: I'm getting
these two little white ladies,
and they're sisters.
MATTHEW: Do you know
what kind of connection
these women might have
to this location?
I feel like they owned it
at some point.
One of them is young.
She has dead children.
And then somebody said,
"Well, you know, in the end,
there's just blood, anyway."
Sickness and death.
That's it.
There were so many dead people
on that property,
I had lost count.
But no matter who I talked to,
the message was always the same.
I know
there's other deaths here
because they're saying, like,
"The floors
are covered in blood."
For whatever reason, all
the people that lived here...
...met with darkness
and tragedy.
NARRATOR: Next...
She wants the house
demolished.
...The terrifying reveal.
It's sickening to me.
And could the clients...
Now we're the ones that are
being tortured and punished.
NARRATOR:
...stop evil in its tracks?
MAN: Remove this curse.
Go into the world of ancestors.
Be gone!
STEVE: Amy, I'd like you to meet
Troy and Tysha.
TYSHA: When I first met Amy,
I was terrified
of what she was gonna tell us,
and I just had a gut-wrenching
kind of feeling
that it wasn't gonna be your
average paranormal activity,
and I kind of knew it was
gonna be pretty traumatic.
When I was upstairs,
I did meet two sisters.
They owned this property
at some point in time.
One of the sisters
had children who died.
And I think
that if people see them,
they're just kind of like
a mist.
The mist I've seen has been
kind of a black-color mist.
Okay.
STEVE: There was a guy
named Starke Robinson
who bought the house in 1870.
He moved here
with his wife, Ellen,
who, within a year,
actually passed away.
About five years later,
he married her sister,
Elizabeth,
who died in this house.
This guy had 14 children,
seven of them which died
before he did.
Geez.
What else did you see?
So, when I went
into the basement,
I saw 4 to 10 black men
that were dead.
Back in its heyday,
this was a tobacco plantation.
Hmm.
And the basement
of this house
was slaves' living quarters.
To tell you
how they were treated and --
I know
how they were treated.
I sketched
that scene in the basement.
There were
several dead black men laying.
There's two black women.
They're pouring water
on the bodies.
Take a look at that.
Wow.
It's sad to see that
in the picture.
It's sickening to me.
It was such a powerful scene,
and seeing that sketch
flooded me
with so many different emotions
because now we're
the ones being picked on
and tortured and punished.
Well, the thing is,
is that the larger lady
is still down there.
She doesn't want
anybody in there,
especially
if they're white.
I'd never felt hatred like that
from an entity in my life.
And then she showed me
children
and said that they were
the only good thing in her life.
Of a slave that used to live
here by the name of Louisa.
She had this child that was
half black, half white,
and they took a big chance
and they ran away.
Her presence
is extremely dangerous
and incredibly powerful.
She's also trying
to give you guys warnings
to get out.
TROY:
Yeah, I was really nervous,
and heart beating fast because
this is my house.
This is a place that I've been
in since I was a little boy,
and while it's under my watch,
I'm not abandoning my place.
She is
the hoodoo practitioner.
What is hoodoo?
Hoodoo comes from Africa.
It is not a religion,
but a system to place spells.
And she put them into place
while she was alive
to ensure things would go
the way she wanted them to
in death.
'Cause hoodoo
is all about gaining power.
And now she's got
all this power --
she's got all these dead people
that she controls.
What does she want
from them?
She wants the house
demolished.
That ain't gonna happen.
All of the dead
want it gone.
So, how many ghosts
do we have?
I would say hundreds.
We've tried to protect
this place,
and everybody's tried to be
respectful to the place.
You're white.
She won't listen
to what you're saying.
There's terrible things
that happen in the house,
and I don't blame her
for one bit feeling that way,
but we're not the ones
who did this to them,
and I definitely don't think
that we should be the ones
suffering for it.
So, is it safe for you
to stay on your property
and pass this house along
to your kids?
The easiest way to go
would be to demolish
the house,
which it sounds like
you're not going to do.
So, my other suggestion
would be to find
a hoodoo practitioner,
who would want to attain
her power,
and they're gonna take her
with them.
If we get this other one to
come in here and kick her ass,
is all these other spirits
that's underneath her,
will they be let go
and everything?
Yes.
So, are you guys gonna follow
Amy's advice
and find
a hoodoo practitioner?
TYSHA:
At the end of the reveal,
I felt vindicated
because we have some answers,
but it scared the hell out of me
because I knew
what I was up against.
TROY: There's still stuff
happening daily,
so I took heed to Amy's advice
so we could start getting
to the bottom of what's been,
you know, coming around
and everything.
MAN: I am sent by the ancestors
to lead you to them.
TYSHA:
It took us a few months,
but we found
the hoodoo practitioner
who's been all over the world
practicing hoodoo.
This house is alive.
It breathes.
He was doing a lot of
communication with the spirits.
I summon the muertos
in this home.
Come before me
and heed my words.
He said they call
the main hoodoo lady "mother."
And show yourself to me,
mother.
Arise, mother.
He did several different kinds
of rituals to get rid of her...
MAN:
It's time to let go of the pain.
Unshackle yourselves from the
minds and deeds of your captors.
TYSHA:
...And the hundreds of spirits
that were falling under
her command.
I am sent by your fathers,
mothers, brothers, and sisters.
You could feel everything
changing --
the energy in the house
shifting.
Then leave this home, mother.
Remove this curse.
Enter the river.
Go into the world of ancestors.
Be gone!
TYSHA:
After doing these rituals,
the hoodoo doctor is supposed to
come back the next day
to finish the ceremony,
but he never came back.
He said that he was sick
in his hotel room,
and he could not leave,
but I have a feeling when
he felt the power of mother,
he realized that maybe he was
over his head.
So, now I'm back to square one,
finding
another hoodoo practitioner,
and my concerns have amplified
even more.
He didn't finish,
and I'm just afraid that
he stirred everything up.
I don't even know
what's gonna happen.
I am so frightened.
AMY:
This is a dire situation,
and one that's only going
to get worse with time,
but I won't let that happen.
I'm already in touch
with Tysha and Troy
to help them find
the right hoodoo practitioner,
and together, we're going to
put a stop to her for good.