"Get away from me."
NARRATOR: Tonight
on "Dead Files Revisited"...
You got some crazy going on.
NARRATOR:...a second look
at some of Amy and Steve's
most terrifying cases.
Sounds a like
a real serious problem.
New information.
TOM: I braced myself
for what I was gonna hear.
NARRATOR:
Startling revelations.
I don't want something taking
one of my family members
from me.
NARRATOR: First, a return
to Manchester, Connecticut...
We can't live like this
any longer.
...where a deranged stalker...
She's running from someone.
NARRATOR:
...attacks from beyond.
I think he wants to kill.
NARRATOR: Then...
I'm very worried that
my children are gonna be hurt.
...we travel back
to St. Clair Shores, Michigan...
AMY:
This is not good.
NARRATOR:...where a family's
biggest threat...
I think it's a poltergeist.
NARRATOR:
...is one of their own.
I feel like it's my fault.
Did they listen to Amy?
Can you fix
what's going on?
Or does the terror continue?
I exorcise thee
by the most holy name
of Eloah Va-Daath!
It's really bad in here.
My name is Amy Allan.
Something is not right.
I see dead people.
This person might have been
a serial killer.
I speak to dead people.
You get those chills.
And they speak to me.
He is darkness.
He is evil.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
I think she broke her neck.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
You telling me the truth?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I think the devil
is down here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who the hell would do this?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
Who's he looking to kill?
We uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
You need to get out of here
right now.
Or time to get out.
It was, like, endless darkness.
STEVE: For our clients
in Manchester, Connecticut,
life was miserable.
Their home had become a hotbed
of paranormal activity,
and the owner, Tom, didn't know
how to protect his family.
And thanks to our investigation,
that guy was about to find out
the only way to tackle
this problem was to man up.
STEVE: Tom, you sounded pretty
stressed out on the phone.
TOM: Yeah.
Our daughter wakes up
in the middle of the night
screaming for us.
As a father,
it's got to be pretty tough.
The look in her face,
just the sheer terror,
it's painful
to watch her struggle.
The level of activity
in the house
had really moved up a notch
at a level
where it was frightening
on a daily basis.
It was almost like the house
was controlling us,
and we wanted to take back
control.
- Now, I understand you're an
ordained minister. - Yes, I am, yeah.
I've done numerous blessings,
and it just doesn't stop.
What are you hoping
we can do for you guys?
We've gone as far as we can
on our own,
and we can't live like this
any longer.
AMY: As usual,
I had absolutely no information
about the location
before I arrived.
immediately sensed
that the house was overflowing
with dangerous activity,
and just like the living people
that Steve meets,
sometimes the dead I encounter
seem trapped in fear as well.
There is this little girl.
She's running from someone.
[ Panting ]
She knows
that if he catches her,
he's gonna hurt her.
I know he gets her.
Is this how she died?
Definitely.
STEVE: So, Tom, why'd you
bring me up into this room?
I saw a solid-black mass
moving down the wall.
I was stunned.
TOM: After that, it was
almost like a siege mentality,
where you kind of hunker down
at night
and just hope
that nothing would happen
and wish for the daylight
to come.
At night, I've heard
heavy objects moving.
I come here
and look at the desk,
and nothing had moved.
It's something that I'm not
equipped to deal with.
AMY:
There's a guy down there.
He's saying,
"Don't come down here.
Get away from me."
Often, it's not easy
for the dead to understand
that I'm there to help.
This is wrong.
There's a lot of problems here,
specifically in this area.
And it became obvious
in that moment
that the angry man
was agitated by my presence.
Can you talk about
what he does up here
that might
disturb people?
I'm hearing, like,
stuff sliding across the floor.
Like,
hearing furniture moving.
He will really go nuts.
STEVE: Tom's daughter, Allyson,
had several encounters
that would have been damaging
to any kid.
First,
I was afraid of the dark,
but then
I was afraid of the ghost.
A ghost.
Like a man?
Yes.
He just stands
by the front of my bed.
But it was Tom's wife
who really concerned me
because the thing
that was haunting her the most
were here memories.
Joanna, where are you
actually from?
I'm from Poland.
Okay.
My father worked
with the government,
and he was involved
with police.
That's my father.
What did he do
for the government?
He would be the part
of spying on people,
or trying to get rid of
everybody who was in his way.
But my mom was opposite side
of the politics.
And my father, I think he had
anger issue or something,
because I saw him holding gun
against her head.
JOANNA:
That was first time I was not
feeling safe around my father.
And it's kind of difficult
talking about him,
but Steve was very
understanding, very supportive,
and somebody who'd help us
to bring things to normal.
Do you talk to them
at all?
They divorced
when I was 18,
and after that, I really didn't
keep in touch with him.
I don't even know
if he is alive, to be honest.
AMY:
There's this guy.
He is some kind of, like,
cop or investigator.
Just a real tough, rough dude.
He's constantly on patrol.
And I'm getting that he was
some kind of grandfather figure
or father figure.
Someone
that's here now?
Yes.
He loves them.
Right then,
I realized that dead man
wanted to protect
the residents of the home.
But there's, like, times
where he's seeing things
that he doesn't agree with
or doesn't like,
and that's when [snaps]
he'll sometimes just snap.
But thanks to his bad temper,
I think he was probably doing
more harm than good.
Does he express that
in any way?
He might influence you, like,
to feel angry for no reason.
And then I just see, like,
black and yelling,
which is his temper.
NARRATOR: Next...
This is unheard of.
...secrets are exposed.
I know she was murdered.
NARRATOR: And in our second
investigation...
I'm gonna take my kids
and walk out that door.
...evil is unleashed.
It hurts so **** bad.
You're not welcome here anymore.
You have to go.
STEVE:
From the moment it was built,
Tom and Joanna's house
was plagued with tragedy.
A couple of years after
the original owner moved in,
he lost his wife
and two infant kids.
But as terrible as that was,
it was no excuse
for what he was accused of doing
after he got remarried.
James and Harriet Lanfear,
they got brought up
on charges of child abuse.
This is 1860.
Were a lot of cases
even brought to trial?
This is unheard of.
It just doesn't happen.
And make it
even more interesting
is the people who's bringing
the complaint.
It's his own family.
This is a very well-respected
family in town.
This is a time period
where everybody's
family business
was their own
and no one else's,
so the abuse
had to have been horrendous.
All right, so,
she got a severe whipping
and an application
of a hot flatiron
on one of
the child's limbs.
That's pretty bad.
So, now, what wound up happening
at the trial?
They were acquitted.
AMY:
I see this, like, black thing.
In life, it was a man.
Now he's, like,
turning into a shadowy thing.
He's like a stalker.
MATTHEW: Do you have any idea
about his life?
He goes all over the house,
so I'm thinking
that he lived here.
AMY: No matter where I went
on the property,
that stalker followed.
At first, I thought he was more
of a nuisance than a threat,
but those feelings changed
as soon as I met
one of his many victims.
Yes.
I see the little girl.
She's a living person,
and there's a dead little girl
here as well.
I know she was murdered
by the stalker.
She's here to warn the living
about him.
I think he killed
the dead girl,
and I think he wants to kill
this girl.
STEVE: By the late 1800s,
Tom and Joanna's property
had already seen
a lot of misery.
And according to a descendant
of another former owner,
things were only gonna
get worse.
Now, Dennis, what I found
interesting was that...
...there was more than death,
as far as tragedy for this family. - Yes.
Thomas' oldest son, Thomas,
married his first cousin.
So Thomas Sr.
disowned his son.
Wow.
But Thomas also had children
that were very devoted to him.
One of them was Edward.
They were very close.
They were both firemen.
He was
the next oldest son,
but he also died
at a very young age of 43.
He suffered over the last
couple years of his life.
Okay.
AMY: This angry guy
in the basement...
he felt very, very ill.
Can you tell anything about
who he was when he was alive?
I think he lived here.
He was a pretty private guy,
got sick in his 40s.
I'm always trying to understand
the motivation
behind a dead person's behavior.
One way I do this
is by experiencing
in a physical way
their emotions.
And using this technique
on that man,
I quickly identified the source
of his anger issues.
And it hurt.
And it hurts, like, here
really bad.
His life was met
with darkness and tragedy.
Oh, this is bad.
NARRATOR: Coming up...
His intentions are to kill.
...what happened
after the investigation?
TOM:
In the name of Jesus Christ,
I command you
to leave this place.
STEVE: Amy, I'd like you to meet
Tom and Joanna.
When I first met Amy,
I had a lot of trepidation.
And I just kind of buckled down
and braced myself
for what I was gonna hear.
Their biggest concern is their
8- year-old daughter, Allyson.
AMY:
When I walked in the basement
and I saw this entity,
he was very angry,
and I kept feeling pain
in my stomach, and
it felt like it took a long time
before he died.
Any idea how old
this guy might have been?
45.
Wow. Okay.
One guy to actually live
on this property here
was Edward Coleman.
He died in his early 40s
from kidney and heart failure.
One of the symptoms
of kidney failure
is a swelling of the stomach
and cramps.
What this person likes to do
is just be left alone.
When he's not left alone,
he'll get upset,
and you can feel that.
TOM: That kind of really
caught me off guard
because I had no idea
that Edward's feelings
could influence us
here in the house.
I wanted him to leave.
STEVE:
What else did you see?
I met this other man.
He was, like, a tough guy,
like a cop,
and he had a short temper.
I felt like he was a father,
a grandfather
to somebody who lives here.
JOANNA: I don't know
if he's alive or not,
but my father was a cop,
and he had a temper,
and one time,
he would take gun
and put to my mom's head.
JOANNA: I didn't want to believe
that it could be my father,
but he fits that description,
and I start feeling worried
about him
affecting the family and energy
in this house.
So, he's not the kind
of guy that we'd want
to see around here.
Trying to protect.
I was a little conflicted
in that
the father/grandfather figure
could have been Joanna's father.
He wasn't a good person,
but it was reassuring
that there was
a close family member, perhaps,
being here, watching over us.
I saw an entity
I was afraid of.
I felt that this entity
hates women.
When he was alive,
he did harm them.
STEVE: Let me tell you
about this guy, James Lanfear.
He lived on the property here.
He and his wife went on trial
for severely beating
their 10-year-old daughter.
I was watching through the eyes
of a little girl
that he was stalking
and then murdered.
He was so filled
with negativity
that he is turning into
kind of like a dark mass.
I did do a sketch of something
that I saw upstairs.
And then there's
a little girl here.
She's wearing
a little dress,
and there's, like, this weird
black thing behind her.
That's their daughter.
This is the little girl
that he murdered.
TOM: When I saw the sketch
of Allyson's bedroom,
I had a pit in my stomach.
As a father,
it just disturbs you
to think that
I can't protect my daughter
while she's sleeping.
So, why would he come to me
and my daughter?
His victims are coming to her
to try to warn her and you.
His intentions are to kill.
Who's he looking to kill?
Your daughter.
It does make me feel mad.
I wanted to say to this entity,
"Get the hell out of here."
And I was anxious to know
if Amy can see the way
to save my family.
STEVE: Well, I realize
this was a tough night,
but we still haven't answered
your most pressing question.
Is it safe for Allyson
to grow up here?
One of the things
that I would like to see happen
is for you to have an exorcist
perform a ritual to remove him.
Once that's done,
it's very likely
that all of the victims
will leave,
because their job is done.
- So, will that exorcism
get rid of the fireman? - No.
So, for him, perform
the real basic cleansing.
What about Joanna's dad?
One thing
that I would ask you to do
is to write a letter
to your father about everything.
And then at the end, tell him
to now leave you alone in peace.
I just feel very helpless
through the whole thing,
you know?
As a man of this home
and this family,
you have to buck up.
You got to be strong
for your daughter.
You need to help her
and your wife get through this.
TOM:
Shortly after the investigation,
we did have a flurry of activity
in the house,
and I was ready to do
whatever was necessary
and find a way to beat this.
Our Father who art in Heaven,
hallowed be Thy name.
I blessed the house myself,
went through with a thurible
and said "The Lord's Prayer"...
Forgive us our sins
as we forgive those
who sin against us.
...and commanded Edward
to leave.
In the name of Jesus Christ,
I command you
to leave this place.
This is our home now.
It's time for you to go.
PRIEST:
I beseech Thee, O my Lord,
to illuminate
the light of my conscience
with the splendor of Thy light.
TOM: While the priest
was preparing for the exorcism,
he started by drawing
the convocation circle
to draw the spirits
to the basement
and protect him
during the ceremony.
I've never seen anything
of that nature before.
Oh, ye spirits, ye, I conjure
by the power, wisdom, and virtue
of the spirit of God.
His voice got more intense
and louder.
And I exorcise thee
by the most holy name
of Eloah Va-Daath!
He started doing the exorcism
both in English and Hebrew.
[ Speaking Hebrew ]
That is -- Holy, holy, holy...
It was kind of
a building process.
And by all these names,
be delivered from this place.
And by that last fire
which shall consume all things.
Priest took the athame
and did the final banishment.
[ Speaking Hebrew ]
It was very abrupt
and very final.
I exorcise ye anew
and powerfully conjure ye
by him who spake
and it was done.
Amen.
TOM:
After the exorcism was over,
the atmosphere of the house
is different than it was,
and as time went on,
Allyson became
more and more comfortable.
JOANNA: As for my father,
I didn't write the letter
because I spoke with my mom,
and I find out
my father did not pass away.
TOM:
Thinking into my past,
my grandfather
was an actual policeman.
So that possibly could be
my grandfather.
I never really got to share time
with him.
So, to know that he's with me --
I mean, it just is a blessing.
AMY: I'm pleased that Tom
was finally able to take charge
and protect his family.
As for Joanna,
now that she's learned
the fate of her father,
it seems that the final chapter
of that relationship
is in her hands.
STEVE: When I arrived
in St. Clair Shores, Michigan,
our client was a wreck.
She claimed that the paranormal
activity in her home
had actually become violent.
But what Amy and I uncovered
was that her real problem
wasn't caused by any ghosts.
STEVE: So, Emily,
when we spoke on the phone,
you sounded pretty upset about the things
that are happening here. - Yes.
We hear voices, footsteps.
We see shadows move,
apparitions.
EMILY: The activity
had taken a toll on me.
We've lost friends,
even family members.
They won't come to our home
anymore
because they think
we're gonna bring
whatever is happening here
to their house.
Okay.
How many people
actually live in the house?
My husband,
my 12-year-old twins,
my 7-year-old twins.
Why did you call us now?
In the last year,
it's gotten physical,
and I'm very worried that
my children are gonna be hurt.
AMY: You got some crazy
going on here.
Looking back, that home gave off
an erratic energy,
and it was seriously affecting
my ability to do a walk.
What's going on?
I feel really sick.
****
I don't feel good
in this place.
That had me worried because
if I couldn't find my focus,
there was no way I'd get
to the root of the problem.
Oh.
It's like stomach and heart
Like an unsettled feeling.
[ Groans ]
Terrible, terrible pain.
- It's got to be tough on your family.
- NARRATOR: Next...
It's definitely capable
of causing physical injury.
NARRATOR:...innocent lives
caught in the crossfire.
Does that scare you?
Mm-hmm.
STEVE: When Emily said
her young children
were too scared
to be in the basement,
I was a bit cynical.
Lots of kids say
they're scared of basements.
But after learning
what happened to Emily,
those kids were smart
to stay out of there.
I've had my hair pulled
from the back very violently.
Nobody was down here.
I was alone.
It sounds like you have
a serious problem here.
It's actually
even worse than that.
I've been burnt.
It was like someone took
a hot curling iron
to the back of my neck.
It happened four times.
Every time,
I was taking a shower.
EMILY: The attacks that have
happened to me in the shower
were very frightening.
And of course,
I was very worried
that the abuse
will move on to my family.
Geez.
Now, what if Amy says
this is only gonna get worse
and you can't fix it,
what would you do?
I'm gonna take my kids
and walk out that door.
Okay.
AMY: It just felt like
somebody touched my hair.
Oh.
I just got grabbed, like,
behind my -- right here.
And he said,
"Get out of here ****
Shut up."
And one would think
that it's a dead male,
but it is a fully formed
PK manifestation.
A PK manifestation is the result
of imbalanced excess energy
created by a living person
that can feed off of the dead.
Even in their earliest stages
of formation, they're dangerous.
And if a PK can manage to reach
its full potential,
the living don't stand a chance.
How advanced
would you say it is?
Well, it's definitely capable
of causing physical injury.
STEVE: Even though Emily
seemed to be the main target
of the activity in the house,
she wasn't the only one
being tormented.
Her husband's experiences
were getting worse by the day.
But unlike Emily,
he wasn't ready to walk away
from this fight.
Erich, what have you been
experiencing?
I came down to take a nap
one afternoon.
It felt like two kids
jumping on a bed.
Okay.
But when I went to look,
they weren't there.
Have you seen anything?
There's a guy,
and he will walk behind me
and come into this bedroom.
It's pretty unnerving.
Because of all the paranormal
issues
we are having in our home,
I didn't want to go to work.
I wanted to stay home
and protect my family
and kick out whatever is here
in order to stay.
It's got to be tough
on your family.
Sometimes
you got your kids,
and they look at you,
and they wonder,
"Why did you
do this to me?"
AMY:
This is not good.
There was, like, a man
crawling out from under here.
Just, like, a black,
slithery, snaky thing.
Ever since coming to terms
with my abilities,
I've learned to expect
the unexpected.
But, really, I wasn't prepared
for what I was seeing
at that moment.
He makes you feel fear.
And watching him squirm around
on the ground,
I wasn't sure if he was in pain
or planning an attack.
Then you feel like
you're gonna throw up,
like, 'cause it's so --
Your stomach feels scared.
STEVE: It's always tricky
when kids are involved,
but since Emily and Erich
were concerned
the activity was affecting
their younger children,
I knew that the best thing
for me to do
was hear
their side of the story.
Okay, so, Erich, why don't you
tell me what you've been seeing?
Sometimes I see a shadow
in the hallway, like, a man.
What about you, sweetie?
When I go to bed,
I always see a man
go down the hallway.
Is it the same
like he sees it?
- Does that scare you?
- Mm-hmm.
Do you have trouble going to bed
at night because of that?
Sometimes.
Me too.
People are hiding
under blankets and sheets.
I'd say at least three of them
have some PK **** going on.
Okay.
I think it's really
just mainly a poltergeist.
NARRATOR: Next...
So, how bad was it?
All the babies died.
...tragedy hits home.
It was awful.
It took so many of them.
STEVE: I began my research
into Emily and Erich's home
at the most logical
starting point --
the previous homeowner.
This route
doesn't always pan out,
but this time, it paid off.
And not only did
our conversation help my case,
I think it helped her, too.
Shannon, now,
you mentioned on the phone
that you had some information
that could help my case.
Well, my grandfather passed away
here in the house
of natural causes.
Did anybody else die
in the house that you know of?
Ah, yes.
My other grandfather's
girlfriend.
There was a coatrack
next to the stairway
to the basement,
and Georgina
went towards the coatrack
and fell down
the stairs.
How'd your grandfather
take that?
It's the first time
I ever seen him cry.
I haven't thought about it
in years.
AMY:
Somebody died back here.
What happened?
It was very fast.
A lot of fear.
And it's like a sudden --
Man, it's like, "Bam!"
As I was trying to get a handle
on the activity outside,
I felt driven to go inside
and face that PK manifestation
one last time.
In hindsight, I wish I hadn't.
I'm, like, very confused
right now.
Like, like --
[ Sighs ]
Here's the pain again.
Like, the grabbing?
Yes.
It hurts so **** bad.
STEVE:
Combing through the archives,
I found that one of the original
landowners, Noah Furton,
was met with one misfortune
after another.
But from the sound of things,
Noah's cousin Adolphus
had it even worse.
And that's when I realized
that the property
was prone to tragedy.
Adolphus comes from a long line
of French Canadians
who settled
in this area.
Okay, and then, they settled
here to do what kind of work?
He went to the occupation
of sailing.
I know that's dangerous work
today,
so how bad was that for them
back then?
AMY: This black, like, slithery,
snaky thing.
I'm trying to figure out what he
looked like when he was alive.
He's a big guy.
Has an accent
and/or spoke another language.
I think he's scared,
and there's a lot of violence
around him and in his life.
Was Adolphus married?
Yes, he was.
His wife, Mary,
was married to him
the 29th of January
of 1886,
and they had seven children
together. - Okay.
Now, you mentioned he had an
unthinkable tragedy in his life.
What was it?
AMY: I saw a graveyard...
that was built for children.
All of the children
died as infants,
except for his daughter
Julia.
She died as a teenager
from consumption
at the age of 17,
but all the babies died.
Wow.
So, he buried
all of his kids.
AMY:
I hear a voice say,
"It was awful.
It took so many of them."
Now, with all this tragedy
in his life,
what wound up happening
with Adolphus?
The men here have problems.
Yeah. Dead and living men
have problems in this location.
Adolphus, on November 21, 1916,
drowned in Lake St. Clair.
He was lost on the ice,
and his body was not found
until
the following spring.
Okay.
And they ruled it accidental?
Yes.
Some normal guy moves in,
and then he gets involved
with bad ****
or drops dead or goes crazy.
But it doesn't have anything
to do with the PK phenomena.
Is this anything
that might be dangerous?
Yeah.
NARRATOR: Next...
You seem pretty upset
by what she's saying.
...the shocking truth
is revealed.
It's like a curse.
But can this frightened
family...
EMILY: We just wanted
to make things right.
NARRATOR:
...face their demons.
Only love...
...light...
...and peace...
...may enter.
STEVE:
This is Erich and Emily.
EMILY:
When we started the reveal,
my stomach was in knots.
I was just so anxious to hear
why the activity
was happening to my family.
STEVE: Things have gotten
very physical,
and it looks like it's directed
more towards Emily.
I did see the graveyard
that was built for children.
And this property
is not good for men.
It's interesting
you say that it's bad for men
because an original owner of
your property was Noah Furton.
And he had lost two sons.
He had a cousin named Adolphus
that lived with him.
All of Adolphus' seven kids
died young.
Not only that, he ends up
drowning in Lake St. Clair.
Wow.
It's like a curse.
EMILY: I was scared
for my husband and my two sons.
I don't want something
I can't see
ripping my family apart,
possibly even taking one
of my family members from me.
The next thing
that I encountered
was a dead person
underneath the car.
And the way he moved
was snakelike.
I did do a sketch
of the man that I saw.
He doesn't have,
like, any legs.
He still has,
like, his head and torso.
And he's wrapped
in a black mist.
Whoa.
Mm.
Is there any chance
that this guy here
could be one of the Furtons?
Very possible.
ERICH: When I first looked
at the sketch,
I came very close
to breaking down at that point.
I didn't know exactly
what that entity was,
but I wanted to somehow
make it go away.
So, what I finally figured
is that there's three
main experiences
that you guys
would encounter.
The first thing
is physical abuse.
And this seemed to be directed
towards women.
Tell her what happens
when you take a shower.
It's like a burn.
Whoa. Okay.
Wow!
The second experience
was the voices.
When I got into the kids' room,
it was crazy out of control.
We all hear it every day.
The third thing,
my heart hurt.
I had a heart attack last year
for no reason.
What happened?
The doctors
can't explain it.
EMILY:
I never mentioned it to Steve
because I really didn't think
me having a heart attack
was relevant,
but how can you not think that
it's being caused by this house
when you hear information
like that?
So, there was another sketch
that I did.
We both see them.
It has developed into
a full-blown poltergeist.
So, these strings of light
that we see,
that's a poltergeist.
You both
seem to have abilities,
and then all of this energy
builds.
Then we can feed
off of the dead.
So, with this guy here,
he's being absorbed
by your poltergeist.
When Amy told me that
we were creating a poltergeist,
it blew me away.
I actually felt really bad
for the slithering man.
He's suffering still,
and it's our fault.
STEVE: But the main question is,
"Can you live here safely?
And can you fix
what's going on?"
We need to get the dead
out of the house.
So, to start off,
you're going to be doing
home cleansings
three times a week.
Also, to eliminate
this poltergeist,
I would suggest tai chi
as a family, together.
So, what's gonna happen
to this guy?
Once the poltergeist
is dissipating,
it's going to release him.
What can they do about
this thing that's bad for men?
I would suggest
bringing in a shaman
to do a cleansing ceremony
on the land.
So, are you gonna listen
to our advice?
EMILY:
After the investigation,
the poltergeist activity
really ramped up.
We just wanted
to make things right,
so that's why we took the steps
to get rid of this
as quick as we can.
First, we cleansed
all the walls in the house
with the warm saltwater
and said the chant.
Only love...
...light...
...and peace...
...may enter.
All the dead...
...must leave.
ERICH: We wrote the saying
on a chalkboard
that is in our kitchen.
SHAMAN:
Nothing negative may remain,
and any spirits
that are on this property
may you be released.
The shaman was outside
doing her cleansing
to release the children
that were stuck here.
If there are any children
on these grounds,
may they be, please, returned
to their families
and loved ones.
But then the wind picked up.
The black clouds rolled in,
and the thunder started.
SHAMAN: I call on the ancestors
and spirits above.
May you charge and bless
this home
with positive energy,
absorbing all the negativity.
EMILY: She could sense
something evil in the house,
and she was gonna get rid of it.
You're not welcome here anymore.
You have to go.
She started to sweat.
It was like something
was trying to fight her.
May love and light
enter this home.
Nothing negative can remain.
Her final step
was a shamanic extraction
in order to lessen our abilities
to create a poltergeist.
You're just gonna feel
a slight tug,
and I'm pulling
the negative energy out of you.
ERICH:
It was a wild experience.
SHAMAN:
You're no longer welcome here.
Anything negative or evil,
be gone.
EMILY: After the blessing,
I felt revived,
and I truly felt no negativities
in the house.
ERICH: We have started tai chi
as a family
to help focus on controlling
our energies
so this doesn't happen again.
EMILY: I feel like
my family can just move forward.
It's like weight
off of my shoulders.
AMY: I'm happy to hear
that Emily's family
is finding their balance,
but having that many people
with abilities under one roof
won't be easy.
And that means staying safe
could be an everyday challenge.