There is a lot of death.
NARRATOR: Tonight on
"Dead Files Revisited"...
You can feel the fear.
...a return to Pennsylvania...
I'm gonna square off with that
son of a **** on his own.
He wants a piece of something?
Come and **** me.
...for a second look
at two of Amy and Steve's
most terrifying cases.
So, basically,
they suffocated to death.
New information.
We knew it was bad,
but we didn't know how bad.
NARRATOR:
Startling revelations.
And I'm thinking, "Oh, my God.
What are we gonna do?"
NARRATOR: First, in Cressona...
How do you protect them
against something like that?
...a dangerous presence...
I think the devil
is down here.
...stalks a family.
He said, "I'll see you soon.
I can't wait."
NARRATOR: Then...
You can feel
that you're being watched.
...we travel back
to nearby Cambridge Springs...
This is going to be
a difficult walk for me.
NARRATOR:...where
a hotel's troubled past...
I think that there were
a lot of ill people here.
NARRATOR:
...could seal its fate.
Nobody wants to go into a hotel
that they don't feel safe.
Did they listen to Amy...
STEVE: Do you think
they'll be okay?
...or does the nightmare
continue?
Take the negative energy
and just go away.
It's time for you to leave.
It's really bad in here.
My name is Amy Allan.
Something is not right.
I see dead people.
This person might have been
a serial killer.
I speak to dead people.
You get those chills.
And they speak to me.
He is darkness.
He is evil.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
I think she broke her neck.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
You telling me the truth?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I think the devil
is down here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who the hell would do this?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
Who's he looking to kill?
We uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
You need to get out of here
right now.
Or time to get out.
It was, like, endless darkness.
STEVE: As soon as I heard
that two veterans
in Cressona, Pennsylvania,
needed our help,
I knew the situation
had already gotten out of hand.
Having served myself,
I know you never call for backup
unless you absolutely have to.
By the time we got there,
the battle was in full swing,
and I was just hoping
we weren't too late.
STEVE: Now, Randy, I understand
you and your fiancée, Angela,
have got some pretty serious
things going on here.
There's apparitions.
There's shadows.
There's been things moved
that I know
nobody has touched.
RANDY:
It was getting to the point
where it was causing animosity
between myself and Angela.
There's constant fighting.
There's constant tension.
It was just getting
worse and worse.
Who lives in the house?
Myself, Angela,
my two daughters,
and my stepson.
Are they frightened
to be in the house?
Samantha is.
Samantha actually lived here
with me last year
and moved out
because she's so afraid.
- That's got to be heartbreaking
for you. - It is.
That's my little girl.
It's hard to be a father
and protect your children
when you can't --
how do you protect them
against
something like that?
Did you guys ever consider
moving out of here?
It's not an option.
AMY: Without question,
this was one of the worst walks
I've ever done.
The physical impact
lasted for days
and made every step of the
investigation almost unbearable.
There's this really tall,
crazy guy.
He has, like,
a long cape and a hat.
He is very excited
for us to be here tonight
because he thinks
he's all that,
as far as being able
to mess with people
and scare them.
He said, "I'll see you soon.
I can't wait."
Like, "You'll know
when you get there,"
you know, "what I'm all about."
STEVE: This is
your youngest daughter's?
RANDY: Yes.
She had described to me
a large, dark figure
with a cape
and a hook hand.
She won't even go in the closet
by herself.
That's scary for anybody,
let alone an 8-year-old.
The way I understand it,
she sees it pretty often.
Something or someone
was in Samantha's room.
And we knew it was bad,
but we didn't know how bad.
And I actually wasn't sure
if I could protect the home.
I don't even know the kid,
and my heart's breaking for her.
If I think about it, I get
emotional. That's my daughter.
AMY: You can feel the fear
that these people feel.
He likes the closets.
He doesn't really care
for children.
They're easy mark.
Bottom line,
the tall man was simply a coward
who fed off the vulnerable.
And over the years,
this approach had only
made him stronger.
And now he was ready
for a new challenge -- me.
He's like, "Oh, I'm gonna
**** with your head
if you're gonna ****
with my head."
MATTHEW:
And what is he doing?
He's just making me dizzy
and feel like I want to vomit.
I feel like someone's
pushing my throat in.
Right here.
Like that.
Really hard.
STEVE: It was clear the activity
was hitting Randy pretty hard,
but what his fiancée witnessed
in the basement
was enough to make anyone uneasy
in their own house.
You all right?
What are you feeling
when you come down here?
I just feel evil.
One night, I heard banging
and growling and scratching
coming from
the basement door.
What do you think's
down here?
I think
the devil is down here.
I was concerned
that this evil entity
was going to hurt the children,
and I just wanted
to get rid of it.
One of the things that I feel
that may be behind it all
is my mother.
My mother passed away
in '98.
She died
of bone-marrow cancer.
STEVE: Being a veteran myself,
I knew I'd have a lot in common
with these clients.
But what Angela shared with me
next
hit home in a way
I just didn't see coming.
I had some issues
with my mother.
We'd try to make amends,
but it didn't happen.
I feel tremendous guilt.
I absolutely understand
what you're talking about.
Same thing happened to me
with my father.
I didn't get
to say goodbye.
We had an argument
the night he died.
[ Sniffles ]
I still have guilt
about it.
And if I can
do that night over...
[snaps fingers] I'd do
that night over in a minute.
Unfortunately,
before she died,
we never had a chance
to say goodbye to each other,
so I do believe
that my mother is here.
AMY: I want to say
that this lady
is related to the people
in the house now.
She keeps saying
that she's very sorry
about everything
that's happened.
Oh, my God.
Something about cancer.
I think she died from it.
Do you know
when this was?
Late '90s.
She might be death
come to this house.
She's coming
to take the lady.
NARRATOR: Next...
Cressona was absolutely hammered
with death.
...evil is exposed.
He does not want anybody to know
who he is.
NARRATOR: And,
in our second investigation...
The lights flickered,
doors slammed.
...death lurks
beneath the surface.
It was agony --
absolutely just agony.
STEVE:
When Cressona was first settled,
the construction of the railroad
helped put it on the map.
And back then, many of those
workers lived in Randy's house.
Obviously, a life
of manual labor isn't easy,
and a local historian
told me about one man
who only made things worse.
John Chapman Cresson
was the founder of Cressona.
His contemporaries
describe him
as quite a tall man.
He was a very shrewd
businessman.
STEVE: And how's it go
from the land into a town?
What John Cresson did
is he broke the land up
into individual plots
and had homes built
on the plots.
He sold them
to the railroad workers.
So, on one hand, he was
putting money into their pocket,
and on the other hand,
taking it out.
So, it sounds like
this guy's kind of ruthless.
He was.
AMY: I think that this is
the tall, creepy guy.
He does not want anybody to know
who he is.
Do you know how he looked
in life?
He had, like,
kind of a slender face,
a kind of a hook nose,
dark eyes.
He's saying, "Stop, stop,"
'cause I'm, like, trying
to get into his head.
Instead of attacking me,
the tall man
started to resist me.
That's how I knew
he had something to hide.
And, in the end, I was right.
I think he sells
a variety of merchandise.
And I know
he was a very, very bad person.
STEVE: In 1918, the Spanish Flu
struck the town of Cressona,
and the only doctor there
lived in Randy's house.
I was about to find out
that doctor's work
followed him home.
Can you tell me anything
about Dr. Gray?
He was
the only doctor in Cressona
during the Spanish Flu,
and his clinic and his residence
were in the same building.
Okay, so did he practice out
of the house I'm investigating?
Yes.
How bad did Cressona get hit?
Cressona was absolutely hammered
with death.
Wow.
Yeah.
You would feel
like your chest
was being compressed
or squeezed.
So, basically,
they suffocated to death.
Yes.
They would have been
convalescing in his house
and dying there.
Wow.
AMY: It's ridiculous
how many dead people are here.
There's, like, illness in here.
Oh, my God, it's bad.
This had already been
a difficult walk,
and now a mob of sick
dead people were coming at me.
I wanted to help them all,
but it was just too much.
Oh, God.
I can't breathe again.
I feel **** terrible.
NARRATOR: Coming up...
I want this guy.
I'm gonna get this guy.
...what happened
after the investigation?
Ye who are unwelcome
are to leave.
STEVE: Amy, I want you to meet
Angela and Randy.
I've never met a medium before,
so I was a little bit
apprehensive.
I was very nervous of that, and
we had seen something evil here.
The activity in this house
is so intense
that it's literally
ripping their family apart.
AMY: There were just
so many dead people,
and they were all trying
to talk at once.
Pretty much every room upstairs
made me sick.
Some of the symptoms
I felt that night
was dizziness, vomiting.
- That's why you sound sick?
- Yeah.
That's interesting.
Back in 1918,
the Spanish Flu hit here.
Approximately 20% of the town
died from this flu.
James Gray,
the guy that lived here,
happened to be
the only doctor in town.
And he treated a lot
of those patients
right here in this home,
where a lot of them
probably passed away.
Oh, my God.
I went through exactly
what you just described
on many occasions.
Yeah,
that makes sense.
The residual here
is very thick.
I didn't know how many people
have died in this house,
and here we find out that it was
giving me the same symptoms.
It blew me away.
I mean, that's not something
you hear every day.
STEVE: So, how did the rest
of the walk go?
This guy shows up.
He was extremely tall,
had a hat on, cape --
shadowy.
He's very creepy,
very powerful.
I know he bought
and sold things.
And I know he had a hook nose
and dark eyes.
Really?
Yeah.
Kind of reminds me of somebody
who's important to this town.
It turns out it's a guy
named John Chapman Cresson,
hence Cressona.
This guy ran the railroad here,
and he had some shady dealings.
If you look at his nose,
he's got this hook nose
that she had...
Interesting.
I did do a sketch
of the man.
He had a long,
thin, pointy nose.
His eyes are rounded on top,
straight at the bottom.
Wow.
Take a look at that.
Wow, that's freaky.
It looks spot-on to me.
So, basically,
the guy that built Cressona
is hanging out
in our house.
Yes.
And I think he's an evil
presence in your house.
He likes
to mess with people.
Wonderful.
RANDY:
I wasn't very happy to hear
that there's something evil here
and it's scaring everybody.
I was thinking, "Oh, my God.
We can't move.
What are we gonna do?"
The other thing that I got
was he hates kids.
And then I saw
one of the things he was doing,
which I thought
was very disturbing,
and I did sketch it.
- Where did you see this?
- This.
- Oh, so it's in Samantha's room.
- Samantha's room.
I don't even know
if I want to show this to you.
That's the closet.
I want this guy.
I'm gonna get this guy.
RANDY:
When I saw that sketch of John
Cresson standing over Sammy,
I just wanted to kill him.
I wanted revenge.
And when I meet him
in another afterlife,
it's gonna be me and him.
That John Cresson ****
him and I are gonna have
some dealings.
I'm gonna sit down,
and I'm gonna square off
with that son of a ****
on his own.
He wants a piece of something,
come and **** me.
STEVE: All of our clients handle
our findings in different ways,
and Randy's angry reaction
made me understand
just how hard he was willing to
fight to protect his family.
I hate to even ask this
right now,
but was there anything else
you saw?
I saw a lady,
and I got
that she might have been
a relative of someone
who lives here...
...that she died of cancer
in the late '90s.
Oh, my God.
Her mother
died of cancer.
She felt guilty.
She's back to take the woman
of the house.
Death was gonna come
to the house, but she came,
for her
to take death's place
so that she'll be
comfortable.
Whoa.
When Amy said that my mom
was always going to be there,
that really freaked me out.
But it did give me comfort
knowing that she felt guilty
for not making amends with me.
Well, listen,
it's been a tough night,
and I think you guys got a lot
more than you bargained for.
But the reason you called us
is to see if you and your family
can live here peacefully
and straighten out
what the hell you got going on.
If it's at all within
your means, I would move.
We went through everything
we went through so far.
I'm not gonna just roll over
and say, "Go ahead and take it."
No, I'm fighting
for what's mine.
They're getting
the hell out.
Is there anything else
they can do?
Because it seems to be
encompassing the town,
you need
to build your fortress.
First, get bags of salt,
and go around
the entire property line.
Then, with a holy person --
They're gonna bless the house.
And after they're done
blessing each room,
sprinkle brimstone.
It'll get rid of the dead people
here.
What about her mom?
That woman will stay.
That process
cannot stop.
It's natural, organic.
Now, I'm gonna ask you,
are you gonna
follow Amy's advice?
RANDY:
After the investigation,
I was very concerned
for my family's safety,
and I just wanted
to move forward with our lives.
First, I had to spread
a salt line around the property
for protection
and to help clear
residual energy
that was already here.
SHAMAN:
I call the spirits and helpers
of the northwest
to come.
Ye who are unwelcome
are to leave.
RANDY:
When the shaman arrived,
she was kind of like
a guiding spirit.
I banish
that which is unclean.
She had burned sage
from the attic to the basement,
cleansing the house.
She could feel John Cresson
in Samantha's room,
and the shaman proceeded
to do chanting and drumming
to push the negativity
out the doorway.
[ Chanting ]
Yee-ooh!
The last step
was the fire ceremony
to bring peace and serenity
to the whole property.
Let it be known that those
who are unclean are not welcome.
You are not
to bother this family.
It was pretty powerful.
I ask you now
to bless this family, this land
and help them
now and always.
Let there be love and happiness
and protection of this house.
Purify this house, this land.
Protect it now and always.
After the ceremony, there has
been virtually no activity.
Samantha is not afraid
to be in her own bedroom,
and me and Angela feel safer.
We're gonna be maintaining
and blessing
to make sure
no evil can penetrate the house.
RANDY: So, I hope what we did
is gonna last.
It's been hard here.
It's been real hard.
AMY: When I first arrived,
I was concerned for anyone
who lived in this house.
But after meeting Randy
and seeing his determination,
I'm confident
that he'll continue
to do whatever it takes
to protect his family.
STEVE:
As a business owner, a bad
reputation can ruin everything.
And that's exactly what happened
to our clients
in Cambridge Springs,
Pennsylvania.
Word had spread that
the Riverside Inn was haunted,
and they were on the verge
of shutting down.
But Amy and I were determined
to make sure
that wasn't gonna happen.
STEVE: Brenda?
BRENDA: Yes.
How long
you owned this place?
This is the beginning
of our fourth year.
So, at what point did you
realize you have a problem here?
Well, after we talked to
some of the employees,
I realized
that we had a couple
that were afraid to work
in the dish room by themselves.
Talking to different customers,
I realized
that there are
quite a few things.
BRENDA:
It was starting to escalate,
and we didn't even know
what to do.
When you know that there's
something going on at your hotel
that you have no control over --
I was close to tears
most of the time.
- Is it hurting business?
- Absolutely.
I think there are people
that really would be afraid
to come and stay at a place
that they think is "haunted."
And you got how much savings
invested in this place?
Everything.
So, for you to shut it down
would --
I'd go bankrupt.
This is going to be
a difficult walk for me.
I'm still amazed that I was able
to make it through the night.
The location was huge,
and the activity
was overwhelming.
I feel dizzy and...
confused -- very confused.
There's a lot of death.
Someone did suffer
major head trauma here.
It was agony --
absolutely just agony.
Mm.
They are plotting and planning
in here.
NARRATOR: Next...
It would destroy
my reason for living.
...lives are caught
in the crossfire.
There's a lot of inner conflict
with the dead people here.
STEVE: As I walked around
the Riverside Inn,
our client, Brenda,
made it clear
that her main concern
was the safety of her customers
and employees.
But it was her own experience
that really got my attention.
Why'd you
bring me in here?
This is where,
at one point in time,
my husband and I came up,
and the lights flickered,
doors slammed,
and we were the only people
in the hotel.
Okay, did the breaker go
or something like that?
Nope. Nope.
Not at all.
BRENDA: There are definitely
certain areas in the hotel
that are more prone to activity,
and nobody really cares to go
in there if they don't have to.
Anything else
going on up here?
Well,
I always feel watched.
Just a general feeling
of eyes being on you.
Do you feel that way now?
I always have that feeling
that there's always
somebody watching me.
There's a lot of inner conflict
with the dead people here.
I'd say there's about three
cliques of dead people here.
And they fight a lot.
The dead here
had banded together
into three distinct groups --
old people, young adults,
and juvenile delinquents.
Each group
presented its own threat,
but there was one entity
that none of them
would dare mess with.
There's this old man here
with a cane.
He's a very dominant presence.
And he beats the younger people
with his cane
when they fight.
The living actually
can hear or feel this.
It would be really scary
to them.
STEVE:
It was obvious to me that Brenda
wasn't managing her stress well,
and her husband
wasn't doing any better.
But somehow, he found the
strength to put on a brave face.
Larry, your wife said that
you've been experiencing stuff
down here
in the theater.
LARRY: Absolutely.
Mostly things disappearing
here.
Like what?
Props, shoes.
They disappear for two weeks,
and then they reappear.
LARRY: I was so concerned
because my wife spends nights
here alone.
If something ever happened
to Brenda,
it would destroy
my reason for living.
You sure it's nobody
borrowing this stuff
and bringing it back?
Positive,
because I have the key.
I personally had a costume
go missing backstage,
and three months later,
it appeared
at the front desk.
And nobody could explain
how it got there.
The younger people
are far more rambunctious
and angry
than the old people.
They get all pissy.
They work each other up,
and then they run amok.
So, to the living people,
it seems constant.
There's always something
that's been moved.
You can feel
that you're being watched.
In what way, though --
like, somebody's peeking
around the corner at you?
Like maybe just standing there,
watching.
It can be disturbing.
These are where the
juvenile delinquents hang out.
They're like little spies
around and watching people.
You know,
a little inappropriate behavior.
Like what?
Like shower watching
or people
going to the bathroom.
Of the three cliques,
the juvenile delinquents
were the hardest to figure out.
Yeah, what they were doing was
disgusting but mostly harmless.
Unfortunately, I sensed things
weren't going to stay that way.
They are plotting and planning
in here.
And I think
they're the bad seeds.
All right.
So, this was an accident?
NARRATOR: Next...
French Creek
has taken a lot of lives
up and down its length.
...no one is safe.
She's trying to get me
to go in the water.
STEVE: The one piece of history
I had on the Riverside Inn
was so bizarre
I was almost certain
it would lead to a dead end.
But after years
of working with Amy,
I knew it was just the type
of clue I had to chase down.
STEVE:
So, my client said
that the property
I'm investigating
might have been
a fountain-of-youth
type of a place.
It was.
Dr. John H. Gray.
He was the one who discovered
the mineral waters.
He was out probing,
looking for oil on his property.
He discovered not oil
but rather a spring.
So he had it tested,
found it was high in iron,
sodium, magnesium,
potassium,
so he starts prescribing
to the locals.
Okay. What kind of people
went to him?
A lot of these people
would have come
with pre-existing
medical conditions.
So, did anybody get cured
from this stuff?
Large amounts of magnesium
can actually lead
to serious issues
to the point of even death
for some.
AMY:
Something is not right here.
And there's, like,
this wetness...
like oil or water.
It caused the misfortunes.
And then I do hear
convalescent?
It seems like this place
did serve a lot of purpose.
What do you mean?
I literally see,
like, gurneys?
It seemed like
every time I turned around,
a new dead person would appear.
And each one
was sicker than the last.
[ Door creaks ]
I think that there were
a lot of ill people here.
[ Exhales deeply ]
You okay?
I just feel sick.
I'm a **** mess.
STEVE: Expanding my search
of the property,
I found an article
about a kid that drowned
right behind the hotel.
And after speaking to
a local author,
I learned that tragedy
was just one of many.
So, I came across
this kid that drowned
right here on the property
I'm investigating.
That happened
in August of 1979.
Okay.
Young man's name
was Robert Griffith.
Here you go.
He was swimming with
some friends in the river here
and drowned.
All right.
So, this was an accident?
Yeah, and they were kind of
common in French Creek,
as a matter of fact.
What do you mean
by common?
Well, there was a young man
who drowned in the river
almost in the same spot
the very next year.
His name
was Michael Catalano.
It was
similar circumstances.
Now, is the river
that bad?
French Creek
has taken a lot of lives
up and down its length.
There's some people
in the water.
They're bloated.
I think they're dead.
And there's a woman.
She likes to jump people.
She's, um...
trying to get me
to go in the water.
Can you describe it
at all?
She's in me...
was inside of me.
Right then, that dead woman
tried to jump me.
And as I struggled
to fight her off,
her intentions became clear.
She wants to make people
go in the water.
NARRATOR: Next...
Oh, my gosh.
...dark secrets are exposed.
People might have
killed themselves doing it.
I could feel my heart racing.
I could hardly swallow.
NARRATOR:
Can this hotel be saved?
So, take the negative energy,
and just go away.
STEVE: Amy, I want you to meet
Larry and Brenda.
I was on the edge of my seat.
All I could think of
was if Amy's advice would have
been that we had to leave.
I don't know if I could.
STEVE: Their dream
was to own the hotel,
but it came with a price.
AMY:
I was out on the grounds,
and I was seeing
this substance,
like oil or water or both.
I felt like it had caused
a lot of problems here.
That's interesting.
The original owner
of the hotel itself
was a guy
by the name of Dr. Gray.
Back in 1859,
when he acquired the property,
he started looking for oil.
But what he did discover
was mineral water.
He decided that,
with the mineral water,
to make this place
into a wellness sanitarium.
- So, they'd just come here
and drink it? - Yeah.
The people that did come here,
they were all sick.
Interesting,
because I saw
a lot of sick people,
and I saw
a lot of gurneys.
So, most of the people
were kind of O.D.'ing on this?
Yeah. Instead
of getting better,
people might have
killed themselves doing it.
Oh, my gosh.
We knew that the inn
had be founded as a sanitarium,
but we didn't know
that these sick, dying people
were still here.
This is not the place for them,
and they need to move on
and find peace.
STEVE:
So, what else did you see?
There were three different
cliques of dead people --
elderly people,
young adults,
and juvenile delinquents.
The leader of
this elderly group of people
was this guy
who had white hair,
and he was just
very authoritative.
You get a good look
at this guy?
I sketched the man I saw.
AMY: He has a cane.
He has a mustache
and a beard,
and he has
very light, intense eyes.
You guys take a look.
To me,
this actually looks like
a younger version
of Dr. Gray.
BRENDA: Yeah.
LARRY: The expression
looks the same.
So, do you think that the guy
with the cane is Dr. Gray?
I think so, yeah.
When I saw the sketch
and I compared it
to the picture of Dr. Gray,
I could feel my heart racing.
I could hardly swallow.
Why was he here,
and were we doing something
to upset him?
Now, do these cliques
do anything
that can affect
the people that are living?
Oh, well, yeah.
It'll just get worse
and worse and worse.
BRENDA:
I'm thinking, "Oh, my God.
What are we gonna do?"
I've always wondered
if I was truly safe here,
and now I know
that we're in big trouble.
STEVE:
What else did you see?
I saw people on the ground,
and they were dead.
And their bodies
were bloated,
so I got that they drowned.
Well, that's easy enough
to explain.
This is French Creek
out here.
And there's been a lot of
drownings associated with it.
Two of those drownings
actually took place
right on the property.
I saw this woman.
She jumped inside of me.
She was trying to make me
go in the water and drown.
Oh.
What about the guests
that go near the water?
Could they be at risk?
Yes.
She's capable of jumping
other people.
BRENDA:
I'm not afraid of water,
but for some reason, I've never
gone that close to French Creek.
Now I know why.
And we have canoes that
we allow people to take out.
We need to stop doing that.
STEVE: Larry and Brenda,
You got hit with a lot
of information today.
The big question is,
is it safe for you guys,
your employees, and your guests
to be here?
Obviously, I think
that the woman outside,
she is possibly a threat
to the living.
So, what I would recommend
is to find
a psychotherapist.
But this psychotherapist
also needs to be a medium.
This individual
should find out what's up,
what's going on,
why is she here, all of that.
The second thing is to do
a cleansing of this building
to help with the removal
of the three main cliques
that are here.
Then, teach the housekeepers
how to do this basic cleansing
and that one time per week
they incorporate it
into their regular duties.
Let me ask you --
What about Dr. Gray?
I wouldn't try
to move him on.
But if he chooses to go,
then he can leave.
- He's not a threat?
- No.
Once they do all this,
do you think they'll be okay?
BRENDA:
When the reveal was over,
we had to make sure
that anything that was negative
would see its way out the door.
We hit roadblocks right and left
trying to find mediums,
but then I got a lead
on two ladies
who not only are sisters
but they also counsel the dead.
She said, "I'm crying.
I'm sad.
My child is gone,
and I want to hurt people."
They said the woman
down by the water was hurting.
Everyone goes through pain.
Everyone has loss.
We have to heal from that.
We have to move on.
You're just going to have to
find peace
and know that God is with you
and to go into the light.
And we're gonna help you
with the power of the prayer.
LARRY: The psychics made certain
she doesn't suffer anymore
and she doesn't
make anybody living suffer.
Our father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done,
on Earth
as it is in heaven.
It's time for you to leave.
BRENDA:
And then, it was time to get rid
of the three different cliques.
I'm going to send some
healing energy and some sage
to cleanse.
They started walking through
the common-area rooms
and doing blessings.
The negative energies
who are here,
please cross into the light
and please go in peace.
I'm asking
that the bad spirits go out
and that the good spirits
come in.
Positive energy, stay.
Feel the love.
Feel the white light.
Then,
they went up to the guest rooms,
and they used holy water and a
clapping method with vibration
to get the cliques to leave.
Vibrations,
I'm asking you
to attach the vibrations
to the spirits
and to just keep them moving
into the light.
LARRY:
It was intense not knowing
if the cleansing would get rid
of those negative forces.
So, we're asking the elders
to just leave this room.
Take the negative energy
and just go away.
In the name of the father,
the son, and the Holy Ghost.
Just go into the light
and be at peace.
Because this building
is so old and so large,
the mediums
taught me and my staff
how to do the cleansing
on a continual basis
so that it becomes
a weekly ritual.
You're asking them
to go into the light,
to attach to the smoke.
So, say,
"attach to the smoke."
Attach to the smoke.
Go into the light.
There's still
some activity here,
but when I walk through
the front door,
I can feel
a more positive energy
in this building.
But my concern is
can we keep those negative
energies from coming back?
BRENDA: People that come here
come to stay and relax.
And the dead
need to respect that.
I honestly feel that this place
is a wonderful place
and we belong here.
AMY: The Riverside Inn
had attracted a lot of dead,
but only a few of them
posed any real threat.
Now that Brenda has the tools
to help move them on,
she should be able to make sure
any unwanted guests
don't overstay their welcome.