AMY:
There's a darkness here.
NARRATOR: Tonight
on "Dead Files: Revisited"...
He said
that somebody pushed him.
...a second look at some
of Amy and Steve's
most terrifying cases.
- You think there's still
bodies there? - I do.
New information...
It actually makes you
feel helpless.
NARRATOR:
...startling revelations.
I thought,
"This is why he's so ill."
NARRATOR: First...
They typically kill people.
...in Neosho, Missouri...
He just leaned in forward,
like, "I dare you."
...a menacing shadow...
Oh, no.
That's not good.
NARRATOR:
...leaves a family in pieces.
- I don't want my girls
to have a mixed-up life. - Then...
I think the house
is gonna kill us.
...a return
to Starks, Maine...
It's almost like
nothing can live here.
...where failing health...
He should've broken
his neck.
...is no accident.
I've seen things
that I can't exactly explain.
Did they listen to Amy?
You're up
for the fight?
Or does the nightmare
continue?
WOMAN: In the name of
Jesus Christ, leave this house.
ALL: In the name of
It's really bad in here.
My name is Amy Allan.
Something is not right.
I see dead people.
This person might've been
a serial killer.
I speak to dead people.
You get those chills.
And they speak to me.
He is darkness. He is evil.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
I think she broke her neck.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
You're telling me
the truth?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I think the devil
is down here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who the hell
would do this?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
Who's he looking to kill?
We uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
You need to get out of here
right now.
Or time to get out.
It was, like,
endless darkness.
STEVE:
When a fellow cop called us here
to investigate his home
in Neosho, Missouri,
I knew he must be under
a lot of stress.
To go from protecting
your community all day
to your family all night,
that's got to break anyone down,
and as hard as Amy and I tried,
the outcome of this case still
doesn't sit right with me.
STEVE: Well, Dennis,
now, who exactly lives here?
My wife and her daughters
moved out two months ago.
We're separating.
Does it have anything to do
with the paranormal?
A lot of it did.
DENNIS:
What we were experiencing
was devastating
to myself and my family.
We were on the verge of divorce,
and it was very heartbreaking.
It made me feel just helpless.
So, give me an idea
about what's going on here.
Shadow figures,
scratching.
What are you hoping
we can do for you guys?
My wife and I are going
through some problems,
and we're hoping
to actually fix that
so we can stay here
and live in a loving family
without being frightened
for our lives.
AMY: While I often interact
with the dead
almost everywhere I go,
the overwhelming number
of entities in this neighborhood
was like nothing
I had ever seen before.
There's a lot of activity
around here.
[ Sighs ]
There's a lot of dead people
outside,
and they're talking
about the neighborhood.
Some guy is just like,
"Insanity and death."
DENNIS: I was inside
and saw a black figure
looking directly at me
through this window here.
Can you show me
what it looked like?
DENNIS: Being a fellow
law-enforcement officer,
when I first met Steve,
it was really a relief.
It was actually like
I was waiting for my backup.
I felt a little bit more calm
in the situation.
The shadow person came
from this direction.
He just leaned in forward,
like, "I dare you,"
and then just got up
after a second
and just walked
straight off.
AMY:
There is a darkness here.
It walks down the street.
It's not a person.
It's, like, a huge curtain
of darkness.
STEVE: As a former cop,
I know it's difficult
to balance your family life
with the demands of the job,
but what Dennis told me
gave me a pretty good idea
of just how much pressure
this guy was really under.
I walked out
of the bathroom,
and I got struck from behind
by this very curtain rod,
right in the back.
What do you think's going on
in this house?
I wish I knew.
DENNIS: We were really unsure
if we were safe here.
You know,
you can take on a lot of things
that you can physically see,
hear, and touch,
but when you know
that it's really not something
of a human form,
it actually makes you
feel helpless.
I want to make sure that my wife
and my girls are safe here.
I love them.
I'm worried about it.
AMY:
Whatever this thing is...
it can, like,
do very physical things.
Grab people, move things,
and break things.
And this darkness
saturates the whole house.
STEVE:
Dennis' wife, Aundrea,
was still living in the house
after he'd moved out,
and their experiences
with the paranormal,
unfortunately helped me
establish a clear pattern
to the activity.
So, Aundrea,
have you experienced
anything paranormal in this
house, anything unusual?
With Dennis not being here,
I didn't feel safe at all.
I felt abandoned,
and I was facing the unknown.
I see a shadow man here
at the foot of my bed
staring down at me,
and I was petrified.
Okay. Now, is that the only
place you've seen him?
No.
I've seen him upstairs.
He was standing on the far side
of the bunk bed.
Okay.
So now you've got your little
girls you got to worry about.
It's very overwhelming.
I had a somewhat erratic
childhood.
Grandpa was the only father
I knew.
He died
when I was 7.
So, I don't want my girls
to have a mixed-up life.
- You said your grandfather died
when you were 7. - Yeah.
Do you remember much
about him?
He was amazing.
AUNDREA: Grandpa
was my everything growing up.
If I could talk to him,
I'd tell him
about his great-granddaughters
that he never got to meet.
I miss my grandfather
a lot.
Did he die young?
Yeah, he was only 58.
He died of -- Well, he died
of complications from chemo.
Okay.
I want to fix this
for my girls.
AMY: There's also, like,
a father figure
that's with her a lot.
And he's -- he's upset.
He said, "I told her when she
was younger to not do this."
What did he tell her
not to do?
Be into all this dark stuff.
But I'm trying to tell him
the darkness
pretty much goes everywhere.
That's why she has to deal
with this ****
It's at this point
that I realize
the old man wasn't the source
of danger here.
Unfortunately, the problem was
much worse than I had feared.
What I see here is this thing
standing at the end of the bed,
really big.
And I think
there's a closet connection.
Oh, no.
This looks like a shadow man.
They typically kill people,
the shadow people.
NARRATOR: Next...
Hit him in the head
and killed him instantly.
...evil knows no bounds.
This darkness,
it walks down the street.
NARRATOR: And in our
second investigation...
It felt like
we were under siege.
NARRATOR:...the living
fight for survival.
This is, like,
the house of the dead.
STEVE: In a close-knit community
like Neosho,
sometimes the neighbors
know more
about your own business
than you do,
and after talking to a woman
who had lived nearby,
whatever was going on
in my client's house
didn't sound
like an isolated case.
I had some unusual things
happen at my house.
Like what?
There was a dark streak
that would go
from the top of the ceiling
down almost all the way
to the floor,
and I painted over it,
and I papered over it,
and it would just inevitably
come back every time.
Really?
Even with the wallpaper?
Even the wallpaper.
AMY:
When I started my walk,
I saw this darkness
that walks down the street.
It'll come right in the door,
and there were little people
or something in it,
and there's panic
because of this.
STEVE: At this point
in my investigation,
it seemed like the
whole neighborhood
could've used our help,
but after digging
through the archives,
I came across some info that
set my client's house apart.
Not only did a brothel operate
on the land,
but a violent murder
took place there in 1875.
One of the rooms was leased
to Lizzie Sanford,
and she opened a brothel
there in Neosho.
This area, it has this sadness.
A desperate sadness.
She was entertaining
a 17-year-old young man
named Lane Britton,
and another young man
named Wiley Huffaker
demanded entrance and
started pounding on the door,
and Lane Britton threatened
to shoot him.
And Wiley said,
"Well, shooter be damned."
AMY: At one point,
I did hear a gunshot,
and I heard somebody saying,
"Ha ha ha.
That little ****
had it coming to him."
And Lane took him up on it
and shot through the door
and hit him in the head and
apparently killed him instantly.
AMY:
I just hear crying, whimpers.
People -- they, like, die.
STEVE: The brothel shooting
was a solid start,
but Dennis and Aundrea
had reported so much activity,
I was determined to make sure
I didn't overlook
any other secrets
buried in their property.
So, I hit the hall of records
and came across a woman
named Emma Mae Liebhart,
who died from lung cancer
in the house in 1938.
AMY: I'm seeing
the crying woman again.
Do you know
how she died?
I think it was some kind
of respiratory thing.
Mm.
I think this is the woman
from outside,
and she spent a lot of time
in here,
and she doesn't want
to be bothered
by these things anymore.
What things?
This darkness.
I mean, she calls them
little monsters.
Now that I had spoken
to a few of the dead here,
I was sure that they weren't
the ones causing harm.
They were the victims.
I think she kind of feels
like they did contribute
to her death.
They, like, attack her.
NARRATOR: Coming up...
That picture kills me.
...what happened
after the investigation?
You're not welcome
in this house. Leave this house.
ALL: You're not welcome in
this house. Leave this house.
STEVE: Amy, I'd like you
to meet Dennis and Aundrea.
When the reveal started,
I was an absolute wreck.
Aundrea and I,
we were ready to hear
what was going on in the house,
but at the same time,
I was really, really nervous
of what Amy would find.
STEVE: When the two of them
called us in,
they were living together.
Unfortunately,
the activity drove them apart.
So, Dennis
no longer lives here,
but he doesn't think it's safe
for Aundrea and the kids
to be here,
and he called for our help.
When I first pulled up to
the house, I was like, "Whoa."
It's not just this house.
There's activity everywhere
in this neighborhood.
AUNDREA:
When I found out that my
neighbors might be in jeopardy,
it just frightened me.
I don't want anybody else
to ever go through this.
I actually spoke to one
of their former neighbors,
and it was her opinion
that a lot of the houses here
had activity.
AMY: I was outside,
and I saw two men,
and I heard a gunshot.
Okay. At one time, your property
had a brothel on it.
Really?
It was run by a woman
named Lizzie Sanford,
and one night she was
entertaining a young guy
by the name
of Lane Britton.
The guy on the left.
Another guy by the name
of Wiley Huffaker
came up to the door and
was drunk, demanded to get in.
And this kid puts one round
through the door
and catches him in the head,
kills him instantly.
Oh, my gosh.
I went in the master bedroom,
and I met a male.
He seems to be
some type of father figure.
And he feels
that his baby's gone downhill,
but on the other hand,
he does love this person.
That would make me think
it was Grandpa.
He died when I was 7.
He'd had prostate cancer.
[ Voice breaking ]
His death affected me badly.
I'm sorry.
When Amy told me
about my grandfather,
it broke my heart
'cause he's not supposed to
be down here guarding me.
He's supposed to be in Heaven.
This individual is here
because he is protection.
From what?
Well, in the bedroom
downstairs,
I saw
this shadow person.
It is
extremely dangerous.
Then I went
into the pink room.
That's Danielle's room.
Yeah.
Okay.
And I saw the shadow man
crawling out of the closet,
going towards the bed.
My goodness.
I've seen him at the foot
of my bed downstairs.
I see him
all over the place.
DENNIS: It makes us worry
for our safety here,
but it also pissed me off
because I felt helpless.
What can I do
to protect our daughter?
Well, I did do a sketch
of what I saw.
Crawling towards the bed
from the closet.
And there's a kid
sleeping in the bed.
He's creepy.
- STEVE: That's your daughter's room.
- Yeah.
That picture kills me.
AUNDREA: When I saw the picture
of the shadow person,
I went into shock.
I was horrified at the fact
that I haven't been
protecting her like I should.
That's disturbing.
It bothers me a great deal.
I love this family, and I don't
want anything to harm them.
So, question is,
what the hell is going on here?
There must be
some specific location
in this neighborhood,
some type of doorway,
where the shadow people
and little humanoid creatures
I saw are coming from.
And these things
can kill?
Yes.
Oh, my gosh.
I got to keep my girls safe.
They're everything to me.
This is the last thing
that I wanted it to be.
You can't fight this,
can you?
No.
That's what we needed
to know, though.
Knowing that none of us are safe
in our own home
and we have to get out,
it's disturbing.
If we move out of here,
can this follow us?
No.
There's a lot of people
who think
that shadow people
can be dealt with.
I personally don't.
After the reveal,
almost immediately that night,
my wife and I talked.
We decided we'd loved
each other enough,
and we got back together.
I moved in a short time later,
and we've been perfect
ever since.
AUNDREA: It feels wonderful
having Dennis home.
I feel a whole lot safer
with him here.
We started weighing our options.
We listed the house
and started looking
for a new place to live.
DENNIS:
Since we are still here,
and since we haven't found
a house to move in yet,
we thought it best if we contact
a spiritual advisor
to come in and see if she can
bless and cleanse the house.
AUNDREA: The first thing
the spiritual advisor had us do
was open all the windows
in the house.
She said that when
we're cleansing the house,
it would help push
the negative energy out.
DENNIS: The second thing
the spiritual advisor did
was bless Aundrea and I.
Visualize God's protective light
surrounding you.
Focus on that light of energy
just encircling you.
It's gonna protect you
throughout this blessing.
[ Blows ]
AUNDREA: After we finished
with the sage stick,
we used holy water and we went
around all of the entryways --
doors, windows --
and blessed them
and sealed them
from any negative energy
coming back into the house.
ALL: By the grace of the Lord,
this house is protected.
Our next step was to actually
try and just cleanse the house.
In the name of Jesus Christ,
leave this house.
ALL: In the name of
Jesus Christ, leave this house.
[ Bell ringing ]
DENNIS:
We walked around the house,
and we were told to ring a bell.
It was meant to break up
the evil spirit.
You're not welcome
in this house.
Leave this house.
ALL: You're not welcome
in this house. Leave this house.
AUNDREA: I'm hoping
now that the house is cleansed,
it'll stay quiet for a while.
I actually felt like a weight
was lifted in the house.
The air felt lighter.
It felt better in here.
DENNIS:
Regardless of what happened
with the cleansing
and the blessing,
my family and I decided
we are going to move.
We are doing our best
to get out of here,
and we're looking at new
properties to call our new home.
AUNDREA:
It really is wonderful to
have the family back together,
but I will always be concerned
that the activity will return
in this house.
I've seen too much
in the last four years.
I'm praying that it stays calm
long enough
for us to find a new home.
AMY: Telling a family
they need to leave their home
is never easy,
but Dennis and Aundrea
are making the right decision,
and while bringing in
a spiritual advisor
may be good for the moment,
I hope they stay focused
on finding a new house
and get out as soon as possible.
STEVE: The breaking point
for most of our clients
is when they feel
physically threatened
by something
they just can't explain,
but for a family
in Starks, Maine,
it was no longer just a threat.
By the time Amy and I arrived,
the activity was so out of hand
I wasn't sure
she could get it under control.
So, Ann Marie, you live here
with your parents.
- Is that correct?
- Yes.
And what's going on?
There's a lot of
sort of unexplained noises.
We've seen things.
People are getting attacked.
Our health has gone downhill
since we moved into this house.
Whatever was here
was making us ill.
Our health just kept declining
and declining.
It felt like we were
under siege. It really did.
What are you hoping Amy and I
can do for you and your parents?
I just want to know
what to do.
I think the house is gonna
kill us. I really do.
[ Engine shuts off ]
Nothing here is sacred.
This was one of those walks
where I picked up on the living
before the dead.
I sensed right away that
their anguish was overwhelming.
I began to worry there wasn't
much I could do to help.
Ew.
MATTHEW: What?
It does not feel good
in here.
There's so much fear and anger.
Just sick.
It's almost like
nothing can live here.
There's just
all these dead people
and it's, like,
all these deaths.
This is their house.
This is, like,
the house of the dead.
Does your aunt know about
this cross thing you did?
NARRATOR: Next...
He said he went down
headfirst, backwards.
...innocent lives
are on the line.
I'm just seeing these
weird images of dead bodies.
STEVE:
After hearing how Ann Marie
and her parents' health
was failing,
I understood why she was
so freaked out,
but her reaction to the basement
was stronger than I expected,
and once I learned
what was going on,
I can understand why.
I was down here one time
with my nephew,
and two huge bins
of, like, tools
fell on me,
pinned my leg.
And it wasn't slanted
or anything like that?
It was stuff
that was stacked forever.
It was -- It was solid.
It never moved.
Something bad happens every time
somebody comes down here.
ANN MARIE: Being down
in the basement with Steve
felt a lot more safe,
but I was still unnerved.
I was still feeling creepy,
and he was very supportive,
but I couldn't wait
to get out of there.
AMY: There were people
hiding down there.
At first, I was startled by the
amount of dead in the basement,
but there were a few
in particular
that made me really nervous.
I want to say
they were, like, robbers.
You know, but one of them
was pretty bad --
on the run for a long time,
a long time.
I think this house
is a purgatory place.
STEVE: Now that I knew what
Ann Marie was going through,
I wanted to speak
to her parents,
but what she told me next
made it clear
that that wasn't gonna happen.
What's going on here?
Um, my father fell
down these stairs.
Okay.
He ended up down there.
He said he went down
headfirst, backwards.
ANN MARIE:
During the investigation,
my father was in the hospital.
I was really concerned
and really worried.
What did he say
happened?
When we got to the hospital,
he said that somebody
pushed him.
Did you believe him?
Oh, yeah.
I believed him.
I mean, he should've
broken his neck.
It's terrifying.
We had to move his bedroom
downstairs.
- After this incident.
- Right.
AMY: You could say
you can't live here.
I'm just seeing these weird
images of, like, dead bodies.
They crowd around the house,
and they're like,
"If we don't get any rest,
nobody gets any rest."
STEVE: Ann Marie's nephew spent
a lot of time in that house,
and with her dad
laid up in the hospital,
he was my next-best witness.
But as much as he wanted
a solution to all this,
what he told me made it sound
like he was part of the problem.
I've seen things
that I can't exactly explain.
Like what?
Halloween of 2011,
I was playing Bloody Mary,
and we were holding a cross
in our hands.
Then the cross
just got a little bit colder
and a little bit colder,
and finally we just set it down,
put the lights on.
It was very shocking.
I'm not in the business
of taking things at face value,
so even though Adam
looks pretty shook up,
I needed to push him
for more details.
So, let me get this straight.
Were you doing that here?
Yeah.
Where?
Upstairs.
In which room?
In my aunt's room.
Does your aunt know about
this cross thing you did?
Yeah, she's not happy.
- You blame her?
- No.
You know, I think your aunt
has a right to be mad at you.
Yeah.
I think so, too.
Yeah, so --
She's a sweet lady, so...
- I know. I love her very dearly.
- Okay.
It does sometimes feel like
we're up against something,
and I'm scared of it.
AMY: There's just
some weird **** going on.
Really strange stuff.
There's, like --
Somebody's doing, like,
all these séances and stuff,
but there's --
But they shouldn't be,
and they know it.
This whole walk, I was picking
up on the living and the dead.
I was getting
really disoriented,
but then I noticed
a common thread.
This is a very angry,
fearful house.
Everybody's confused
in this place.
It's like a frickin' madhouse.
Did they
just dig the body up?
NARRATOR: Next...
They're discarded people.
NARRATOR:...some secrets
can't stay buried.
Some of the bones
were left behind.
STEVE: My client's whole family
was facing health problems,
so I hit the archives to see
if the past held any clues.
While there,
I found the previous owner,
who had his own problems.
Angier was
a pretty prosperous guy.
He had been given the farm
by his siblings
after his father died,
but with a condition.
He had to support
his brother, George,
who was
mentally disabled.
In 1911, George
physically assaults Angier.
He leaves.
Angier closes the door
and never allows George back.
Wow.
And Angier was estranged
from the family after that.
Now, do you know
what he died of?
He died, in the house
you're investigating,
of apoplexy,
which is a stroke.
Ernie, let me ask you
a question.
I know a lot of people
were buried on the property
they lived on
back in those days.
What about Angier?
He wouldn't
have been buried there,
but there is something
you might want to know --
is that the house
that you're investigating
is either adjacent to
or encroaches on
an old village
burial ground.
Really? Okay.
There was this man,
and he was mean.
He looks like an undertaker,
just nasty.
But, like, he's very much
a part of this house.
I think he was kind of deserted
by his family.
Okay.
He's all alone.
He was bad.
STEVE:
Learning about the property's
previous owner was helpful,
but that historian
gave me a lead
that proved to be a big
turning point in this case.
When it comes to finding out
about my client's land,
I rarely get a break like this.
So, Paul, is it true that
the house I'm investigating,
there might've been a graveyard
either under it
or at least
right next to it?
Yes, that's true.
In fact, my
great-great-great-grandfather
was originally
buried there.
- He died in 1822.
- Okay.
And he was reburied
in this cemetery.
All right, so,
when did this take place?
I have a map here
of the village in 1860.
And you can see
there's a cemetery marked
adjacent to the home
that you are investigating.
This is the corner, and this
is the cemetery right here.
Okay.
And, uh, this is an 1883 map
of the same area,
and you can see there's
no cemetery at that site.
Okay. So, we know it had to
happen between those two times.
That's right.
So, how did
the moving process work?
I mean, did they just
dig the body up and...?
Well,
they did in some cases,
and in other cases, the bodies
may have not been relocated.
They may still be
in the ground there.
Somehow, these people
are dying here, or died here.
It's their -- It's their place.
The dead were just all over me,
each one trying
to share their agony with me.
I couldn't make out one voice
from the next,
so instead of telling me
about it,
they tried to make me feel it.
Like, you can't escape
their pain.
It just is not good.
Now, would they ever move
a headstone and not the body?
- Yes. Headstones are easy to move.
- Right.
Bodies are
much more difficult.
I don't think that they were
very well taken care of
when they died.
And some of the bones
were, in all likelihood,
left behind.
You know that they are,
like, the true lost souls,
the ones that people
have forgotten about
or turned their backs on.
- Do you think there's
still bodies there? - I do.
Uh, they were discarded.
They're discarded people.
NARRATOR: Next...
I was just shocked.
...dark secrets
come to light.
Scares me to death,
really.
I really feel like this house
is trying to kill us.
NARRATOR:
Can this home be saved?
WOMAN: Sadness,
confusion, fear, let go.
So, Amy, I'd like you to meet
Ann Marie and her nephew, Adam.
Ann Marie actually lives here
with her elderly parents.
She believes
that whatever's in this house
is making them all very sick
and is possibly trying
to kill them.
AMY: This was the first time
on a walk
that I almost didn't make it
all the way through.
ANN MARIE: When Amy told me she
almost couldn't finish her walk,
I was just shocked.
I couldn't imagine
what she was gonna say next.
I was overwhelmed with how many
dead were located here.
STEVE: I may have
an explanation.
This house is either built on
or literally right next door...
...to what used to be
a graveyard. - Wow.
There's just so much stuff
they didn't tell us
about this house
before we bought it.
I'd be really mad about that
if I were you.
It really pisses me off.
We would've
never bought this house
if we knew it was built
on the site of a cemetery.
It's a house
full of dead people.
They don't want
living people here.
There's one male
that's here,
and he is not okay.
He just seemed
extremely unwell to me,
but he was very much estranged
from his family.
There was a guy
named Angier Gray.
He lived and died
in this house.
He died of apoplexy,
which is a stroke.
And you said he was estranged
from the family.
Angier had to take care
of his younger brother, George,
who was
mentally handicapped,
but George got into
a physical fight with him
and left the house, and Angier
never let him back in.
That's where the estrangement
comes with the family.
This is how he looked.
Amy, do you think
this is the guy you saw?
Yeah.
Can we be influenced
by him?
I think that's
a huge possibility, yes.
I did do a sketch of the dead
down here in this room.
They were congregating,
and it was all around the bed.
That's where
Ann Marie's dad sleeps.
Right.
Just don't freak out.
Just...
Oh, my God.
When I saw the sketch
of the people
that were surrounding
my father's bed,
I thought
this is why he's so ill.
These are the people who
feel lost, who feel discarded.
They're trying to become,
like, these inhuman creatures.
Now,
one of the main reasons --
Her breaking point
for calling us in
is an incident that happened
here with her father.
Tell her what happened.
My father fell down the stairs
backwards, headfirst.
Oh, my gosh.
And when we got to the hospital,
he said he was pushed.
Could they have pushed
her father down the stairs?
I think so.
I really feel like this house
is trying to kill us.
You know, you feel bad for them
that they were stuck here
and their graves were desecrated
and stuff,
but I don't want them
to kill my family, either.
They told me they won't allow
anything to live here.
Nothing.
It scares me to death, really.
It's so hard to live
in this house.
Yeah, it just feels like
it never lets up.
Ann Marie,
now you know why your family's
been going through hell
since you've been here.
The question is,
how do you fix it?
What I'm going to say,
it's kind of difficult for me,
because they kind of
damned themselves.
They've done that
via attempted murder.
We have to proceed
as if they were some type
of a demonic presence.
They are not demons, but they
have become a type of evil.
The first thing
is to move them on,
and it has to be
a religious, holy person.
So, you know, it could be
a minister, a priest.
You know, whatever you feel
comfortable with.
The other thing is,
is that you are going to
have to have an exorcism done.
Of the land and the house.
You're up
for the fight?
ANN MARIE:
Amy told me to take care of the
dead on the property right away,
so immediately after
the investigation,
I started looking for someone
who could help.
I need our health to improve.
I need to get it done.
My goal was to get
an exorcism done.
I couldn't find anybody
to do that,
but I did find someone
who had a different approach.
So, I'm bringing in
a spiritual healer,
someone who will facilitate
people moving on
and do it in a peaceful way.
The first thing she did
was lay directional stones
to point the energy outward.
WOMAN: Making an offering
to the land here.
There's a healing energy
available
for the spirit world
and the land.
ANN MARIE:
She got her smudge pot,
and she smudged
the outside of the house.
WOMAN: Spirits of sadness,
confusion, fear, let go.
ANN MARIE: The healer came in
and mixed some herbs that
were specific to this house.
She burned the herbs, and she
smudged every room in the house
to help clear
the negative energy.
As the healer
walked through my house,
I was starting
to feel more and more hopeful
that things could improve.
WOMAN: Spirits, it's important
for you to release your sadness.
ANN MARIE: After the healer
cleansed the home,
she did a Reiki healing on me.
WOMAN:
There's a strong connection
between the physical world
and the spiritual world
which is made stronger
by coming from the heart.
ANN MARIE: During the Reiki
healing, I could feel my pain
sort of rising to the surface
and disappearing.
Do your elbows
bother you?
This one.
That's where
we hold anger.
I was really hoping
that this would help
the situation quite a bit.
You have a beautiful glow
around you.
After the house was cleansed,
I noticed a significant
difference in the way it felt.
I already feel a difference
in the energy in this house,
but I'm still going to look
for an exorcist in the meantime.
Since the investigation,
my father has returned home
from the hospital,
and he is currently stable.
He's been able to stay home.
He hasn't been hospitalized
again since then.
He's doing pretty good.
How are you doing?
Thank you. Good.
Yeah?
You having a good day?
Yep.
Doing all right today.
The most important thing
is my parents' health.
Having them safe
is my number-one priority.
So, I'm not sure
if we still need an exorcism,
but time will tell.
AMY: I'm really glad
that Ann Marie
was able to get some form
of help so quickly,
but since her family's
well-being is on the line,
I hope she finds an exorcist
immediately.