♪♪
[crying]
What's happening?
(narrator)
Tonight, on Dead Files
Revisited...
- Scared the heck out of me.
- It did, huh?
(narrator)...a second look
at some of Amy and Steve's
most terrifying cases.
...so he told me
I should leave.
(narrator)
New information...
It just became real for me.
...startling revelations.
- Someone could really get hurt.
- (narrator) First...
I have nightmares
about this house.
...in Chicago, Illinois
It disfigured him horribly.
...a vengeful spirit
Ah! He hurts people!
...haunts more
than just dreams.
At night, I'm afraid
to open my eyes or move.
- (narrator) Then...
- [crying] This is not right anymore!
...a return
to Waxahachie, Texas
[crying]
Something terrible's
happened to her!
...where a family restaurant
Don't slap one of my children.
...harbors pure evil.
(Amy)
I think this girl
is being murdered.
(narrator)
Did they listen to Amy?
This is very upsetting to me.
(narrator)
Or, does the nightmare continue?
♪♪
In the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy Spirit,
Amen.
You're mine. You can't escape.
My name is Amy Allan.
(crying)
What's happening?
I see dead people.
It seems like the devil.
I speak to dead people...
He's pissed off.
...and they speak to me,
- I felt real fear.
...but there is only
one way to know
if my findings are real.
I think she's being murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Shiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective...
Serial killer pops in my head.
...and I know every person--
every house has secrets.
- Nobody believes me.
- It's my job to reveal them.
- Do you think there's still
bodies there? - I do.
(Amy)
But Steve and I never speak.
We never communicate
during a investigation.
- Until the very end.
- You got problems-- I got news for you.
When we uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
- This is our house whether
they like it or not. - Or time to get out.
This is their house--
the house of the dead.
[whispering]
[eerie music]
♪♪
(Steve)
Some of the most important
evidence of any kind
of investigation
is witness testimony,
but like our case in Chicago,
sometimes not everyone
is willing to talk.
Our client Cristina
had been terrified
of unexplained
activity their whole life.
Her parents had been reluctant
to admit their own fears.
Looking back, all I can say
is that our work on this case
definitely shook things up.
♪♪
- You're concerned for your
father, I understand? - Yes.
But what about you?
I have heard voices
and I have nightmares
about this house.
I haven't lived here
since I was 18
and they still continue.
The activity that's been going
on here has put a strain
on my relationship
with my parents,
because I don't really like
to come over here
if I don't have to.
There was a boy
and half his face was gone.
Why are you calling us in now?
My daughter is only 3,
and when she's staying here.
She's having
these kind of bad dreams.
[eerie music]
[cars passing]
This walk was torture.
Every entity I met seemed
to be against me.
I am seeing
this older woman, uh...
Ow!
- What's wrong?
- Ah!
The only time I could actually
interact with them
was when they wanted to cause
physical harm.
So I look and there's a guy
who came from below the house.
He was punching me nonstop,
and he's got blood on him--
like dried up blood,
and he told me I should leave.
(Steve)
Cristina had witnessed some
pretty horrific stuff,
but her dad, Mark,
was still living
in that house,
and after what he said he saw,
I was shocked he
hadn't moved out already.
Cristina's concerned
for your safety.
You gotta be a little
bit worried yourself,
I would think?
Very worried.
Cristina went ahead
and wrote Steve and Amy
without me knowing,
and I, at first,
was apprehensive,
but for my family,
I decided to do it.
- Now, do you know any history
about the house? - A little bit.
I know that a doctor lived here,
and he was a TB doctor
here in the area.
I see what appears to bees here?
a black mask coming up
the stairway.
- It scared the heck out of me.
- It did, huh?
It's very frustrating--
it's hard to even accept it,
because I can't prove it
and I can't--
I really can't understand it.
(Steve)
I couldn't deny Mark's logic,
but as he told me more
about what was happening
that frustration of his
turned to fear.
Okay Mark, so why did you
bring me here?
I see a male apparition
and a female apparition.
- He had a suit on, I recall,
a tie and glasses... - Okay.
...and she was in
some sort of dress.
This is his preferred area
in here.
Ah! He's pissed off--
he's angry.
People definitely see this guy.
(Amy)
This man was irate,
and I needed to find out why,
but as soon as I tried
to talk to him
he became even more
aggressive and attacked.
Ow! Ah! He hurts people.
He's making my head hurt.
Ow! Knock it off!
Cristina and Mark
were freaked out, but it was
actually Mark's wife, Lori,
who seemed to be
getting the worst of it.
Not too long ago I went to bed
one night, and all of a sudden,
in a sound sleep I felt
hands come up and grab my waist.
The most frightening out of
the experiences I had was
getting touched in my sleep.
You're not equipped to fight
back. You feel helpless.
I don't feel safe.
I'm facing Mark, so it couldn't
have been him.
Now I'm more nervous
of going to bed.
If I wake up in the middle
of the night I'm afraid to,
like, open my eyes or move.
Bad...
Lots of physical ****.
He's like...
****
beating on
somebody in the bed.
Hates 'em!
(Amy)
Right then, I realized
I wasn't the only one
being attacked,
and I knew that whoever
lived in this house
was in serious danger.
[hisses]
****
Dammit!
I gotta get away from this guy.
He's really hurting me.
I got scared, because I thought
I don't know what this dude's
fully capable of.
(narrator)
Next...
It disfigured him horribly.
...the face of evil is exposed.
I know what he **** looks
like now, to me.
(narrator)
And in our second
investigation...
- One, two, three scratches appear
on my arm. - That could be a problem.
...the dead leave their mark.
She's getting panicked, again.
[whispering]
(Steve)
Sometimes the best clues
come directly from our clients,
and when Mark told me
a doctor who had treated
TB patients
lived in his house I knew I had
to follow up on it.
What I didn't know was
just how far this one lead
was gonna take me.
So, it turns out that my client
was right that the house...
...was occupied by a doctor at one time?
- Yeah, Dr. George Gindele.
He was
a General Practice doctor,
and he had 10 children.
- And he did treat TB patients
in the house? - Yes, he did.
This guy sounds like he put
a lot on his plate.
He must have been terribly
stressed out in his life.
Ah! That hurt.
I know what he **** looks
like now, to me.
Very professional,
dark brown hair,
average build,
as far as I can tell.
He does have a coat on.
This angry man had been
attacking me throughout my walk,
but now that I can see
what he looked like,
I actually started
to feel a little sorry for him.
He had a very, very
**** stressful life.
Very **** stressed
about work.
You mentioned that he had some
tragedy in his life?
Yeah, some years before
a couple of his sons
were going through
an apple orchard,
and this man suddenly appears
and telling them
to get out
of the apple orchard.
Then he takes a shotgun
full of buckshot...
...and starts firing 'em at the kid.
- You all right?
There's a lot of pain
in his head.
And, the oldest son, George,
got hit I the face,
and he didn't die, but it
disfigured him horribly.
[whispering]
And then, I see trees around me.
That's when things get sketchy,
but then he came back here.
It's a tragedy,
but 8 years later, 1926,
the doctor gets
a house call and he decides
to take George out with him,
and the house call
is around the Des Planes River.
George got out of the car,
evidently, and he went
and he sat on the edge
of the bridge
looking down at the river.
This guy, he fell down--
he slipped on the ice.
Meantime, Dr. Gindele comes back
and the kid's missing.
They finally found his body
a couple of weeks later
downstream.
- This had to devastate him.
- Oh, it had to,
and it just broke him up.
It just destroyed him.
Maybe he kinda
snapped a little
when it-- when, you know,
'cause he's not dealing with it.
It triggered his pain
and he got really angry
pretty quickly.
Losing your own child
in such a traumatic way
has to be unbearable,
and after I tracked down
one of Dr. Gindele's
grandchildren I found out
just how bad it can get.
This is a picture of Dr. Gindele
and his oldest son, George.
He had a nervous breakdown
and as a result
he went and lived
in Oak Park
with one of his sisters,
and my grandmother stayed
in the house with the children.
So, he just left them there?
Well, yes.
I feel very tired here.
Just...
worn...
out.
- This might be that old lady.
- Okay.
Something about
the family is broken.
She felt really lonely,
confused.
I don't like it.
- It's a little **** unnerving.
- (narrator) Coming up...
Are you seriously
gonna do that?
what happened after
the investigation?
Peace be with this house
and to all who live here.
[whispering]
♪♪
Amy, I want you to meet Mark,
his wife, Lori, and his
daughter, Cristina.
Now, Cristina is actually
the one who called us in.
Even though she doesn't live
here she's still getting
tormented by nightmares.
Now she has a 3 year old
daughter who's having
similar dreams,
and she's getting very
concerned about it.
When I first met Amy,
I was really anxious
and nervous
about what she was going to
reveal to us.
I'm outside and I meet this guy
who's definitely the most
powerful entity
that's in this house.
He looked very professional.
He was obsessed with his work--
extremely stressed out man.
This house was
occupied by
a guy by the name
Dr. George Gindele.
Chicago had a big
tuberculosis outbreak.
He treated a lot of
those patient's right here
in the house.
He had 10 kids here.
That's a lot of stress.
I was curious if this
could possibly be
the guy you saw?
I did do a sketch of him.
- You guys take a look
at the sketch. - Wow!
Wow, is right.
That's the apparition I saw.
100% definitely!
That's the guy I saw.
Oh, my God!
I didn't know what we were
dealing with or who,
or what was actually going on
here, so when I looked
at that picture,
it just became real for me.
Now, did you get anything else
from this guy?
He had had two big accidents
during his life.
The first one I saw
was that he slipped on ice.
The other one I saw,
he was all bloody
and there was something
wrong with his eyes.
I have nothing that says
Dr. Gindele had any accidents,
but there were two events
in his life
that basically destroyed him.
This is the doctor
and this is his son, George Jr.
- The guy that lived on the farm
decided to take a shot at him. - What?
Shot him in the face and neck,
so this kid was disfigured.
My dream.
I had a nightmare one night,
and there was a boy
who looked like he was
in his late teens
and he looked like he had
been shot in the head
because half of his face
was missing.
At that moment,
I just couldn't
hold my composure anymore,
because it had been such
a horrifying dream for me.
It was something
that I felt trapped in
and I didn't even
live here anymore.
[sobbing]
This is hard for me to take.
(Cristina)
You guys thought I was crazy.
- You all right?
- I'm okay.
Now, you mentioned
falling into the ice.
George Jr, in April of 1926
fell accidentally,
or he jumped into
the Des Planes River.
I have his death certificate.
It just says
"Accidental drowning."
This eventually destroyed
Dr. Gindele.
- He moved out of his house, left
his wife with their nine kids... - What?
...moved in with his sister,
and left her here alone.
Now she stayed here until
she died in 1960.
This is his wife, Julia.
(Lori)
Oh, my gosh.
Could this be
the woman you saw?
Yes.
With him-- you'd experience him
in a lot of very different ways.
I did do another sketch of
something that he does.
- That's really freaky.
- He's touching you.
When the second sketch came out
with me being assaulted
it really kind of
freaked me out,
because I didn't realize
it was just us imagining things
or if things were
really happening,
but now I knew it was for real.
I know you guys got
overwhelmed with a lot
of information tonight,
but the big question is
can you live here
without all the torment
and protect your
three year old from having
the same issues?
The first thing would be
to get a clinical psychologist
who practices providing therapy.
The second thing is
you need to bring in
a chaos magician.
Cristina's nightmare's
at home--
how do we fix that,
or can it be fixed?
When you wake up you need
to tell them
"You get out of my house.
You leave me alone--
you leave my daughter alone."
Will it affect her daughter?
- Well, that remains to be seen.
- Are you going to do what Amy suggests?
I'll do my best, but that
psychologist isn't for us.
He'll have to leave.
We'll force him to leave.
Are you seriously gonna do that?
(Mark)
Immediately following the
investigation it seemed like
everything was calm,
however after a few weeks
things started
picking up again.
There's has been a lot
of strange things
still happening here.
When Amy told us
what to do in the reveal,
I still feel what she said
is probably the right
thing to do.
We're following Amy's advice
in that we're going
to do something,
but we're going to do
it in a way
that's comfortable for us.
Peace be with this house
and to all who live here.
Amen.
I've known Mark and Lori
for approximately 16 years,
and Mark asked if I would do
a blessing of the house
to get rid of whatever
was going on,
and it
was quite an experience.
We did have a priest come in
and perform a house blessing
in hopes that that solves
the problem.
We ask that this water call
to mind our baptism in Christ
who has redeemed us
by His death
and resurrection.
Father Bob got my entire
family together
in the heart of the house,
in our dining room, where
we had an opening prayer...
Peace be with this house
and to all who live here
and for this we pray.
Lord, hear our prayer.
(Mark) I assisted Father Bob by going
with him room to room...
...holding the holy water while he continued
to bless each room of the house.
(Father Bob)
Let this water call to mind
our baptism in Christ.
He took us through
the entire home blessing each
room from top to bottom.
Let this water call to mind
our baptism in Christ
who has redeemed us
by His death and resurrection.
Bless this house
and those that live in it.
I asked Father Bob
to say a prayer
for the soul of
Dr. Gindele and his family.
If he's lost and trapped
in darkness and death I wanted
to help him move on.
In His great love the God
of all consolation
gave us the gift of life
and to all who have passed,
especially Dr. George Gindele
and his family--
may they all have a place
of light and peace.
In the name of the Father,
and the Son...
...and the Holy Spirit, Amen.
- Amen.
Immediately after the blessing
there was a feeling of calmness
that overcame us.
It was a peaceful feeling.
Hopefully, we do see a
difference and we can
assume a normal life.
In the week
of the investigation
my daughter has not had
any nightmares,
but since my parents
haven't done what Amy suggested,
I still don't feel safe here.
(Amy)
I know that not everyone
will be comfortable
with my advice
but Dr. Gindele
suffered greatly in life
and now in death he poses
a serious threat.
Even though it's not exactly
what I recommended,
I really do hope
that this blessing
will bring peace
and that Cristina's nightmares
come to an end.
If you own a restaurant
your odds of failure
are overwhelming,
but throw in reports
of violent paranormal
activity at your place
and it's
a recipe for disaster.
Our clients
at The Catfish Plantation
in Waxahachie, Texas
were under constant threat,
and it was on us to fix that,
or they would have to walk away
from their own family business.
So Shawn, you sounded pretty
concerned on the phone about
what's going on here?
My daughter works up here--
she's 16 years old.
My mother, my husband
and my dad are up here,
and we've seen apparitions,
shadow people,
things moving around,
so it pretty much
runs the gamut.
So why are you
calling us in now?
Things have seemed to kind of
start picking up, like objects,
you know, being thrown at people
in my kitchen,
and my daughter, Amelia,
was physically slapped.
So we're worried about her.
I was really concerned about
the safety of people
in the restaurant,
primarily my family,
and that was the breaking point
right there, you know,
don't slap one of my children.
Now, what do you know about
the history of this place?
There's a legend
about a love triangle
that occurred near
this location
where a young lady
was murdered.
[crickets chirping]
(Amy)
Every walk I do is dangerous,
and I always try to stay safe,
but the entities I encountered
here needed my help so badly
that I had to risk everything
if I was going to help them.
I'm getting
a really weird smell.
What a weird smell.
What is this?
Blood. It's blood.
I'm tasting it.
Yeah. Yeah, it's blood.
Ugh.
- Did you have any idea it might
be haunted? - (narrator) Next...
I'm not right!
This is not right anymore!
...Amy is overpowered.
Uh, and then I can't breathe
and it hurts.
[crying]
[whispering]
A restaurant kitchen
can be a dangerous place.
There's hot ovens, knives,
open flames.
So when Shawn told me
people had experiences in there
I knew that cuts and burns
were going to be
the least of their problems.
I have had what appeared
to be scratches,
like three--
one, two, three scratches
appear on my arm.
In my experience, working
with Amy, that could be
a problem.
Working in a kitchen environment
is very dangerous
in and of itself,
and if you have
a wildcard,
like something
throwing objects,
someone could
really get hurt.
(Steve)
Anything else in the kitchen?
I was here one day
and I see something like
a white apparition.
It looked just like a person.
It had arms and such.
Okay.
This area is not good.
I'm seeing a weird shadow
of a female...
...and her arms are long
and thin.
She's stretching out.
I have been jumped a lot
during my walks,
but this was the first time
that I actually allowed
it to happen.
[groaning]
Are you okay?
No. She can't feel
her arms or legs.
And she can't breathe.
****
Why are my arms so long?
[panting]
Oh, my God! What's happening?
Oh!
I'm not right.
She's not right anymore!
Something terrible's
happened to her!
Oh! My arms!
Oh, my God!
She can't find what she's
looking for.
That moment was one
of the most
painful and terrifying
I've ever experienced,
but it allowed me
to start seeing what was really
going on there.
She's a mess. She's a mess.
She does not understand
what's happened to her.
(Steve)
Despite all of Shawn's
unexplained experiences
she seemed to be handling
the stress very well.
Her husband, on the other hand,
was still coming to terms
with what he'd seen.
When you bought this place
did you have any idea
it might be haunted?
No. I was a total skeptic.
What changed your mind?
One time I came in through
the back door
and passed one of our
assistant managers who was
working there,
and all of a sudden
this loud bang crash
happened right behind me.
What we call our "fish racks"
flew over his head
and landed right
in the middle of the kitchen.
(Amy)
Being jumped was exhausting.
I almost couldn't continue
my walk, but once I got outside,
I picked up
on the young girl again
and had to find out more.
She throws things in here--
in the kitchen.
She looks scary to people.
[bell rings]
She's trying to understand
what is going on.
She's getting
panicked again.
And then I can't breathe
and it hurts.
Like she can't breathe.
I think this girl
is being murdered.
[groans]
This doctor is apparently
interested in her
in a romantic way.
(narrator)
Next...
She might be dying.
...an unhealthy obsession
turns deadly.
He hits her once in the head
twice in the body.
[whispering]
(Steve)
Shawn had mentioned something
about a love triangle
that ended in murder.
I know a story like that,
no matter when it happened,
would have made headlines.
Normally, I would have to go
to the local archives,
but I caught a break
when I found a local police
chief who knew all about it.
April 30th of 1929,
there was a young lady murdered
on that property area.
Miss Lola Roller,
and this doctor,
Dr. Harry Dowling
is apparently interested
in her in a romantic way.
So what does she wind up
doing next?
She leaves the Temple area
and comes to Waxahachie
to get away from him.
She comes up here
where her uncle lives,
Mr. H.L. Hempkins.
Well, Dr. Dowling
forced his way in.
Mr. Hempkins gets ahold
of the Sheriff.
They find Dowling
and her are involved
in a physical altercation
going on at that time.
(Amy)
At first, I wasn't sure
if allowing this girl
to jump me was a good idea.
But I finally
started picking up on
what she went through
and it began to pay off.
I hear the men talking.
There's like...
three of them.
I feel pain.
Some kind of pain.
The Sheriff can see
that Dr. Dowling has a weapon.
The Sheriff tries to get the gun
away from Dr. Dowling.
- Dr. Dowling fires three shots
at Miss Lola... - Okay.
...hits her once in the head,
twice in the body.
Oh, God!
**** She can't move.
She's so angry.
She can't move her
**** legs.
Mr. Hempkins,
from behind the Sheriff,
shoots Dr. Dowling
and hits him in the head.
See how much it hurts
and then I can't breathe.
She thinks
that she might be dying.
Amy, I'd like you
to meet Shawn and David.
They are part owners
of the Catfish
Plantation Restaurant.
There's a lot of activity
in this place
and their concern is--
is it safe for them,
their family and their guests?
During the reveal
I was concerned
that Amy would find
something really bad
after all the blood,
sweat and tears, literally
that I've put into this place
it would be totally devastating
for our entire family.
I was in the bathroom area,
and I started to get
this really intense
negative feeling.
I felt a woman near me
and then I did something
that I very rarely do--
I let her jump me.
(Steve)
Is she trying to communicate
through you?
What was going on?
Well, I can show you,
'cause we have
Matt's camera, so...
Let me see it.
- Oh, my God! What's happening?
- (narrator) Next...
I don't like that you did it
to be honest with you.
...will crimes of the past
It would be devastating
for our entire family.
...condemn this restaurant's
future?
She, uh-- she feels trapped.
[whispering]
(Steve)
Is she trying to communicate
through you, or what
was going on?
Well, I can show you,
'cause we have
Matt's camera, so...
Let me see it.
Oh, my God! What's happening?
Oh, my arms!
Oh, my God!
Something terrible's
happened to her!
Seeing what Amy had
experienced--
it kinda upset me.
It made me feel really bad.
I was really concerned
about her well-being.
I don't even know what
to say about this.
I don't like that you did
it to be honest with you.
What is this woman's deal?
What's the story with her?
She's very confused and scared.
She's constantly
reliving her-- her death.
I think I have an answer,
but I'm not sure.
Back in 1929, on April 30th.
Her name was Lola Roller--
she was 19 years old.
Dr. Harry Dowling
fell in love with her
and she wanted nothing
to do with him.
He drives up,
goes to the door-- knocks on it.
The uncle answers...
he went to go get his
gun and then get the Sheriff.
When they come back,
the doctor-- he's got a gun
in his hand.
The Sheriff tried to get
the gun away from him--
a fight ensues.
The doctor, he puts one in her
head, two in her chest.
Oh.
When Steve shared Lola's story
with us-- it was very sad.
She was trying
to get away from this person,
and there was nothing anyone
could do to stop it. - It was very tragic.
She does not know
that she's dead.
The way that she sees herself
is basically like a shadow,
and her limbs
are extremely long and thin.
I kind of thought that maybe...
...that's how living people would
see her... - Okay.
...like a female shadow that's
kind of distorted.
I'm having trouble understanding
how that would actually look.
Well, I did do a sketch.
(Steve)
Well, that's odd.
Take a look at that.
Wow!
I've seen that.
This is very upsetting to me.
So, is it possible
that the shadow thing
she's seen is Lola?
Yes.
My biggest hope
is that Lola is going to
find some sort of peace
and not blame herself
for her own murder
and not have to relive
those experiences over
and over again.
- (Steve) What does she do?
- Well...
she will break things.
She'll throw things around, um,
especially in the kitchen.
We have our racks
that we use for cooking,
and I was almost out of
the kitchen
and they flew
off the shelf
and flew over our
assistant manager's head
and landed right behind me.
Oh, wow.
Now, one of the biggest
reasons we're here
is she's been scratched
on her left arm.
Show Amy where
you were scratched.
It was just right like that.
Just like three
fingernail marks.
Wow...
that's her.
(Steve)
We still haven't answered
your most pressing question.
Is it going to be safe here
for you,
your family, your guests?
And even more importantly...
...is it going to be okay for you to pass
it on to your kids? - Right.
For that answer I'm going
to turn it over to Amy.
As far as she's concerned,
there are two people
you need for this.
You get another medium,
and a grief counselor.
So they have to come together,
the medium and the counselor?
Yes.
Okay.
The medium might get jumped,
so they should take this
slow and steady.
The grief counselor
will really take over
as far as counseling
this person who's dying.
(Steve)
I gotta ask the question
I ask all my clients.
Are you gonna take Amy's advice
and do what she says?
Since the investigation
the activity has pretty
much been the same.
Because so many people
were having all
of these experiences
and because we had
so many people coming in
in general,
I felt it was very important
to follow Amy's advice
to make sure this was a safe
environment for everyone
including our guests.
We're going to get Lola moving
towards a better
afterlife experience.
[clock ticking]
The first person that came in
to assist us was David,
and he is a grief counselor
in addition to
being a psychic medium.
This is where I feel
a female energy is in this room.
Um, and this female
that I'm feeling in here.
I'm feeling a tremendous
amount of, like,
she's weeping.
When I was with David,
we basically went through
the restaurant
and got what his impressions
were about
the different types of spirits
that were here.
He immediately did
pick up on Lola.
She did come forth
for him immediately.
Because when I come in here,
um...
[crying]
she's talking about how she--
she feels trapped.
The grief of this female
is occupying this space.
She just feels that she
is not going to move on.
One of the things
that David helped do
is to reassure
that Lola's actually
making that transition
and is feeling
more confident
about her situation.
(David)
What's going to be
a process of time--
you're going to have to work
with her to build up that trust
is what I'm feeling with her,
and then she'll be ready.
I feel that she is gonna
eventually move into the light
and move into the spirit world,
and I think that you
will be able to help her
do that, so that's--
...that is what I'm feeling
is going on in here. - Okay.
(Shawn)
After David came in we had
assistance from Amanda,
who is a medium
and does a slightly different
process than David.
Do you have one that
likes to bang the pans?
They like to move the pans
around, yeah.
The fact that you're acknowledging her
and her grief is helping. - Okay.
Lola has trust issues.
She has developed
a relationship with Shawn.
Shawn has been working
with her,
so she was comfortable
talking to her.
Let's go where you feel her
the strongest.
(Shawn)
I-- okay.
(Amanda)
"It's my fault. It's my fault
It's my fault" is what I'm
getting with her.
So find a way to say
"You were a victim--
you couldn't help it."
Amanda suggested
that I need to speak with Lola
and help her to
cross over to the other side.
Lola, honey, you were
not responsible
for anything
that happened to you.
Lola, he can't hurt you
anymore.
He's not physically
able to harm you.
You have control
and it's totally fine
for you to let go.
Yeah, I'm getting that she's
listening to you.
Her energy is going from dense
to more light.
Okay. This is why this
is a good spot for her,
so if she's not ready to go, but at least
she can help elevate... - Right.
...she's not stuck.
- She's lifting.
- Okay.
Now that we've gone forward
with Amy's advice.
I feel like it's
helped me to understand
a little bit more
why I'm in the position
that I'm in.
I think that this is something
that we can live with
and work with,
and I believe that
everything is headed
in the right direction
at this point.
(Amy)
Lola has endured unimaginable
pain in life,
as well as death,
so I'm relieved to see
that Shawn followed my advice
and is personally helping her
to move on.
As long as Shawn
keeps an open dialogue
with Lola,
I'm hoping that
they'll both find peace.