Somebody killed themselves.
NARRATOR: Tonight
on "Dead Files Revisited"...
I've had customers
run out the door.
A second look
at some of Amy and Steve's
most terrifying cases.
That's just really tragic.
New information...
Put everything in
a whole different light.
...startling revelations.
DONNA: It couldn't be
anything but paranormal.
I had to come to grips
with that fact.
First...
He wants revenge.
...in Potsdam, New York...
I need a solution
'cause it's got to stop.
...a ruthless spirit...
This is where
he took his last breath.
...rules an army of dead.
He had control
over everything.
Then...
The more work we do,
the more the activity picks up.
...a return
to Deadwood, South Dakota...
They might have had
some sex slaves.
...where scars from the past...
Some of them beat the crap
out of the girls.
...could be lights out
for this casino.
I may never
get the place fixed.
Did they listen to Amy?
Are you gonna do
what she says?
Or does the nightmare continue?
DONNA: If you do not leave now,
you will be removed.
Leave now.
"You're mine.
You can't escape."
My name is Amy Allan.
[ Crying ]
What's happening?
I see dead people.
It seems like a devil.
I speak to dead people.
He's pissed off.
And they speak to me.
I felt real fear.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
I think she's being murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
Serial killer pops
in my head.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
Nobody believes me.
It's my job to reveal them.
Do you think
there's still bodies there?
I do.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
You got problems.
I got news for you.
When we uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
This is our house...
whether they like it or not.
Or time to get out.
This is their house,
the house of the dead.
STEVE: This case seemed like one
I should've identified with.
We were in my home state
of New York,
and our client was
a retired homicide detective.
But I got to tell you,
there was nothing familiar
about what we discovered
in the town of Potsdam.
Donna had moved her family there
for the peaceful community,
but the unexplained activity
in the house
sounded more like a war zone.
DONNA:
We've been terrorized here
with the things
that have been happening here.
Our son has seen things,
I've been woken up
and seen things,
and my skeptical husband
has even seen things
and been touched.
And how old is your son?
He's 17.
Latest apparition he saw,
he ran into my room screaming,
and that's why
I wrote you guys a letter.
I need a solution
'cause it's got to stop.
Since I retired,
I came up here
for peace and quiet,
but it's been nothing
but a nightmare.
I feel trapped
living in this house.
That's why I called
Amy and Steven.
This was the last stop.
I'm pissed off,
and the fight's on.
AMY:
This was, without a doubt,
one of the most physically
and emotionally draining walks
I've ever done.
Immediately, I had to look past
the dead's disturbing disguises
and focus on the real threat.
I saw these men
who were walking like monkeys,
like gorillas.
It just looks like
their, you know, skin
has been painted on black.
One was saying that
they get used up.
He was a living person.
So,
what's going on up here?
This is the worst of it.
The other night,
I was sleeping,
and, all of a sudden,
right in my face
was this wolf-looking guy,
and he went "Raah!"
right in my face.
You're not on medication
or anything, right?
No.
DONNA:
As a retired detective,
the activity here
was so ridiculous
that looking at it in
an intellectual, factual way,
it couldn't be anything
but paranormal.
I had to come to grips
with that fact.
And then another time,
I woke up about 3:00
in the morning for no reason.
I see this huge, big guy
standing on the side of the bed,
looking at me.
He was about
at least over 6 feet tall.
He didn't look like
he was happy.
He was kind of menacing.
I saw an older man.
He's very condescending.
He has an elitist attitude
about everything.
He's very scary.
MATTHEW:
Is there any connection between
him and the painted people?
AMY: He put them to work
for him.
He painted them all black
and creepy-looking,
and he makes them
show themselves to people
and scare them.
When they're all used up,
they become like dust.
And what happens, then,
when they turn into dust?
They cease to be.
STEVE:
Donna's son was a big part
of why she moved out here,
but unfortunately, the activity
was hitting him the hardest.
And after he described
his experiences,
I understood why his mom
was so concerned.
I've experienced
some things here.
I was sleeping on this bed,
and I woke up,
and I saw a man dressed in an
army uniform standing over me.
And he was
just staring at you?
Yeah.
And then I thought it was
a human being standing there,
so I kicked him in the face.
My foot went through his face,
and he disappeared.
I don't like being here
alone.
Okay.
AMY:
This older man I saw --
He is pissed,
because when he died,
he kind of lost control
over everything.
This older man was already
really powerful,
and his intense desire
for control worried me.
Okay.
He says
that most of these people
were men when he met them.
He made them
what they are now.
But it was when I saw
he was motivated by revenge
that I realized how dangerous
he could be.
When he was alive,
I think he was haunted by them,
and he flipped
that whole **** around.
STEVE:
During these investigations,
I've come across
some pretty bizarre stuff,
and I still consider myself
a skeptic.
But if I witnessed
what Millard did,
I think I'd have
a different perspective.
I was laying on the sofa,
gonna take a nap,
and I felt a vivid touch
on my face,
and it felt like this...
Okay.
Like a finger?
Yes.
And I opened my eye,
and it was nothing.
And I remember feeling
some kind of a --
I don't know --
a presence.
I am a skeptic,
and I don't really buy into it,
but I knew this process
was important to Donna,
so I was supportive.
I'm glad Amy and Steve came here
to set things right.
Whatever was there that caused
that, I couldn't explain.
Okay.
AMY:
I feel a lot of pressure.
Somebody pushing.
I want to say this is the leader
and his little posse.
He doesn't like living people.
They violated him...
and he wants...
revenge.
NARRATOR: Next...
There was no signs.
There was nothing.
Sudden death spawns
an eternal evil.
He got really mad.
And in
our second investigation...
She was dying
of internal injuries.
...will this casino's luck
run out?
He's trying
to scare them to death.
STEVE:
Even though Donna's husband
was reluctant to put
a label on it,
everyone in that family
was having strange experiences
in that house.
So I reached out
to a former owner,
and she told me
her father passed away there.
I knew it would be hard for her
to talk about it,
but I had to follow it up.
STEVE: And what'd your father
do for a living?
He had been in the service.
I brought a picture
to show in his uniform.
So, what kind of a guy
was your dad?
He was a tough guy.
It was either his way
or the highway.
He was basically
a very strict dad.
What kind of a relationship
did you have with him?
I was always cautious.
He would get heated
pretty quickly.
Makes you be on eggshells.
I was, like, on eggshells a lot.
AMY:
I see that older man in here.
He doesn't like it
when people know about him.
It **** freaks him out.
It disturbs him. He hates it.
I had been following this
dead man for most of the walk,
and I started to get the sense
that he was just as domineering
while alive.
He had control
over everything, every aspect,
and then he died
and, like, "Oh ****
He's dead."
I think it was unexpected death.
He didn't have any control,
and he got really mad.
What the **** is that about?
STEVE: Betsy seemed
to be holding it together,
so I asked her to show me
where it happened.
And as she walked me through
her father's death,
I picked up some info
that ended up being
a crucial part of this case.
Does it bother you
being in here?
It's very strange
being in here.
This is where
he took his last breath.
It was very hard
to come in here
and know that
this is where it happened.
Right.
MATTHEW:
Do you know how he died?
Some kind of, like,
aneurysm, sudden heart a--
you know,
sudden death, whatever.
And what year did he die?
He died in 1992.
Now,
was there any indication
that he had a heart problem
or a heart condition?
There was no signs.
There was nothing.
You know, it was something
completely unexpected.
Do you know
when he was alive?
'80s, '90s.
Who was the first family member
to come home?
I was.
You were?
Mm-hmm.
What did you see?
Well, I found over in this area
a small round circle of blood
where he had hit his head.
AMY: Right then, I began to
experience the old man's death.
The agony was overpowering.
But it allowed me to view things
from his perspective.
I feel a pain --
back and my neck --
pretty **** bad.
I feel anger and stress.
[ Sighs ] ****
Did you clean it?
It's the first thing I did
after I pulled myself together.
It was important to me
'cause I didn't want my mom
to see that when she got home.
He died alone,
and that's just really tragic.
AMY: When I'm hearing
his thoughts,
I'm thinking, "I'm dying.
I'm dying. I'm dying."
NARRATOR: Coming up...
Oh, my God.
...what happened
after the investigation.
Go into the spirit world
and leave these people alone.
STEVE: Amy,
I'd like you to meet Donna.
Now, she's being terrorized
by the things
that are going on in this house.
DONNA: Meeting Amy
the first time was really scary.
I was so afraid that
she was gonna tell me
that I had to move.
STEVE:
This is her husband, Millard.
He's had a few experiences,
but he remains a skeptic.
With that,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy
and have her tell us
about her walk.
Well, the most powerful entity
that I met in the house
was this older dead man
who was very controlling.
The way that he died
was maybe an aneurysm
or a heart attack,
and this really upset him
because it was something
that was out of his control.
And this was probably
in the '80s or '90s.
[ Scoffs ]
He is upset
with living people
because he feels like
when he died,
he was very disrespected.
There's a guy
that died in this house in 1992.
The name of Cleave Lytle.
He died unexpected, died
of a heart attack in the garage.
Great.
Now, I talked to his daughter,
Betsy.
She described him as a "My way
or the highway" type of guy.
Not affectionate.
Now, I got photos of him.
He was actually in the army.
He was in the army.
Wow.
Your son said he saw somebody
in an army uniform
standing over his bed, right?
He sure did, plain as day.
DONNA: When Steve
pulled out that picture
of the previous owner
in an Army uniform,
I was so glad that my son was
not sitting there to see that
because that was
the same apparition
he saw in his room one night.
STEVE: And here's a couple
of pictures of him years later.
Wow.
I did do a sketch.
Take a look at that.
Oh, my God.
Mm.
It could pass for him, yes.
That's definitely him.
The eyes are right on.
What's this guy's story?
He is kind of a leader
of about 25 other dead men.
Oh, boy.
And what he did to them was,
he painted their skin black,
and he makes them
kind of move like a gorilla.
The living people would probably
perceive them as shadow men...
Huh.
...but they're not.
Oh, my God.
Now, you've mentioned
you've seen shadow figures
in the kitchen.
In the kitchen.
You look out
of the corner of your eye,
and you see something
about 6 foot tall,
and I go to look, and it...
Away it goes.
And I've seen that several times
recently.
I did a sketch
of what I saw.
Ooh.
What the ****?
I don't know if you're gonna
want to see this.
Oh, my God.
This is exactly
how I see that.
DONNA: When Steve brought out
that second sketch of me
standing there with those
painted people tormenting me,
that really creeped me
right out.
However, it validated exactly
what I've seen many times
in my house.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
That's crazy.
He can blind you
through migraines,
cause hallucinations,
fear and panic.
He can touch
by, like, shaking, pushing down,
feeling smothered --
things like that.
Now, you said he could
cause hallucinations, right?
Yes.
Tell Amy what you saw
in your bedroom.
When I first moved in,
I got woke up
by this horrible wolf thing.
Now, is that what he's capable
of doing, what she's describing?
I think so, yeah.
Absolutely.
What does he want?
He wants control
and to dominate.
He would probably prefer
no living people around here.
Well, you two said
you were up for a fight.
Looks like you got one
on your hands.
The big question is, is it safe
for you guys to stay here?
And is it safe for your son
to stay here?
The first thing
is to take this
quick-lighting charcoal.
And then
take the yellow sandalwood
and sprinkle it on
so it'll smoke.
Mm-hmm.
And what will that do?
Basically, she's opening a door
for the ones who want to leave.
Do you think this guy is gonna
be the last guy standing?
Yes.
So, the next thing
that needs to be done is,
you need to find a medium
and a holy person.
Hmm.
First, you're gonna
have the medium come.
Have that medium remove
the remaining dead.
Okay.
Once the medium's done,
the next day,
you need to have
a holy person
come and bless the house
and then the ground.
You down with it?
Since the investigation,
things now have gotten physical.
As I went into the garage,
something grabbed my foot,
and I fell down the steps,
cracking my knee wide open.
When that happened, I got scared
that I may not win this battle.
I decided the fight's on,
and I followed
Amy's instructions
and I lit the charcoal
and the sandalwood
and smoked my home.
I'm allowing you to follow
this smoke out of my home.
If you do not do so,
you will be removed.
Once I smoked my home,
I told some of the entities
in this house to move on.
If you do not leave now,
you will be removed.
I am granting all the power.
Leave now.
WOMAN: A spirit that you've had
in this house is still here.
I was able to find a medium
who was able to talk to the dead
that were still left here.
I'm telling you that you have
passed away, that you are dead,
and that you do not belong
in this house.
With much talk and intervention,
I think she was able to get
the angry man to move on.
You need to leave here.
This is not your home.
You need to leave this place
and go into the spirit world
and leave
these people alone.
After the medium left, even
though the place felt better,
I wanted to follow Amy's advice
and get a holy person here
to bless the home.
May rose bless this house
with love.
Using the four elements
allows for us to bring balance
back into the house.
We started with the fire
and the candles.
As you light it,
imagine health and prosperity
being spread
throughout every corner
of this house.
From there, the goblet,
which is of the earth.
And then finally, we created
the water and the air.
This is the water
that we will bless
and then use for the house
and the ground.
You're going to pour
the water over.
And then, the holy person,
she actually blessed
the grounds outside the house.
With the rising of the sun,
spirit of the east,
be with us always.
Blessed be.
This house feels like
a whole new house.
It's a major difference.
After all the things
we've been through,
I can finally look forward
to spending the rest of my days
in retirement in this home.
My husband's a skeptic,
but I'm glad he supported me
throughout this whole ordeal
because things are a lot better
with our family
now that the negative entities
have been cleared out.
AMY: The angry man
who inhabited this home
was causing a lot of harm
to both the living and the dead.
So I'm relieved that Donna
followed my advice.
Not just for the safety
of her family,
but so that all of the dead held
captive there could be set free.
STEVE: Our investigation
in Deadwood, South Dakota,
had everything you'd expect
from a town
straight out of the Old West.
But what we uncovered was
even grittier than I expected.
Our client, Ron, was
renovating an historic casino.
He claimed that paranormal
activity was getting worse
with every swing of the hammer.
And with the fate of his
entire business riding on this,
we had to get results.
STEVE:
This place is amazing.
RON: It's a great place.
Can you give me,
like, a broad idea
of all the stuff
that's happening here?
Well, we've had things
thrown around.
People hear noises,
doors are opening and closing.
You know, people are feeling
that they're being touched
and they get
really frightened.
That's a problem.
Oh, yeah. I've had customers
run out the door.
Do you know any history
about the building itself?
It was a brothel
in the past
and there was
illegal gambling here.
Why are you calling us now?
The more work we do,
the more the activity picks up.
Some of the investors
get spooked off.
I've been trying to get
financing and investors here
for the last 24 years.
The activity here
seems to put some people off,
and moving forward's become more
difficult, especially recently.
I love this place,
and it hurts me not to see
the place of my dreams
come to fruition.
[ Crickets chirping ]
AMY: As soon as we pulled up
to the location,
I knew it was going to be
a difficult walk.
I saw dead people everywhere,
and the first group
I encountered
were too frustrated
with their surroundings
to focus on me.
[ Chuckling ] The dead
don't care for the decor.
So, each dead person
tries to keep it
the way it was
when they were alive,
because it confuses them,
and that makes them upset.
It does hurt my head.
Now, would you stay over
at night alone again?
No.
NARRATOR: Next...
[ Chuckles ] I think
she did sleep with people.
...coming face-to-face
with evil.
And she was
just looking at me.
STEVE: In any casino,
the house is always against you,
but that took on
a whole new meaning
every time Ron
tried to fix the place up.
It seemed like something
was trying to stop him
from getting work done, and
even though he owned the place,
the odds weren't exactly
in his favor.
Activity picks up
as soon as we start
doing construction here.
So it's as if
whatever's here
doesn't want you
to make changes?
Yeah, exactly.
RON: There's only
two finished rooms here.
The activity has scared off some
contractors and some employees,
and it puts me
in an awkward position.
I have to try
to keep moving forward
and makes it more difficult.
So now,
have you ever experienced
anything yourself
up here?
Yeah.
There's this gray-haired woman,
and I don't know why,
but she's always laying
on the floor.
Okay,
is there anything else?
I've seen a guy
that's clothed
in dark clothing,
like a long rider coat,
late at night, dark hat.
Okay.
And moves
from the ladies' room area,
and then kind of vanishes
towards the back of the room.
The dead cowboy dudes,
someone's saying
a lot of good times over here,
drinking and gambling.
One of them says
that something bad happened.
Now that I was able to interact
with the dead directly,
I got a glimpse into what
their lives were like
until one of them insisted
that I experience how they died.
And I feel, like,
an impact in my head.
I feel like it's male.
Maybe they got shot in the head
or they shot themselves
in the head.
Well, I was laying down
over here, sleeping,
and I was laying
like this.
And all of a sudden,
I just went up like this
and, "What the..."
And I seen --
right where you're standing
is where I saw
this tall woman.
She was in a green dress
with red hair.
And I couldn't move,
and she just stood there
about four or five minutes,
and I just couldn't move.
Now, would you stay over
at night alone again?
No.
If we don't get
this paranormal problem fixed,
I might never get
any investors.
the place fixed.
There's a male who is not
a happy camper at all.
This grumpy guy,
he stays up here a lot.
At first, I didn't think
this unhappy man
would be that dangerous,
but his temper flared
and I saw his true intentions.
I feel like up here is, like,
off-limits for living people.
And he gets pissed.
He's trying
to scare them to death.
STEVE:
With everything Ron witnessed,
it was no surprise
that he had trouble
keeping employees for very long.
But luckily,
there was one bartender
who had been there for years.
After learning about
her experiences on the property,
I'm surprised she stuck around
that long.
I was here for a week.
And I am the only person
on staff
who will come up
into the 2nd floor.
I've had my hair stroked,
I've had a hand on my forehead,
and I've had a hand
on my lower back.
Can you tell if it was
a man's hand or a woman's?
It seemed to be as if a man
was escorting a lady
out for the evening.
So, is there anything else
you've experienced up here?
I woke up
around 3:20 in the morning.
I heard footsteps outside.
I heard voices.
I opened my eyes,
and there was a woman
at the foot of my bed
wearing a blue dress.
I think her hair was red.
And she was
just looking at me.
AMY: There's a woman,
and she was always talking.
You can still hear her, you
know, going on and on and on.
People, if they don't see her,
that would **** shock me.
She worked here.
What did she do here?
[ Chuckles ] I think
she did sleep with people.
NARRATOR: Next...
So, this happened
in the Fairmont,
she jumped out --
She jumped
out of the Fairmont.
...the truth
comes crashing down.
I think that they died
down here.
STEVE: Ron told me
the Fairmont Hotel
used to be a brothel.
In an old mining town
like Deadwood,
that didn't surprise me.
But when a local author
described the violence
those women endured,
I was disgusted.
STEVE:
I got to ask you a question
about prostitution here --
Was it pretty prevalent?
Yes.
The ratio of men to women
was about 50 to 1,
Okay, so how were
these girls treated?
Well,
there some of them down there
that would beat the crap
out of the girls.
Really?
Okay, so the guys could act
however the hell they wanted?
Pretty much, as long
as they didn't kill the girl.
AMY:
That's kind of strange.
They might have had
some sex slaves.
I felt so much anguish
in this building,
but had no idea why until now.
I think that they died
down here, a lot of the ladies.
It was cold.
They would not eat.
The images were horrific,
and the abuse I saw is something
that will stay with me forever.
And they're all naked,
and they put them in here.
Do you know
who is putting them here?
Men?
STEVE:
When I first spoke to Jerry,
he told me two people died
in the Fairmont Hotel.
And the story he told me
sounded like it could've been
straight out of a movie.
It was in 1907,
and, Vinegar Rowan,
a sheep herder from Montana,
had a girlfriend
who worked as a prostitute
in the Fairmont.
Okay.
And he came in one day
to see her.
And when he entered the room,
found out
that she was with another man.
So, he pulls out his gun
and then he took a couple
of shots at his girlfriend,
and he missed entirely.
So, she leaps out of bed
and grabs him by the shirt.
He reaches around with his gun
and is trying to shoot her.
Boom, boom, boom.
And shoots himself
in the **** damn head.
He's dead.
[ Laughs ]
I've seen a lot of things
in my career,
but this is one of the funniest
stories I've ever heard.
So, what was the other death,
Jerry?
Maggie Broadwater.
She had been visiting
a boyfriend in Wyoming,
and they had
had a bad parting.
And she came back and started
drinking quite a bit.
I definitely feel like
there was somebody
who killed themselves here.
A female.
It wasn't long
before she decided
she was going to jump
out of the third-floor window.
And here's
a newspaper clipping.
So, this happened in
the Fairmont, she jumped out --
She jumped
out of the Fairmont.
And she did it
very dramatically.
She was hysterical.
It says here,
"Jumps three stories and lives."
The ground was so muddy
in the road where she jumped,
she actually stuck
in the mud.
And they extracted her
from the mud
and took her
to the hospital...
Okay.
...where she lingered on
for about 36 hours,
maybe a little longer.
They thought
she was gonna survive.
But it turned out that she was
dying of internal injuries.
Really?
All over some guy?
Yeah.
Okay.
Something bad happened.
She was so sad...
like she maybe lost someone.
It was really bad.
Very, very sad.
NARRATOR: Next...
Feels like
I was meant to be here.
...dark secrets are uncovered.
That's about as accurate
of a hit that I've seen her get.
Will this casino survive?
RON:
Good or evil, leave now.
Move on.
STEVE: Amy,
I'd like you to meet Ron.
Now, Ron owns this building.
And his dream is to turn
this historic place
into a thriving hotel.
Problem is, every time
he does some construction,
the activity here
goes wild.
RON: I feel
a personal attachment here.
Feels like
I was meant to be here.
And so, I was nervous
that Amy might find things
that would make me feel
more uncomfortable than I am.
STEVE: He's worried about
his guests and his employees.
Now, Kathleen here
is one of his employees.
So, with that,
I'm gonna ask Amy
to tell us about her walk.
I came inside and there were
several dead people
who were commenting negatively
about the decor.
Basically, all of the dead
have different ideas
about how this building
should look.
He can't get
any construction done
because every time they take
a hammer and swing it,
there's --
activity picks up here.
And the activity scares off
some of the contractors.
Oh, no.
And the employees, and then we
have to stop and regroup again.
RON: I have to do
almost all the construction
and renovation work myself here.
It's a lot of work
and a lot of misery at times.
STEVE:
Okay, so what else?
When I finally made it down
to the basement
I saw several women
who were down there,
and they were nude.
And I did hear something
about sex slavery.
Makes sense, though.
This building was built
as a brothel.
The men that controlled
the prostitutes here
did whatever they wanted to
to keep them under control.
And when they didn't do
what they were told,
a lot of them,
from what I was told,
would get beat up.
Well, I did do a sketch
of that scene.
You did?
Yeah.
It's pretty extreme,
though.
RON: When Amy told me
what she saw in the basement
and presented me
with the drawing,
it opened my eyes
to a whole new aspect
of the prostitution industry
here in Deadwood.
They seem to have glorified it,
but in fact, it puts these women
in a whole different light.
I was walking by a bedroom
on the third floor
and I got that someone
had killed themselves,
that it was a female.
She had lost someone
very close to her.
And I got
that she killed herself
in a very dramatic fashion.
That's about as accurate
of a hit that I've seen her get.
There was a prostitute back
in 1907 named Maggie Broadwater.
She had a relationship
that went bad.
And she took it hard
and started drinking heavily,
before she killed herself.
Now, you saw a woman when you
lived on the third floor.
Yes, I did.
I saw a woman
and I woke
in the middle of the night
and she just stood there
for about four or five minutes.
RON:
I think that's the spirit that
was in my room looking at me.
And I think Maggie is just lost.
Just a lost soul.
STEVE:
What else did you see?
Then I met a character,
who I called the grumpy man.
He feels like
he would like the third floor
to be an area
just for the dead people
and that no living people
should be allowed up there.
He does want to physically harm
the living.
You've had investors
that have stayed overnight
and physically had their --
Arm moved.
Four or five other people
have been in that room
and they all had
the same experience.
RON: I've had the investors
in that same room
that have been touched in this
hotel, and I've lost them.
They never came back.
That would be something that
this person is capable of doing.
Well,
you guys have been hit
with a lot of information
tonight.
But the big question, though,
is are you gonna be able
to fulfill your dream
and turn this into the hotel
you wanted to,
and keep your staff,
your guests, and yourself safe?
For that,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy
to see
what she can tell us.
I believe that you can do
what you would like to do,
but it is going to take
a bit of work.
Because
there's so many layers,
this is going to take
about a year,
doing cleansings
one to two times per week.
What kind of a cleansing
are we talking about?
What you need
are basic things --
salt, sage, and holy water.
The first thing
that you're going to do
would be getting some sage,
lighting it.
What this does is it removes the
buildup of the residual energy.
And then, I want you to take
some salt and water,
mix it up, put it
into a spray bottle,
and then spray the floors
and the walls.
The holy water
is going to prevent
any more negative individuals
from coming in.
Once all of this has been done
and it's been about a year,
you will see a change.
The dead that occupy this
location -- they'll be gone.
Now, I'm gonna ask
the obvious question,
are you gonna do
what she says?
RON: Since Steve and Amy's
investigation,
the activity here has peaked.
The negativity here
has affected my business.
Business has been dropping off
for some reason.
I've recently just lost
Kathleen.
She just stopped coming in
to work.
So, now I have to do
everything that's required.
Run a restaurant, run a casino,
and try to do the repairs
and maintenance.
Got to get
this building cleansed
so that we can move forward
and get that business back
that we've been losing.
I went out
and I got some sage,
and I smudged all around
the hotel -- basements,
all the rooms,
all the hallways,
every place, every nook
and cranny that I could find.
Whoever's here,
you're no longer wanted.
Please move on
to a better place.
And then filled up some bottles
with salt and water,
and then we sprayed around the
entire premises of the building.
Maggie.
Maggie Broadwater.
Move on.
After the salt,
I got some holy water and
I spread the holy water around.
Coming up, Maggie.
In the name of the Father
and of the Son
and of the Holy Ghost,
I ask all the spirits
here within to leave.
I put more intensity
into cleaning the basement
because of the immense
negativity down there.
I want all the spirits herein
to leave now,
in the name of the Father,
the Son, Holy Spirit.
Amen.
The basement seemed to have
a whole different feel to it
than the rest of the building,
so I decided
to smudge the place again.
All the women who have
been trapped down here,
it's time to go.
Good or evil, leave now.
Move on.
Since I've been cleansing
the building,
I've been feeling relieved.
That a big burden has
been lifted off my shoulder,
and we can move forward now.
It's been a long run.
I think it's time
for a new beginning.
AMY: The activity
in the Fairmont Hotel
definitely reflects
Deadwood's chaotic past.
But if Ron continues
to cleanse the building,
I'm confident the dead
will move on
and he'll be able to finish
the renovations in peace.