She's a real freak.
NARRATOR: Tonight,
on "Dead Files Revisited"...
Able to manipulate
people's minds.
NARRATOR: A second look
at some of Amy and Steve's
most terrifying cases.
How the hell are you sleeping
in here?
NARRATOR:
New information...
It really just took the breath
out of me.
NARRATOR:
...startling revelations.
I always knew
that they were here.
NARRATOR: First...
She did die poorly.
NARRATOR:...a New York home
under siege...
SUE: I don't what my kids
to grow up
experiencing anything I have.
NARRATOR:...where
an other-worldly evil...
It was some type of alien.
NARRATOR:
...targets the young.
They definitely had their sights
set on the children here.
NARRATOR: Then...
Something's trying
to harm my child.
NARRATOR:...a return
to St. Louis, Missouri...
There's something about
bad kids.
NARRATOR:...where the children
do the hunting...
They cause really very,
very violent things.
NARRATOR:...and a dream home
becomes a playground of horror.
Her head, you know,
got chopped off.
NARRATOR: Have they done
what it takes to fight back?
It's not a game.
It's not.
Or are they still
under attack?
Give us the strength
to destroy all of the evil!
"You're mine.
You can't escape."
My name is Amy Allan.
[ Crying ]
What's happening?
I see dead people.
It seems like a devil.
I speak to dead people.
He's pissed off.
And they speak to me.
I felt real fear.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
I think she's being murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
Serial killer pops
in my head.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
Nobody believes me.
It's my job to reveal them.
Do you think
there's still bodies there?
I do.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
You got problems.
I got news for you.
When we uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
This is our house...
whether they like it or not.
Or time to get out.
This is their house,
the house of the dead.
STEVE:
We get hundreds of submissions
every week
from people looking for help,
but when kids are in harm's way
like in Rome, New York,
I know it's a case
Amy and I have to take on.
And once I heard
that Joe's wife, Sue,
had already moved out once
with the children,
I knew
that this terrified family
was at the end of their rope.
STEVE: Give me an idea
of what you're going through.
We hear banging.
I've seen apparitions.
I've been
physically touched.
I've tried to make up
every excuse in the book
other than
it being paranormal.
SUE:
We called Steve and Amy
because of everything
that was going on here.
I was scared.
I wanted to pretend
that it wasn't there,
but we needed some kind
of answers.
What really made me
believe in it
was when
my 8-year-old daughter,
you know, she heard
people talking --
whispering.
You had actually left with
the kids at one point, right?
Yes, I moved out
for 11 months.
[ Sniffles ]
I just couldn't take it
anymore.
I don't want my kids
to grow up experiencing
anything I have.
AMY: Even though
every location I visit
presents
it's own unique challenges,
there was something very unusual
about this walk.
So, in my opening,
I saw all of these thick trees,
and there were all these
Native American warriors
standing with their
bow and arrow drawn.
This Native American guy says
that there is some kind
of a family of beasts,
and they think
that they're ghosts.
These things
are occasionally trying
to enter the house.
They're very dark,
and they look
kind of like human beings,
but they're definitely not.
I faced something
I've only encountered
one other time -- aliens.
Were they living?
I don't know yet.
They just look creepy.
STEVE: Sue had mentioned
she was physically touched,
which is bad enough.
But when she told me more
about what happened,
it made total sense
why she and her daughters
moved out for nearly a year.
There was an incident
in the living room on the couch.
Okay,
what happened?
I felt this...grope.
So, I'm assuming
it was forceful.
Okay.
AMY: These things
are pretty tall.
How tall?
Well, see where
that dent thing is?
About that tall.
These dark creatures
looked menacing,
and as I was able
to make out more details,
the situation looked worse.
Their head kind of jets forward
on a long neck
and they're hunched
and you can really see
their shoulder blades
and then really long arms
with the long fingers.
The way they surrounded
the house was threatening.
And suddenly, I saw
what they were looking for.
They definitely have
their sights set
on the children here.
Maybe, these are what
the Native American warriors
are fending off?
Maybe they are trying
to protect the kids.
STEVE: How's this
for a difficult situation --
Sue's husband, Joe,
inherited the house
from his grandparents.
But instead of it providing
a secure place
to raise his family,
they were being terrorized.
And it looked like
Joe was gonna have to choose
between the safety
of his wife and kids
or preserving the legacy
of his ancestors.
STEVE: When did
your grandfather die?
He died
September 10, 2001.
I think that he had
a massive heart attack.
He was a hardcore smoker --
three packs a day.
He actually passed away
right here in the kitchen.
Okay.
Okay, so, what kind of a guy
was your grandfather?
He was
Sicilian-American immigrant.
He was very tough, hard-nosed,
old school Italian --
somebody
that I looked up to.
I actually have a picture here
of him and I
from when I was
a little guy.
Both my grandmother
and grandfather
were really important to me,
and I can't just walk away
from my house and my land.
It's just not
the type of person that I am.
Would they want you
to stay here
and fight whatever the hell
is going on?
They, you know, instilled in me,
you know, you never give up.
[ Sighs ]
I think that this is a male.
He's pretty dang old.
He's probably, like, 70 maybe.
Yeah, I think he's Italian --
a heavy, heavy smoker.
He's not a bad guy.
So, you know
when he's from?
Maybe he died
in, like, the 90s --
1990s, early 2000s.
Do you know
how he died?
I think
he had a heart attack.
Maybe it was emphysema,
'cause I can't **** breathe
for **** from him.
NARRATOR: Next...
It all seems
to center around this guy.
NARRATOR:
...lost souls lash out.
She was mutilated.
NARRATOR:...trapped
in a gruesome Hell.
Her head got chopped off.
NARRATOR: And in our second
investigation...
I think that I was pushed.
NARRATOR:
...evil spawns a dangerous game
of child's play.
He was pretty **** powerful.
STEVE: Even though both his
grandparents died there,
Joe had a lot of good memories
in that house,
but he might have been
the only one that felt that way.
Turns out
Joe's grandparents' death
was just the tip of the iceberg.
There was a lot more tragedy
attached to this problem.
It all seems to center around
this guy -- Henry J. Kobler.
It started at the age of 9
when his dad died.
His father
was about 34 years old
and passed away
of unknown reasons.
34 is young.
It is very young.
Okay.
But it continues.
In 1901,
his grandmother
was picking berries
one day on the property
and was attacked by a bull
and killed.
She was mutilated.
All right.
AMY: There's this crazy lady
who does run around outside.
And she did die poorly.
What do you mean?
Her head, you know,
it got chopped off --
or ripped off more.
It's not a nice, clean cut.
Oh, my gosh.
It's messy, very messy.
STEVE:
One tragic death on a property
would be bad luck,
two, maybe a coincidence.
But after what I found out next,
I couldn't deny there was
some sort of pattern
happening here.
This is probably
the darkest part of his life.
He had a daughter.
Her name was Ella.
And in 1920,
she was 16 years old,
and she was struck
by a car.
Wow.
She was an only child.
Oh, geez.
This guy can't catch a break,
can he?
Correct.
The tragedy in this guy's life
is overwhelming.
This Native American guy
is saying,
like, how it's not safe here.
There's no place
that's safe here.
Everyone's at risk.
The dark figures
I'd seen earlier
had disappeared for the moment.
And for the first time,
the spirits protecting this land
were able to tell me more
about the location.
He is saying
that it's just
for ghosts to live.
So he just wants to help
and clear the area out.
Of what?
Living people.
STEVE: By the time
I hit the local library,
I didn't think
there was anything left to find.
But I caught a lead
on another family
that lived there.
As it turned out,
their time on the property
was filled with nothing
but death and heartbreak.
Now, Mary,
when I did my research,
I came across
a couple of deaths
associated
with the Jocelyn family,
but you said
there was a lot more.
There was a lot more,
yes.
Okay.
How many
are we talking about?
They had 10 children.
And four of those children
died as babies.
And then they had
two young adults die
from tuberculosis,
which was very prevalent
in that era.
AMY: I'm seeing
those weird creatures again.
A lot of children
they would eat.
I do see, like,
the kids are being bit.
Open their chests.
Kids?
Kids.
It's pretty gross and sad.
NARRATOR: Coming up...
I'm getting so ****
out of here.
...what happened
after the investigation?
To all the beings,
seen and unseen,
heal this family.
STEVE: Amy, I'd like you
to meet Joe and Sue.
The activity in the house
is ripping them apart.
It got so bad last year,
Sue actually left
with the three kids.
The night of the reveal was,
you know, full of anxiety.
I was very apprehensive,
very nervous to find out
what they actually found.
I met this
older Native American man.
What he said was that this place
was not meant
for the living to be in.
STEVE: The first white settlers
on your land
was the Jocelyn family.
They had 10 kids.
Six of them died.
1874-- the Koblers
moved into your property.
Most of the tragedy surrounds
a guy named Henry J.
His father drops dead --
34 years old.
He gets married.
His 16-year-old daughter's
coming home on a bicycle.
She gets hits by a car
and killed.
I got a picture of her.
AMY: Wow.
So, it's like
there's nothing but death
surrounding this property.
AMY: A bit later
when I went upstairs,
I encountered an older man.
He looked Italian,
and when I was around him,
I couldn't breathe.
Like, I felt that he was
a very heavy smoker,
and he either died
of a heart attack or emphysema.
And I think that he died
in the 90s or early 2000s.
JOE: Grandpa
was a heavy smoker,
worked construction
his whole entire life.
My grandfather passed away
in the kitchen,
and my grandmother passed away
in what is now our bedroom.
JOE: When Amy spoke to us about
Grandpa still being around,
it was beyond comforting.
It was like I always knew
that they were here,
but to hear it from somebody
that can actually see
is, you know --
it's reassuring for sure.
This is his grandpa,
and that's him as a baby.
AMY: Oh, okay.
I did do a sketch
of the person I met.
Oh, geez.
That's your grandfather.
Trust me.
Oh, my gosh.
I miss him.
He watches the kids.
I'm just glad to know
that he too watches over
the little ones
'cause that's how he was with me
when I was a little guy.
STEVE:
What else did you see?
I saw this thing, like,
trying to get into the house.
It was odd.
It was very, very tall.
It was kind of hunched
by its neck.
It did not look human.
I did do a sketch.
Oh, I'm getting so ****
out of here.
JOE: When Steve
pulled the sketch out,
I didn't even want
to look at it.
It was not something
that you normally see,
nor anything that I imagined
she would ever find
here on my land.
I think that these things
harmed children in the past --
like, way back when.
I was being told
that, in fact,
it was some type
of alien creature.
****
I know it's a lot,
and they're trying
through subtle ways
to have the living people
get out of the area.
Since Native Americans
are guarding your land,
I suggest
you contact a local shaman
who can help you
remove the dead
that have been attracted
to your property.
In the meantime,
this is black salt.
Take just a little bit
of this
and put it at the entrance
of each bedroom door.
STEVE:
So, Joe, I got to ask.
Are you gonna take Amy's advice
and do what she says?
JOE:
Since the investigation,
the paranormal activity
has stayed the same.
I'm fed up with it.
I'm just ready
for things to be taken care of.
WOMAN: Balance, peace,
harmony, love, and joy
be restored
to the home of Joe and Sue.
Sue and I definitely took
Amy's advice seriously,
and we contacted a local shaman
to come in and clear the dead
from the property.
I know you've been
through a lot.
You've been
through Hell and back,
but everything
that you're dealing with
can be resolved and healed.
JOE: To see somebody
with that kind of confidence
and with that kind of attitude
was very reassuring.
All my honorable ancestors
and spirit guides
are with me now.
I call into this space
the healing power
of God's white light.
JOE: Her plan of action
was to go outside
and start a bonfire
and do a blessing outside.
I call upon you great spirit,
great mystery,
and all the beautiful beings,
seen and unseen,
to assist us to heal this land,
to heal this house,
and to heal this family.
JOE: Her explanation was
that the bonfire's
gonna open up a portal
to let the dead pass through
and give an offering
to the Indian spirits
that occupy the land here.
If you could please make
an offering to the fire.
When you create a sacred fire,
it makes a vortex
and the spirits
are attracted to it.
And so, their souls,
their spirits
can transition and go on
and find peace and joy
and happiness.
Thank you to all the beings,
seen and unseen,
that have joined us here today
to help heal this family.
JOE: Then, her next plan
was to do a blessing inside.
I'm gonna begin
the cleansing of the house now
by opening sacred space
and calling in spirit
with my drum and my rattle.
STEVE: The shaman used
the rattle and her drum
to break up the residual energy
that was here
as a part of getting the dead
to pass on to the other side.
After the shaman
did her cleansing
of the house and the property,
it's definitely a relief
and just a sense
of peacefulness in the air
instead of how it used to be.
To have our house cleansed
makes me look forward
to happy times with the family
and sharing and spending
time together once again.
[ Laughter ]
AMY: It's a good thing
the Native Americans,
along with Joe's grandfather
were watching over the family,
or things could have been
a lot worse.
And I'm pleased
they followed through
and blessed their house
and land.
But, unfortunately,
since there's nothing
they can do
to remove the aliens,
Joe and Sue will have
to closely monitor the activity
for as long
as they stay in their home.
STEVE:
When I was on the NYPD,
there was nothing worse
than a mom telling me
she feels helpless
in protecting her kids.
So when a terrified mom
in St. Louis
called fearing
for her children's safety,
I knew we had to find out
what that hell was going on
and fast.
Three years ago,
me and my children
moved in the home
with my sister,
and little things
just started happening --
noises, footsteps.
And then everything
just started to get physical.
Okay, what happened?
Haley, my 10-year-old,
was hit with an object.
SHANNON: Being a parent,
you always want to protect
your children no matter what,
but under the circumstance,
I really did not know
what to do.
There was
so many crazy things going on,
I just had to call
Steve and Amy.
This a picture of them?
Yes.
And that's her?
This brush
came from nowhere
and just hit her
in the back.
It terrified me
because something's trying
to harm my child.
That was the last straw.
That's why
I called you guys.
Since we have moved out,
my sister is in more danger.
It's gotten worse.
Okay.
AMY: This was an extremely
complicated and dangerous case,
and it all started the moment
I stepped out of the car.
Someone here,
and I think
it's this tall, scary man.
Right away, I saw what
this aggressive entity
was capable of.
He's able
to manipulate the living body.
Like, he can cause physical pain
in the body.
And I knew
that whoever lived here
was in serious trouble.
[ Groans ]
Wait.
What's wrong?
He is
pretty **** powerful.
Hey, I'm concerned.
It's become a nightmare.
NARRATOR: Next...
How the hell
are you sleeping?
NARRATOR:...the dead of night
hides an even darker secret.
They cause really very,
very violent, bad things
to happen.
STEVE: I could tell Shannon
was barely holding it together.
I mean,
her sister and her own children
were being physically attacked
by something
she couldn't even explain.
Then when she told me about
her own experiences,
it was obviously just too much
for her.
I am sitting here.
As I look
toward this way,
apparitions came to me
one after the other.
Now,
describe the apparitions.
The first one,
it was like a gladiator.
And then
there was another one.
It was just a white,
like, tall, long mist.
SHANNON: When I first saw
the three apparitions,
every emotion
just filled my head.
I was scared.
I just wanted it
to be a dream.
It's not a game.
It's not.
AMY:
That guy is here.
MATT: Who?
The tall one.
[ Groans ]
He was able to manipulate
people's minds like puppets
and cause them to hallucinate.
This dead guy
was extremely powerful,
and up until this point
in my walk,
I thought he was the only entity
the living had to worry about.
And there's a whole bunch
of kids.
What are they doing?
These kids orchestrate
really very, very, violent,
bad things.
This group was out of control
and way more dangerous
than the old man.
I don't this place is good
for kids.
I don't think this **** place
is good for anybody.
STEVE:
Shannon had enough.
She packed her kids and split.
But her sister Crystal
had her life savings
tied up in that place
and refused to leave.
Now, part of me respected that,
but after I heard
what she experienced,
she might have better off
taking off with her sister.
My bed shakes.
The first time it happened,
I thought it was an earthquake,
but nothing else
was shaking but the bed.
Show me how it shook --
how hard.
What are we
talking about?
Well, I was kind of sitting
like this,
and then I just started moving
like this.
Like, somebody was,
like,
on the other end,
like, pushing it.
I was so excited when I was able
to buy my first home by myself.
And I moved into it,
and it's become a nightmare.
How the hell are you sleeping
in here?
I really don't sleep.
That's not good.
That's gonna take it's toll
eventually.
Mm-hmm.
It already has.
AMY: This tall, scary man,
he does stuff.
You know what I'm saying?
He's a very physical presence.
That was the moment
I began to see the old man
in a different light.
Even though he was violent,
his intentions
were not as bad as I thought.
He's able to interact
like a living person.
He's, you know, kind of, like,
torturing people
to get them out of here
because of these kids.
So, he thinks
he's helping the living
to get them
to leave here
before something happens
to them?
Yes, he does.
He does believe that.
STEVE: I knew what I was about
to ask Crystal next
might be tough on her,
but it had to be asked,
both for her sake and the sake
of our investigation.
We haven't talked about
why I'm really here --
the staircase.
Yeah.
Take me through
what happened.
So, basically I just walked
up the steps,
and then all of a sudden...
I fell down the stairs.
And then I fractured my elbow
at the bottom of the stairs.
How do you think
you fell?
I think
that I was pushed.
At the time it happened,
I felt hands on my shoulders,
and I have no explanation for it
because no one else was here.
I'm really concerned
for you.
You were almost killed.
That would have killed
most people.
Yeah, one of the kids
probably wouldn't have made it.
AMY:
These little kids that are here,
I think that they...
are really damaged now.
MATT:
What do these kids do?
They cause really very, very,
violent, bad things to happen.
I don't like this.
NARRATOR: Next...
They were buried
on the property.
...the hunt for answers
puts Amy in danger.
'Cause he's doing
some pretty bad ****
I don't really want
to be down here anymore.
STEVE: I had spent
enough time with Crystal
to know that underneath
that brave face,
she was scared and scared bad.
And she needed two things if she
was gonna save her home --
hope and answers.
I managed to trace the land
her house was built on
back to its first owner,
which then led me straight
to one of his descendants.
MARCIA: Basil William Alexander
was my third great-grandfather.
What can you tell me
about him?
He was a self-made man --
made a lot of money.
This is a picture of him
when he was in his heyday --
quite a prominent man.
He's a big guy.
Even though this looks like
he's a healthy, well-fed man,
death records show
when he finally died at age 79,
he actually died of marasmus,
which is malnutrition.
He wasted away
to nothing.
AMY: This tall, scary man,
he's very thin.
He's very lanky.
I think he, you know,
kind of did
maybe shady things, you know,
to make money, you know?
This is going pretty back.
You know, like, 1860s.
Sometimes in death,
people's personalities
will fracture,
and they'll appear to me
like different dead people,
but they're not.
They're simply different aspects
of the dead person.
When I started to get in there
to see things,
he got really sad and was, like,
kind of, like, vulnerable.
He didn't like that,
but now he's very angry.
1860 is what we show.
He bought 80 acres.
We have a map here
that shows his land.
He had a home there.
He had a rock quarry,
a vineyard.
He had slave quarters.
Now, do you know
how many slaves he did have?
Family records show
that during the Civil War,
he had up to 23 slaves.
That was families --
you know, men, women,
and, of course, their children.
And, you know, if they died,
they were buried
on the property.
AMY:
The tall, scary man,
he definitely has
a lot of control
over the other dead people here.
There's something about...
bad kids --
well, bad children.
And then I'm hearing
"head master."
You know, that they're,
like, **** demons
and, you know,
they don't have souls anyways.
I don't know
what's going on here.
This time,
I'm getting weird, man.
I want to say
that he lost a child.
I think he lost a son.
STEVE:
Turns out Basil's slaves
weren't the only ones
buried on his property.
Out of the 13 children
that were born to him,
only six of them
lived to adulthood.
He believes in Heaven
and Hell and God,
but he denounces them.
I finally understood.
This man was broken,
without faith,
and had nothing left to lose.
'Cause he's doing
some pretty bad ****
I don't really want
to be down here anymore.
NARRATOR: Next...
These childlike entities
orchestrate catastrophes.
NARRATOR:
...the shocking reveal.
Oh, ****
Are you kidding me
right now?
NARRATOR: Clients face
the terrifying truth.
It was shocking.
It scared me.
NARRATOR: And the living
determine the fate of the dead.
Give us the strength
to destroy all of the evil!
STEVE: Amy, I'd like you
to meet Shannon and Crystal.
Now, they're sisters.
Crystal actually owns this home,
and Shannon was living here
with her four kids.
Activity got so bad here
a few months back,
she packed up herself
and the four kids and got out.
Crystal is still in the house,
but she's here alone.
I knew Amy
was gonna find something.
I mean, it wasn't a question
of whether or not she would,
it was just
what she was gonna find.
AMY: I met
an elderly gentleman.
He's very capable of interaction
on a physical level.
People
definitely see this guy.
I saw this person
push himself out of his skin,
and then he was just, like,
a skeleton with muscle.
This man can cause the living
to have hallucinations.
These girls talk about
hallucinations for both of them.
Mm-hmm.
These three images just came
to me one after another.
When Amy explained the entity,
it really just took the breath
out of me.
It terrified me so bad.
People were very afraid of him,
and after quite some time,
I got that he did lose a child,
and that it was a son.
Now, back in 1860,
this property was acquired
by a guy, B.W. Alexander.
1861,
he moved his entire family here
along with his 23 slaves.
Now, you said this guy
was tough, smart,
and intimidated people.
Well, Alexander was
a pretty powerful man
in this neighborhood
and became
a self-made millionaire.
Now, this guy had 13 children
altogether.
Six of them died.
Four of them were boys.
You said he was skinny?
Mm-hmm.
He died of malnutrition.
Oh.
The other thing I got
was these childlike entities.
They like to orchestrate,
like, catastrophes.
I actually believe whatever
is in my house wants to hurt me,
so when Amy mentioned
the childlike demons
causing chaos in my home,
it was shocking.
To have it validated was scary.
I was seeing
a lot of different scenarios
that these kids
were planning,
and one of things was something
that I sketched.
STEVE: Okay.
Oh!
Are you kidding me
right now?
This is what
I was afraid of.
CRYSTAL:
When Amy showed me this sketch,
I literally just could not
control my emotions anymore.
It's an unbelievable feeling
to see
that someone else sees
what happened to you,
and they weren't even there.
It's amazing.
Stop it.
I was standing on the landing
at the top of the stairs,
and then I felt a push.
I tumbled, like, completely,
and I fractured my elbow.
Well, Shannon,
the big question is,
can she stay here safely?
For that,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
So, you need to bring in
a chaos magician.
AMY: Chaos magicians
are very powerful and effective,
but I only recommend using them
in the most extreme cases.
So, everything would be
cleared out then?
Yes.
Including the kids?
Yeah.
But I do have a concern
for you being here
in the meantime
because
they're going to feel
extremely threatened
and very unhappy.
Basically, you're telling her
she should
go stay someplace else
until she gets this guy in.
I think you should.
Yes.
Would you be able
to swing that?
Since the investigation,
the activity has not let up.
Most nights,
I stay with my best friend
or my boyfriend.
And I come home to get clothes,
and I leave back out again.
I left my home
for a couple of days,
and I came back
to check things out.
I saw some weird things.
I came home one day
to find this empty space here.
See, it looks like
there's shoes missing.
See how they're all lined up?
Came back a couple says later
only to find this.
It looks like kind of a pyramid,
triangle sort of thing.
Why would someone do this?
It scared me,
and it was hard
for me to explain it away.
MAN: I feel bad
that so many atrocities
have happened around here.
But these people,
they are innocent.
So, I followed Amy's advice,
and I found a chaos magician.
I can feel the pain.
You know that you are done,
and it is time to go.
CRYSTAL:
I hope that the chaos magician
can take all these entities,
round them up,
and head them out.
I love my home,
but if this does not work,
I'm moving.
MAN:
Cross them through!
Let them cross
through water and altar.
Drag all the dead to the altar.
CRYSTAL: The first thing
the chaos magician did
was perform
a voodoo altar ritual.
It's to help the entities
cross over and leave my home.
MAN: Look at all we've brought
for you.
The Baron calls you home.
Let go of your pain.
Let go of your suffering.
CRYSTAL:
And then the chaos magician
told my sister and I
to let go of the anger
and the hostility
we felt towards these spirits
because it would help them
to cross over.
There are things here
that are not of the dead,
but forgive them.
Be at peace in your heart.
In your mind, you might
even say, "I forgive you."
Move on.
The next ritual was
the archangel cleansing ritual.
Those seven archangels
of creation,
walk with me
to make sure nothing remains.
The purpose
of the angelic ritual
was to remove
the demonic influences
that Amy had picked up,
to give them a choice
to leave on their own accord
or to get forced to be expelled
from the property and the area.
Descend into our space.
Descend down into our circle,
oh, Michael great angel,
the son --
he who vanquishes evil.
Surround great Marshall.
Marshall, archangel.
Archangel of Mars,
of victory and strength,
grant us that, today,
we shall have complete victory
over all the negative spirits.
Give us the strength to dispel
and destroy all of the evil!
CRYSTAL: When the chaos magician
was calling on the archangels,
I can't really explain it,
but it was kind of like
I was feeling a light,
so to speak.
My house feels comfortable.
I feel like it's my house.
I don't feel the eyes
on me right now.
At this moment,
I feel like the dead
and the entities
are out of my home.
I just hope they stay out,
and I'm gonna do everything
that Amy suggested to me
to keep them out.
AMY: I'm really glad
Crystal and Shannon
followed my advice.
Now that a chaos magician
has been in the home,
they should be able
to live in peace and quiet
for a long time to come.