Somebody's gonna die over there.
This house wants people's soul.
There's this man. He
makes them kill themselves.
They each suffered
fatal blows to the head.
She was attacked.
Mommy wasn't acting
right. Something's wrong.
He's insane.
This seems like a possession.
I just hear death.
My name is Amy Allan.
God.
It's like, "I'm going to get you."
I see dead people.
Her face was all demonic.
I speak to dead people.
He's like, "You think you can
stop me? Because you can't."
And they speak to me.
- What is he trying to do?
- Kill them.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
Something happened. Bam, bam, bam!
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Am I seeing what I think I'm seeing?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
They're everywhere.
It's my job to reveal them.
This guy's got the
markings of a serial killer.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end...
Is this dead guy doing that to her?
...when we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
That's it.
...or time to get out.
Somebody's gonna die
over there soon, yeah.
I'm in East Flat Rock, North Carolina.
It's about 30 minutes from Asheville.
I got a call from a
young woman named Briana.
Now, this poor kid's
story broke my heart.
Both her parents died violently
while living in the house,
and she blames it on the paranormal.
Now, she thinks whatever killed them
wants to take her out next.
Before Amy arrives,
I have to clear the area
of anything that could
influence her findings.
Personal items, photographs,
and religious texts
have to be covered or removed.
When I'm finished,
tonight's walk can begin.
There's something
weird about religion here.
Their faith has been lost.
Who is it you're
saying lost their faith?
The people who live here.
There's this man...
and he's creepy.
This crazy, manic guy
manipulated them into
losing their faith.
He's, thin, tall, white.
He looks young. You
know, he looks like...
I don't know...
you know, 20s maybe.
He turns you from the good to the bad.
That has something to do with
why they lost their faith.
And it's because he's just...
He's rancid.
So, Briana, when
we spoke on the phone,
you sounded pretty upset.
Now that we're here,
what are you hoping
that we can do for you?
I want to be able to keep this home
and not be afraid to come in here.
I grew up here.
I just don't want to give it up.
There's just so much
family history here.
So, before we get to that,
what's going on in the house?
I hear sounds.
I see shadows.
Things move on their own.
And while we're in the house,
we have health problems and mood swings.
So now, who do you live here with?
My fiancé, Tracy.
So obviously, the
activity here now is bad.
Was it like that when
you were growing up?
Yes.
But when my dad passed
away, it really picked up.
Let's talk about what
happened with your father
and how he died.
He was going down the road.
And they found his truck
flipped over on its side,
no skid marks, nothing.
The truck barely looked wrecked.
- Did they deem it an accident?
- Yes.
What do you think happened?
Whatever is in here
could have messed with
him or the vehicle.
It seems like we're not meant
to have anybody in this house.
So I know this is tough
to talk about, sweetie,
but what exactly happened with Mom?
She committed suicide.
It'll be 2 years in November.
Mom was the happiest,
nicest person in the world.
Was there anything in her life
that might have got her depressed?
There was a renter,
about 8 months before my mom passed,
she found passed away.
You remember her name?
Laquada.
They were very good friends.
How did your mom commit suicide?
With a shotgun that I bought her
on the back porch.
I feel real... really guilty
since I bought her the gun.
Don't blame yourself.
If people want to commit
suicide, they're gonna do it.
Do you think the paranormal
had something to do
with your mom's death?
Whatever is in this
house is very strong.
I think it could have got
to her and made her do that.
This house wants people's soul.
Okay. Somebody's
talking about a suicide.
Something from in this direction
made somebody kill themselves.
And somebody's talking about,
"It makes you feel depressed.
It makes you feel weak,
weak, weak in the knees.
Weak in the knees."
Okay. Okay.
Really bad neck pain
here, really **** bad.
****
I'm seeing something
crawling out of water,
something, a man.
Nasty, nasty.
He died bad, bad.
And he's, like, revenge.
He's all about it.
He influences people that he dislikes,
and then he makes them kill themselves.
Somebody's gonna die
over there soon, yeah.
I haven't moved
much since she passed.
I just want to keep
things how she left it.
So tell me about
some experiences you've had in the room.
About a month after my dad passed,
I wrote a note,
this note right over here.
Okay. That's the note?
Yes.
And I wrote, "I love you, Dad.
Please sign this every night."
He initialed it.
Are you sure your mom didn't
get up in the middle of the night
and sign this for you
to make you feel better?
I'm sure.
You can see her handwriting on the back.
It doesn't match up.
Anything else going on in this room?
One day, I went to get in the shower.
I laid my phone down.
And I came out,
and my phone was in
three different pieces.
Anybody else home?
Tracy was outside doing yard work.
Have any kids in the
neighborhood that...
We don't talk to nobody around here.
It was right after I contacted you guys.
You're kidding.
Whatever's here,
to me, don't want you guys here.
Poltergeist, poltergeist,
poltergeist, poltergeist, poltergeist.
Damn.
They think they have a poltergeist,
but it's really him.
- Who?
- The creepy guy.
He's a manipulator.
There are two powerful
dead people here...
the vengeful guy outside
who wants the living to kill themselves
and the creepy guy in the house
who makes people lose their faith.
And I'm, like, seeing this,
like, dark...energy
coming in, onto the floor, onto the bed.
It's the creepy guy again.
Aah.
It's like somebody just came
up behind me and went... fomp!
On my back.
I can't breathe, and it hurts a lot.
This seems like a possession to me.
Yeah. Somebody's being
possessed by this dude.
I want to say it's a woman.
So that's bad.
Okay, so tell
me about the experiences
that you have when you're here.
I see shadows, really tall.
You can see an outline
of, like, a person.
Okay. So where do you see it?
In this corner.
It'll move, like, from
the corner to the door.
It feels evil. It doesn't want us here.
Okay. Why do you say that?
I'll get, like, sick to my stomach
when I feel it's there.
My chest will hurt.
My heart will start racing.
Yeah. It sounds like an anxiety attack.
Do you suffer from that?
No.
Are you sure?
I've tried talking to my
doctor about how sick I feel.
She's like, "You're okay."
Anything else?
Very weird mood swings
when I'm in the house.
Do you take any kind of
medication on a regular basis?
Nothing.
- And it's only when you're here?
- Yes.
When I leave, maybe 5 minutes, I'm good.
I'm really scared
that it's gonna try and
make me take my life.
Okay. So somebody in here is possessed.
What is he making them do exactly?
He's making them bad.
They're, you know,
turning into a bad person.
Boy.
Okay, it's bad in here, you know?
You've just got the bad
guy coming and going,
coming and going, coming and going.
How would he affect
the person in this room?
They would think they
were losing their minds,
feeling weird pains,
illnesses, um, feeling drained.
Do you know what he
wants from the living?
Yeah, you know, make them
kill everybody in, you know...
- In the house?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's his goal. That's what he wants.
Why? Why does he want them to die?
Because he's insane.
So, Tracy, I talked to Briana,
and, she's going through a lot.
She was telling me
how she's changed emotionally
while she's been here,
mood swings and stuff like that.
Have you noticed that?
Yes. I've noticed mood swings with her.
So what about yourself?
Have you had your
own experiences here?
Yes.
Okay. Tell me about what's going on.
We were sleeping in
the middle of the night.
And I was awakened by the door opening.
And it startled me so much
to where I had retrieved my handgun
to see who was coming in the house.
There was no one in the house.
Is it possible that the
door slammed out here
at one of your neighbor's houses?
Well, it's a different sound.
Windows open that night?
No windows open.
Okay. So anything else?
One weekend, as soon
as I opened the door,
it just hit us right in the face.
It was a horrible smell.
It smelled like a rotting
carcass, roadkill.
- Really?
- Yes.
You never found any
remains of any animal
that was dead or anything like that?
Nope, no remains.
Even under the house, there was nothing.
Now, Briana told me about
a physical reaction she gets
when she's upstairs.
To me, it sounds like anxiety.
Do you get any kind
of feeling like that?
Yes.
I can't fall asleep and get good sleep.
I'm always anxious and nervous.
Okay.
This creepy guy smells
like rotting dead things,
and it can make the living feel sick.
They're always nauseous.
I don't think anybody sleeps here.
I think it would be **** impossible.
It's too **** loud.
And because of this, I
would say that the people
become very, um, angry...
short, um...
argumentative.
I, like... I'm literally
getting, like...
Like, "Shut up."
God. There's too much. Stop it.
So, Kim, I understand
you're really good
friends with the family.
Right.
Briana seems to think
that her mom's suicide
had something to do with
the activity that's
going on in this house.
- Do you agree with that?
- Yes.
Okay. Why?
She always was really sweet and nice,
and she just seemed like...
All of a sudden, she seemed real evil.
I can't say for sure,
but she could have been demon possessed
the way she was acting.
Like, I got cold chills right
now just thinking about it.
So what about yourself? Any experiences?
I was by the steps.
Okay.
And all of a sudden, just
felt like some kind of force,
like, almost pushed me down the steps.
So how hard did you get pushed?
Just push me so I can
get an idea what you...
It was kind of like this,
and it was like... like that.
Okay. So you went off balance.
Right.
All right, so enough where
it could have broke your neck.
Right.
It scared me so bad I didn't
want to ever come back.
And I just feel like it's still here.
Now, do you think Tracy
and Briana are in danger?
Yes, I do.
I think there's something evil in here.
I'm afraid, if we don't do something,
that they could be hurt.
Okay.
We've got a lot going on up here.
It's the bad guy.
He's blocking the **** out of me.
He, has been trying to, jump me
'cause he wants to
control me and stop me.
This man is hanging upside down.
He's, like, glued to the ceiling
on his hands and knees.
And he's, like, making
his, like, mouth open,
you know, and his tongue
is, like, hanging out.
He wants everybody, you know, to die.
So, I haven't even started
my investigation yet,
and I know about three deaths
on my client's property...
Briana's mom's suicide,
her dad's weird accident,
and the renter who died
right on the property.
Now, I managed to track
down that woman's daughter,
and she thinks there's
something suspicious
about her mom's death.
Savannah, I want to
thank you for meeting me.
I know this is a tough
thing to talk about.
So, before we even get to what happened,
what could you tell
me about your mother?
She's a beautiful lady.
I actually have a picture of her.
- She was pretty. Wow.
- Yes.
Everybody remembered her.
If it wasn't her name,
it was her personality.
And your mom's name was...
Laquada.
All right, but she wound up living
in my client's house at some point?
Yes, in July 2012, and passed June 2013.
All right. So what happened?
She did gain a good amount of weight,
um, within a year, about 70 pounds.
- Seventy pounds in one year?
- Yeah.
Did she fluctuate in weight before?
Nope. She was always 120 pounds.
Now, I know you did
some digging into this
because you were a little suspicious
about the circumstances of her death.
Yes. I did manage to get
a medical examiner's death certificate.
Okay.
Okay. So Mom was 54 when she died.
And here is the autopsy
report I was sent.
So, sweetie, she's got an
awful lot of medication in her.
Yes.
What was the reason for all that?
She was in a very serious
car accident in 1997.
Okay.
Well, this is strange.
The contributing factors
leading to her death
were undetermined?
I don't know.
Something just isn't right.
Did something fail on her?
Did she have a massive heart attack?
What would all of a sudden just
cause a decently healthy woman
to just not wake up the next day?
It hurts.
I can imagine it would hurt.
Nothing worse than not knowing
what the hell the answer is.
I feel that something just isn't right.
And I have no closure,
no answers, no reasons.
You don't think it's a suicide?
I don't.
So let me ask you.
Do you think the house
might have had something
to do with your mom's death?
Yes.
I'm seeing, like, a dead lady,
probably in her mid to late 40s.
And she's short, white, plump.
And she's got bleached blond hair.
You know, she curls it.
She's wearing, like,
a sweatshirt and jeans and tennis shoes.
So she's recent, you
know, like, by her clothes.
And she's blaming the house.
She said, "The house, the house.
I know the house killed me."
I feel fear, a lot of fear.
It's almost like somebody
got their head cracked open.
Like, it feels like that to me.
This is very, very bad, very, very bad.
My God.
I don't know what the
**** is going on here.
Like, it's, like, a vise
grip on my **** head here.
So far, I've
got three tragic deaths
associated with Briana's property,
two of them her own parents.
But I need to see if
there's anything else
that could help my investigation.
Searching through old records,
I see the previous owners, the Shipmans,
lost not one but two of their children
right on my client's property.
So I'm on my way to
meet with a genealogist
who looked into the
Shipman family for me.
She says she's got information
that will definitely help my case.
So, Edith, you mentioned on the phone
the Shipman family
had a pretty tough time
on my client's property
when they were there.
When exactly did they get there?
They bought the property in 1952.
They held on to it till 1994.
Okay. So who exactly moved in?
Well, Clarence, his wife,
Elsie, and their son, Sherwood.
What were you able to find
out about Clarence himself?
Well, here's a picture of him.
He did farm those 13 acres
that he was living on,
and he was also a cook
in a local restaurant.
Okay.
I know they lost a couple of kids
while they were living on the property.
Who was the first?
So I have the death certificate
here of Martha Verda,
who was the first
child to die at age 44.
She died of cancer.
The second child to
die young was Sherwood.
He died of a sudden heart
attack at 59 years old.
Now, when he died,
he was pretty wealthy.
He had several successful businesses.
Okay. So what happened with Clarence?
Here's the death
certificate for Clarence.
He died of a heart ailment,
and he might have been ill for some time
leading up to that.
Okay.
Well, I appreciate you really
looking into this for me.
You know, there's something else I found
when I was looking into this family.
One of the most gruesome
murders in Henderson County
occurred in the '60s,
and one of the victims was a Shipman.
Heart attack, heart attack.
Somebody died here from a heart attack
or at the hospital, whatever,
but they had a ****
heart attack here.
I wonder if it happened in
the house or right outside.
He's old. I know that. He's **** old.
And then this dead lady,
the one who says the house killed her,
she points to the little dead man.
And she says, "And I'm pretty
sure that it killed him, too."
Yeah. This place is very bad.
****
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity in your home,
go to the "Dead Files"
page at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help me, Dead
Files!" to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
So Edith's tip checked out.
Turns out, there was a
triple homicide back in 1966.
And one of the victims was
a relative of the Shipmans.
I'm on my way to meet
with a local crime reporter
who says the case remains
unsolved to this day.
So, Emily, thanks for
looking into this case for me.
I appreciate that.
Let's start from the beginning.
The victims, who were they?
The first victim was
62-year-old Louise Shumate.
What do we know about her?
She lived in a town a few miles away
and worked at a music company.
She was kind of a mystery
for the investigators
in connection to the other two.
Okay.
The second victim was Vernon Shipman.
So this is the guy
that's related to the people
that owned my client's property.
Yes. He was 43.
He owned the Tempo Music Store,
which is just a couple
of doors down from here.
All right.
He actually had a romantic relationship
with the third victim,
36-year-old Charles Glass.
Glass was the manager
of Tempo Music Store.
So what do you know
about this guy, Glass?
He kind of lived a flamboyant life.
He didn't seem to care too
much about public opinion.
He wrote a book on voodoo or a magazine.
On voodoo?
On voodoo. Really?
This could be interesting for the case.
I'm seeing the revenge guy.
He was murdered.
Any idea when this was?
I'm getting like '40s, '50s.
Okay.
This vengeful guy who gets
people to kill themselves
is showing me how he died,
and it's beyond brutal.
He was on his way home from work.
To me, it seems like he was attacked.
Seems like there's multiple people,
at least four people.
It's nighttime. He's scared.
He's scared.
They kill him. They kill him.
And, and they, like,
leave him there to rot.
And now he's taking revenge.
The bodies were found July 22, 1966.
They were discovered in a grassy
field near a body of water.
They were found laying
in this semicircle,
and they were all facing up
and they all had
objects on their bodies.
Really?
You know, I've seen
cases like this before,
where bodies will be
displayed in a certain manner.
A lot of times, it's a sociopath
that's just trying to send a message.
I think, the way they were found,
a lot of people thought it
was ritualistic in nature.
Interesting.
So, what is the official
cause of death of each victim?
Well, according to
the death certificates,
they each suffered
fatal blows to the head.
Fractured skull, fractured skull.
Was anybody ever arrested and charged?
There were several suspects,
but no official arrests were ever made.
50 years later, it remains unsolved.
Okay.
Every time I walk inside,
the creepy guy flips out.
He's trying to jump
me and get me to leave.
He's making my head hurt really bad.
Yeah. He's pissed now.
He's not happy.
He doesn't want me to
know anything about him,
and he's doing everything
he can to screw with my head.
He ain't giving me ****
All I know is, he liked opera.
He liked classical music.
He was wealthy. He liked theater.
He liked literature.
Are you okay?
He was definitely in a mental
institution that's nearby.
He's very upset about this.
He was deranged his entire life.
I saw several dead
people during my walk,
so I'm meeting with a sketch
artist to describe two of them.
First, the woman who
said the house killed her.
She was probably in
her early to mid 40s.
Her face was pretty roundish,
definitely had some
lines around her mouth.
Next, I describe the creepy man
trying to possess someone
in the bedroom downstairs.
There was this black fuzz coming up,
onto the bed.
And it's surrounding the person
that's closest to the window,
engulfing them.
Is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients for the first time.
So, Amy, I want you meet Briana,
and this is her fiancé, Tracy.
I don't want to give away too much,
but this poor kid's been
through hell in this house.
As the night goes on,
you're gonna see why
she so desperately wants
to hold on to this house.
The trouble is, she
thinks that whatever's here
is after her and that she's in danger.
Now that Amy knows just a
little bit about you guys,
I'm gonna ask her to
describe her walk for us.
There was a lot of stuff going on.
Right away, I got something
about people losing their faith here.
Then, I went to the backyard.
And a woman came forward
and said that she believed
that this house had killed her.
She was pretty short.
She was, like, I want
to say pleasantly plump.
She had bleached blond hair.
You might be onto something here,
but I don't want to
jump the gun just yet.
Did you get anything
else from this woman?
Not really. It was a
very short exchange.
But I did have a sketch done of her.
It's a really damn good sketch.
Look like anybody to you?
Yeah. But the hair's
throwing me off a little bit.
I don't know if you noticed,
but one of the bedrooms
upstairs has no furniture in it.
It's, like, hardly anything in it.
Yeah.
In 2012, a renter moved into that room.
Her name was Laquada Cantellops.
Now, in June of 2013,
she wound up dying
in her sleep upstairs.
Interesting.
I have her death certificate.
Now, to this day, there's still
no official cause of death.
It's still undetermined.
Now, when I spoke with
Laquada's daughter,
she gave me a picture of her mom.
And when I show you the picture,
you're gonna know why
that sketch blew my mind.
This is Laquada right here.
Does this look like the
person you might've seen?
Yeah. It looks very much like her.
The resemblance is uncanny.
I went into the backyard.
I got that somebody killed themselves.
I didn't get much
information on who it was,
but I did feel, um, some
very horrible neck pain.
And the person who did this
was influenced by a deceased male.
And what he does is,
he actually goes around,
and he will draw the
depression out of someone
to the point where they
will then kill themselves.
Mom committed suicide on the
back porch with a shotgun.
Um, it was unexpected.
Nothing was left...
no note, no nothing.
I've always thought
something pushed her to do it.
I got a photo of her mom.
I did manage to track
down the death certificate.
All right, so this is the
official cause of death.
That's probably where
the pain's coming in.
Yeah.
Tell Amy how, the last
couple of weeks, though,
she did change.
Her attitude changed, more worried.
She wasn't the type of
person to stand up to anyone.
Okay.
And over the past couple weeks before,
she started standing up to people.
So now, this dead guy
you're talking about
that influences people
to kill themselves,
how's he do that?
I saw him crawling
out of a body of water.
And he does not look good.
And what he does is,
he gets vulnerable
people to do things...
things like shoot themselves,
cut themselves, take pills,
turn the car on, anything
to get the job done.
Okay, so you think that this dead guy
influenced Briana's mom to kill herself?
Yes.
Now, Briana's lost her father, too.
I got a photo that Briana had given me
of her and her dad.
Tell Amy what happened to your dad.
He was working on his truck one day
at one of his friends' homes.
And the truck had flipped
over on its side...
no skid marks, no witnesses, no nothing.
The cops couldn't
tell us why he wrecked.
This is why Briana's so determined
to hold on to this house.
This is the last of her
connection to her parents.
I just want to stay where my family was.
It means so much to me to be
able to stay in this house.
I recognize that I'm
pretty much the only family,
the only support group she has left.
So whatever we need
to do to keep her safe,
it's exactly what we're gonna do.
Do you have any idea who this
guy might have been in life?
Yeah. I think that he
died fairly recently.
I got the '40s or the '50s.
He died at night,
and he was on his way home from work.
I got that he was attacked
by at least four people.
He was terrified.
They killed him somewhere else,
and then they threw him in the water
to get rid of him.
So he was murdered violently.
Now he just is very angry
and just functioning off of one thing,
and that is revenge.
That terrifies me.
There's a couple of
things that you were saying
that remind me of a triple homicide
that occurred in town in 1966.
Now, the police theorize
that the victims were
murdered in one place
and then left near a lake.
One of the victims of
that triple homicide
was this guy, Vernon Shipman.
He was a
43-year-old male.
He was actually related
to one of the original
owners of the property here.
The second victim was
this guy, Charles Glass,
who was 36 at the time.
Now, Charles was his lover.
Now, thing about Glass,
which was interesting,
is that he wrote about voodoo.
What?
He self-published a book
about tales of voodoo and black magic.
Now, there was a third victim,
who was a 62-year-old
female named Louise Shumate.
Now, I got death certificates for them.
All three were basically
bludgeoned to death in the head.
Now, this happened almost 50 years ago,
and it's still unsolved to this day.
So the thing that interests
me here is the voodoo thing.
If he practiced the black
magic and the voodoo,
I would think it would be him.
Pretty mad if it's the one
that made my mom do what she did.
Anything else?
I met another person.
And this person seemed to me
to be a much larger,
direct threat as of now.
He was extremely tall, very creepy.
This person was extremely wealthy.
He was very into music.
I got that he had been in
and out of mental institutions
when he was alive.
He is very unstable.
So the guy that you were describing,
when I pulled the deed for the property,
it was a 13-acre farm.
And it was just basically
hardworking people here
nobody that fits that description.
But when you mention music,
all three of the murder victims
worked in the music industry.
Okay. Interesting.
But I don't think this creepy guy
is connected to any of them.
The other thing with him is
that he smells really bad.
We'd been away for about a week.
When we came back up
and we opened the door,
and this awful, awful smell
just hit both of us right in the face.
It was terrible.
This **** what else does he do?
He can cause physical problems.
What I got was, like,
feeling physically sick,
being nauseous, and feeling drained.
He makes the living
feel like they're crazy.
He'll make you feel intense anxiety.
And people will feel manic.
And the reason why he's so dangerous
is because he can change
and influence people.
He can make people see good people
as being bad or evil.
I'll get really sick on my stomach,
and my energy's just gone.
And my head hurts all the time.
Do you guys ever get manic episodes?
Enraged, yes.
I'll be happy one minute,
pissed off at him for no reason,
and then depressed.
Well, you're, you know,
basically living with a sociopath.
So, when I was in the
downstairs bedroom,
I saw this black mist thing coming in,
dipping down onto the floor
and then coming up around the bed.
It was this sociopath.
He was influencing and affecting
and trying to possess this person.
I felt that it was a female
and that what he was attempting
to do or doing was a possession.
****
That was your mother's room.
She's the only person
that slept there, right?
Yes. All right.
So I had a sketch done of what I saw.
I'm sorry, honey.
I don't even want to
show you this, but...
I think this is probably what
was going on with your mom.
My God.
I'm really pissed off.
My mom didn't deserve that.
She didn't deserve to be picked on.
That's kind of the way
that I felt like she was
towards the end.
The life was being strangled out of her.
Do we think he's going after Briana now?
That's what I'm afraid of, yeah.
What he wanted to have happen
and what he would like to
eventually see happen here
is to cause the individual
to kill everyone in the house.
So, Briana, when we first met,
you had told me you thought
that your mother's suicide
had something to do with the paranormal.
- Yes.
- And it turns out, you were right.
Now we need to find out how
to kick these dead people out
so that you can honor your parents
and raise your family
here in the house that
you so badly want to be in.
For that answer, I'm
gonna turn it over to Amy.
It's my belief that your
mother was, unfortunately,
being influenced by two
very unsavory characters,
one being the dead guy
that influences people
to kill themselves
and another being a dead male
who was trying to possess
her to harm others.
I think your mother, on some level,
knew that this was happening
and that, in fact, she
had a choice to make.
And she chose to take the option
that would not harm
anybody else but her.
Do you see what I'm saying?
- Yep.
- Yeah.
She would do anything to protect me.
What I would like to see happen
would be to have a priest come
and bless the property line.
And this is, you know,
going to keep him away.
All right. So what about
the **** inside the house?
The more intense thing
is to have a priest do
an exorcism of the house
to get rid of him.
It might get a little intense.
I also believe that the dead want you
to return to being more religious.
They feel like that's
something you need.
Up until now, I was mad
at God for taking my mom,
letting her do what she did.
If that will help...
...get this gone
and me to be strong enough
to get my faith back,
I will.
If these guys do what you told them,
could she start a family and live here?
I believe so, yeah.
As long as whatever it is is gone.
I mean, we're gonna do what
we can to get it out of here.
I'm ready to get this started
and get whatever it is gone.
If Briana and
Tracy follow my advice
and bring in a priest
to bless the property
and perform an exorcism,
they'll be able to safely raise a family
in the childhood home
Briana loves so much.