Nobody's at rest here.
The living aren't. The dead aren't.
One evening, two hands
grabbed me real hard. Bam!
All I heard was, "He is a murderer."
She just got attacked.
He tells me they should get out
of here as quick as possible.
I feel like this is
coming straight from Hell.
Unfortunately, this
is not a happy place.
I just hear death.
My name is Amy Allan.
God.
It's like, "I'm going to get you."
I see dead people.
Her face was all demonic.
I speak to dead people.
He's like, "You think you can
stop me? Because you can't."
And they speak to me.
- What is he trying to do?
- Kill them.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
Something happened. Bam, bam, bam!
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Am I seeing what I think I'm seeing?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
They're everywhere.
It's my job to reveal them.
This guy's got the
markings of a serial killer.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end...
Is this dead guy doing that to her?
...when we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
That's it.
...or time to get out.
Somebody's gonna die
over there soon, yeah.
I'm in the small town
of Gates, North Carolina.
It's about an hour
south of Virginia Beach.
I got a call from a woman
who was in hysterics.
She says she has a
17-year-old daughter
whose life is in danger,
and she has absolutely no
idea how to protect her.
She sounded horrible on the phone.
She broke my heart
and said Amy and I are her last hope.
Before Amy arrives,
I have to clear the area
of anything that could
influence her findings.
Spiritual items, photographs,
and religious texts
have to be covered or removed.
When I'm finished,
tonight's walk can begin.
There's some problems here.
There's a lot of anger here.
The living here, I just
feel like this anger,
it's really deconstructing their lives.
This place is not good.
It makes me feel horrible.
Some of the living here
don't know what's real and what's not.
Was that a dream or
not? Am I awake or not?
Did I see that or not?
Nothing makes sense.
I don't like it. It makes my head spin.
Oy.
I literally feel like I'm spinning.
So, Deborah, I'm glad I'm here
'cause when we spoke,
you sounded pretty
terrified on the phone.
Do me a favor.
Just give an idea of what's going on.
Hearing voices, getting
things thrown at you.
Seeing some shadow people.
And physically violent at this point.
It's attacking my daughter.
I don't feel like she's
safe here any longer.
The physical attacks on Nikki,
what are we talking about?
And just a couple of weeks ago,
she... she was sexually touched.
That kills me.
I feel like this is
coming straight from Hell.
And I don't know how to fight it.
Is it just you and Nikki that live here?
No. My husband, as well.
Nikki, she's sleeping
in my room at this point
and has been for a year.
My husband, Jeff, he's been
moved to the spare bedroom.
How's that working on your marriage?
İt can be hard at times.
I'm not gonna deny that.
You know, for
a 17-year-old
to be sleeping with
her mom at this point,
it's a little... it's a little strange.
It is. Um... but she is so terrified.
I'm... I'm afraid...
I'm... I'm afraid it's gonna take her.
I've seen the markings around her neck.
What if I'm not there one of those times
that the thing decides to attack her?
That's why I called you guys.
I'm at my wits' end at this point.
I need help, and I need big help.
Let's get some basics out of the way.
How long have you guys been living here?
We moved here in 2011.
My father, he was diagnosed
with cirrhosis of the liver
and died of liver failure.
He was a constant alcoholic.
I made the choice to be closer.
And that's why I moved here.
When did he die?
In December 2012.
All right. And how old
was he when he died?
He was 62.
What kind of guy was he?
Well, this man was loving, caring
but very strict at the same time.
He liked everything cleaned,
everything put in a spot.
Everything had its home.
He would get my mom to walk
around with a white glove
to test the dust on our
beds and our dressers.
Do you think your father's here?
Yes. I know he's here.
There's a dead guy
that is really physically present.
He looks 50s, like late 50s, early 60s.
And he's very fussy.
Almost, like, neurotic,
like with touching people.
Yeah, like a weird fixation for him.
Because of him,
I'm having these,
obsessive thoughts.
Living people here
would have, um, some
pretty bad OCD problems.
And he feels recent.
He was sick. Sick, sick, sick.
He's kind of a disaster.
Deborah, what's going on in the kitchen?
In here, we have
experienced cold spells.
It feels like a good 10-degree drop.
And it feels like when
they are around you,
they feel like they just
drain energy from you.
Like, instantly, you get very tired.
I'm gonna ask you a
silly question, though.
Are you going through any
kind of menopause or anything?
Hell yeah, I am.
But it's... that's...
That's a totally different feeling.
This is not the same.
I feel it staring at me
and watching my every move.
And it's like an evil presence.
It does not want me around.
I'm also seeing this younger guy,
and he is a freak.
He grabs people.
When he touches people,
they get like a...
They actually get, like,
the cold chill thing.
And when he touched my shoulder,
it just felt, like, icy cold.
So the younger dude, right?
When he first shows up, right?
He says, "I want to kill things."
He's very angry, this guy.
And then this dead lady shows up,
and she is all over him,
like, trying to be all
lovey-dovey and ****
But he doesn't want
nothing to do with her.
He doesn't want her there.
And he's livid.
And I just feel like
it's really taking a
toll on these people.
It's like they never
get a moment of... peace.
Ever.
So this is the master bedroom
where you and Nikki sleep?
It's the worst room,
for me, in this house.
I can't sleep.
One evening, I was laying here
in the bed with my daughter, Nikki.
All of a sudden, it just felt
like two hands grabbed me...
one on this side, one on this side...
and real hard, up against the bedpost.
At the same time. Bam!
And at the same time this was going on,
I'm feeling a third hand.
And it feels like a man's
hand grabbing me by my throat
and just kind of like pulling my neck up
and choking me at the same time.
And so how long did it last?
About 2 or 3 minutes.
I felt like I was
getting ready to pass out.
And my daughter, she
immediately jumps out of bed
and she's grabbing Bibles
and she's praying over me
at the same time all this is happening.
I'm afraid to even ask you
if there's anything else.
And there is.
And I drifted off to sleep,
and I'm wakened by a finger... fingers.
Went from here and they go slowly.
And they kept coming.
And they kept coming
until it reached my breast.
And I tried to jump up,
but the covers, they
got real, real tight.
Real tight. I couldn't
get out of my covers.
I can't push it off. I can't shoot it.
And all I felt was the hand... the hand.
I was violated.
I've
never told nobody this.
All right. It's okay.
I'm sorry. You're okay?
It's just so much.
I know, baby. I know, babe.
This is more where, like,
that man and woman are.
So what does this guy do to people?
He's capable of touching, grabbing.
Anybody in particular that he targets?
Well, I think females.
I think he's about that.
And he wants to kill people.
Is that what he's trying to do?
Yeah.
God! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Leave her alone!
After interviewing Deborah,
I stepped away for a second.
And that's when I heard
screaming and crying
coming from her room.
Stop! It's my daughter, not yours!
You have no right to touch her!
I rushed over, and all I can say is
I've never seen anything like this.
She just got attacked.
It started on her back
first, just scratching.
And then it grabbed
her again by the neck.
Geez. Look at that.
You can see the welts.
- What happened?
- She just got attacked.
It started on her back
first, just scratching.
And then it grabbed
her again by the neck.
Geez. Look at that.
You can see the welts.
I feel really helpless.
Whatever's here can go to Hell.
So, how are you doing? You're
doing better from before?
I was able to get some rest,
and I'm doing a little bit better.
- That happens a lot to you, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
Okay. Well, you're the
reason Mom called us in.
She thinks you're in danger.
Do you feel the same way, that
you're in deep danger here?
At times, I really do.
I'm scared for my family.
Okay.
I want to talk about all the
experiences you're having.
What's going on?
I'd get scratched.
Like, earlier today, I was,
and I would get scratched in the shower.
I'd feel these burning sensations.
And then I'd look down,
and I have scratches all over me.
Now, what do these
scratches exactly look like?
Are they long?
Actually, these are
what it can look like.
Geez.
So it's almost exactly
like what I saw before?
Yes.
You're not doing this
to yourself, are you?
- No, I'm not.
- Look at me.
I'm not doing this to myself.
I
wouldn't do this to myself.
Okay. 'Cause sometimes people
do things to get attention.
Yeah, I know.
Are you getting touched any other way?
Yeah.
Um, I had been sleeping
out on the couch,
and I started feeling like
something just touched me,
just like that,
and then go all the way down my body.
It got sexually inappropriate with you?
Yes. It just really freaked me out.
I've never been touched
like that before.
Okay. It's all right.
I feel like because of it
singling me out all the time,
maybe it has something to do with me.
The younger guy,
he stated that he would
like to be killing things.
Would the living in
here be aware of him?
Yeah, no, they're
aware. Yeah. Totally.
Um, maybe feeling, like, movement.
Hearing, like, mumbling,
feeling pressure on the bed,
like, when they're laying on the bed.
I don't trust him.
Jeff, I was talking to your wife,
and I understand this is
where you're sleeping now?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I mean, that can't be
good for the marriage.
It is aggravating,
frustrating, you know,
that you just want to...
Right.
Well, earlier, I walked
away for a second.
I come back and your
daughter's getting attacked.
It's something I've never seen before.
It... it just seems to
go after, you know, women.
To me, that's weak and...
- Cowardice.
- Yeah, exactly.
So you consider yourself a skeptic?
No, not anymore.
So what changed your mind?
The time when I saw for myself.
There was a pot on the counter.
It actually went off of that
and onto the floor in the next room.
- You saw this happen?
- Yes.
How did you react when you saw that?
It got me pretty angry,
I mean, to the point
where I screamed at it,
"Come on, you coward, S.O.B.
Here I am. Take me."
Have you seen anything else like that?
I've seen, like, shadow figures
out of the corner of my eye.
In which part of the house?
Usually right around between
the bedroom I'm in now
and my daughter's room.
- Okay, so right here basically?
- Yeah.
Could you tell if it
was a male or a female?
- Male.
- Okay.
I got to ask you a question
as a husband and a father.
Do you think the girls are in danger?
I don't really want to admit
it, but they are getting harmed.
I want to protect them.
I never thought I'd
ever be in a situation
that I wouldn't be able to.
And I don't know what to do.
That old fussy man, the
OCD man, he's in here a lot.
He's... He tells me, "I'm
trying to wake them up.
Wake up! Wake up!"
Wake who up?
I see...
I think it... I think it's a male,
probably in his 30s or 40s,
waking up because he is
hearing, "Wake up! Wake up!"
The dead OCD man is
trying to help this person.
He's trying to warn.
He's trying to give a warning.
About what?
Everything in this house.
I think that this person
is probably the most sensitive
person in the household,
and because of that,
is being severely affected by this.
He's very depressed.
He's trying to tell them
they probably should get out
of here as quickly as possible.
So one of the first things
I do when I start an investigation
is reach out to the local
cops, reporters, and historians.
I just got a call
back from a genealogist
who says she might be able to help.
Turns out,
one of the original owners
of Deborah and Jeff's property
had a real tragic time there.
Now, you mentioned on the phone
one of the original owners of
the property I'm investigating
had a pretty tough time
while they were there.
But before we get to that,
though, who was this guy?
His name was Mills H. Eure.
He got the land in 1840,
inherited from his grandmother.
Okay, so the land he inherits.
What kind of land is it?
- It was most likely farmland.
- Okay.
Most likely a plantation.
And the 1860 census we do have,
where Mills owned 11 slaves.
Now, Cathy, you mentioned on the phone
that there was tragedy with this family.
What was the story?
Well, Mills married in the early 1840s
to a Miss Williams.
They had a little girl in 1845.
And by 1850, the mother was dead.
Do we know what she died of?
We do not.
North Carolina did not
require death records
at that point in time.
Does he ever remarry?
He does.
He married in 1853 to
Sarah Louisa Savage.
She was 18. He was 32.
And then tragedy hits him again
because the second wife died in 1859.
She was dead by 24.
What does she die of?
Again, we don't know.
All right. So I'm afraid to even ask.
Did this guy ever get married again?
No, he did not.
He remained single for
the rest of his life.
Well, this is pretty good information.
I don't know how it's gonna
help in the investigation,
but it's interesting
how this poor guy lost two
wives pretty young in life.
I do have something
else that might help you.
His only son died in a very tragic way.
What happened?
He apparently was an alcoholic.
He went on a 10-day bender,
and he was firing his pistol.
People were running left and right,
trying to get out of his way.
He came upon a local
merchant, Edward Gatlin,
and told him he was going to kill him.
Okay.
Gatlin managed to reach his gun first
and fired and shot
young Mills in the back.
We have a newspaper article
that talks about that.
Mills lingered on and died 2 days later.
This guy was, like,
super psycho when he was alive.
The second I walked back outside,
the young dead guy is all over me.
And I'm starting to see he
was a violent man in life.
He's telling me he wants to kill things.
He probably wasn't the nicest dude.
He might've hurt people.
Nobody's at rest here.
The living aren't. The dead aren't.
It's hard.
So far, I know the
previous landowner Mills Eure
suffered one tragedy after another,
losing two wives at a very young age.
But I need to see if
there's anything more.
Searching through old
records, I find Thomas Pitman,
who purchased the land from Mills Eure.
Turns out Pitman also lost two wives
while living on the property.
Believe it or not, this guy's
granddaughter is still alive.
She's 96, feisty as hell,
and willing to talk
about her grandfather.
So your grandfather, you remember him?
- Now, how old
were you when he passed away?
Ten years old.
Now, I understand
your grandfather purchased
my client's property in 1882.
Yeah. But I wasn't around then.
I would hope not.
What kind of a man was he?
He was a good man, always
doing something for us.
I know that your grandfather's
first wife, Annie,
died in 1874,
but the records are
unclear as to how she died.
Do you have any idea?
It was diphtheria.
Now, I know your grandfather remarried
to a woman named Sally.
Sally died in 1891,
but I couldn't find any records
to tell me what she died of.
Okay, so she died from the same thing?
I know your grandfather
lost two wives at this point.
Did he remarry again?
Yes, he did, in 1894.
Stella, that's my grandmother.
That man on the end is my grandfather.
Now, do you know when he died?
He died one week after
his 80th birthday.
Unfortunately, this is
not, a happy place.
Like, I'm hearing that word "sorrow."
There's a lot of sorrow here.
A lot of sorrow, a lot
of pain, a lot of loss.
Boy.
There's something very wrong.
Nothing is as it seems here. Nothing.
It's pretty crazy.
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity in your home,
go to the "Dead Files"
page at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help me, Dead
Files!" to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
Now, another thing that
caught my eye during research
was The Buffaloes, a deadly gang
that tore through town
and murdered a woman
right next door to my client's property.
I'm on my way to meet with a historian
who says that The Buffaloes
were cold-blooded killers and thieves.
So, Chris, I know a
lot about the Civil War
from research I've done.
But I never heard of The Buffaloes.
Buffaloes were a ragtag group of men.
This is a picture of
some Buffalo soldiers.
They were a wandering group
who were ex-Confederate soldiers,
runaway slaves, thieves.
I mean, biracial? I mean, 1860s? Really?
Very, very unusual.
All right. So what would these guys do?
Well, they went on a huge
crime spree in the area.
They would attack farms,
steal the people's property.
If they met any resistance,
they wouldn't hesitate
to kill the person.
There are men outside,
all different colors.
They seemed to be very agitated.
It seems like a very desolate place,
but I'm getting a lot
of wrongful deaths here.
That's how it feels with these men.
So now, I know they
attacked and killed a woman
that lived right next door
to my client's property.
Do you know anything about that?
Yes, her name was Mrs. Spivey.
On a raid in February 1865,
they attacked her house.
They took all of her belongings,
and then they wanted a
little something extra.
And she refused them,
and they summarily
shot and bayoneted her.
Okay.
On that same day,
they actually attacked
your client's property.
Okay, who was living there at the time?
Mills Eure.
I already came across
him in my research.
What happened?
They attacked, took all of his property,
and beat him up.
I see this woman, and
she's got long black hair.
I'm just, like, in her,
and I'm feeling a man grabbing me
and, like, slitting my throat.
Then he, like...
caved in basically half her face.
I felt, like, this horrible
pain in the right eye socket.
And then I hear lots of
women screaming and moaning.
And then, quickly, very
quickly, I see a male
who's dressed in very
dark blue with gold trim.
I've never seen any kind of
military dress like this before.
All I heard was, "He is a murderer."
All right. So did these
guys ever get caught,
or did they just get away with it?
Yes, they did get caught.
The Confederate Army came in,
attacked their base camp,
and captured 14 of these men.
Ten were returned as deserters
to their original unit,
but four of these men
were taken to Mrs.
Spivey's house and executed.
And here's a newspaper
account of that attack.
And what was the reason for
going back to the property?
To teach a lesson to any of
the other thieves in the area.
Okay.
I saw several
dead people on my walk,
but the young dead man
tormenting a living woman
had me the most concerned.
His face is all black.
Thin nose.
He had a weird kind of look.
He was standing on the bed
and touching her shoulder.
Is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to meet
Deborah, her husband, Jeff,
and their daughter, Nikki.
Now, I spent the day with the family
and got a firsthand look
at how bad things are.
And it was very disturbing.
Probably one of the most
serious cases we've ever done.
And the family's convinced
that whatever's going on
is going after Nikki.
And they'll do whatever
it takes to keep her safe.
Now that Amy knows
just a little bit about what
you guys are going through,
I'm gonna ask her to
describe the walk for us.
When I was outside,
I saw this woman that
was being murdered.
She was in her 20s or 30s.
She had long black hair.
And I suddenly felt like I
was kind of inside her body.
And a male came up and grabbed me
and slit my throat.
I felt horrible pain in my eye socket
and also my nose.
And then, I saw a male
who was wearing this really
strange military outfit.
And it was dark blue with gold.
And he kind of had a
strange hat, as well.
It was, like, more like a cowboy hat.
There were quite a few.
And they were all
different ages and races,
but they were all male.
Well, I think I can
help you out on this one.
Back in the 1860s,
there was a group of
outlaws called The Buffaloes.
The strange thing about
this group of men were
they were multiracial,
which was pretty odd
for the time period.
It was during the Civil War.
They were a gang made up
of ex-Civil War soldiers,
criminals, escaped slaves.
Wow.
I was actually able to get a photo.
You mentioned the uniforms.
Yeah. How weird.
Now, in February of 1865,
they came onto your property
that was inhabited by a guy
named Mills Eure at the time.
I have an article here
that says how they
nearly beat him to death
and stole all his property.
Now, right after that happened,
they decided to go right
next door to your property
and attack a woman named Mrs. Spivey.
The historian I had spoke to
said they tried to rape
her after they robbed her.
She fought back,
and they wind up bayoneting
her and shooting her.
She died right in the property.
Now, 14 of these guys were caught.
They turned 10 over
to the Confederate Army
'cause they were deserters.
And the other four,
they actually brought back
to to where Mrs. Spivey lived.
They executed those men
right there on the property.
Okay.
Inside the house, I encountered a couple
of very solid, conscious dead people.
One was an older man.
He has severe OCD.
And I felt like the living
might have some of these experiences,
going through spells of OCD.
So you'll, like, work
a problem to death,
or you'll reflect on something to death.
And he likes messing with
people's ears and faces.
He likes to touch that.
You just hit that on cue.
The hair pulling,
the messing with my
face constantly at night.
And the OCD part, I have
seen that especially on her.
Yes. I can get on one thought,
and I can just wring it
and just take it as far as
it can go, and then some.
But does that happen to
you when you're not home?
No.
Do you have any idea who this
guy might've been in life?
He was in his late 60s.
He seemed short. He
died fairly recently.
He had compulsive
behaviors in life, you know.
He was fussy with other living people.
He was very neurotic.
He's not okay right now.
Well, that's the 800-pound
gorilla in the room.
My father.
Really?
He was 62 when he died.
Okay.
He was a... just a hard-ass, period.
Strict, loving at the same time.
My mom, she had to walk around
the house with a white glove,
check for dust.
Wow, okay.
Compulsive.
So the thing is, he's drawn to you.
He's trying to always talk to you
to give you warnings.
He tells me, "I'm
trying to wake them up.
Wake up! Wake up!"
But you're just completely, like,
I guess kind of ignoring him?
He's trying to warn you.
He's trying to protect from
the other dead that are here.
You were hinting at him,
like you think he may
have some abilities.
You do have quite a few
dead people around you.
And it feels like they can
really talk to you, so...
Well, I got a couple of
photos of Deborah's father.
This is her wedding day.
Okay.
Is that who you think it was?
It looks like him, but way thinner.
Way thinner.
And when he passed, he was way thinner.
Okay, that makes sense.
When we spoke,
you said you thought your father
was there from time to time.
Yeah.
Here, take that.
Thank you.
Just miss him. I miss him a lot.
You mentioned you ran into
a couple of dead people.
Who else?
One of the people that
I'm most concerned about
is this young dead guy.
He is a threat.
It, to me, felt like
he didn't particularly care for women.
I think he's kind of a psycho.
My assumption was
that he wasn't a particularly
good person when he was alive.
At one point, he was like,
"Yeah, I want to kill things."
Well, it... it's a shot in the dark,
but remember the guy I
told you about, Mills Eure,
who got beat up by The Buffaloes?
Yes.
He had a son, Mills
Jr., who was a drunk.
And one time, he went on
a 10-day alcohol bender.
Apparently, he wound up
walking through the
streets downtown nearby,
shooting his gun in the air.
And people were scurrying
all over the place.
He approaches this local merchant
by the name of Edward Gatlin.
And he says, "I'm gonna...
I'm gonna kill you."
And he goes for his gun.
Gatlin was a quicker shot,
pulled out his gun, and
shoots him in the back.
There's only other one weird
thing about the property.
And you mentioned women?
Mills had two wives who
died young on the property,
and there's no record
of what they died of.
Then I spoke with
a 96-year-old woman
whose grandfather
bought the land in 1882.
His name was Thomas Pitman.
He had lost two wives
as well on the property.
- Wow.
- And they were both young.
Interesting. Okay.
Now, this young dead guy you saw,
what could he do to affect the living?
Well, the thing was, a female showed up,
a dead female.
And this person
seemed to have been in
a relationship with him.
And he was very irritated
that she showed up.
And they were, like, arguing.
And he was, like, you
know, really pissed off.
What I saw was, like,
the living picking up on
their anger and fighting,
and so they're emulating them.
So they're fighting, as well.
And if he's around, you
could feel, like, ice.
Like, it was really, like...
can go right through you, you know?
You can tell when he's around
because it's like total
10-degree drop instantly.
With the arguing,
I've actually seen
that between my parents.
It's just so much
drama, so much argument,
so much, just, chaos.
We're not together.
We're not solid.
Okay.
Well, what concerned me
was the room with the pastel bedspread.
That's Nikki's room,
but she's so terrified in
there, she sleeps with her mom.
They're maybe feeling, like, movement.
Hearing, like, mumbling,
feeling pressure on the bed,
like, when they're laying on the bed.
He was grabbing my shoulder,
and he was grabbing the back of my leg.
And because he can be so physical,
that's where it gets scary,
because he does really hate women.
Deborah and Nikki both feel
that whatever's in the
house is targeting women.
Everything that
you said about the bedroom,
I've experienced everything.
The voices, the mumbling.
I've felt the bed shake.
Once, I got pushed back,
and I felt like something
was on top of my chest.
Like, I couldn't breathe.
It felt like something was on my neck.
It also happened to Deborah.
She got attacked the same type of way.
I was sitting on the bed.
My hands are just in my lap.
And all of a sudden,
they flew back and
hit the headboard hard.
And my throat just literally went up,
and I'm being choked.
They've been, um...
touched inappropriately, both women.
I was kind of sleeping.
I was going in and out.
And all of a sudden,
I started feeling something touch me.
And it was going from my neck,
and I felt it go lower, lower,
then I was feeling it just caress me.
My gosh.
But she's not the only
one that's been touched that way.
So has Deborah.
He's done that, but he
got a little further.
Why didn't you tell me about these?
How can I tell you
that I think I just almost
got raped by that dead guy?
I had a sketch done of what I saw.
Geez!
Can he really do this?
Deborah, he has.
Can he take her life?
I did do a sketch.
Geez!
Can he really do this?
Deborah, he has.
Can he take her life?
Yeah.
He is insane, and he
wants to kill people.
It would scratch me everywhere...
my chest, my back, my stomach, my legs.
You can actually see the
scratch marks going all over.
And I got photos of them.
Wow.
I've always felt he wanted her.
He can do anything,
but I can't stop him.
Well, guys, I know
tonight was a rough night,
but I don't think any of us
thought it was gonna be an easy one.
No.
Now we need to answer
your big question...
how to keep the women of the house safe.
For that answer, I'm
gonna turn it over to Amy.
What I would like to see happen
is for a medium to come out
and for you to receive a
reading with this medium
to talk to your father.
- Are you okay with that?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Okay. He'll have a lot
of good advice for you.
I think it'll be a
really good experience
for both of you guys.
And that should help him to move on.
Then, the next day, two
mediums need to come back,
a male medium and a female medium.
The female medium needs
to be really feminine.
The male medium needs
to be pretty tough.
Both of the mediums
will engage with the guy in your bedroom
and forcefully remove
him from the location.
And his dead girlfriend will go with him
because of their situation.
So let me ask you a question.
Why a feminine woman?
Because a feminine
woman would be, to him,
someone that he could
dominate and possess
because he views women as weak.
Well, this has got to be good news.
You told me you thought it was
a frigging demon in the house.
Yeah, I'm glad it's not.
Well, it's the next thing to a demon.
I'm hoping that, once
all of this is out,
that the family can come
back to where it was.
Because it wasn't always a strain.
It wasn't always chaos.
It wasn't always hateful.
Are you gonna do what
Amy suggests you guys do?
Yeah.
Can't wait to start.
If the family follows my advice,
Deborah's dad will finally be free,
and the evil man tormenting
the women of the house
will be kicked out for good.
Then this family will find
the peace it's been searching for.