My head hurts so bad!
There was a female figure.
She was hitting me.
She does attacks in here.
This is one of
the worst stories
I've ever heard
about a guy's life.
Get it away.
Get it away from me now.
I'm overwhelmed.
I need answers.
This is my room.
Get the **** out.
He's a problem.
I just hear death.
My name is Amy Allan.
God.
He was like,
"I'm going to get you."
I see dead people.
Her face was all demonic.
I speak to dead people...
He's like, "You think you can
stop me? Because you can't."
...and they speak to me.
- What is he trying to do?
- Kill them.
But there's only one way
to know if my findings are real.
Something happened.
Bam, bam, bam.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
Am I seeing
what I think I'm seeing?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
- They're everywhere.
- It's my job to reveal them.
This guy's got the markings
of a serial killer.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
Is this dead guy
doin' that to her?
When we uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
That's it.
Or time to get out.
Somebody is gonna die
over there soon. Yeah.
I'm out here in the small town
of St. Charles, Michigan.
It's about 45 minutes northwest
of Flint.
I got a frantic call
from a woman
who says she and her daughter
are under attack.
They're both scared
for their lives, and they said,
"If we don't get there fast,
somebody's gonna get hurt."
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area
of anything that could influence
her findings.
This home is filled
with family photos,
so it's important that I cover
or remove them all.
When I'm done, the location will
be ready for tonight's walk.
There's something about, like,
this male that lived here.
He had a family.
He has this strange idea
that him and his family
were cursed.
And he's saying that
because of the curse,
everybody died.
He's a problem.
When we spoke on the phone,
the only word that can describe
how you sounded was pure panic.
Yeah.
It's like a pressure cooker.
Like, everything's falling to
a head And it's gonna explode.
I mean, that's how I feel
in the house.
Okay. So what's goin' on?
We hear banging and knocking,
screams, voices,
things being thrown,
and now physical attacks.
My daughter, Kaleigh,
has woken up with scratches.
Um, her health
is pretty bad.
- What's she dealin' with?
- Stomach migraines and a racing heart.
Okay.
How old is Kaleigh now?
-20.
And she won't
stay in here by herself.
Okay. Now who's
living here right now?
Me and my daughter.
My husband, he's overseas.
And he comes back
in 18 months.
What's he doin' over there?
Construction in Africa.
When exactly did you guys,
move in here?
2002.
When the activities start?
Immediately,
but it was small.
When did it get violent?
2013, after Mike's mom
passed away.
She had cancer.
We have her ashes.
Where? Here in the house?
- Yes. I...
- You're kiddin' me.
What can you tell me
about your mother-in-law?
Um, she was 65
when she died.
- Okay.
- Her name was Ruth.
And those are
some pictures of her.
How was Mike's relationship
with his mom?
Bad.
- It was bad?
- It was bad.
She was
a very controlling woman.
You all right?
She brought men home
in front of Mike.
I know there was infidelity.
So let me get this
straight...
While Mike's mother
and father were married?
So how did he deal
with it?
From what I gather,
at the time that he was 16,
he quit talking for a year.
Quit talking to her
or just quit talking?
Quit talking.
This looks like
it upsets you.
It does.
Yeah.
Here, take those.
I don't think a child
should have to go through that.
When we got together,
she didn't like me.
Do you know why?
I was 26
when I ended up pregnant.
When we told her that I was
pregnant, she's like,
"Well, I thought you weren't
that type of girl."
She wasn't a nice lady.
So there's this dead lady.
She gives a creepy vibe.
I don't like her.
She's, like, young mentally.
She's a pretty girl.
She was disgraceful.
I think that she might have been
married a few times.
Something about babies.
I don't know.
And I don't even know
who the ****
she was with to have the babies.
Like, you know what I'm sayin'?
Like, these other men...
She's creeping me out.
Okay, so why'd you bring
me into the kitchen?
One day,
I was doin' the dishes...
Okay.
...and a box of tea bags
came flyin' at me
and almost hit me,
landed behind my feet.
- A box like that?
- Yes.
Okay, so what you're tellin' me
is it was up here?
Yes. Laying flat, yes.
- All right, so...
Me flingin' it a little bit,
it only lands here.
- Yes.
- All right.
Well, you got a main road
out here. Trucks go by a lot.
I saw when I was comin' up.
Right, but that won't make
a box of tea bags fall off.
- Well, not to where you were.
- No.
Okay. Anything else
in the kitchen?
I always have the unnerving
feeling of being watched.
- You feelin' it right now?
- Yeah.
Where you feelin'
it's comin' from?
Like, right here,
like I'm in its space.
Interesting.
All right, anything else?
I hear a woman's voice
saying, "Where's Mike?"
- "Where's Mike?"
All right.
The obvious question is,
did it sound like
your mother-in-law?
Yeah.
You got some strange
stuff goin' on.
- Yeah.
- You okay?
Yeah.
It's a lot.
The dead lady,
she's, like, um,
a creeper, man.
She gets creepy
up on the back of you.
So then your --
your hair goes up.
She just smothers everybody.
She just starts screaming
and being weird.
What the ****?
Really likes this room, a lot.
She -- she very much likes
the closets.
I saw her, like,
throwing shoes or something.
Okay, so what's goin' on
in here?
I've been wakin' up
with bruises,
I just started
noticing them, like fingers.
- Just recently?
- Yes.
Have you had
any blood work done
to see if you have
any immune system problems?
Nothing's wrong.
Okay.
So this seems like a pretty
terrifying room for you.
Yeah.
Um, this morning,
at 4:00 in the morning,
woke up,
and there was a female figure,
saw the outline.
She was hitting me.
Who'd the female
look like to you?
Short hair. I mean,
the outline was short hair.
Do you think
it's your mother-in-law?
Yeah.
But I don't wanna say
that it was her.
Why would she slap me?
- Well, she didn't like you.
- I know.
You okay? Okay.
To see something
coming at me to hit me...
I don't know
how to explain it.
What do you think's
goin' on here?
I think
I made somebody angry.
Why do you say that,
sweetie?
Possibly angry
because Mike's overseas,
and she didn't want him
to go.
And who are you gonna tell?
I mean, people are gonna
think I'm crazy.
I don't think you're crazy.
All right?
All right. It's okay.
Somebody yelling in here,
"Don't be a stupid ****!
Don't be a stupid ****!"
It seems like
she does attacks in here.
What does she do?
Very slowly opening the door...
then she'll rush.
I feel like the living people
feel her open, open, open, open
and then attacking.
It's really bad in here.
I guess this is her space.
Like, I think
she's claimed this room.
It's, like, direct.
"This is my room.
Get the **** out."
So, Kaleigh, I had
a pretty emotional,
discussion with your mom.
Are you worried about her?
- Yeah.
What about Dad bein' away?
I don't like that he's gone.
But, I mean,
it's also kind of nice
because we don't have
to walk on eggshells.
What do you mean by
"eggshells"?
He gets really mean
when he's in the basement.
But after he's up here
for a while, it's fine.
Interesting.
So, Kaleigh, when I was
talkin' to your mom,
she said the activity
picked up enormously
after your grandmother's ashes
came into the house.
So do you agree with mom
that she may be here
and haunting you guys?
Yeah.
She was just a mean old lady.
Okay.
She treated me like crap.
Okay. So I know you guys
are havin' experiences.
I wanna hear about yours.
I hear knocking
coming from the closet
that's connected
to my bedroom.
Like, you know, like,
almost like something's falling.
But there's nothing in there
that could have fallen.
That's strange.
Anything else?
Um, I sometimes wake up
with scratches on my face.
- On your face?
- Yes.
So the scratches,
how often do you get them?
Maybe
once every couple weeks.
Let me see your fingernails.
Well, it's not your nails.
What about the cats?
The cats
don't come in here.
So, Kaleigh, do you think
you and mom
are in danger in this house?
- I do.
- Okay.
There's, like, a child here.
He has on, like,
overalls, lederhosen.
And there's some relationship
between him
and the guy who thinks
he's cursed.
Some of the things
that he does...
It's terrible. It's terrible.
He touches people.
You know, he touches them.
What he does to other kids,
not good.
The thing with him
with other kids, he'll glom on.
Like, get in them
for a little bit,
just a short period.
How people would see the kids
being influenced
by this dead kid...
Yeah?
...Is that
they would see, like,
the living kid
being, like, spaced out
because they're absorbing
dead energy.
They could have
heart problems.
And the more he does it
and the more the living kids
are exposed to him,
the worse...
You see what I'm sayin'?
It could be bad,
really, really bad.
Lord, what the ****?
Get it away.
Get it away from me now.
What just happened?
Something...impacted my head.
I was talking about the little
boy, and that happened.
My head hurts
so **** bad.
Ooh!
Even though
Mike's halfway across the world,
I need to know what he thinks
is goin' on at home.
So I've arranged a meeting
with him over the Internet
to see what he's got to say.
So, Mike, I understand you're
over in Africa, correct?
-Yes.
- Okay.
I'm gonna be blunt.
Are you -
Do you believe what your wife
and daughter are sayin'?
I believe it
to a certain extent.
Okay. Your wife thinks
when your --
your mom's remains
came into the house,
things changed then.
Do you -- Does that make
any sense to you?
It does.
And I'm beginning to wonder
if we need to do something
sooner than later.
Okay. Talkin' to your wife,
she said that
you and your mom
had a difficult relationship.
Yeah. It wasn't --
it wasn't very pleasant.
You know, and she was always,
...you know,
trying to get
into everybody's business
and trying to tell them how
to live, and stuff like that.
Okay.
The dead man who thinks
he's cursed likes it down here.
I think that people
get really sad --
really, really sad down here.
There's a living male here.
The male has issues,
big-time issues.
It's, like, emotional ****.
Like, emotional problems.
He comes and goes.
I mean, I don't think
he was A-okay to begin with.
You know what I mean?
So he was, like,
a really easy target
for this cursed dead guy.
And what does he do
to him?
He influences him to act angry.
Mike, have you had
any experiences in the house?
I've, you know,
seen, like, shadows
out of the corner of my eye.
You know, I'd be
in my workout room,
and I got some big mirrors
down here.
And -- and it would seem
like I'd see it
out of the corner
of my eye in the mirror.
So how often
were you seein' this?
Maybe once every couple
of weeks or so.
Okay. Anything else?
I've had, like,
a-a breath or something,
like, on my neck when I was,
you know, on the treadmill.
Okay.
Could you figure out if it came
from a vent or anything?
There -- there's not
a vent, right there.
All right. So I don't know
how much of a skeptic you can be
after experiencing
something like that.
Right.
The guy
who thinks he's cursed,
he feels like this is his hell.
But his main focus
is just to get these
living people out of here.
He pushes weird,
emotions on them.
They feel ashamed for no reason.
They feel guilt for no reason.
They feel sad for no reason.
How do you think
prolonged exposure to this guy
would affect the living?
I think that he would drive
the living male insane.
The second I get
to a town, I work the phones --
cops, historians,
local journalists.
I try to see if anyone has
a lead.
I just got a call back
from a genealogist
who says one of
the original owners of the land
has pretty amazing
and tragic story
I'm definitely gonna
wanna hear about.
You had mentioned
on the phone
one of the original owners
of the property
I'm investigating
had a pretty tragic time there.
But before we get to that,
who was this guy?
Well, John Baumler.
He came over from Germany,
immigrated in 1880.
He was 29 years old.
This is John Baumler's
immigration record.
He came with his wife Anna
and two children --
Leonard and Frederica.
Okay. It says here
he's a farmer.
He's a farmer.
Six days after they got here,
their 9-month-old daughter
dies.
And 8 days after that,
their son dies.
My god.
I managed to track down
the death records.
And here they are,
the two children.
Do we know what
they died of?
No.
They may have contracted
something on the boat.
Okay, so at some point,
they make it to St. Charles
with no kids.
Correct.
Do they try to start
a family again?
Yes.
They had two more children.
And then tragedy strikes again
for John Baumler.
What happened?
In 1884, his wife dies.
Do we know why or how?
No, we don't have
the records,
but we think it probably
was childbirth.
Okay.
This cursed guy,
he's very much like,
"I lived here.
I lived here. I died here."
So he...
I don't know how he died.
Do you know what
he did in life?
I believe he was a farmer.
I saw him working with land
and cows and horses and stuff.
Something happened
to his entire family.
He feels responsible.
Already this guy's life
is a sad story.
- Yes.
- Wh-- what happens next?
Well,
over the next 31 years,
he actually marries three times
and loses each of his wives.
What the hell happened?
The next wife,
whose name was Minnie Kutzbach,
she died in 1890.
Okay, so she dies, say it --
what is says here is,
"consumption," which is...
- Tuberculosis.
The next wife's name
was Wilhelmina Wall.
Okay.
She dies in 1913
of an infection
which affects her heart
and her kidneys.
He marries again
in less than a year,
in 1914.
Okay.
And their marriage
was the shortest of all.
And within a year
and a half, she dies.
She is struck and killed
by an automobile.
Okay, I'm almost
even afraid to ask
if this guy
got married again.
Yes, he did, Steve.
In 1918, he marries
a 47-year-old widow
by the name
of Christina Barnekow.
Okay.
And in 1920,
he buys
your client's property.
All right, so they're on
my client's property.
Please tell me it went well
for these guys.
Well, it did for a while.
But in 1929,
John Baumler
was struck and killed
by a hit-and-run driver.
A hit-and-run,
so nobody ever got caught?
No one ever was caught.
This is one of
the worst stories
I've ever heard
about a guy's life.
It was a very tragic life.
I think that a lot
of things went wrong, like,
with his business
and his family.
His whole family dies.
L- like, I feel a wife.
I feel like there were kids.
But I do think
that they died from an illness.
And I think
that he feels responsible.
They got sick
and -- and they died,
and he feels that somehow
he contributed to that.
And then he said
that everybody died.
And so he felt
like he was cursed.
It feels like there's still
a curse here existing,
like it never ceased.
This curse, he thinks
it's like a monster.
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity
in your home,
go to the "Dead Files" page
at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help me, Dead Files!"
to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
So far, I've got
a mother and daughter
being terrorized on a property
that's had several
tragic deaths.
But I need to see
if there's anything more
that could help
my investigation.
Searchin' through old records,
I find a man
who was crushed to death
right in front of his son.
Turns out it happened
in a coal mine
just a few thousand feet
from my client's property.
So I just spoke
to a mining expert
who says that tragedy
is just the tip of the iceberg.
He says that St. Charles' mines
were nothing less
than deathtraps,
and he's got the headlines
to prove it.
So I came across
that tragic accident
that happened in the mine
right near my client's property.
But before we get to that,
what was mining like
in St. Charles at that time?
Well, it starts
right around 1896, Steve.
Okay.
Um, and it's kind
of an accident in and of itself,
what all that happens.
Um, you got a guy
that's diggin' a water well...
Okay.
...and, he basically hits
a bunch of black rock.
Turns out to be coal.
And,
the next thing you know,
basically you got a little bit
of an economic boom goin' on.
Who would have worked
these mines?
A lot of,
Eastern European immigrants
that came into the area.
And you know,
you gotta remember,
this is before labor laws.
And so you got literally kids
workin' in these mines.
So, T.J., I know
mining's dangerous,
but what were
the conditions like
for the mines
here in St. Charles?
You got cave-ins.
You got,
highly explosive gases
that are down there.
I mean, all you gotta do
is look at pictures like this.
And all you can see there's --
there's the guy's legs.
Jeez.
Okay, so now the accidents
that happen
near my client's property,
what're we talkin' about?
How close was it?
Well, you're lookin' at
less than a 1/2-mile.
I got a map here
that actually shows
the Robert Gage No. 8 mine.
And, your client's
property's right about here.
Okay, almost towards
the end of the mine.
Yeah, exactly.
So when did
this accident happen?
The year was 1901.
And, the victim's name
is Albert Newman.
He and his son,
were working
in one of the rooms
in the mine.
And, he was evidently
testing out the roof
of that room
to, get ready
to drill into it.
Sent his son
out to another room,
and, the son heard what
he thought was water rushing.
And it turned out it's,
basically his dad's own blood.
He walked back
into the room to find that,
about 50 tons had,
dropped onto his dad.
That's a pretty sad story
when, you know --
you know, a son's finding
his father like that.
So now, T.J.,
you mentioned on the phone,
you found some more accidents
near my client's property.
Basically December of 1907,
we have a Ray Clipper.
Again, here's a guy
that's crushed to death.
What a way to go. Mnh.
This guy's only 21 years old.
- Yeah.
In April 1920,
Nelson Carl Smith
fell 20 feet.
All right, so, T.J.,
you said it started in 1896
with the mining.
Do we know how long the mine
by my client's property lasted?
The Robert Gage No. 8 mine
lasted until roughly about 1931.
This cursed dead guy
is talking about tunnels,
something about a tunnel.
Tunnels, tunnels, tunnels.
There's, like, multiple bodies,
and he's just, like,
rambling about it.
Where are they?
They're just lyin' on the floor.
How many?
Three or four.
Can you describe them?
It's, like,
this mangled mess of flesh.
He just says, "There's tunnels
all over the place,"
and that we should put
the bodies in the tunnel
'cause that's where they belong.
I saw a lot of disturbing things
on my walk,
but the dead lady
tormenting a living woman
had me the most concerned.
It was in
a small, blue room.
She had eyes...
- Okay.
...but they were not
human-looking.
And then her face
looked like a witch.
Is this what you saw?
Yes, that's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready
to reveal our findings
to each other and our clients
for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you
to meet Janice.
This is her daughter Kaleigh.
Um, to put it bluntly,
what's goin' on here sucks.
These two have no life.
They live in fear.
And the worst part is they're
goin' through this alone.
Now Janice's husband Michael...
He's away in Africa working
for about 18 months.
Now, they can't afford to leave,
but they can't go on like this,
so hopefully we can
help them out tonight.
So now that Amy
knows just a little bit
about who you are,
I'm gonna ask her
to describe her walk.
There are three conscious,
dead people
that are causing issues here.
But before I get
into discussing them,
I wanted to tell you something
that I got when I was
in the basement.
When I was down there,
one of the deceased individuals
was going on and on
about something about tunnels.
And he was showing me maybe,
like, three or four dead people.
But they were such a mess.
Just, like, a clump of gore.
And he told me that
these bodies needed to be moved
into the tunnels
where they belonged.
I didn't really have to think
about this one too long.
Back in 1896,
St. Charles became a really big
mining town for coal.
Take a look at this map of...
the Robert Gage No. 8 mine.
Your house sits right here.
This is the end of the mine.
Yeah, that makes sense.
As you guys probably know,
mining's dangerous work.
The expert I spoke to told me
there was a ton
of accidents here --
cave-ins, explosions,
the whole nine yards.
I've actually got a photo.
This is a picture
of what it would look
like when a mine
caved in on somebody.
- My god.
- Wow.
In 1901,
an accident just like this
happened within 5,000 feet
from your property here.
The man working was basically
crushed to death.
Wow.
The first dead person
that I'm going to talk about
is the female
that I encountered.
She's very creepy.
She kind of spooked me.
She likes to torture
living people.
One of the things
that I saw her doing
was messing around
with shoes and, like,
throwing them
and moving them about.
And in the very back bedroom,
um, I saw her smother people.
Like, they couldn't breathe.
Is it possible that these guys
would be able to see her?
It's possible.
Janice encountered a female.
Tried to slap me.
Ooh! Okay.
Tell her what happened
in the kitchen.
I was doin' the dishes,
and the tea bags
were on the top shelf.
And they came flying off
and landed, um, behind my feet.
Okay.
Does she do anything else,
this woman?
Yes. One of her things to do
is to creep up behind people.
One of her favorite areas
is this blue room here.
I saw her, like,
creeping out of the closet.
Very slowly opening the door,
then she'll rush.
I thought that maybe
the living would experience,
like, kind of a panic attack
kind of feeling...
- Associated with this.
That closet, um,
is also connected to my bedroom.
- And I'll here, like,
knocking noises, almost like
stuff is falling over.
- Interesting.
- She watches.
- I feel...
- Yeah.
...constantly watched
wherever we are.
I mean, I always feel like
I have to look over my shoulder
and make sure that, you know,
there's nobody there.
I did have a sketch done
of what I saw her doing.
****.
- My god.
I don't like that.
That's creepy.
She's...in my room as well?
Which room is yours?
- The pink one.
- İn the closet.
And that's why I don't
like my closet.
Who do you think
this woman might have been
when she was alive?
She was actually pretty.
I got that she had either
a lot of men in her life
or was
married multiple times.
Um...her family tried
or did have her locked away
at some point.
They thought that she was kind
of a disgrace to the family.
And I got that she is jealous
of a female here,
and that's why
she's acting out so much.
Well, we got the elephant
in the room to talk about.
I know the three of us are
thinking about the same person.
You know what? This is
who we're talking about.
These are the remains
of her mother-in-law Ruth.
In 2013, Ruth dies of...
leukemia?
Yes.
Now, when they brought
the ashes home
is when things got violent.
Wow.
Do me a favor, Janice.
Tell her how she was in life.
She wasn't a very good person.
She traumatized Mike.
When she was married
to Mike's dad,
she had multiple lovers,
and did it in front of Mike.
She didn't like you either.
No, she didn't like me.
I got photos of her
at different ages.
Wow.
Any idea if this might be
who you saw?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Her face is
exactly like that.
What else is goin' on?
Then I saw a dead child.
So I'd actually put him
between 7 and 8 years of age.
And he was wearing
a funny outfit,
kind of resembled
lederhosen.
He interacts consistently
with the living here.
I saw him touching
living people.
Um, specifically,
caressing faces,
playing with their hair.
The problem with him is that if
there's any living children
within the vicinity,
he will try to, like,
glom on to them.
It's very bad for the living
because it can make them sick.
It can cause
major health problems,
one of which
could be heart issues.
He can also become
violent.
When I was talking to him
in the middle room,
I suddenly had, like,
a horrible blow to my head.
Well, that just about hit
every friggin' experience
you guys are goin' through.
I have had stomach problems
ever since I was a baby.
Now on top of that,
there's something wrong
with my heart.
Wow.
They still have no idea
what's wrong.
See, I think she's doing this.
I think she's doin' you.
I think the kid's doin' you.
It's like you're his toy.
You said there are
three dead people
you're concerned about.
The other person was
this guy,
and he is
a pretty serious threat.
He's somehow related
to this little kid.
I don't know if it was father
or grandfather.
One of the things
about this guy
is that he feels
extreme sense of guilt.
Um, I saw him at one point
where he, like,
falls to his knees.
And he's like,
"Aah! It's all the curse.
It's the curse.
I caused the curse."
Somehow he lost
his entire family
and he feels completely
responsible for it.
What I got about him was
that he worked outside a lot.
I felt like he was a farmer.
He lived on the property,
died on the property,
was buried on this property.
So I do have one guy
in my research
that fits that bill.
One of the first owners
of the property
was a guy named John Baumler.
He was a German immigrant
who came to the country in 1880
at the age of 29.
So when she said "lederhosen,"
it kind of made sense.
Now you mentioned he lost
his entire family.
When he crossed the Atlantic
with his wife,
he had a baby girl
and a 2-year-old boy.
But within 2 weeks
of arriving in America,
they were both gone, both dead.
Jeez.
We think they died of some kind
of disease on the boat.
There's no records of it.
He must have felt guilty
about putting his family at risk
by bringing them over here.
Now I wish this was the end
of John Baumler's story,
but this was just the beginning.
Four years after gettin'
into town, Baumler's wife dies.
Now, get this --
over the next 30 years,
he's married three more times,
and every single one
of them died.
- That's insane!
- He marries a fifth time.
No.
He should've just stopped.
For 9 years, until 1929,
he lived right here on your land
where the house is built.
And, he gets killed
by a hit-and-run.
What?
I got
his death certificate here.
This guy had one of the most
miserable lives I've...
My god.
...ever come across.
- Wow.
Do you think this is
who you might've seen?
Yes.
Now you said you were worried
about this guy.
What's he do?
- This was interesting.
He can't do
anything physical,
but he's, like,
mastered emotional abuse.
Living people will become
extremely overwhelmed
by these sudden emotions.
One of them is shame, feeling
an intense amount of shame
for no reason,
guilt for no reason,
feeling sad for no reason.
I...
I feel guilty for not bein' able
to take care of her.
I feel guilty about things
that happened in my past.
I've been constantly saying
that I'm overwhelmed.
Do you think that this guy
could be influencing her?
Yeah.
His favorite area
is the basement.
When I was down there,
I got,
that he had his sights
set on a male.
He felt like this male was
an extremely easy target
for him.
I got that the living male comes
and goes from the house a lot.
I got that he does have
emotional issues.
And he will act out,
in anger and lash out.
I got that
if this living male
is exposed
to this dead male
for a long period of time,
that it would, like,
drive him insane.
You know we're talkin'
about Mike.
He's the only living male
in this house.
When he spend a lot
of time in the basement,
it's like
walking on eggshells.
He's agitated, angry.
We can't do anything right.
You know, he should be nicer.
But, I mean,
if he's in the basement,
it's horrible.
Does he recall these outbursts
that he has?
No.
Okay. It's worse --
worse than I thought.
This dead guy
you're talkin' about,
what does he want?
He views this entire space
as his personal hell.
He's very depressed
and he wants to be alone.
He is at the point
where he's willing to do
whatever it takes
to get y'all out of this space.
Well, Janice,
it's been a tough night,
but at least you got
a lot of answers.
The only thing
we haven't told you yet
is whether you can
make this home safe again
so you can finally
get the peace
you deserve for you
and your family.
For that, I'm gonna
turn it over to Amy.
The first thing
that you would need to do
is to find a male medium
and a priest.
The first day,
you're going to deal
with Grandma.
And the male medium
will start with her.
My hope is that
you'll let her vent,
and some things can be
just kind of laid to rest.
And then she'll move on.
Now if she doesn't do this,
then the priest
will then make her leave.
Okay, so how's he gonna
take care of that?
He'll exorcise her.
For the boy,
bring the male medium back.
Male medium
will engage the boy --
this might be
for a few hours --
and will move him on.
Now another day,
again for a few hours,
male medium comes back,
and he's going to focus
on the cursed dead male.
Now, this male, as well,
may have a lot to talk about.
Just sit back
and listen,
and then he'll move on.
The look on your face
went from sobbing to, like,
"Hey, I can stay in my house."
I can stay in my house.
Yeah.
- How's that make you feel?
- Wonderful. Yeah.
I'm gonna take Amy's advice.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's the first time
I've seen you smile in a week.
Yeah.
- How do you feel, Kaleigh?
- Relieved that we can stay.
Will her health issues
get better?
- Yes.
- Cool.
What about Mike,
when he comes home?
If they do all this,
will his attitude change
when he's in the basement?
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm very happy with...
That we got answers, for one.
Yeah, 'cause we've been dealing
with this for a while.
With the help
of a male medium and a priest,
Janice and Kaleigh
can set the dead free,
giving them a safe and peaceful
home for Mike to return to.