Their souls can't leave.
It's like
there's a war here.
This could manipulate
living people
into harming one another.
Get the freak outta my head.
It could kill them.
Turns the ignition to the car,
and the whole car blows up.
What the **** is happening?
There's something very wrong
with this land.
I just hear death.
My name is Amy Allan.
God.
He was like,
"I'm going to get you."
I see dead people.
Her face was all demonic.
I speak to dead people...
He's like, "You think you can
stop me? Because you can't."
...and they speak to me.
- What is he trying to do?
- Kill them.
But there's only one way
to know if my findings are real.
Something happened.
Bam, bam, bam.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
Am I seeing
what I think I'm seeing?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
- They're everywhere.
- It's my job to reveal them.
This guy's got the markings
of a serial killer.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation...
...until the very end...
Is this dead guy
doin' that to her?
...when we uncover if
it's safe for you to stay...
That's it.
...or time to get out.
Somebody is gonna die
over there soon. Yeah.
I'm in Youngstown, Ohio.
It's a struggling city about
75 miles east of Cleveland.
Now, I got a call
from a woman named Lorie.
Her story broke my heart.
She has stage IV cancer
and she knows she's gonna die.
But she believes there are
forces inside the house
trying to rip her family apart.
Her dying wish
is to kick those spirits out
and have her family
live there in peace.
I really hope we can help
this woman out.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the house
of any leading information.
Family photographs, mementos
and even
Native American artifacts
need to be covered or removed.
When I'm finished,
the location will be ready
for tonight's walk.
So this is very strange.
The thing about this land
is that the dead can't die here.
Their souls can't leave.
A lot of 'em are roamin' around.
And they occasionally
are walking around in --
in through the house.
You see? They're trapped.
So there's something
very wrong with this land.
I know this is tough
to talk about,
but you have
stage IV cancer.
Yes.
The chances of me
living through this...
It's not gonna happen.
The doctor said
2 months to live.
So the time I have,
I need
to make this house safe.
That's why we needed you.
It's heartbreaking.
But yet, you...
you're more concerned about
everybody else but yourself.
Well, of course.
They're my family.
I'm a Christian.
I know where I'm going.
It's okay.
It's just...
I don't wanna
leave my family this way.
It's like
there's a war here.
I have to live
until it is done.
Who exactly lives
in the house now?
My husband and I.
My daughter, um...
moved out recently.
She can't live here.
The house basically
drove her out.
Okay. Do you know any history
about the house?
My daughter was here
with her fiancé Marcus,
and he passed away
in the living room.
How long ago was this?
- Three, 4 years ago.
- Okay.
What did he die of?
Um, some type
of heart condition.
So I'll look into that.
Lorie, how long have
you guys lived here?
- About 19 years.
- Okay.
Did you ever talk
to the previous owners,
if they've had problems
or anything like that?
My mama owned this home,
and she gave it to us
shortly after we got married.
Is your mom still alive?
No. She, um...
- This her here?
- Yes.
- When'd she pass?
-2008.
- How old was she?
-78.
What'd she die of?
Breast cancer.
So there's a...
older woman here.
So I guess she recently died
or something.
She has very,
very short curly hair.
With her, I get a lotta eights.
1998 or 2008.
She was 68.
She was worried about,
um, her grandchild.
She's afraid.
We've always had activity,
but it's gotten a lot worse.
What's goin' on
in the house?
Voices, things moving,
physical attacks,
and personality changes.
Okay. What do you mean
by personality changes?
My husband.
He's changed so much.
In what way?
There's times
when he'll enter a room,
and he's fine.
And he comes back,
and he has this glazed mean,
evil look.
I'm scared when it happens.
He'll say something or throw
something or punch something,
and then he runs outside.
You don't think it's frustration
about you and your sickness?
I'm sure he's frustrated,
but that doesn't cause
the outbursts of evil anger.
I've even talked to him
about possibly leaving him.
I mean, we've been together
22 years.
You break my heart.
I'm sorry.
I'm just glad you came
because I know if anybody
can help, it's you.
I promise
I'm gonna try my best.
So I'm definitely
seeing a big blob.
And it's, like,
moving like a pulse.
Goes up into the ceiling.
And then it has veins.
Like, it looks
like blood vessels.
What is this thing?
It's a manifestation
of all the negativity
that's here.
Sucked it all in.
One living person
is being eaten by this thing.
The weak ones, it gets.
So they're probably sick
or they might be dying.
Losing their personality.
So psychologically and mentally,
they're kind of, like...
not them anymore.
This blob
is the worst thing here.
So what's goin' on
in the bedroom here?
I have a statue
that I used to, um,
have just above my head.
And I was sleeping,
and it struck me real hard
in the head.
Was it on that lower shelf?
Yes.
It felt like it was
picked up and struck me,
like it was tryin'
to kill me.
Okay. So anything else happen
in here?
I was upstairs, um, repacking
a box of Marcus' things
to give to my daughter.
Marcus is your daughter's fiancé
who died in the house.
Yes.
And I was grabbed
real hard and held.
And then I got marks on me.
What, like human hands
were touching you?
Yes, like that.
I was grabbed hard.
And how long did that last,
that feeling?
About 5 minutes.
I think it was Marcus
trying to stop me.
I don't think he wanted
his stuff to leave.
Okay. So has anything else
physical like that happen?
I watched my husband
being shook violently
back and forth.
And he wakes up finally
and says, "What?"
And I go, "It wasn't me
that shook you awake."
Does he suffer from seizures
at all?
- Never.
- Well, you mentioned earlier
about your husband's
personality changes.
What about you?
Have you had any of that?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll be
in the kitchen cooking,
and I'll get a thought
real strong.
Somebody talking in my head,
"Why don't you just take
that knife and put it in there?
You'll be over."
And I'm like, "No!"
How often does this happen?
Every day.
Somebody's in
the kitchen cooking.
And then I see, like,
a knife in my hand.
And I'm gonna go up
and stab that person.
This is, like, a vision.
This blob --
that's what it wants.
It wants people
to hurt each other
'cause then it gets bigger.
It needs to eat to stay alive,
to grow, to survive.
So, Roy, I was talkin'
to, Lorie.
I'm sorry about
what she's goin' through.
She says that the house
has changed your personality.
Do you agree with that?
Yeah. I do.
So how are you being
affected emotionally?
Just violent thoughts.
You know, when you wake up
out of a sound sleep,
you hear a dog barkin', you know
the dog wants to go out.
But by the time you get to her
to let her out,
all you wanna do
is kill her.
Dog ran from me.
I wanted to grab her
and choke her.
I was chasin' her
to kill her.
Somethin's tellin' me,
"Get outside. Get outside."
I open the door.
I go outside.
I'm out there
shaking my head saying,
"Get the freak
outta my head!"
It's, like, when it comes
outta me, I'll stand there.
And I'm, like, "What the hell
is doin' this?"
But if I coulda got ahold
of that dog, I woulda killed it.
This thing, it affects everybody
in the house.
It gives them, um, nightmares.
And visions
of hurting each other.
This could actually
manipulate living people
into harming one another.
Okay, so as far as experiences
go, have you had any?
- Bad smells.
- What kinda smell?
- A smell like death.
- Okay.
I mean, this is a big house,
and you've got woods everywhere.
Dead animal, maybe?
No. There's no dead animals
in my house.
All right.
Anything else?
I see shadows all the time.
Okay.
Where do you see those?
Mainly downstairs,
watchin' TV.
You can see 'em run by
the TV.
Have you ever seen 'em
up here?
Only once.
Okay, when was that?
When I was held down.
Tell me about what happened.
Well, I was sleepin'
one night.
And somethin' woke me up,
and I seen a big, black mass
over top of me,
holdin' me down.
It started floatin' back.
I jumped up outta bed
and I says,
"Is that all you've got,
you son of a ****?
Don't you ever touch me
again."
And then it dissipated.
- Now you seem angry.
- I am angry.
It's, like, okay,
you wanna pick on me? Fine.
I could...I'll --
I'll handle it.
Right.
But when
you start interferin'
and gettin' to my family
and my wife,
now it's time to do somethin'
and do it now.
Right.
There's this dude.
He's **** intense.
İf you're, like,
thinking about him
or talking about him
or anything like that,
he's, like, right on top of you.
I was getting stuff on his wife.
She smells really bad.
I think living people
can smell her.
She does look like
a weird **** version
of a shadow person.
And the thing that she does is,
like, she'll be, like...
at their beds and watching.
So, Kristina, I understand
that you moved out
about 6 months ago.
- Yes.
Okay.
What was the reason for that?
Mostly because of the activity
in the house.
Now I know it's a tough subject
to talk about,
but I understand, um,
your fiancé...
Had passed away in the house.
Yes.
In the living room.
He was my best friend.
It's the hardest thing I've ever
had to go through in my life.
I can imagine.
I didn't think I was gonna
make it through it.
I know you've had experiences.
So tell me about some of 'em.
Um, one night I woke up
in the middle of the night,
and there was an old man
standing at the end of my bed
staring at me.
And he was just there
for, like, a couple seconds,
and then he disappeared.
So okay, anything else?
Bad anxiety attacks.
I mean, right now,
I- I'm havin'
a hard time breathing.
I- I just feel like somethin's
really heavy on my chest
and that my heart
goes outta rhythm.
And I start sweating
really bad.
- Okay.
- Sometimes I feel overwhelmed,
like I just wanna
break down crying.
And it's uncontrollable.
This dude would affect
living people,
make them feel a lotta stress.
If anybody would have
a problem with him living-wise,
it would be any female
in this house.
He probably does bad things
to women here.
Pain. Lots of pain.
My god.
I feel like I have
this pain in my back.
And I feel nauseous, too.
What the **** is happening?
Look, 39-year-old guys
just don't drop dead
of heart attacks.
There's gotta be more to it.
I reached out to Marcus' mom,
who's agreed to speak to me.
She says he did have
a condition,
and thinks his death
could have been prevented.
I know this is
a tough subject.
And I understand Marcus
did pass away in the house
I'm investigating.
- Yes.
Before we even get
to any of that stuff,
tell -- tell me about
your son.
This is a picture
of my son.
He's the oldest of five.
Okay.
Big, lovable guy.
He was like a big kid.
- Okay.
On the phone, you had mentioned
Marcus had a condition.
He had what is called
Atrial Septal Defect,
which is one of
the causes of his death.
It's actually
a hole in the wall
in between the two,
top chambers of the heart.
Did he take it serious?
He did not, you know,
take the best care of himself.
He, smoked cigarettes
when he was younger.
And, he wasn't one
to work out or anything.
My son was a chef.
Chefs love food.
- Right.
They love rich foods.
When's the last time
you had seen him?
Last time I saw him
was Thanksgiving Day, 2011.
Okay. And how soon after that
did he pass?
He passed away
on December 19th.
I'm assuming
they did an autopsy?
Yes. Here's a copy
of the autopsy report.
The autopsy found that he had
a grossly enlarged heart.
His heart basically
just gave up.
Okay. Now you think
this could've been prevented.
Had he been going to a doctor
like he should've, yes.
I don't know how a parent could
lose a child. It's devastating.
Very devastating.
Lorie thinks he's still around
the house. How 'bout you?
I do.
He loved Lorie and Roy.
They were like
a second family to him.
I wouldn't be surprised at all
if he is around.
Especially, ya know,
looking after them.
There's, like, a dead guy
in here a lot.
He's a big guy.
He was stocky.
He smoked a lot.
He ate a lot of bad stuff.
I think he died
from a heart attack.
Very sudden, very quick.
He's very angry,
very angry about it.
He's trying to get out,
and he can't.
None of the dead people
can get outta here.
So far, I've got
a terminally ill client
whose family's being torn apart
by bizarre activity,
and a young man
who died of a heart attack
right inside their house.
But I need to see
if there's anything more.
Diggin' through old records,
I find a notorious gangster
named Cadillac Charlie.
In 1962, he and his son were
killed in a gruesome car bombing
only 600 feet
from Lorie's property.
Turns out, they were the victims
of a mob hit.
Now I'm not sure
how it's gonna help my case,
but I gotta check this one out.
So, Tom, I came across a mob hit
near my client's house.
I was even surprised to know
there was any mob in Youngstown.
Actually, Youngstown was
a pretty big mob city.
Now were car bombs like the one
near my client's property
a common way
to take people out?
In the --
in the 10 or 11 years before,
Cadillac Charlie
was blown up,
there were, like,
81 car bombings.
It drew the attention
of the Attorney General
of the United States --
Robert Kennedy.
And - Kennedy,
called J. Edgar Hoover
and got the FBI
involved in the case.
Something happened here.
And all these men
were in the process of dying.
I didn't see a battle or a war,
anything like that.
There's, like, piles and piles
and piles of dead bodies.
- How many?
- Like, hundreds.
These people, these men,
were **** up.
Like, some of 'em missin' a leg.
You know, they maybe got a shirt
and there's blood all over it.
Somehow, it reached all the way
to Washington, DC.
I saw a big, round table
with seven or eight politicians
discussing men dying here.
And it was a big deal.
Cadillac Charlie.
This guy sounds like
a made guy, a wise guy.
What do we know
about him?
He's
a Sicilian immigrant.
Came to the United States
in 1921.
This is a picture here
of, of Charlie.
Not much is known about him
the first 10 or 15 years
he's in the country.
And then a few years later,
in, in 1940,
he first shows up
in Youngstown,
gets involved with
the organized crime figures
in town.
Um, he buys a pool hall,
slash lottery house.
He rose pretty fast.
And,
by the time, -
the early '50s rolled around,
he was --
he was the man
in Youngstown.
So, Tom, I know the house
he lived in
is a pretty suburban area,
by my client's house.
Um, I assume
he had a family.
Yeah, he did.
He lived there
with his second wife.
She was about 14 years younger
than he was.
He had,
four kids total.
Okay. So how did this whole
car bombing go down?
Well, the bombing and --
and the murder occurred,
the day after Thanksgiving,
November 23rd, 1962.
Okay.
It's Friday morning.
Charlie's kids
got football practice.
Okay.
Charlie and Tommy
get in the car,
turns the ignition to the car
and ka-boom, the -- the --
the whole --
the whole car blows up.
The garage blows up.
He's blown --
Him and his son
are both blown to bits.
Here's a photo of,
of his son.
His 11-year-old son that was,
killed in the, um,
the car bombing.
Jeez.
Any idea why this guy was
the victim of a mob hit?
Well, there was a couple
of, of --
of theories runnin' around.
One of 'em was that he --
he was deeply in debt.
But nobody really knows
for sure.
Nobody's ever collared
for this or arrested?
No one was every arrested.
Okay.
I don't like this guy.
The angry man
is pulling me back upstairs,
and he's bragging
about all the terrible things
he did in life.
He says he owned men
or laborers.
He's wearing, like, a suit.
I guess he owned...businesses?
I see, like,
two small businesses.
And he's definitely
from back east.
And he moved here.
Maybe he was in prison.
I see a fire,
and I see him kind of burnt.
He's, like, charred.
He died,
and was murdered apparently.
And he's very
pissed off about it.
He feels like it was, you know,
he didn't deserve it.
He says, "I didn't deserve it.
I didn't deserve it."
He says it wasn't an accident.
It was deliberate.
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity
in your home, go to
"The Dead Files" page
at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help Me Dead Files!"
to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
During my research,
a former owner
of my client's property
caught my attention.
So I had a local genealogist
look into this guy,
Paul Wick, for me.
She just called me back
and said this guy's story
is filled with tragedy,
heartbreak, and bankruptcy.
So, Kimberly, why did you want
to come here to talk?
Because in its better days,
this was a mill a lot like
what Paul Wick ran.
I figured this would be
a good place
to tell you his story.
Okay.
So how does Paul wind up
with my client's property?
When he was 14 years old,
Daddy handed him, basically,
117 acres.
Part of that is where
your client's house sits.
Here is a picture of him
right here.
All right.
So Paul, does he get married?
Does he stay single?
What's his story?
He does get married
when he's 22 years old.
His wife is named
Susan Bull.
And here is her picture.
They got married in 1846
and the raised six kids.
Now, Kimberly,
you mentioned on the phone
that this guy
suffered from heartbreak,
tragedy, and bankruptcy.
Let's start with heartbreak.
What happened?
1882, Susan unexpectedly died
of heart disease...
Okay.
...leaving him to raise
six kids.
Okay, so let's move on
to the tragedy.
Well, one of Paul's holdings
was an iron mill.
Would've been a lot like this
in its better day.
Paul's iron mill
had 10 boilers.
Okay.
August 28th, 1872,
nine of the 10 boilers
exploded.
There were three fatalities.
A one-ton piece
of one of the boilers
flew a quarter of a mile away
and fell into a house,
killing a mother
and a 9-month-old son.
Jeez.
All right,
now these explosions,
is that what leads to
his bankruptcy?
Partially.
But back in 1883, Youngstown
was going through a depression,
especially
in the iron industry.
There were signs,
but he ignored 'em.
For the next 7 years,
he ties things up in court.
Ten days after the final
court hearing, Paul Wick dies.
He was a broken man.
Heartache, tragedy,
and bankruptcy.
You weren't kidding.
It followed him
his entire life.
What this thing is,
is a culmination
of all the negativity
that has been within
these walls.
Even though the angry dead man
poses a serious threat to
the living women in the house,
I'm most concerned about
this thing in the dining room.
It's absorbed living energy
from living people.
Horrible things
that it's absorbed.
It's collected
into this big blob.
What happens if it were
to continue to -- to get bigger?
It'll then become intertwined
with the house...
to the point where it'll just
meld within the walls.
And then it'll become one
with the house, the structure.
And the structure is actually
like a living organism.
And then, it does form
a consciousness over time.
And then it can project
entities, to do harm.
So it could kill them.
I saw several disturbing things
on my walk,
but two stood out the most.
First, the angry man.
He was, I believe,
in his 40s.
Like, stocky.
A very, like, thick neck.
Next, I described the thing
growing in the dining room.
It's this big, black,
undulating mass.
And it looked like it was
made out of tar.
And it had, like, veins.
Amy,
is this what you saw?
Yes, that's who I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready
to reveal our findings
to each other and our clients
for the first time.
Amy, I want you to meet
Lorie and her husband Roy.
There is no easy way
to say this,
but Lorie doesn't have
much time left.
She's been diagnosed
with stage IV cancer,
and the doctors give her
about 2 months to live.
Now the activity here
is pretty bad.
And Lorie's dying wish
is to know her family's gonna
be okay once she's gone.
Now that Amy knows a little bit
about you guys,
I'm gonna ask her
to describe her walk for us.
There's something very unusual
about this particular area.
What I saw was that
the dead can't move on.
They're trapped.
And I saw a wall
surrounding this property.
When I walked into the house,
I went into the master bedroom,
and I saw a dead man
in there.
Um, he was
extremely stressed out.
This was very recent,
within the last 10 years.
I got that he was
a big, stocky guy
who did a lotta hard work.
I got that he was
unfortunately unhealthy,
and smoked and ate
a lot of bad food.
And that he died
very suddenly,
from a heart attack.
And he's extremely upset
about that as well.
We kinda think we know
this might be, right?
Yeah.
Lorie's daughter, Kristina,
was living here
with her fiancé Marcus,
for about 2 months.
I got a picture of Marcus here
with Kristina and their dogs.
Marcus was born
with a Atrial Septal Defect.
Despite that, he did lead
an unhealthy lifestyle.
He had smoked.
He ate a lotta rich foods.
He was a chef.
Now, on December 19th, 2011,
he was sitting right here
in this room with Kristina,
um, when his heart stopped.
He was only 39 years old.
Now does this photo look like
the person you ran into?
I would say yes.
Tell Amy the story
about the bruise around the arm.
I was upstairs.
I was
repacking Marcus' things,
and arms grabbed me.
And I began to burn.
It hurt so badly.
And I'm like, "No!"
And I thought it was Marcus
the minute it happened.
I don't get the impression
that he --
that he would harm anyone.
No, I don't either.
I don't think he wanted
his stuff to leave.
I loved him.
The next people that I met,
when they were alive,
they were a couple.
The wife is
an emotional wreck.
Extremely depressed.
I think that
the living would --
would associate her
with, like, a shadow person,
um, because she is
all black.
And she likes to watch
people in the beds.
The other thing is she doesn't,
smell very good.
Now you see shadows.
Yeah. I see shadows,
mostly when I'm sittin' here
watchin' TV.
And I'll see a shadow...
real fast go by the TV.
- Okay.
- You mentioned a smell, right?
Yeah.
All the time.
It's, like, walkin' past death.
Her husband is the one
I'm more concerned about.
He was
an extremely angry man.
I felt like he was insane.
He goes all over the house.
He has major issues
with women.
He gets really pissy if somebody
starts talking about him.
And he'll get right up on
that person,
like, right in their space.
This'll make a living person
very stressed out.
Um, I think that living people
might be able to see him.
Lorie got
physically attacked by --
There's this horn-shaped
kind of figurine statue thing
with elephants on it.
I was in bed
and I was sleeping.
And it was low enough
that it shoulda just
fallen on my chest.
But it bashed me
in the head.
And I still have pain.
Yeah. He's a bully.
The other thing is anxiety
throughout the house.
Everybody has anxiety attacks.
I'm actually dizzy,
like I could pass out.
I don't know why.
This house...
Yeah.
You get anything on this guy,
like who he was?
I got that
he'd been in prison.
I got that he was from back east
and that he moved here.
I got that he owned a couple
of small businesses.
I got that he was murdered.
Um, and he feels
like he did not deserve it.
And I got constantly,
him in fire.
Half of his face is, like,
burnt, singed.
Definitely reminds me
of somebody
who came up in my research.
One of the most
notorious gangsters
in Youngstown
lived about 600 feet from here.
His name
was Charles Cavallaro.
He went by the name
of Cadillac Charlie.
Charlie was
a Sicilian immigrant,
came to the US in 1921.
He lived in New York City.
You said the east coast.
He was in the mob.
He was probably a made guy.
And we know he got arrested
a few times.
Now in 1940,
he moved to Youngstown.
You said something about fire
and him saying he was murdered.
That's about as spot-on
as it gets.
On November 23rd, 1962,
he was gonna take the kids
to football practice.
Charlie turned on the car,
and boom, it exploded.
****.
The car bomb killed him
and his 11-year-old son
Tommy instantly.
Now I have pictures
of Cadillac Charlie.
And his son.
And this is car
after the explosion.
The crime was never solved.
Definitely a mob hit.
My god.
Is that who you think
you saw?
I had a sketch done
of him.
-100% this is him.
- Absolutely.
You tell me if you think
that's him or not.
Yeah.
My.
Yep.
Yeah.
Why would he be here, though?
'Cause there's somethin' else
that's here.
The thing that I'm most
concerned about
is the thing
in the dining room.
It's, like, a big mass.
A big blob.
It has, like veins on it.
And it's, like,
always pulsating.
Like a heart.
This has a very large impact
on anybody in this house.
It feeds on negativity,
and that's how
it gains power and grows.
And I saw one living person
being consumed,
by this thing
on an energetic level.
This living person
would feel like
they were losing themselves,
like they were losing
their personality
and aspects of their being.
This person could be sick
and/or dying.
We talkin' about Lorie here?
Sounds like it.
Yeah.
I feel like I'm here
and not here.
And here and not here.
I was getting
that the living would experience
a lot of nightmares.
And also, visions.
One of the things
that I was shown
was somebody
watching someone cooking.
And all of a sudden, they get
this, like, vision of them,
like, picking up a knife
and walking up
behind the person.
It can manipulate the living
to harm one another.
When I'm in the kitchen,
when I go toward
the sharp knives,
something in my head
tells me,
"Slit your wrists. It'll be
okay. It'll be over."
But it's, like, somebody talking
to me, not in my own brain.
Now it makes sense.
Yeah.
You wanted to kill
the family dog, too.
Yeah. Soon as I opened
the cage to let her out.
The dog knew it wasn't me
because that dog ran from me,
and she don't never run from me.
It's a good thing she did
'cause if I'd have caught her,
I'd have killed her.
I go outside and shake my head,
and I'm like, "Get outta me!"
And it goes away.
The last time it happened,
I punched a hole in the wall.
And I would never
do anything like that.
- Weren't we talkin' about this?
- Yeah.
That we hoped it wasn't him,
and it had somethin'
to do with the house.
- Right.
- You know it's not him.
Yeah.
Now what did this thing
look like?
I had a sketch done.
This looks like somethin'
out of a science fiction movie
or somethin'.
Whoa.
And it grows?
Yes.
A long time ago,
it first started.
Like a seed.
And everything negative
that's happened
over these many, many years
has fed it.
And it's grown bigger and bigger
and bigger and bigger
to this now.
It is like a little animal.
And as an animal,
what do they want?
They want food.
And they wanna be strong,
they wanna survive.
The only way it's gonna do
that is by taking living people.
Going after people
who are vulnerable
that it can absorb.
So this thing, every time
they fight, it gets stronger.
Yes.
Every time Roy has his rage,
it gets stronger.
Yeah.
So if this goes unchecked,
what happens?
Well, I go that
it'll keep growing.
And then eventually,
it would mesh and become
part of the house.
And basically the house
would then be alive,
essentially.
Can anybody live in a house
like that?
No. Mnh-mnh. No.
I was right.
This house
is going to kill me.
Well, Lorie,
I gotta tell you,
you're one of the strongest
people I've ever met.
Amy, listen, I don't wanna put
pressure on you,
but I really hope you can
come up with something for Lorie
so she can live out
her final days in peace.
For years,
this thing has fed
and it has
only grown stronger,
to the point,
that I don't think
any living thing
should be near this thing.
What does this mean?
They gotta move?
The only way that this thing
in this area could be cleansed
is if many mediums,
many holy people
came over months and months
and dedicated
many days, hours,
to eradicating first
the negative dead,
and then attacking this thing
at its source.
The thing of it is,
we leave this thing here,
what's gonna happen?
What I'm honestly hoping
is that this area
will be leveled.
It needs to be leveled.
It's all right, hon.
It's just a house.
Right.
We can get a house.
That's no big deal.
It'll be all right.
It'll be okay.
Well, I guess we better hurry up
'cause I'm not doin' too good.
I know, baby. I know.
Once these guys move,
will she start to feel
a little bit better?
I hope so.
It can't come with me,
can it?
No.
Now will Roy's rage go away
once he's...
Yeah, that'll --
You'll change dramatically.
I hope so.
Listen, you guys
may have lost a home,
but now you got
each other again.
Right?
I know the answers
you were lookin' for
wasn't the ones you got.
No.
But you got answers.
We will be
outta this house quick.
We've had enough.
I wish I had better news
for Lorie and Roy,
but leaving this house
is their best option.
If they do that, things
should improve between them,
and Lorie can live
her remaining days in peace.