He can do
physical stuff.
He can touch you.
Your mom was murdered
right here in this room?
Yes, she was.
She's pissed.
She feels
like she's being tortured.
A shadow person
started to charge at me.
I think that a living person
was attacked.
He shoots himself
in the mouth,
and the bullet comes out
the top of his head.
What is this thing?
A demon.
He doesn't want anybody here.
I just hear death.
My name is Amy Allan.
God.
It's like,
"I'm going to get you."
I see dead people.
Her face was all demonic.
I speak to dead people.
He's like, "You think you can
stop me? Because you can't."
And they speak to me.
What is he trying to do?
Kill them.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
Something happened.
Bam, bam, bam!
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
Am I seeing
what I think I'm seeing?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
They're everywhere.
It's my job to reveal them.
This guy's got the markings
of a serial killer.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end...
Is this dead guy
doing that to her?
...when we uncover
if it's safe for you to stay...
That's it.
...or time to get out.
Somebody's gonna die
over there soon, yeah.
I'm in the small town
of Lake City, Florida,
about an hour west
of Jacksonville.
I got a call from a woman
who was crying hysterically
on the phone.
She says her house
is a war zone.
She says, if things
don't change soon,
someone's gonna
get hurt really bad.
I'm hoping Amy and I
can help her out,
'cause she sounded terrible.
Before Amy arrives,
I need to make sure
any photographs,
religious symbols,
or personal items
that may influence her findings
are removed
or hidden from sight.
When I'm finished,
the location will be ready
for tonight's walk.
There's, like,
a lot of pain here.
This one guy in particular
who died,
he's not, like, human.
He's, tall, really tall.
Um, but he is kind of
like an orange, red --
like, that kind of a color.
He...thinks, like,
humans, I guess,
are interesting,
and he likes to imitate them.
So when he is imitating them,
he takes on
a more human, form.
He's not a good thing.
So, Regina,
I'm glad I'm here now,
'cause when we spoke
on the phone,
you sounded
pretty desperate.
My nieces, my cousins' kids,
my nephews --
they won't come over no more
'cause they're terrified.
Well, do you have
children of your own?
No, me and my husband
can't have kids.
It breaks my heart.
All right, so, give me
a list of what's happening.
Knocking and banging
and things move around.
Um, we've seen
shadow people -- apparitions.
Um, and lately, it's been
getting kind of violent
with people getting scratched,
pushed, shoved.
Okay, so, when did you guys
move in?
Um, we moved in,
um, 2005.
And we moved in to take care
of my husband's grandmother.
Well, what can you
tell me about it?
His mother was killed.
Your husband's mother?
In this house?
Who did it?
Her brother.
My husband will tell
you more about it.
Okay.
Now, you said
you moved here to take care
of your husband's
grandmother.
Did she witness
the murder?
Yes.
Okay, is she still alive?
No.
Okay, when did she pass?
Um, 2008.
Here's a picture
of Dorothy.
And how old was she
when she passed?
Um, 92.
Where did she die?
And what'd she die of?
Um, natural causes.
And here, at the house.
She had dementia.
It was a hard thing
'cause that's the first time
I've ever really
watched somebody die.
Okay.
Have you done anything
to try to fix things here?
I have saged the house.
I have salted the yard.
There was always something
about the side yard
I've never liked.
Why don't you
like it outside?
One morning --
it was early --
I went outside the door
and looked up.
And there was, like, a --
a shadow person
about 6 foot...
maybe bigger --
started to charge at me.
And I'm like, "Whoa.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no."
There's something out there,
something bad.
Someone put a barrier up.
It's keeping
this tall thing out.
He can't come in here
and do anything.
And he's angry about it.
Is it just focused
on this house?
Yes.
It looks at it
as, like, a challenge.
He says
that he will find a way.
He will.
He will find a way.
Okay, what are you
experiencing in here?
Um, when I was
sitting on the couch,
it was sitting behind me.
Okay.
And I seen, like, a light
out of the corner of my eye.
I looked at it.
And it came down.
But it had
Uncle Jack's face on it
as it disappeared
in the chair.
All right.
Who's Uncle Jack?
My husband's uncle
who was involved
with the murder-suicide.
Were you on any medication?
No.
Nothing like that.
That woulda freaked me out
a little bit.
Okay.
Anything else?
Last night, I was out there
in the laundry room.
Something came up
and hit me in my back.
It felt like somebody had,
like, a knife or a screwdriver,
and he went down into it.
Getting assaulted, basically
is what's going on.
Yes.
Anything else going on?
Little shadow person,
about yea big.
He runs around.
All right.
So, this -- the shadow,
how big are we talking?
Um, about that big.
Well, what about
the dog casting a shadow
as it's running around?
When I see it,
usually,
I can see my two dogs
in here with me.
He can run...after them...
and follow them.
You mean
when they leave here?
Yes.
I see him,
like, in a car.
He says he gets really little,
when he does that.
Can you describe what it looks
like when it's small?
It looks like a troll.
But the thing is, like,
it's really muscular.
Do the living see it?
I see a living person
looking out...the door
and seeing it,
like, quick outside.
And I -- you know,
I would be concerned
about him trying
to injure them in the car.
What is this thing?
Some kind of demon.
So, what's going on
in here?
I constantly feel
like I'm being watched.
But it's coming
from the outside,
like something's
out the window,
looking inward.
Just...I feel
like somebody's out there,
standing there,
watching me.
All right.
Anything else happening in here?
Yeah.
I was scratched in here.
Here's the pictures
of them.
One's on my chest
and on my lower stomach.
That's pretty bad scratches.
These are pretty deep.
Yeah.
You sure the dog
didn't do this?
Dogs aren't
allowed in my bed.
So there's no way.
So how the hell are you
sleeping at night
knowing that, you know,
this could happen to you?
I have
a lot of nightmares.
Now, describe
the nightmares to me.
What are we
talking about?
Bad things happening
to my husband.
Sometimes, they're violent.
There's a lot of energy
in this house.
That's why the dead are
so attracted to this place.
There's a military officer.
He's like...
"Stand down.
Stand down."
And I feel sick.
I feel sick.
Like, I feel his fear,
like, shaking.
He can bother the living.
If he feels like people
are too much in his space,
he wigs out.
He can do physical stuff.
He can touch them, like...
poking really hard.
He can make you feel sick.
He can touch you.
He's like, "You don't want
to see when I get angry."
Bad.
So, John, I know this is not
easy to talk about.
But your mom was murdered
right here in this room.
Yes, she was.
It happened right here.
Her chair was sitting here.
Assassinated her.
He killed himself
20 minutes later.
The bullet hole's still up
in the ceiling right there.
Wow.
Now, what about
your grandmother? Where was she?
She was sitting over there
in the corner in her chair.
And when it happened,
she got up and ran outside.
This is my mom, Becky,
and my Grandma Dorothy
and my Uncle Jack.
And this is the uncle that --
that did this thing?
Yes, sir.
How old was your mom
when she passed?
59.
What kind of woman
was she?
She was a nurse --
the head nurse.
She didn't get her way...
there'd be hell to pay.
She was very difficult
to be around.
Sounds like you guys
had a tough relationship.
Yes.
So, John, any indication
as to why your uncle snapped?
He was...
a military vet.
I think he had PTSD.
He was...real crazy.
Okay, so this man
was a troubled guy?
Yes.
You find it hard staying here
knowing this happened here?
Yes.
Do you ever think maybe
you should leave this place
because of what happened?
Yes,
but it's financial reasons.
We can't.
Do you think...any one
of those people are here?
I feel my ma.
And I s--
I hear my grandma.
What about your Uncle Jack?
I think he's here, too.
I just feel his presence.
Okay.
I'm seeing
the military guy again.
He's tough and very,
territorial.
I think he lived here.
I feel like he had a lot
to do with this house.
Like, he's like,
"Get the **** out."
He's got issues.
He's got mega issues.
It is terrible back here.
Have you had
any experiences?
Yes.
Okay.
Tell me what happened.
I was standing in the middle
of the living room one evening.
Okay.
And it felt
like something shoved me
and on my lower part
of my leg.
And I went forward
into the window.
And you're sure
you didn't trip?
I didn't trip.
I was just standing there.
You're lucky
you didn't cut an artery.
Something very bad...
happened here.
You know what?
I think that a living person
was attacked in here,
like, bad.
I wanna say this is that dude --
the angry military guy.
Think I hear glass breaking.
And I'm feeling it,
like, on me.
I'm, like, falling down.
And there's,
like, glass everywhere.
Like, I'm being pushed.
I can't breathe.
They end up on the floor.
This angry man,
he doesn't want anybody here.
Why'd you bring me
out here?
I...have a feeling
of an ominous presence
in the woods.
Are you feeling it
right now?
Yes. I --
What --
what are you feeling?
Something's watching me...
over in the woods.
It's looking at me
right now.
Where's it looking
at you from?
It's over there.
But you can't see it.
I can't see it.
But I feel it.
All right.
Anything else?
Banging.
Okay.
What kind of banging?
Like somebody knocking
on the door?
Yeah.
Like,
cabinets opening and closing.
I was in the kitchen
one time.
And, there was a dish
on the sink.
It fell off the counter,
onto the floor.
It broke my toe.
And so what makes you think
that's paranormal?
Nobody touched it.
I didn't touch it.
Think it was pushed.
It's just devious.
I don't know what it is.
There's a woman.
She has an accent.
I feel like
this is really recent.
She says that
if she would not have died,
none of this would be going on.
I'm gonna say
that she lived here.
She was cooking
and cleaning all the time.
She's slamming,
slamming, slamming,
banging, banging, banging.
She says she keeps
trying to leave.
But she says someone keeps --
living person --
a living person
keeps pulling her back,
keeps calling her back.
This is a living female
doing this to her.
She's sleeping.
Living lady's sleeping.
She goes into her dream.
And she gives
the living woman nightmares.
She's pissed.
She feels
like she's being tortured.
She says that they know her,
that they know her.
They know she's here.
"Why won't they let me go?
Why won't they let me go?
They know I'm here.
Let me go.
Let me go."
Well, obviously,
the first thing
I'm gonna look into
is this murder-suicide.
Now, John gave me a lot
of good information about
why his uncle might've snapped.
But I wanna know exactly
what happened that day.
I'm heading over to meet with
a Jacksonville medical examiner
who's gonna take me through
the crime second by second.
The murder takes place
September 19, 2005.
Can you take me through that,
exactly what happened?
Apparently, the sister, Becky,
is sitting on the recliner.
Jack comes up behind her
and shoots her one time
in the back of her head.
And she probably turns
to see what happened.
And then,
she takes a second shot
to her left temple area.
Based on the crime scene
photographs,
it doesn't seem
like she moved anywhere.
She just died right there
in the recliner.
The woman
who is being trapped here
won't talk about her death.
She's, like,
really trying to block me
from getting how she died.
She said...
Let's just say,
like, her death was
a freak accident.
Um, she was young.
She was only, 52.
It's wicked bad.
She wants to leave.
All right,
so she basically didn't even
know what hit her?
Probably not.
Well, Jack --
how does he kill himself?
He shoots himself
in the mouth.
And the bullet
comes out the top of his head,
like you see right here.
And then, he falls back
and dies in that hallway.
Okay, so, Doctor,
I'm assuming
a toxicology was done?
Yes.
He had
multiple medications.
They were not
illegal drugs
or drugs of abuse
that were in his system.
Do we know
what he was taking drugs for?
He suffered from PTSD,
because he was
in the Vietnam War.
Apparently, he was
a helicopter pilot
and was shot down twice.
Okay.
In addition,
he was depressed.
He suffered from
Parkinson's disease.
He had a heart condition --
apparently, had a heart attack
prior to him coming to live
with his sister,
who was gonna
take care of him.
And do we have any idea
why he might have wanted
to kill his sister?
His mother had signed over
the deed of the house
to his sister.
And this right here
is the deed.
So he got cut out
altogether.
That's correct.
He had, um, what we interpret
to be a suicide note.
This is very brief.
He says he's depressed.
"Becky is mean to us."
And then, he says
he didn't want any CPR.
He didn't want
any resuscitation.
So he wanted to make sure
that he would die.
I feel like he had a lot
to do with this house
'cause he's like,
"Get the **** out."
The angry dead man
who attacks the living
is following me everywhere I go.
He's furious that I'm here.
But I'm not leaving
until I find out
who he was in life.
He had a heart attack.
Feel like he started dying here
or died here.
Feel like he was in wars.
He fought in wars.
And he had injuries
or something.
His legs feel...so weird...
...like, burning,
like, they're on fire.
He is angry, angry,
angry, angry, angry.
If you need us
to investigate
unexplained activity
in your home,
go to the "Dead Files" page
at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help Me, Dead Files!"
to submit your story.
And we'll help if we can.
So far, I've got clients
being physically assaulted
in a house where
a murder-suicide took place.
But I need to see
if there's anything else
that's gonna help
my investigation.
Reading two old
newspaper articles,
I find one of
the original owners
of my clients' property
was a sheriff.
Turns out a local
Syrian couple was murdered.
And he was caught right in
the middle of the scandal.
So, I'm heading over to meet
with a local professor
who says he's got information
that will definitely
help my case.
The sheriff that lived
on my clients' property,
what can you
tell me about him?
Sheriff Wiley "Babe" Douglass,
born in 1885.
He became chief of police
in the city in 1920.
He must have been very popular,
very charismatic
because he ran
for sheriff and won.
This is him
in his uniform
shortly after
winning that election.
What kind of sheriff
was he, though?
I mean,
what are we talking about?
Well, he was corrupt.
Sheriff Douglass was accused
of bootlegging,
running gambling
operations.
And he was also accused
of selling young women
into prostitution.
Geez.
Why exactly does he come onto
my clients' property?
Do we know that?
Well, Steve, he purchases
your clients' property in 1928.
All right.
So let's get to the murders.
What exactly happened?
The Romey family,
they're a successful,
Syrian family,
immigrants.
They own
a small produce store.
The Romeys' son, Esau,
is involved in an auto accident.
And the mother, Fannie Romey,
doesn't like the way
that the city chief of police
handled the investigation.
And so she contacts
the chief of police.
She calls him a liar.
Back then,
you didn't call
the chief of police
in any Florida city a liar.
Okay.
So what happens next?
Well, Steve,
on May 17, 1929,
the chief of police goes to
the Romeys' store,
with two of his men and also
one of Sheriff Douglass' men.
Okay.
But Douglass is not at the scene
when this all goes down.
That's correct.
All right, so when they show up,
what happens?
There's
a huge altercation.
They actually take
Mr. Romey,
and they actually
pistol-whip him.
And he's knocked unconscious.
He's on the ground.
At that point, Mrs. Romey
comes into the store.
She panics.
She grabs a pistol the family
has kept as shopkeepers.
And she actually
shoots the chief,
wounds him,
not seriously.
Then the police return fire.
She's killed.
And at that time,
the police didn't know this,
but she actually was pregnant.
Geez.
All right.
And so at that point,
the police pull her husband,
Mr. Romey,
Nola Romey,
out of the store.
They pull the son, Esau,
out of the store, as well.
They actually bring them
to separate jails.
Later that evening, a mob
comes to the city jail.
They abduct Mr. Romey.
They take him
out of the jail.
They shoot him 13 times,
murder him.
These were some articles
I found on the case.
Even though he wasn't
at either one
of these crime scenes,
his culpability is --
is pretty high.
And, got away
with, basically, murder.
So after all is said and done,
is,
Babe still on my clients'
property at this point?
He is on
your clients' property
until the day he dies
in 1947.
And at that point,
he is 61 years old.
He goes out in his car.
He's driving.
He has a heart attack
and dies.
Okay.
I'm seeing
that red-orange thing again.
He's, like, really racist,
which is weird
'cause he's, like, not human.
Who is it racist towards?
I think really everybody.
This thing,
he gloats about how,
when he first came here,
he was able to influence
and manipulate men.
He would, like, do ****
to people.
Like, cause them to turn
against each other, death,
fighting and --
and all this kind of bad ****
mostly people
killing other people.
But he had
a great success rate.
You know, one other thing caught
my attention in research --
A woman who used to live
on the property
died in a fire
right on Regina and John's land.
I'm heading over to meet
with a local genealogist
who says that tragedy could
have been easily prevented.
Why'd you bring me here?
This house is very similar
to the house
that Louisa Smith Markham
lived in
when she died
from the fire.
What about the fire?
What happened?
So in 1886,
Louisa, um,
was taking care of the youngest
child, who was Elton.
He was severely ill,
had, a real bad cold.
So she bundled him up
and was --
was sitting at the rocking chair
in front of the fire.
Well, her nightgown
caught on fire.
And as that occurred,
the first instinct
of a mother, of course,
is to save the child.
Right.
Which she did.
She got Elton
away from her.
And by that time,
she was completely engulfed
in flames, screaming.
The house is very small.
Everybody would have seen it.
It was so tragic
because the children
would have seen her die.
How old was she
when she died?
She was 32.
They're lucky that the whole
house didn't burn down.
So she was a hero, really.
She saved the kid.
Right.
I saw several disturbing things
on my walk.
But what really concerned me
was the angry man
attacking a living woman.
He was an elderly man...
pretty much bald.
He has, like, a big belly.
He was, like, pushing her head
into the wall.
Was this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready
to reveal our findings
to each other and our clients
for the first time.
Amy, I want you to meet
Regina and her husband, John.
Now, here's the issue --
Regina can't have children.
So she's always filled the house
here with nieces and nephews.
But the activity's gotten so
violent, they won't come over.
And Regina doesn't even
know if it's safe
for them to live here.
So with that being said,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy
and have her talk
about her walk.
When I first arrived,
I saw this being outside.
And it's very
strange-looking, very tall.
And it was also --
The color of it was interesting
because it was kind of
like a reddish orange.
This entity cannot get
into the house.
To him, or to it,
something or somebody
put up a barrier
around this property
that is keeping him out.
And because of that,
he's become very obsessed
and fixated
on finding a way in.
I saged the house.
Okay.
I salted the yard.
Now, would that be
what's keeping him out?
Yes, so, then,
more than likely,
that's probably
the barrier
that is keeping
him at bay.
Even though he can't get
into the home,
he can follow you
off of the property.
I saw him get into a vehicle
with a living person.
And when
he travels with you,
he kind of
shrinks himself down
so he has little arms,
little legs.
But they're
very, like, strong.
My concern
with him doing that is
that he could cause you
to have a car accident.
Well,
that's pretty interesting.
We got a lot
to discuss now.
Why don't you
tell Amy, Regina,
about the shadow figure
that rushed you outside?
There was a dark,
6- footish figure,
black, black, black.
And it charged at me.
I'm like, "No.
Go away."
And it vanished.
Now, Regina has a problem
where she actually sleeps facing
the wall because...
'Cause I feel
like I'm being watched.
that could be him.
He's ob-- obsessed.
What's unusual
about it was
that there was no recollection
of where he originated from.
He stated that he's never
been human,  ever.
Even though he's never
been human, he's a racist.
I'm not exactly certain
what it is.
Um, but I would say,
you know,
possibly a demon.
Not good.
I thought
it was evil.
It was dark,
very dark.
He was saying that he was able
to influence men
to kill one another
and wants that to continue.
But he's a racist
in general.
Yes.
A lot of what you're saying
makes me think about a man
that actually lived
on your property
from the '20s to the '40s.
And his name was
Wiley Douglass.
Everybody knew him
as "Babe."
I actually got
a photo of him.
He became
the county sheriff.
And in 1929,
there was a Syrian family
in town
known as the Romey family
that ran a grocery store.
It was real nearby.
Now, the kid
of the family
got into some kind
of a car accident.
And they didn't like the way
the police handled it.
So now, the mom, Fannie,
calls the chief of police
to complain about
how they handled things.
And she basically
called him a liar.
Well, that didn't sit too well
with the guys.
On May 17, 1929,
the police chief,
two deputies
and one of the sheriff's
deputies go to the store.
So now, when the cops
entered the location,
they pistol-whipped
the dad, Nola,
and knocked him out
to the ground.
The mom, Fannie, saw her husband
lying on the ground,
thought he was dead.
She picked up the gun
they kept in the store.
And she
shot at the police.
The police returned fire
and killed her.
Now, this is
where it gets really screwed-up.
The son and Nola were arrested
and brought to separate jails.
Now get this -- That night,
a mob comes in, drags out Nola.
And they shot him
13 times.
And then they dumped his body
in some farm,
wind up making
national news.
So, now, could any of that,
what happened,
had to do with
this red-orange guy outside?
I do believe that,
more than likely,
he influenced the cop
to make poor decisions
and cause
the deaths of others.
So, what else
did you see?
The next person that I met
was an interesting character.
She, looks to be,
in her 50s.
She's trying to leave.
But a female here
keeps pulling her back.
She said that she's getting
called directly by name.
She said it's torturous,
and she's furious about it
because she wants to leave.
And she said to me
that she goes
into the female's dreams
and gives
this female nightmares.
And she is talking to her
in the dreams,
saying, "Let me go.
Let me go.
Let me go."
Well, you're the only female
that lives in the house.
Right. I have
different bad dreams.
I've always
had bad dreams, though.
It's because you're,
more than likely, a medium.
I've always been able
to hear things
and see things
and talk to things
that's not there.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
This dead woman, she also
is capable of slamming doors.
She also has a fixation
in the kitchen.
She showed me her slamming
the oven door and banging it.
Now, John,
you talked to me about noises
you heard in the kitchen, right?
Yes.
I get done with the dishes
and stuff.
And I'll come back
out here and sit.
And it sound
like somebody's in there,
messing with
the dishes.
You think that's
the woman doing that?
I think so.
Now, did you get any idea
who this woman
might have been in life?
I think she might have lived
in this house.
She showed me images
of her cooking and cleaning
all the time.
And I sensed
that someone in this house
knew about her dying.
But she wouldn't talk to me
about her death at all.
She kept blocking me
from seeing it.
It's time we tell Amy
about the 1,000-pound gorilla
in the room.
John's mother, Becky,
was murdered right over there,
in that corner.
My goodness.
To make things worse,
the murderer was her brother,
John's Uncle Jack.
Got it.
Now, it happened
on September 19, 2005.
That night, John's mom
was sitting in a chair
right there
when his Uncle Jack
came up this hallway.
He put two bullets
in her head and killed her.
He went halfway
down this hallway here,
put the gun in his mouth,
and shot himself in the head
and killed himself.
My gosh.
John's mom, she was 59 years old
at the time she died.
Tell Amy about your mom,
what kind of woman she was.
Very headstrong,
where if it wasn't her way,
it was the highway.
She'd get mad.
At the snap of a finger,
she'd get mad at anything.
Your uncle, was he ever
in the military?
Yes, he was.
He was in the Army.
He was
a helicopter pilot.
And he was
shot down twice.
My God.
Okay. Got it.
It sounds like you might have
seen Becky, John's mom.
I have a picture of Becky.
Okay. Yeah.
Let me see her.
This is Becky.
Yeah.
That's who I saw.
I just don't want her
to be stuck here.
Regina's accidentally
trapping her here, though.
Yes.
Which happens to a lot
of mediums that I meet.
We like to have
dead people around us.
So, then I met
another person.
And it was
in the laundry room.
When I walked in there, I felt
that a living person, female,
was being violently attacked
by an older, deceased male.
And to me, it was so intense,
it nearly killed this person.
And I think the living person
was, pushed to the ground.
I saw, like,
a pane of glass, um,
break and shatter
onto my head.
You know, everybody's getting
attacked here.
I was standing,
looking out the window.
And it felt
like something pushed me,
the middle part
of my leg.
And I fell forward
into the four panes of glass
and broke the glass.
He's lucky
he didn't cut his wrist open.
Right.
The other night,
I was in there,
taking stuff
out of the dryer.
And it felt
like somebody took
either a very narrow knife
or a sharp blade...
...and hit me
right back here.
I felt it here.
And I could feel it
through my skin.
I had a sketch done
of the attack I saw.
Should be interesting.
I'm sorry, guys,
to even show you this.
What are you thinking
when you see this?
Jack.
You're thinking
of your Uncle Jack?
That's why
I turned away.
I know you did.
I don't need to see it.
I don't wanna see it.
Can we take him
off the table?
Yeah.
We'll take him off.
There we go.
Did you get anything
about this guy in life?
Yes, I did.
Let's talk about that
before we go
jumping the gun.
I got that this male
has extreme issues.
He's incredibly angry.
He was a very tough guy
in life.
I got that he had a heart attack
at some point.
I got that there was
something extremely wrong
with his hips and legs.
It hurt so freaking bad, it felt
like there was fire shooting
through my legs
and into my hips.
I got
that he was in a war
and that he had suffered
injuries from that war.
I got that he lived
and died here
and that he was extremely
territorial about this house.
He didn't want me
or anybody else here.
Well, remember when I told you
about John's mom
being killed
by her own brother?
Okay.
Now, his name was Jack.
He had a ton of issues,
both mental and physical.
He was a helicopter pilot
in the Vietnam War.
He was shot down twice.
John believes
he suffered from PTSD.
He was also
a physical wreck, though.
He suffered from Parkinson's
and walked with a walker.
Okay. Got it.
Now, you mentioned before
that you thought he had
a heart attack.
Yes.
He did have
a heart attack.
And that's why John's mom
told him to move in here,
so she could
take care of him.
Now, the family thinks
there's a couple of reasons
that he might have snapped.
PTSD was the main reason.
Through the fact
that their mother, Dorothy,
was giving the house to Becky
and not to Jack.
The territorial.
Okay. Yeah.
Do you have any doubts
that it could be him?
No.
Okay.
Absolutely not.
Why is he being
so violent?
He still wants
the house.
He wants this for him.
He coulda killed you.
Yes, he could have.
So, John,
your family lived here.
They died here.
And, apparently,
they're still here.
Question is,
how can we move them on
and take care of this thing
outside and to get your lives
back to where there's children
in this house again?
For that, I'm gonna
turn it over to Amy.
I do think
that thing outside is
a...agent of chaos.
I think
he may have influenced
what happened
in your family.
That being said,
I'm very happy
that you had the insight
and wherewithal
to put down that salt.
But this sucker
is tenacious.
And he will get in
eventually.
The first thing
that needs to be done
is the removal
of the dead.
A medium needs
to come into the home.
On the first visit, the medium
needs to take care of the dead
that you don't know.
Okay.
The second visit
is going to be
to assist your mother,
um, to move on,
and then,
once that's been completed,
to move on
to your uncle.
I need for you to recall
two really good memories
about your uncle
and give those to the medium
because it's only
through those memories
that she'll be able
to reach him.
Now, this is
very important.
Okay.
Hold on for a second.
You seem
a little shocked.
I think he is.
- You okay to let go?
- Yes.
Okay.
'Cause you don't want them
to be here.
You want her to...
Move on.
Okay. Good.
The entity is next.
What needs to be done
with that situation
is a priest
needs to come,
needs to exorcise
the outside of your house
and then do a blessing
outside of your home.
It's going to keep
all negativity out forever.
So, once all these steps
are done,
they should feel a difference
in the house, right?
Yeah. You'll feel
a substantial difference.
This is
pretty freaking good news.
Definitely.
We can have the kids
to come over and play, you know?
I'm glad you guys
called us in.
You know, it broke my heart
listening to your story.
But now you can go from
the house of basically the dead
to the house of a happy,
living family.
Yeah.
I cannot imagine the pain
John and Regina feel
knowing they have
deceased family members
inside their home.
But I believe
if they follow my advice,
they can set them free
and banish the demon outside
forever.