The living
don't stand a chance here.
I feel like
we're being watched.
- You do.
- Yes.
I feel like he would
hunt me down and kill me.
I had a couple cases
of beer.
Right after I left the room,
they fell.
There's also, like, a lot
of sex and bad --
it's so bad.
A lot of times,
these women would get
black market abortions.
This man was a killer.
I just hear death.
My name is Amy Allan.
God.
It's like,
"I'm going to get you."
I see dead people.
Her face was all demonic.
I speak to dead people...
He's like, "You think you can
stop me? Because you can't."
...and they speak to me.
- What is he trying to do?
- Kill them.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
Something happened.
Bam. Bam. Bam.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Shiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
Am I seeing
what I think I'm seeing?
I know every person,
every house has secrets.
- They're everywhere.
- It's my job to reveal them.
This guy's got the markings
of a serial killer.
But Steve and I
never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation...
...until the very end...
Is this dead guy
doing that to her?
When we uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
That's it.
...or time to get out.
Somebody's gonna die
over there soon. Yeah.
I'm in Paso Robles, California.
It's halfway between LA
and San Francisco.
I got a call
from a guy named Ron.
Now, he owns a historic bar
in town,
but activity's so bad employees
are quittin'
and regular customers
are staying away.
The last thing he wants to do
is shut the place down,
but if Amy and I can't help,
that's exactly what
he's gonna have to do.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area
of anything that might
influence her findings.
This is a large space with a lot
of artwork and signs
that need to be covered.
When I'm finished,
the location'll be ready
for tonight's walk.
Boy. I don't like this.
So there's a female.
I got...
really creeped out by her.
She's almost...
like, a real shadow person,
but she's a dead person.
After she died,
she plucked out her eyes
because she didn't wanna
see anymore.
She made her face just a skull
so that other dead people, like,
around here and around town
call her "The Reaper."
She definitely makes me
very uncomfortable.
She is very angry.
She's bent on revenge.
So, Ron, when we spoke
on the phone,
you sounded pretty upset
about the things
that are happening here.
I mean,
what the hell's going on?
I'm hearing things
from my employees.
from my customers.
Something's happening.
I'm not sure what it is,
but whatever it is, I need
to get it taken care of
before somebody actually
does get hurt.
Okay. Tell me, what -- what are
things that are going on here?
Well, my customers and employees
are telling me
they're hearing noises,
they're seeing apparitions.
Things are moving around,
and it's gettin'
physical, so...
Sounds like this is
all happening to other people.
Actually, I have seen
a few things myself.
Okay. Like what?
One of them was,
I was --
I was standing
at the end of the bar
and just looking down
the bar,
and I saw this shot glass
go from here to here.
The second thing was
by my coffee machine over there,
I had a jar
that literally went over the top
of some wine glasses
and just went off
on the ground.
Was anybody around
to knock it over?
No.
Why don't you just
sell it and walk away?
Well, one reason
is because my mom
started this place
45 years ago,
and, you know, and I took it
over about 5 years ago,
and I wanna keep it going
for her.
There's also another reason.
It's kind of like a mainstay
in this town.
It's one of the oldest buildings
in Paso Robles.
There's a lot of weird things
happening around here.
I need some help.
I need to know what it is
and I need to get rid of it.
Okay.
It doesn't feel very right.
It doesn't feel right.
The shadow woman
is like a hunter.
Her voice sounds like...
death.
Like, if you hear it,
like, she's coming for you.
You get that cold down --
all the way down,
like, from the neck
and all the way down.
So she can get
physically violent here.
I know, too, she definitely
follows somebody
and has, tried to,
harm them, in their homes
on several occasions.
So why'd you bring me
in here?
Well, I've had many reports
of things happening in here.
Okay. Did you ever see
any of this stuff?
No, I never did, so I decided
I'd stick some cameras in here.
All right.
Did you catch anything?
I did.
I had a couple cases of beer
just went off the stack
right after I left the room,
and they fell.
We're in California. You sure
it wasn't an earthquake?
Yeah, I'm sure because if
it was an earthquake,
half of my storeroom
would've been on the floor.
And I can't figure out
how the hell this...
This could be dangerous.
Yes. Yes.
Anything else going on
in this room?
I had an employee workin'
back here in the bar,
and she was looking
over in that corner.
There was about
an 8, 10-inch knife
laying on a tray,
and the knife just went...
Like that.
And it missed her by...
It could've been worse,
and we just lucked out
on that one, I think.
Yeah. She could've gotten
seriously hurt.
The shadow woman,
she's physically capable
of hurting people.
- How?
- She runs around with a knife.
Maybe they feel sharp pains
or something.
I don't know.
She also attacked people
in their throat area.
She's so creepy.
She's so **** creepy.
And she's, like,
really freaking the **** out.
She's hurtin' me.
Ay. She's hurtin' me.
So, Ron, what's the story
with the second floor here?
The history is it used
to be a brothel,
but I use it strictly now
for my customers
as a place to rest when they've
had too much to drink.
All right. So is anything
going on up here?
Some people have told me
about somebody was hanging
from the ceiling.
All right. So, how did they
describe this thing to you?
They told me that
they saw something hanging
or like they were holding on
to the ceiling.
And they -- they --
they described him
as like a mannequin
or like a person.
Okay. Anything else?
I had a couple
from down South.
When they came back down,
I noticed the lady was,
like, 5, 6 shades lighter.
And I was like,
"What the heck?"
I said, "What'd you guys do
up there?"
And the wife,
just out of nowhere, said,
"It grabbed my butt.
It grabbed my butt," and that's
all she could say, was,
"It grabbed my butt."
I have a camera
that's up here in the corner.
Well, I thought,
Okay, let me check and see
if it's in that camera,
and by golly, I found something.
I did keep the video
of that one.
Wow.
Something touched her
because you can tell by
her reaction that's not acting.
You know, most of the time,
I get photos,
and I look at them
with a...
You know, like, "Hey,
any photo can be doctored."
Right. Right.
But unless you got some tech guy
that can fix video like this,
this is some pretty compelling
evidence you got.
- Yes.
- If Amy suggested
that you should leave,
how would you take that?
It'd be pretty tough.
This has been in my family
for 45 years.
I don't wanna get rid of it,
and I will do whatever it takes.
Okay.
The shadow woman,
she's also able to jump people,
living people
who are sensitives.
The shadow woman is up here.
She kind of goes in between
where the ceiling
and the walls meet,
and then she'll
spread herself out,
and she can put her face
and her arms down.
I feel like this is a very,
very, very bad thing.
Like, I feel panicked.
So, Kim,
I was talking to Ron.
He said you worked here,
but you recently left.
Yes, I did.
Okay. How long
did you work here?
Almost 7 years.
Why'd you leave?
I'm curious.
I think the paranormal activity
is becoming more, um,
direct, more violent.
For my safety,
I had to go.
So now Ron mentioned
to me about,
customers havin'
experiences up here.
Now have they told you
the same thing?
Yes, many, many times.
I have customers that refuse
to come back up here.
There are customers
that have been so scared
that they will not return
to the saloon.
Okay. So what have you seen
or experienced?
Anything that you can
tell me about?
Yes.
We have a vacuum upstairs
that was moving up here
in the hallway,
but the electrical cord
was wrapped all the way around.
It was moving freely,
as if somebody was vacuuming.
So you didn't see anybody
holding it.
There was nobody holding it.
There was nobody up here.
That scared me.
That convinced me.
Okay. Anything else?
There is a presence
that you feel
when you come into
this place.
You always feel
like you're being watched.
I won't stay up here.
By doing that,
I'm challenging or welcoming
something to happen to me.
Are you feeling
any of that now?
I feel like
we're being watched.
- You do?
- Yes.
There is an energy
in this building.
By coming up here,
I become a target.
Okay.
There's, like, somebody saying,
"I know you. You know me."
And this is a dead person.
He's like, "I know you.
We've met."
Yeah, I don't like him.
I don't like him.
There's something wrong.
I'm feeling pain right here...
and right into my throat.
It feels like I'm being stabbed.
My leg -- I feel like
I'm being stabbed there.
Who is this person?
I don't know.
He's crazy, totally insane.
I don't like this.
I feel threatened.
I fe-- I don't feel safe at all
with this person.
He thinks, like, I'm -- like I'm
ratting on him or something.
I'm thinking that he can
probably do a lot of bad things,
like, really, really ****
bad things.
Like, I feel like -- like --
like he would
hunt me down and kill me.
He's totally crazy.
My God, like,
totally **** out there.
After meeting with Kim,
I started talking
to other employees and customers
of the Pine Street Saloon...
I witnessed,
for the first time
in my life,
a full apparition.
I even verbalized
to my friends,
"Are my eyes deceiving me
right now?"
...and everyone --
and I mean everyone,
had experiences to share.
All right.
So, you heard footsteps.
What else is going on?
Objects, you know,
being thrown.
That's a little strange.
Once I noticed
the activity here,
things started happening
at my own home as well.
With all the stories
I'm hearing,
I'm surprised
Ron's still in business.
The mirror up there
just, like, psh.
Like, if I would've been
sitting there,
my face would've
been cut up.
And I went, "What the hell?"
One night,
I was sitting on the bed
when I looked up and seen
somebody goin' into the room.
So what you saw
was an apparition?
Yes. He -- he was
a little creepy, you know?
I even looked away,
and when I looked back,
he was still looking at me.
There's something here.
There's definitely --
I feel like the man
knows everything.
He can, like, hurt you
and, like, control you,
and you can't escape from him.
You can't hide.
Like, he just owns you.
He can mess with your mind.
You feel like you need to run,
you need to get out of here.
You would feel frightened.
You would feel panicked,
scared.
He's gonna find you
and he's gonna get you.
He can manipulate them
and brainwash them.
People would have
nervous breakdowns.
They would be very sick.
They would have a lot
of physical attacks on them.
Living don't stand
a chance here.
Just, they don't
**** stand a chance.
So the minute
I get to a location,
I reach out to journalists,
local cops, genealogists,
anybody that can help me
with my case.
I just got a call back
from a local reporter
who says the original owner
of the property
has a story so colorful
it should be made into a movie.
So, Peggy, I appreciate
you helping me with this.
But let me ask you.
Why'd you bring me
all the way up here?
Well, this is a winery now,
but this property
was actually owned originally
by the Blackburns
that had the property
that you are investigating.
It was two brothers,
James and Daniel.
When did they get here, and how
much property did they have?
1857, they bought 26,000 acres
of what became Paso Robles.
And they split it evenly
between the two of them,
13,000 acres each.
Daniel went ahead
and took the portion
that actually is now
the, um, Pine Street Saloon.
Okay. So what do we know
about him?
Daniel was kind of
the dominant brother.
He was a very ambitious man
and he was a clever man.
And to protect his property,
he had himself
appointed sheriff.
He actually even had a vigilante
group that he directed.
They had 200 deputies
that were charged primarily
with removing Native Americans
and Mexicans from the property.
And very sadly,
a lot of people were killed
by this vigilante group.
Now, Peggy, you said
this guy Daniel had
a pretty rough time with things
while he was here.
Yes, he did. He --
he had married a woman
named Cecelia Dunn,
and this is her later
in life, of course.
And they had three children.
And in 1871,
she was in a carriage
with the three children,
and something spooked
the horse,
and, their
1- year-old daughter Jenny
was thrown out
of the carriage.
A soapbox flew out
of the carriage
and struck her in the head...
and it killed her instantly.
- This was a 1-year-old?
- Yes.
That's pretty tragic,
especially the way it happened.
Yes.
All right, so, Peggy,
when did they get around
to building the saloon
I'm investigating?
They built it approximately
in the mid-1880s.
So what happened after that?
Around the mid-1890s,
Daniel Blackburn's health
started to fail,
and he passed away in 1901.
Even in his death,
there were legal problems
over the property.
- And what happened?
- Daniel's widow, Cecelia,
had been left
all the property,
but he didn't leave anything
to the two sons.
And, within a year or so,
the two sons turned around
and sued their own mother.
Now according
to this article,
Daniel Blackburn actually was
mentally incompetent.
That's what the court found.
They did win the lawsuit,
and that was the end
of the saga of the Blackburns.
The creepy guy
is really dangerous.
Like, he feels, like, ownership.
I was seeing...
something actually
about a horse accident,
and it killed the rider.
I feel like this man
was a killer.
There's victims around him.
There's victims.
Like, I feel like --
like this man is,
like, unhinged.
He can hurt you and, like,
control you.
It's so scary.
There's something
about a code of silence.
You can't hide.
You can't escape from him.
Like, he just owns you.
So Ron mentioned
the upstairs area of this hotel
used to be a brothel.
Turns out it's true.
I'm on my way to meet
with a local crime writer
who says the conditions
were absolutely horrible.
So, Skye, thanks for
helping me out with the case.
I appreciate that.
We can assume then
that Ron's right
and upstairs might've been
a boarding house or a brothel.
Yes. It was kind of
widely known, um,
that a lot of the bars had
these sort of operations
that were happening upstairs.
Um, they were called
boarding houses.
That was the code word,
the kind of cover word.
They would operate above bars
like Pine Street.
Okay, so when would this
have been going on?
It started in, like,
the late 1800s,
and then into
the 21st century.
There was a real boom,
with the prostitution trade,
around World War I
because there was a large influx
of military personnel.
Now I did a lot of cases
with these brothels,
and I know the conditions
were horrible.
Did that happen here?
The conditions were terrible,
a lot of drugs and drinking.
And a lot of times,
they would abuse the women,
beat the women.
Then, of course,
it was not sanitary.
They didn't have access
to good medical care,
so a lot of times,
these women would get pregnant
and have to get
black market abortions.
There's these people,
they seem young.
Like, I'm just seeing,
like, people on drugs,
strung out, partying.
Drugs, drugs, drugs. Okay.
I feel like I'm on drugs.
There's also, like,
a lot of sex going on,
like, a lot of sex.
It's, like, so thick and bad.
It's so bad.
They're bad people.
I don't like it.
I don't know how anybody
could, like, for 1 minute,
be up here and be okay.
All right, so these girls
that had to get
these illegal abortions,
was there a doctor
in town they went to?
Well, actually,
there was a gentleman named,
Christian Thomas
who was a bartender
who moonlighted as,
an illegal abortionist.
What?
So I actually have a photo
of Thomas.
That's him there.
He actually worked in a place
called Lyle's Cocktail Lounge
about 300 yards away
from Pine Street.
All right. So where'd this guy
do these abortions?
He would bring his clients
back to his apartment,
which was
right around the corner.
We actually have
a picture of it as well.
So that was the room where
he would do the procedures.
So this is where
these poor girls were going.
Do we have any idea
how many he performed?
He admitted to 12.
Okay, you said he admitted
to doing 12 abortions.
So what happened?
Did he get caught?
In, -
So September 1, 1953,
he had a client, um,
that he botched the procedure,
and she ended up dying.
Okay. So what do we know
about the victim?
Her name was
Virginia Grider.
This is a picture of her.
She was 30 years old.
She was actually
from San Francisco.
Does he go to jail?
What's the story?
Thomas was arrested,
and later found guilty
of second degree murder.
She's still out here.
Who?
The shadow woman.
No one helped her.
She feels like she was, like,
a younger person when she died.
But she's from the '20s or '30s.
And I did keep seeing a knife,
so I don't know
if she was stabbed by a knife.
She says, "I was not a whore,"
but I think she was murdered.
Very disturbing.
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity
in your home,
go to the "Dead Files" page
at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help me, Dead Files!"
to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
So far I know Ron's bar
was home to a brothel,
and his property used to be
owned by a ruthless sheriff
who was behind several
vigilante murders.
But I need to see
if there's anything more.
Searching through old records,
I find a man
named William Crawford.
Turns out, he was found dead
right outside
the Pine Street Saloon.
I'm on my way
to meet with a local lieutenant
who says this case
was truly bizarre.
So what can you tell me
about William Crawford's case?
July 4, 1947,
he was dead on the doorstep,
on the back porch actually,
of -- of the hotel.
What were the circumstances?
Mr. Crawford was
a 60-year-old ranch hand
that was living
in an upstairs room,
and he'd been drinking
all night long.
So he was found
by some of the dishwashers
that were working at the hotel
the next morning.
They thought
he was passed out,
so they called the police
to come and investigate.
- Okay.
- So when they got there,
what they found was
that he was actually dead.
He died from an injury
to the back of his head.
All right, so what do we think
happened with this guy?
So we think he got
locked out of his room.
He was drunk the night before,
ended up on the back porch,
tried to climb up,
probably slipped off the ladder,
and injured himself.
They ultimately did the,
the coroner's investigation
that he had a,
fractured skull
on the back of his head,
and he died of
a brain hemorrhage.
Ew.
Like, some guy,
like, rolling around
on the floor crawls up to me.
He thinks he's still alive.
Can you see who this is?
Did this guy jump you?
Yes...
I can't even think straight,
Like...so messed up my head.
I feel like...
I feel very confused.
I feel like I'm drunk.
I have this weird...
very weird taste in my mouth.
My teeth hurt.
Somebody broke their teeth.
My head, my head.
My neck hurts.
My neck hurts..
I see, like, blood on my hands.
I feel like I'm yelling
or screaming inside,
and then there's blood
everywhere.
Seems like he wants help.
Is he making you move
like that?
He can make you move,
like a doll.
Do you know if this is something
he does to others?
Yes.
Is this something that could be
dangerous to the living?
Yeah.
Like, you could have, like,
a heart attack, I think.
All right,
I gotta get out of here.
Okay.
Getting out of here.
I'm going now. I'm leaving.
I saw several dead people
during my walk,
but the shadow woman
who can jump people
concerns me the most.
She's spread out
over the entire...ceiling,
but her face
is just a skull.
Her arms are coming down,
and they're coming
for my throat.
Amy, is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready
to reveal our findings
to each other and our clients
for the first time.
So, Amy,
I want you to meet Ron.
He's owned this place
for the last 5 years.
The activity is so bad here
that he's having a hard time
keeping employees,
Kim being one of 'em.
She quit a few months ago
because she thought she was
in danger.
Ron doesn't even know if it's
safe for anybody to be here,
but he's determined to keep
the doors open for one reason --
his mom.
She ran this place for 40 years,
and Ron is not gonna let
the paranormal ruin her legacy.
So now that Amy knows a little
bit about what's happening here,
I'm gonna have her
describe her walk for us.
There's three deceased
individuals here
that I'm most concerned
about.
The first individual
was a woman
that I met
when I was out back.
And the thing
that unsettled me about her
was that she looks so much
like a real shadow person.
It was extremely unnerving
for me.
And after she died,
she said to me
that she didn't wanna see
anymore,
so she actually
plucked her eyes out,
and then her face
became a skull.
I- I do feel like she could
be dangerous, um,
to the living here.
She goes after necks,
like, grabbing people
and poking at their throats.
She's very disturbed.
She carries a-a knife
with her.
I think she wants
to kill people with the knife.
I had a experience with one
of my employees in my back bar.
She was looking over this way,
and the knife was
on the other side,
and then it just went
off the shelf.
And so she turns around
and looks and looks at it
for about a minute
and just takes off running.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
Now Ron here is a skeptic...
...because he doesn't have
many experiences
except for the couple things
he's seen.
But you got so many complaints
from customers and employees,
you decided to put in cameras.
I gotta show you something
that's pretty compelling.
There's a backroom here
where they keep, um, stock.
There's Ron.
Wow.
I thought maybe
with the weight, you know,
top heavy
and all this other stuff,
but it wasn't.
My God.
So is this woman responsible
for all the stuff
that's moving around down here?
Yes.
So is it possible that
knife thing might've been her?
Yeah.
I would think if...Yeah.
I mean, she's all about
the knife, so...
Yeah.
I did have a sketch
done of her,
and it's from
the point of view of someone
seeing her hanging
from the ceiling.
What?
Hold on a second.
Wait till you see this.
- Wow.
Wow.
Eyes are creepy.
About 4, 5 years ago,
rooms 2 and 3 had
two people in each room.
I asked them how their stay was,
and they said,
"Yeah, everything was great,
except we saw this mannequin
hanging from the ceiling."
****.
- Can I flip this?
- You can flip that.
It just creeps me out.
Yeah.
Any clue about her in life?
I got that she died young.
I think she died
in the '20s or '30s.
I wasn't certain
if she killed herself
or if she was murdered.
But I saw her holding
a knife,
so I think she might've
been killed with one.
She kept saying
that she's not a whore,
nobody cared about her,
nobody helped her,
and that she's angry
and she wants revenge.
So she's got a knife.
She died young and she told you,
"I'm not a whore."
Yeah.
I mean, this could be
a long shot.
There was a guy named
Christian "Tommy" Thomas,
who was a bartender
that performed illegal abortions
right here in town
from the '30s to the '50s.
Actually got a photo of him.
He's pretty...
- God.
- Ew.
- That's creepy.
- Really?
Now I got a photo here
of his apartment
where he actually did
these abortions.
As you can see, it's the most
unsanitary-looking place
you can find.
- My.
Now, of course, abortions
were illegal back then,
and he, um, was
the only game in town.
On September 1, 1953,
a woman named Virginia Grider
came to Paso Robles
looking for Thomas.
This is her.
She was from the Bay Area,
and her husband drove her
down here to do it.
But the abortion was botched...
and she died.
- Wow.
- Thomas was arrested.
He plead guilty.
He had a sentence of 5 years to
life, and he did 5 years.
Sad.
Okay, so what else?
I ended up in the attic,
and I had a very negative
experience up there with a male.
I didn't even understand
what was happening,
but he just got me good.
He jumped me, which means
he literally went into my body.
And I think that
he's extremely good at --
at doing this,
which makes me nervous
because I think that he could
affect living people.
He can make you move,
like a doll.
I can't even think straight.
Like...so messed up my head.
Somebody could have
a heart attack.
Any idea who this guy
might've been that jumped you?
What I was able to get
was that he is stuck
in his death state,
which might indicate
that he died suddenly.
I had incredible neck pain,
and then my mouth,
my teeth,
in particular,
felt very strange.
I felt drunk, confused.
There was blood everywhere,
and I know
that he wants help.
He wants out.
Now listen, a lot of people
have come through this place,
so it could be anybody.
But when you talk
about somebody dying suddenly,
teeth smashed in, drunk,
one person comes to mind.
Um, on July 4th, 1947,
there was
a 60-year-old farm hand
by the name of William Crawford
that was staying upstairs.
He was drinking at the bar.
He was hammered.
According to witnesses, left,
tries to get into his room,
he's locked out.
And at that time, there was
a ladder that went upstairs.
They surmised that he fell
trying to get into his room.
He had a fractured skull,
teeth caved in,
the whole nine yards.
Now does this sound
like the guy who jumped you?
- Yeah. I know it was him.
- Okay.
All right, what else?
Okay, so...
on the second floor,
the residual energy up there
was so strong,
it was physically
making me sick.
Wow.
And I don't think that
living people would be able
to stay up there for very long
and feel comfortable.
I was seeing,
people, like, dancing,
singing, drinking,
doing drugs,
some people
being strung out.
Um, I saw a lot of,
sex happening.
Well, when I spoke with Ron,
he said that there might've
been a bordello
or a brothel upstairs.
So I checked it out,
and you were right.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- It was a bordello?
From the 1800s all the way
up into the 1920s and '30s.
Girls were working here
and exposed to drugs,
alcohol, and violence.
- Right.
- You know...
Wow.
So the thing about
the second floor
was that I encountered
a male.
And then I felt, like,
this deep sadness,
and I felt that he was
experiencing a lot of loss.
And this upset him greatly.
I was seeing something actually
about a horse accident,
and it killed the rider.
I absolutely think
that this individual is
completely insane.
I felt that he had
killed people,
and/or had individuals
do this for him.
The thing about
this place
is that he feels
a sense of ownership.
Like, anywhere
this person's ever been,
he feels like he owns
that space and time.
So the guy says he feels
ownership of the place,
killed people,
and had mental problems.
Yeah.
Okay, there is somebody
that it could be.
Now his name
was Daniel Blackburn.
I got a photo of him.
Um...this is him right here.
Wow.
His eyes are
kind of creepy.
Now Daniel was
a wealthy investor
who owned 26,000 acres
of land here,
including your property.
You said the guy either killed
people or had them killed.
So when he came into town,
he formed a vigilante group
of about 200 men,
and he basically got rid
of all the Mexicans
and all the Native Americans
that were here...
And displaced them.
More than likely,
he just killed a lot of them.
Wow.
And you said he was upset
about a loss.
Blackburn's wife was
in a horse and carriage
with their 1-year-old
when the baby was
tossed out from the horse,
getting spooked,
and the baby died.
Now you said
he was mentally unwell.
Check out this article.
It's pretty interesting.
After his death,
courts decided that Blackburn
was mentally incompetent
at the end of his life,
and, he wasn't of sound mind
to make a will.
Now you're the only one that
got a look at him.
What do you think?
I'm not sure
if it's him or not.
The only thing is --
is the eyes.
Like, the eyes,
'cause he had light eyes
and he had thick brows.
His energy
was extremely terrifying.
I got that he was
a telepath.
Telepaths are able to,
really
heavily influence people.
You can't escape from him.
You can't hide.
He can mess with your mind.
You feel like you need to run,
you need to get out of here.
He's gonna find you
and he's gonna get you.
You do feel a sense of panic
and anxiety upstairs,
from all of
this negative energy.
Everybody said
they had the feeling
of being watched up there.
- Yes. Yes.
There are some people
who will not return up there.
A year, year and a half ago,
I had a couple from out of town
that wanted to see
the architecture
of the building upstairs.
And when they came back,
the next thing
the woman said was,
"It grabbed my butt," and that's
all she could say was,
"It grabbed my butt."
And I actually have it on video.
Wow.
Let me show Amy
what we're talking about.
So the husband's
just, like, you know,
I'm going in first, take a look.
He's not paying attention
to her.
And all of a sudden, bam.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
My concern would be
being influenced
over a long period of time.
You could have
nervous breakdowns,
get physically attacked.
Eventually, people could
get killed here.
Is there any place safe
in this building?
No. No, not right now.
Living don't stand a chance
here.
There's something pretty much
in every nook and cranny.
Wow.
Wow is right.
I didn't realize
there was that much going on.
I mean, I...
I love this bar.
There's something special
about this place
and everybody here.
I put my heart and soul
in this place, and -- and...
the...
****
So, Ron,
I know you were adamant
about keeping the doors open
to honor your mom
and all the hard work
she put into this place,
but after hearing what Amy said
about what's going on here,
you're lucky
nobody's gotten hurt.
But I know you wanna fight this,
so I'm gonna turn it over to Amy
to see if there's any way
you can make this place safe.
Let me start with the male
up in the attic, Mr. Crawford.
He wants help.
He wants help,
so you need a medium
who is going to move
Mr. Crawford on.
The female...Okay,
so I wanna give her a chance.
I wanna give her
a fair shot.
So on another day,
you have a female medium come,
work some issues out,
and then move on.
If she doesn't go,
then I want you to contact
a demonologist.
And what the demonologist
will do
is basically do
an exorcism.
Wow.
Also, you need
a Reiki master.
This is
very, very important.
This person would come
two times per month
for 6 months...
- Whoa.
...to remove
all of the residual energy
that has collected upstairs.
And that's...
Yeah, that's a beast.
Okay, so let me
get this straight.
So if the Reiki master comes in
and is able to get rid
of all that residual stuff...
Yes.
...the creepy guy
will go along with it.
Yes.
It'll be very quiet here.
Yeah.
- Sorry.
No, it's okay.
You gotta be relieved.
Yes. Yes.
You gonna take Amy's advice?
- Yeah.
- Whatever it takes. Yes.
If they can
clear things up here,
would you come back to work?
- Yes.
I do it because I love it.
It's an honor to work here
and to serve
the people in here.
Ron has a lot of work to do
if he wants
to keep his employees and guests
out of harm's way,
but with the help of a medium
and a Reiki master,
the dead will move on,
and Ron will be able to keep
this restaurant in his family
for generations to come.