Everything was built on blood.
I seen a shadow run
towards the bathroom.
It's almost like a joint poltergeist.
They just keep beating each other.
They were chasing geese across the pond
and ended up drowning.
The attacks become more violent.
I'm hearing, like,
"Get out of the house."
The blood is still flowing.
Good energy stops right here.
I just hear death.
My name is Amy Allan.
God.
It's like, "I'm going to get you."
I see dead people. Her
face was all demonic.
I speak to dead people.
He's like, "You think you can stop me?
Because you can't."
And they speak to me.
- What is he trying to do?
- Kill them.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real...
Something happened. Bam, bam, bam.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve di Schiavi.
I'm retired New York
City homicide detective.
Am I seeing what I think I'm seeing?
And I know every person,
every house, has secrets.
They everywhere. It's
my job to reveal them.
This guy's got the
markings of a serial killer.
But Steve and I never speak.
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Is this Sted guy doing that to her?
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
That's it.
Or time to get out.
Somebody's gonna die over there soon.
Yeah.
I'm in the city of Magna, Utah
just west of Salt Lake City.
Now, I took this case for two reasons.
First, the woman who called us in.
She was crying on the phone
and sounded really scared.
Second, there are kids
involved, three of them.
And according to their mom
they are being physically
and psychologically attacked
by whatever's in that house.
Before Amy arrives
I throw the house
of any leading information.
Family photographs and
other personal items
can influence her findings
so it's important I
cover or remove them all.
When I'm finished the
location will be ready
for tonight's walk.
Good energy is not
making it into this home.
Good energy stops right here.
Unfortunately the people
who've moved into this place,
have not been very stable.
And because of all of
that they're pulling
in this negative energy.
The dead are attracted to this location
because of all the drama and craziness.
I feel really horrible,
sick, sick, sick.
So, Jennie,
when we spoke on the phone
you sounded really upset.
The reason I took this case is
because it involved children.
- Yes.
- Your kids are going through
- a rough time here?
- Yes, late nights with the kids.
They are not sleeping in their rooms,
they're staying up.
And once I really started seeing
my kids go through things...
- Right.
- That's when it's hard.
Especially for my youngest.
She is, like, so scared.
She tries running out of the house.
And so that's when you, like,
don't know what to do anymore.
It's not anything any kid
should have to go through.
No, especially when you can't
explain anything to them.
Like, when they ask,
you know, why or what.
And it's like you don't have
really anything for them.
All right.
So who exactly lives
in the house with you?
That's all of us.
All right. So who's here?
This is Lexie, she's 11.
And that's Summer, she's 7.
- Okay.
- And then that's me.
That's my son Zeke. He's 12.
- Okay.
- And then my husband.
- And he's 30.
And then, that's my mom.
So Jennie, has your mom
always lived with you?
No, we moved her in
because she was having
some surgeries done.
What kind of surgeries?
She's had to have some surgeries
to remove her brain tumor.
- Really?
- This one was cancer,
- like a stage two.
- Okay.
So she's had to go through radiation.
It kinda did a number on her this time.
She still gets really
bad headaches sometimes.
I don't like this.
Headaches.
Constant headaches, headaches,
headaches, headaches, headaches,
stress, stress.
Constant stress and headaches.
There's abuse.
I think it was some time ago.
This person... This is,
like, a safe haven to
get away from everything.
But there is no really
getting away from everything.
Being in here makes it worse.
How long have you guys been living here?
Since 2008.
It was a beautiful house, you know,
somewhere nice to raise the kids.
So, Jennie, do you know
any history on the property?
- Anything?
- Not a lot except for
that it's a mining town.
- A mining town?
- Yeah.
That's interesting to know. Okay.
Any idea what kind of...
what they're mining here?
It might be copper.
Okay. All right, Jennie.
So do me a favor and give
me a list of the things
you guys are experiencing.
Bangs, voices
and now things are moving.
And we see dark shadows.
And now it's gotten physical.
Okay. Physical with who?
My daughter Lexie.
She got scratched.
That's gotta be killing you.
She's so scared that
something's gonna hurt her.
That's the hardest part.
I don't get a lot of sleep.
We do a lot of camping
out in the living room.
Have you guys done
anything to be proactive?
Like, have you had the house blessed?
- Have you done anything?
- Um, we've tried
blessing it ourselves.
We went and burned sage
through the house...
- Okay.
- And, you know, salt.
Did it work?
No, it actually got a lot worse.
Somebody did something out here.
Some kind of protection thing.
But it's wrong.
It wasn't done right.
It pushed all the bad,
icky **** inside.
It created this, like, suction
thing that's sucking in,
crazy ****.
And it's keeping good stuff out.
So, Jennie, why'd you take
me into the master bedroom?
This is where, um, I have experiences.
One night, I got woken up to the sheets
being moved off of me and,
like, somebody just touching
me, like, rubbing my shoulder.
Now is there any way possible
that your husband coulda
been strokin' your arm?
Um, no, he was sleeping
facing towards the window.
Okay, physically he
couldn't have done it.
No.
Anything else?
- I will just be laying in bed...
- Okay.
And I will get woken up by a humming
- electric sound.
- Okay.
And then all of a sudden these shadows
will come from over there,
from my dresser, and,
like, they will slowly
start moving into me.
And they're darker shadows.
And you can hear them whispering.
And so I'm just frozen there with them
just standing over me.
You must freak out
when you see this thing.
I do. One time
I said, "Okay, just take me."
Like, I'm in full blown panic.
So, like, your heart's racing...
- Right.
- You're sweating,
but I can't move, I can't talk.
I see a woman.
She looks like late thirties.
And she is alive, crying.
And she feels very lonely.
She feels like she's been deserted.
A lot of despair.
I saw a younger male.
He's a mess. He's a mess.
He's done a lot of really bad things
in his life.
I think he's a addict.
He's done just terrible things.
And I don't know if he lives here
or if he lived here.
But I definitely got
that he left a lot of energy behind.
And there was something about guns.
Seems like Jennie is
having a rough time.
- Are you?
- Yes.
Tell me about the
experiences you've had.
I was walkin' into my room.
I seen clothes swinging
and a shadow run towards the bathroom.
At the same time?
- At the same time.
- And you're sure
it wasn't one of the kids
running through the bed room?
No, they were all in school.
Okay, anything else?
I walked into the laundry room
and there was somebody standing there.
I asked him, "Who are you?
What are you doing here?"
He just stood there, blank
stare at me and then gone.
He just vanished.
Okay, describe him to me.
Complete black.
Couldn't make out a face or anything.
How do you explain it?
- I can't figure it out.
- Okay.
That must've scared the hell outta you.
It scares the ****
out of me is what it does.
Somebody was in here.
A living person felt their
hairs stand up, turned,
saw a shadow figure move.
More than once they've
seen this, more than once.
The drug addict guy
is projecting himself
as the shadow figure.
This is a... not good place.
Let me ask you a
question. How old are you?
- I'm 12.
- Twelve.
So, Zeke, tell me about
what you're seeing.
A green guy.
He comes through the wall
and first you hear a big old bang
and then I wake up and I see him.
- And it's coming from that wall.
- Here?
- Yep.
- All right.
You're 12. All right.
Are you fooling around taking
any of mommy and daddy's pills
or anything like that?
- No.
- All right.
So you're not hallucinating
when you're seeing this stuff?
No.
Are you... are you hearing
or seeing anything else?
I'm seeing a guy with a hat.
Okay.
Comes up through my
ceiling in my closet.
Okay, can you see any
features on this thing?
- No, just the hat.
- All right. So, anything else?
Um, I've heard the chairs
moving and the table moving.
Where? In...
in the kitchen?
- Yeah.
- Okay, so when you heard it move
did you go out there and check it out?
- Yeah.
- And what'd you see?
Nothing, I looked just as normal.
The stuff you're seeing is
pretty wild for an adult to see.
Um, you realize this is not
normal for a 12 year old?
Yeah.
Everybody who's alive in the house, um,
is like beating on each other.
It's almost, like, a joint,
like, poltergeist from all these people.
They're, like, literally taking ****
Down on one another
via this poltergeist.
I know they're seeing things
but I can't quite see
what they're seeing.
I don't know what's going
on with the... the ceiling.
I'm feeling like a lot
of physical assaults here,
and this is from living
people to other living people.
It's just a **** mess.
So, Summer, tell me,
honey, how old are you?
- Seven.
- So, Summer, I understand
that you sleep out here most
of the time, is that right?
Okay, because you're
afraid of your room?
Okay, do you ever seen anything
when you're sleeping out here?
Yeah. I see people.
I... I think they
are trying to hurt me.
All right, where do you see them?
In my room, in the
kitchen and the bathroom.
Okay, what else are
you hearing or seeing?
I freak out.
My parents come upstairs
and they check on me
and I wake everybody up.
- Okay.
- And I was like,
"Call the cops."
You're scared of this place, honey?
Yeah.
Well, we're here to try
to get rid of everything.
Would you like to go sleep
in your own room again?
Okay.
I would think that the living here
are experiencing things
like, you know, feeling slapped,
headaches, panic attacks
for sure, anxiety,
punched, kicked,
possible sexual assaults...
Very weird. It's weird.
How old are you, honey?
- I'm 11.
- Okay.
So when I talked to mom, um,
she called us in basically
because the stuff you're going through.
Yeah.
- Is that upsetting you?
- Yeah.
So I understand you've been
having some experiences.
Yeah.
Okay, can you mind
telling me about them?
Um, I went upstairs.
And I heard my door close,
and then open and then close.
And it went on and on and on.
- Which door is this?
- It was that door.
Okay, did you see it open and closing?
Yes.
Yes, but could the window
have been open in the bedroom
that caused the door to open and shut?
My dad came in and checked it out
- and there was nothing in here.
- Nothing here.
Okay, have you seen
or heard anything else?
My dresser and my TV
they were both rocking.
The dresser started going up and down?
No, it started like...
Teetering back and forth?
Yeah.
The whole dresser itself?
Did you guys think you
were having a earthquake
or something?
No, because I didn't see
anything else shaking and...
So it was just these two things?
It was just those two things.
All right. So anything else, honey?
I got scratched right over here.
I was laying in my bed
and my arm was hanging out like that.
And then there was, like,
a little... like that.
So this is a silly question
but are you scared to be here?
I'm really scared to be here.
Okay.
I'm seeing, like, a teenage girl.
Everybody's being affected.
But it's almost like...
like she's really getting,
like, the brunt.
You know what I mean? Like,
she's, like, ground zero.
She has a lot of ability.
She might be,
the biggest source
and doesn't even know
it, doesn't even know it.
So what do you think would happen,
if this were to
continue going on
and nothing was done about it?
I think that the physical attacks
would become more violent,
to where there would be,
um, actual cutting
or scratching involved.
And, possible smothering
or strangulation to occur.
Other than a
family living in fear,
I don't have much to go off
of to do my investigation.
So I'm at the library to
see if I can dig anything up.
Searching through old records,
I find one of the original owners
of my clients property
lost two young kids.
Turns out they both
drowned in an accident.
I'm on my way to meet
with a local genealogist
who's looking into this tragedy for me.
She tells me the kids
who drowned that day
were direct descendants of
a very prominent local man.
So, Christine, before
we get to the drownings
you mentioned that the kids
were related to somebody famous.
Yes, the children's grandfather
was Edward Watkins Clark.
One of the first Mormon
settlers here in Utah.
Okay. When did this guy come here?
So, in 1852 he finally settled in Utah
with his first wife.
All right. So when Edward gets here
- what does he do?
- He was a farmer.
He was very prominent in the community.
Everyone knew him and his wife, Lucy.
He was actually elected
to justice of the
peace out in Santaquin.
Okay, you said his first wife.
Can I assume his first wife died?
No, actually the Mormon church
encouraged polygamy at this time.
And so he was encouraged
to take other wives.
And in 1857 he married his
second wife, Louisa Miller,
who was 20 years his junior.
She was only 17 when they got married.
Seventeen?
I have a picture of
her when she's older.
Now does he have kids with both of them?
- Yes, 18.
- Wow.
He had 10 with his first wife, Lucy,
and eight with his second wife, Louisa.
The second youngest is John Edward,
who is the father of
the children who died.
Okay.
I'm seeing this woman
and she's married to a much older male.
She was probably in her late 20s
and he was, like,
between 60 and 70 years of age.
He was prestigious.
He was a big time business man.
He kept fighting me because
he doesn't want me here.
He doesn't want anything
about him or his family out.
He wants to keep his
private life secret.
And then
there's a...
a... a younger female.
And I don't know if
it's his step-daughter
or if it's his biological daughter.
The girl doesn't look like
either one of them at all.
The daughter is like 16 or something.
Um, and he was having an
inappropriate relationship
with her
and also very abusive and controlling.
I guess you would wanna keep that quiet.
So I know Edward's son, John,
owned my clients' property at one point.
Do you know when that was?
1923 is when he bought
the property out in Magna.
Okay, so now how many kids did he have?
He had eight children in total.
He had three girls and five little boys.
Okay, so take me through
the day of the accident.
- What happened?
- İt was January 2, 1926.
It was a day a lot like
today where the sun is out
and all the snow is on the ground
and the pond probably looked
a lot like this, very frozen.
Three of the little boys, Floydd,
Morris and Lennis, all take
their friend Clarence out.
And they were chasing
geese across the pond
but it was too thin and
all the boys fell through.
Wow.
And Clarence was able to
help Floydd out of the water
but Morris and Lennis ended up drowning.
I have their death certificates.
So this is Morris Ruden,
and his death certificate even says,
"Accidental drowning." Okay.
And then Lennis Dean, same thing.
All right, so they lost
two kids to drowning.
Tragic. I mean, I can't
even imagine losing one
- let alone two.
- Yeah.
So what happened
with... with John?
I mean, did him and
his wife stick around
- after this happened?
- They did.
John actually did not
release the property
until 1953 is when he sold it actually
a few months before he died,
when his heart collapsed.
Okay.
I do see a different house,
that was here prior.
This house took up
several acres of property.
I'm hearing a woman
screaming and crying.
And it's over a death.
She's outside.
It might be in the
backyard or something.
This person couldn't get over it.
can't...
can't get over it.
She's like, "Why?
Why?"
Very dramatic.
Like, her hands are up, like, "Why?
Why? Why? No, no, no."
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity in your home
go to the Dead Files
page at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help me, Dead
Files" to submit your story.
And we'll help if we can.
Jennie told me she thought there used
to be a lot of copper
mining in the area.
So I made some calls and
it turns out she's right.
I'm meeting a historian who
says mining killed two men
who live on my clients' land.
So, Robert, what can you tell
me about the mining industry
in Magna?
Well Magna actually started
out as a farming community.
- Okay.
- But it wasn't until 1906
that the Utah Copper
Company brought in the...
the biggest, refining
and smelting, operation
in world history at the time.
Millions of tons of ore was
being processed every year.
So it's basically all copper?
Mostly copper, that's
what they're renowned for.
You can talk about a real
dangerous work environment.
It was very dangerous,
very toxic environment.
- Okay.
- A lot of sulfuric emissions,
heavy metal particulates
and even asbestos.
So the odds are stacked against you.
So you had mentioned on
the phone, two guys
that lived on my clients' property,
died in connection with the mining.
Tell me about the first guy.
First guys name is Wallace Anderson.
- Okay.
- He bought your clients' property
in 1936.
So what happened to him?
Well, by 1944 it catches up to him.
He's in your clients' house.
He's feeling pain in his lungs.
He's having trouble breathing.
He checks himself into the hospital.
He's there for 12 days.
And he dies.
Okay, so what's the
official cause of death?
It's bronchogenic carcinoma.
It's lung cancer.
Pretty common way to go
for mine workers back then.
It was.
Now, Robert, you mentioned
there was a second guy
that died on my clients' property.
Right. Who, who was that?
His name was Paul William Confer.
He was actually renting the property
from Wallace's widow.
Okay, so what happened?
In 1948, he goes down
inside the mine in a blasting team
- with another fella...
- Okay.
And they never came out
with the other groups.
And so they sent a
search party down there
and discovered that they'd been killed.
They were killed in an explosion.
And here's his death certificate.
Subtotal decapitation,
amputation both arms,
puncture wounds both legs.
Did they ever figure out
what caused the explosion?
- Either a faulty fuse...
- Okay.
Or it was negligence on
the part of the miners.
Geez. Are the mines still going on?
Yeah. The mine is still running today.
So I'm assuming it's a
cleaner operation today?
It is. In 1994 the EPA
stepped in and declared Magna
an environmental disaster zone.
After 100 years of industry,
the water was contaminated.
The soil was contaminated.
What kinds of effects
could that have on somebody?
Today still the lung cancer rate
is 50 percent greater
than the rest of the state.
And not only cancer but high rates
of ADD, autism, delirium
and even hallucinations.
Really? That's interesting.
There's a lot of residual energy here.
I saw on the land
that everything was built on blood.
And I see the blood is still flowing.
And they said it was built
and blood and dirty dealings
and that both of those things
are still happening today.
And that's why the
blood is still flowing.
This is a not good place.
Look, if contaminated water
can cause hallucinations
it could explain some of
the really strange things
Jennie and her family are seeing.
I'm heading back to the
house to meet an inspector
who's going to give the water
a thorough, scientific test.
- Hey, Jonathan.
- How's it goin'?
Thanks for coming by. I appreciate it.
Yeah. You bet.
The reason I called
you out is my clients
that live in this
house, they're telling me
that they're seeing
some really off the wall,
bizarre stuff.
Now I know this place
in '94 was considered
- a EPA disaster area.
- That's correct.
I mean, all along the Wasatch Front
we see a number of locations
that have had some kind of
environmental hazards,
primarily due to the proximity
of local mines in the area.
Now, could you test to see
if there's any kind of
environmental problem
that could cause these
people to have hallucinations?
Yeah. Absolutely.
Okay, good. Let me know what you find.
Will do.
I've clients seeing
things moving on their own
and green men coming out of the walls
which means there are
three possibilities.
One, they're lying to me.
But I don't think that's the case.
Two, their soil
or water is contaminated
causing them to hallucinate.
Or three, there's something
going on that only Amy
can understand.
So, how'd it go?
Well we tested the soil,
the water as well as
the paint on the walls
and we didn't find any contaminants.
Really?
So there's no environmental reason
why clients are seeing what
the hell they're seeing?
- No.
- Okay.
So now I know what it's not.
I saw a lot of disturbing activity
during my walk.
But the drug addict who projects himself
as the shadow figure really stood out.
He was young,
I would say between 18 and 24.
He had a very narrow, nose.
He also had very dark eyes, kinda black.
Is this who you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our findings
to each other and our clients
for the first time.
So, Amy, I want you to
meet Randall and Jennie.
They're experiencing some pretty
bizarre stuff in their house.
But the reason they called us
in is because of their kids.
We got a photo of the family here.
Now, this is Lexie, she's 11.
This is Summer, she's
an adorable 7-year-old.
This is their Zeke, who's 12.
And this is, Jennie's mom, Debbie,
who lives with them.
These guys think that
whatever's in the house
is going after the kids.
And they promised me they'll do
whatever it takes to keep them safe.
So now that Amy knows a
little bit about your family,
I'm going to, ask
her to describe her walk.
Walking up to your
home, to the front door,
I saw a male,
doing some kind of ritual
or protection.
Who ever this was,
and whatever he did, was not good.
It created a type of negative suction
into your house.
And unfortunately all good energy
stops right at your front door.
That's weird because I
don't know about a male,
but you mentioned to me
that you guys did something.
Yeah. Me and my
mother-in-law,
we tried to cleanse the house
with, like, sage and salt.
Now she's talking about negativity.
Have you guys felt that in the house?
Sometimes when you just
come home it just...
just doesn't feel right.
It doesn't feel like home.
Wow.
So what else did you see?
I encountered an elderly deceased male.
What he was saying to me
was that when he was alive
he was very prestigious.
He was a big player.
He absolutely did not want me there.
What I did get was that
there were two women,
of importance in his life.
One was his wife.
The wife was much younger than him.
She was in her twenties.
And then one was a younger girl.
And I didn't know if that was
his daughter or step-daughter.
And the girl was about 16.
And what I did get
was that there was an
inappropriate relationship
between him and the younger girl.
And I felt like that's what
he was trying to conceal.
He's very grouchy, very controlling.
And when he is inside of the home
the men of the house may take
on these kinds of attitudes.
Well, Jennie, have you noticed
that with Randall or Zeke?
Yeah. Big time.
I came across somebody in my research
that might fit the bill.
His name was Edward Watkins Clark.
You had mentioned he was prestigious.
He was a famous pioneer
for the Mormon church.
He came over from England in 1852.
He brought his wife
Lucy over with his kids.
Now you mentioned a teenage girl
that might be his daughter
or a step-daughter.
Well back in those days
they preached polygamy.
He was 37.
And he married his girl, Louisa,
who was, 17 at the time.
Now I got a photo of her
but this is from when
she was much older.
Now together with his
two wives he had 18 kids.
The 17th child,
named John, ended up
living on your property.
The next thing that
I saw is a younger male.
And I honestly couldn't
tell if he was alive or dead.
If he is deceased it
was extremely recent.
He was in the downstairs,
large, downstairs bedroom.
He was very agitated.
He felt like everybody
was out to get him.
He felt like he was falling apart.
The living, who would
be down there a lot,
would feel this sense
of despair or depression.
And I think if you were to see him
it would be a shadow-like figure.
Now, Jennie, you had your own
experiences with shadow figures?
- Yeah.
- Tell her what you told me.
And I'll just be right
there, by my dresser,
and then he'll come towards me.
But then I'm stuck in my
bed. And I'm just frozen.
I'm sweating, breathing
hard, just can't do anything.
Randall, didn't you see
another one leering at you
at one point?
I asked him, "Who are
you? What do you want?"
It just looked at me...
Then gone, just vanished.
Did you get anything
about this guy in life?
What I got on him
was that he was, I think,
in his twenties.
He claimed to have done
a lot of terrible things
during his lifetime.
I just see him with a
rifle and a small handgun.
And I did get that he was an addict
and/or fighting addiction.
I got a sense that he did live here.
And like I said, if he still alive,
he essentially left part of himself.
Did you get a good look at him?
- I had a sketch done.
- Okay.
Maybe you guys can
tell me if they...
he looks like anybody
that you might know.
- My brother.
- Yeah.
My brother's sittin' in jail right now.
What?
Any issues with guns and
stuff that she's talking about?
Yeah. He...
he loves guns.
This is pretty wild.
So let me get this straight,
it's possible for somebody
who's not dead to haunt the house?
Sometimes people
will really leave a, like,
really a part of themselves there.
This has gotta be tough
for you to hear though?
Yeah. Very.
So what else?
I went into the pink room.
And I got a horrible headache.
It was overwhelming.
And I felt like a woman
stays there, goes there,
feels like the room is a safe haven
to get away from everything.
But it's not.
And she keeps feeling
pain from life loss.
I got loss, abuse and death.
When she's in there, it just
feels like it's all
happening again and again.
Well that's the room where Jennie's mom,
Debbie, sleeps.
Um, my mom has had a
couple brain surgeries.
Wow.
And the last one was a stage two cancer.
So she does get headaches a lot.
So what she's saying kinda makes sense?
Yeah.
She's been through a lot.
Now'd you see anything else?
So the thing I'm most concerned about
is the poltergeist
activity in the house.
A poltergeist is usually created
by one living agent who has abilities.
But in your case it's unusual
because you have several people
in your home with abilities.
And they're all feeding this poltergeist
without even knowing it.
And what can happen
is that when you get
upset with somebody,
the poltergeist will affect that person.
So, suddenly, that person will feel
like they're being smacked,
pinched, punched,
kicked, scratches will appear,
things like that happen.
Also, you'll see strange things.
It's a result of this
poltergeist manifestation
from somebody in the house.
Now, she hit on a lot of things
you guys are experiencing.
Lexie with the scratch.
Tell Amy what happened.
We were all getting
ready to leave, you know,
and she's walking down the hall
and all of a sudden
she's just scratched.
Tell her about, pretty
wild, there's the door.
Lexie was going into
the kitchen to get food.
And she was almost to the kitchen
but her bedroom door was sitting
there opening and closing,
like, fully opening and closing.
You were saying people
might see strange things?
Now get this, their son Zeke
was telling me some crazy stuff.
I mean, green men
coming outta the walls...
Yeah.
Could all this activity
be from the poltergeist?
Yes, absolutely.
All right. Now, there's
something you gotta know
about the area that they live in.
It's basically built on
a copper mining business.
1994 the EPA came in
and declared the area an
environmental disaster zone.
- What?
- Now some of the toxins
in the water can cause hallucinations.
So I had everything
checked in your house.
I had the soil, the water and paint.
Everything came back negative.
Yeah. I think the kids
are creating the strange visions
to scare each other.
They're torturing each other.
Do they know they're
doing that to each other?
No, I don't think they do.
But it's subconsciously
they're doing it?
Yes,
The strongest agent in the house,
of this ability
is Lexie.
Wow.
I... I don't know... I
don't know what to say.
I knew she was going through a lot
but I didn't know it was like that.
If this goes unchecked what happens?
It'll get more and more active,
especially when she starts
to go through puberty.
That's when, like, things
can really get crazy.
I never in a million years
would have thought
that that would be it.
How violent could it get?
There was one case
I did where a woman
had over 300 stitches.
Couches I've seen go
flying across rooms,
people being dragged,
through the house by their hair.
So this could happen here, potentially?
Yes, potentially. Yeah.
It can get pretty intense.
So you guys called us in
because you knew you had a problem.
But I'm sure you never
imagined in a million years
that you guys were haunting each other.
To find out how to fix it and stop it,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
What I would like to see
happen is for a psychic
to come in to do the initial cleansing.
And that person is going
to teach you how to do it.
This is one of things
that you and your children
are going to need to do
for the rest of your lives.
Over time, it'll remove
residual energy and impressions.
So it'll be a lot quieter,
a lot more peaceful.
Everybody will feel very chill.
I'm curious about one thing,
the protection that went wrong.
Will these cleansings help reverse that?
Yes, doing the monthly cleansings
will take care of a lot
of the bigger issues.
The second thing I would
like to see happen would be
for the psychic to remove
the deceased people.
That would be the older gentleman,
his main wife
and the second wife,
who is the teenager.
The third thing,
this is again something
that the family will need to do together
and need to keep it up.
One is hatha yoga, and then tai chi.
So that'll decrease the
poltergeist activity?
Yes, immensely.
Saw that look on your face
when you started talking
about yoga and tai chi.
I... I... I
enjoy everything.
Don't matter to me. Let's have fun.
- Okay.
- The other thing
that I would like to see happen
is for Lexie
to maybe see a child psychotherapist
for her to learn
how to open up a little bit more,
how to communicate
about her emotions a little bit more,
which will help her learn
to kind of ground out
and control her energy.
I think that would be
really good for her.
So, Jennie, this is gonna
be a life long thing.
You up for that?
I mean, it'll probably
get us closer and hopefully
get her to open up.
Is this something you guys
are definitely gonna wanna...
Look into and do? Yes.
- Yes.
- Definitely.
I have an answer and
you're turning a negative
- into a positive...
- Right.
For the family, for the house,
for everybody.
Jennie and Randall
have a lot of work
to do if they want to
rid their home of the dead
and the poltergeist
that they're feeding.
But with the help of a
psychic and a therapist,
they can work as a family
to free themselves of the evil
that's been tearing them apart.