This is where the dead roam.
Really not good for kids here,
not good at all.
We want to protect 'em.
It makes me feel terrible.
Somebody's being
stabbed in the stomach.
Are you having any kind
of health issues?
The stabbing pains
in my back.
The shadow people are
**** killing people here.
This house is not a home.
I just hear death.
My name is Amy Allan.
God.
It's like,
"I'm going to get you."
I see dead people.
Her face was all demonic.
I speak to dead people...
He's like, "You think you can
stop me? Because you can't."
...and they speak to me.
- What is he trying to do?
- Kill them.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
Something happened.
Bam. Bam. Bam.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve DiShiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
Am I seeing
what I think I'm seeing?
I know every person,
every house has secrets.
- They're everywhere.
- It's my job to reveal them.
This guy's got the markings
of a serial killer.
But Steve and I
never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation...
...until the very end...
Is this dead guy
doing that to her?
When we uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
That's it.
...or time to get out.
Somebody's gonna die
over there soon. Yeah.
I'm in
Spartanburg, South Carolina.
It's about 80 miles west
of Charlotte.
So I got a call
from a woman named Donna,
who's a mother of three.
Now she lives in a big,
beautiful, suburban house.
Trouble is, she says the whole
family's being terrorized.
But her special needs daughter
is getting the worst of it.
She sounded really bad
on the phone
and says if we can't help her,
someone's gonna get
seriously hurt.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area
of any leading information,
removing religious symbols,
artwork,
and other personal items
that could influence
her findings.
When I'm done,
the location will be ready
for tonight's walk.
I'm having feelings
of very deep sadness
and uncontrollable shaking
and fear.
So much, pain and crying.
Terrible, terrible.
And I hear this house
is not a home.
So, Donna, when we spoke
on the phone,
you were obviously upset.
What's goin' on?
- We moved here,
and it's -- it's been
not what I dreamed about.
We, all five of us,
sleep here in the living room.
You're tellin' me the entire
family's sleepin' in this room?
Right, 'cause no one wants
to sleep upstairs.
We all feel better together.
Give me an idea of what you guys
are goin' through.
Well, we hear, um, footsteps.
Um, we hear
unexplainable noises.
Um, we see shadows everywhere,
apparitions, everything.
Everything that you can
think of,
it seems like we have seen
in every room.
People are being scratched
and just feeling
like they're being touched.
How are you living
like this?
It's very exhausting.
And when we moved here,
I was perfectly healthy.
And -- and now I'm just sick
all the time,
kidney stones,
cervical cancer.
It's gall bladder,
migraines, depression.
It's one thing after another.
I'm just ready for it to
be over any way it has to be.
Whatever, it has to be done.
Okay.
I feel sick in here.
I feel nauseous,
awful, terrible.
I would think the living
would **** feel sick here.
There'd be a lot of nausea,
anxiety, and anger.
I see an angry man.
He hurt people.
He's scary.
The living, they hear the guy.
They hear walking,
up and down the stairs,
all over the place.
And I do feel like,
when they're sleeping,
I feel like,
he does inappropriate things
to the women,
um, very inappropriate.
Um, very, very inappropriate.
I think he's the one
making people sick.
I don't want to go upstairs.
All right, so, Donna,
who exactly lives in the house
with you?
Well, this is my family.
- Okay. Who's here?
- This is Tyler. He's 21.
- Okay.
- Austin's 15.
Abbie is 11.
And that's me and my husband.
Now you mentioned on the phone
Abbie has a condition.
Right. She was diagnosed
with selective mutism.
And it's basically, um,
an anxiety disorder.
When she's asked anything
that actually bothers her,
if it's any tension,
um, she -- she shuts down
and she's not able to talk.
Do you think it's caused
by what's goin' on in the house?
Or do you think it's something
she was born with?
It seems to me
that it may be the cause.
And I think
there's things like,
she doesn't want to ever
go in the bathroom.
And I think
there is something more
that she's not able
to tell me about.
She'll stay in the bed,
she'll cover her head up,
and she just will not talk
for a day.
There's nothing to console her.
You can't do anything.
And it just broke my heart.
That's very concerning
for me
because she may
be experiencing
a hell of a lot more
than you know.
Sometimes I worry that it takes
advantage of the fact
that she can't tell me
everything.
That's why we're just
praying that --
that y'all can help us.
Don't like it in here.
I don't like this space at all.
There's so much here.
My god.
I'm -- I'm like, completely
overwhelmed right now.
There's a teenager here
who's having problems,
long hair, delicate, delicate.
So I think it's a demon.
And this demon is really messing
with the girl,
acting like a woman,
crawling into the bed
and...
touching feeling, cuddling.
It's evil.
It's so **** evil, though.
It's so **** evil.
All right, Donna,
why'd you bring me upstairs?
What's the story?
I was,
sleeping one night, woke up,
and I couldn't breathe,
like I was being choked.
And I couldn't move.
And Abbie woke up and she kept
sayin', "Mom, mom, mom!"
And it kinda upsets me
'cause she was so scared.
And, um, she said my lips
were turnin' blue
and my face was swelling.
- You sure it wasn't a dream?
- Yes.
Do you think whatever's here
wants you here?
No, especially not up here.
This is their place.
And now whatever's here
forced you guys
into not sleeping up here?
Yeah.
Okay. Anything else?
Yeah. I see an apparition
of a-a man.
It's all black.
Um, he's --
he's very tall.
The only thing I do see
that's not black is his --
is a pale --
pale, yellow eyes.
And he has a long, um,
hairy, Grinch-like fingers.
The way you describe,
it's something out of,
like, a horror movie.
It's kinda like his --
like an owl.
I know it sounds crazy.
Any medications
you're taking for the --
the symptoms you're havin'?
- Mnh-mnh. No.
Okay. The only reason I ask
is because I don't know
if you're hallucinatin'
what you're seein' or...
Right.
I would think that, too.
- 'Cause it's pretty bizarre.
- It is.
All right.
The demon went through the wall.
And then it, like, morphed into,
like, a creepy face.
Like, grotesque.
Not only can this demon
project itself
to look like anything it wants,
it's also able to affect
the living in horrible ways.
I can't breathe.
I feel, like, choking.
I think the demon's
making people kill each other
or kill themselves.
This place is ****.
Is anything else goin' on?
Well, I hear, um, um,
a female voice
calling my name.
'Cause this always
usually happens
when I'm at home by myself.
And it --
it scares me to death.
Are there any females
other than you in the house,
other than Abbie?
Mnh-mnh. No.
TV on, anything like that?
No, I had all the TVs
turned off.
Well, you got
your hands full.
They definitely
don't like us here.
They don't want us here.
I think
they just want us gone.
There's a woman there,
and she's just staring at me.
She scares me.
She scares me
because she's so not okay.
She's crawling on the floor.
She's crying.
She's screaming. She's yelling.
She's in pain. She was hurt.
I don't know what's
goin' on here.
My god. I'm so scared.
The dead have been
**** here.
You know, it's not good.
They can't move on.
It's really bad.
I think the dead here
really do think they're in hell.
It's so not good.
So, Andy,
this is your master bedroom?
- Correct.
- Okay.
Well, this is the first house in
over 100 cases I've ever been in
where the bedroom set wasn't
even set up.
So what you're tellin' me is
that stuff was so bad up here
that you guys
didn't even go as far
as even putting the bed
together?
That's right.
Now where -- where do you
specifically sleep?
Downstairs, in the recliner.
So, Andy, I was talkin'
to your wife,
and she was tellin' me about
everything she's going through,
plus the kids.
It makes me feel terrible.
You want to protect 'em.
You -- you want to be there.
But, um, it just seemed like
ever since we've been
in this house, it's just been
one issue after another.
The kids don't like
to come upstairs.
Now, Andy, have you had
any of the experiences
that your wife
and the kids have had?
Well, there's a few things
that's happened.
I've heard noises,
like, maybe something
falling off of a counter.
Then I go and check on it,
and, you know, don't --
don't see anything.
So I just kinda discount it.
Anything else happen?
Severe room temperature
changes.
The hallway will be
one temperature.
You come into this room,
it's like a meat locker.
What time of the year
were you feeling this?
Well, it was during
the summer.
Did you shut off the vents
or anything in this room?
No, they hadn't been.
That's strange.
Anything else?
Since we started remodelin',
I started, you know,
havin' trouble breathin'
and my back started hurtin'
really bad.
And then I had kind of
a tightness of the chest.
Now have you felt that
any place else in the house?
No, I haven't.
- What about at work?
- No.
It hasn't happened
to you since?
- No, hasn't.
- That's kinda strange.
I believe something
attacked me.
You're kinda ****
anywhere in this house.
This is just
where it's most active.
I think that area's
like a portal.
- What does that mean?
- It's a doorway.
It's for dead people,
connects outside.
Other houses are affected.
Something's happening
in my stomach.
So, Tyler,
I was talkin' to Mom.
She said you basically
grew up here, correct?
Right. Yes, sir.
- How old are you now?
-21.
Now what about yourself
as far as experiences go?
Feeling, you know,
drained all the time.
Sleeping for 12 hours
and feeling like I've only
gotten two. So...
Your father mentioned
chest pains and back pains
and stuff like that.
Are you having any kind
of health issues?
The stabbing pains in my back.
I'll -- I'll be in the bed
and I won't be able to,
for about 5 minutes,
be able to get up.
It just hurts.
One second I'm fine,
and then the next,
extreme pain.
I did over six tests,
and they said they had no idea
what would be causin' the pain.
What do you think
is goin' on here?
You think it's paranormal
that's causing your issues?
Without a doubt. I've seen
too many things not to.
All right. Anything else?
The one night I was laying
on Abbie's bed,
I saw a black shadow figure
block out the TV.
It was like a real tall,
stocky man, had yellow eyes.
And then how long does
he hang out?
Three, for seconds, looks at me,
and then disappears.
To this day, it haunts me.
All right. So that's in Abbie's
room where you saw this.
I mean, you gotta be scared
that she may be seeing
the same damn thing.
And you know,
it -- it upsets me
because for something
to go after her...
you know, any --
any time I would say,
"Come after me.
You know, don't go after her."
I'd take her place any day.
If you had a choice of living
here or not, what would you do?
I'd go as far away
from this place as I could.
I don't like it here.
This is a bad room.
This is a very, very bad room.
I'm seein', um...
They're in the walls.
And they're hidin'
in the **** walls.
And they are...bad.
People see these.
- Like, how many?
There was probably, like, five.
They are slitherin' around
on the walls.
They're physical.
Um --
Mother ****, mother.
So the property records
on this place
go all the way back
to the mid-1700s.
In fact, the first family
who settled on
Donna and Andy's property
got the land grant
from King George III of England.
Amazingly, I managed
to track down a descendant
who still lives in the area,
and he says he's got a story
that will definitely
help my case.
So, Caroll, I understand
that you are the descendant
of the original owners
of my clients' property.
Yes. I'm the --
the fourth great grandson
of John Caldwell,
who's buried here.
This -- this is
his original marker.
So from what I understand,
you told me
he was granted the land
from the king?
Yes. He was granted
250 acres in 1772.
So my clients' house
is on the original property.
That's correct, yes.
Now you had mentioned to me
that there was
a pretty interesting story
in regards to your family.
Yeah, John Caldwell,
he eventually ended up
fighting on the side
of the American Revolution.
There was a person
in this area
who was on the side
of the British.
And he was called
"Bloody Bill" Cunningham.
He was a terror
in this part of the country.
He killed many people,
in this area
who were loyal
to the colonists.
In November 1780,
Bloody Bill Cunningham
captured
John Caldwell's younger son,
who was 14 at the time,
hacked him with swords,
scalped him, and left him lyin'
on the side of the road.
That's a brutal way to go.
He lingered till morning and --
and passed the next morning.
And he is the first person
buried here in this cemetery.
I'm seein' an older man.
He's taking a boy, I think.
He's pushin' his face
to the floor,
kickin' him.
"This isn't how you act!"
Kickin' him.
This is residual.
The teenage boy's
in trouble.
He's, like,
maybe 15, 16 years old.
So much anger
between these two people,
between the kid
and the -- the adult,
so much **** anger.
I know that
that man was influenced.
What's doing that?
The demon.
Something's wrong.
Feel like somebody's
being stabbed in the stomach.
I feel like a young male
is being stabbed in the stomach.
I gotta know more
about this Bloody Bill guy.
I'm on my way
to meet a genealogist
who says not only
did he terrorize the city,
but he ended up
killing someone else
who lived
on my client's property.
So, Suzanne, this guy,
Bloody Bill Cunningham,
I understand he was
a bit of a psycho
that killed a lot of people.
- That's true.
- What do you know about him?
He was born
in South Carolina,
and he grew up in a family
that was loyal
to the British crown.
And this is a portrait
of Bloody Bill.
Looks pretty regal
in this photo, doesn't he?
So how's this guy
turn into a bloody killer?
At the age of 19,
he decides
to go against his parents'
loyalty to the crown
and join with
the American colonists to fight,
with the one proviso
that he not be required
to kill or go after
his family.
Okay.
Well, a few months after going
with the American colonists,
he's asked to do
just exactly that.
He's asked to go after
his family.
Okay. So what does he do?
He refuses. He resigns.
And his commanding officer
and some others
went looking for him 'cause they
weren't happy with the decision.
And they found his parents
and his younger brother.
They roughed up his parents
and whipped his brother
to death.
Wow. Okay.
So now I can see where this
guy's anger's startin' to build.
Yes. He gets together
a group of men,
and he starts out
on a rampage to get even.
They traveled through
the countryside burning homes,
killing people, looting.
- So how bad was it?
- He killed at least 50 people,
including
John Caldwell Junior,
who lived on
your clients' property.
I just left his grave site.
All right, so at some point,
this Bloody Bill gets stopped?
In 1782, he was banished
from South Carolina
and fled to Nassau
in the Bahamas.
- What happens to him there?
- He died there,
about the age of 31,
in 1787.
Any cause of death?
Do we have any idea?
Some suggest
that he died of T.B.
- Good. He deserved it.
- Yes.
Do you have any idea
how long these shadow people
have been here?
I would just say forever.
And this demon thing?
Forever.
Do you have an idea
what they want?
The shadow people are
**** killing people here.
And I think the demon's
**** makin' people kill
each other or kill themselves,
****, you know?
This is bad land.
It's bad.
It's not good.
This, activity
does go, pretty far back.
It goes this way
and it goes this way.
And other houses
are being affected.
This is where the dead roam.
Everybody's wanderin' around.
Everybody's wandering.
It's like chaos.
It's not good.
Dead people feel
like they're in hell.
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity
in your home,
go to the "The Dead Files" page
at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help me, Dead Files!"
to submit your story,
And we'll help if we can.
So far, I've got clients
being physically assaulted
on a property
where Bloody Bill murdered
one of his 50 victims,
the child of a former owner.
But I wanna see
if there's anything else.
Searching through old records,
I find two mysterious drownings.
Turns out,
they happened in a quarry
right on my clients'
original property line.
I'm heading over to meet
the sheriff of Spartanburg,
who's gonna tell me
exactly what happened.
So, Sheriff, I came across
those two drownings
in my research
that happened in the quarry,
a little over a mile from
my, clients' property.
So what can you tell me
about the first victim?
Mr. Henry Oglesby
was a 14-year-old male
in good shape.
He ran track.
He was healthy and athletic.
This is a photo here
of Henry Oglesby
at -- at the age of 14.
He was at the rock quarry
and decided to go swimmin'.
This was
a very popular hang out.
He jumped in the water.
And I don't know
what height he jumped from.
He never resurfaced.
I can't imagine the heartbreak
his parents felt
losing
a 14-year-old like that.
All right, so what do we know
about the other drowning?
Yeah, August the 6th of '89,
almost 2 years.
A David Wayne Ellison,
25 years old.
Same -- same deal, ha--
hanging out with his buddies.
Two guys jumped in,
one came out.
And we find him
in about 17 feet of water.
So now you got
two pretty able-bodied,
strong guys drowning?
Right.
Okay.
I'm hearing, like,
"Don't go in the pool."
And I saw a shadow person
go in the **** pool.
"Ya think it's safe over here,
but it's not."
What do you think would happen
if people go in the pool?
I think that,
they might drown.
I think that the shadow person
that hangs out
in the **** pool
would try to drown people.
- Like how?
- It'd pull their feet.
Not safe, not safe,
especially kids,
really dangerous here
for children.
Really not good for kids here,
not good at all.
I come across another case
that you might find interesting
near your clients property.
There was a murder
that took place there
on October the 31st, 1990.
- At the quarry?
- Yes, sir.
Okay,
so what exactly happened?
It's a gentleman by the name
of Ramone Hernandez.
Mr. Hernandez is
24 years old.
This next slide is, photos
of the two convicted killers.
This gentleman here
on the left is --
his name is
Charles Steven Sink.
And his girlfriend,
Ellen Holcolm,
who have both been convicted
of murdering Mr. Hernandez.
Okay. He's got a smirk
on his face.
All right, so how did
the murder go down?
Hernandez, gentleman who was
suffering from a brain tumor
and had a very small amount
of time to live,
he had a settlement, a large sum
of money in his pocket.
And, these two took him out
under the disguise
that they were gonna go party
and have some fun.
This Sink guy had
a- a cocaine problem.
You know, he's needin' money.
And he hits Hernandez
in the back of the head...
- Right.
- With -- with the back of an ax.
So not to really cut him up.
And they tried
to cover their actions
by throwing him into
the quarry
and make it look like
a drowning.
He and her both had planned this
to make it look like
an accident.
All right, so how much money
did these two get?
We know $700
that they took off this man.
All right, so this homicide
happened over 25 years ago.
Are these guys still in?
- Sink got out in 2013.
- Okay.
And, she got -- she got in
or around the same time,
but has, reviolated
and gone back.
Wow, so I got a murder
that pretty much took place
and the body dumped
in that same quarry
where these two kids drowned.
- That's right.
There's a man.
I get he's young,
probably late teens.
I feel like someone
is after him.
He's getting beat up.
He's being beaten.
I see two people around him,
one is a tall, chubby man.
I get the name Steve.
This dude
who's hurting this kid
is in his 30s or 40s.
So this is recent, 1990s.
It's dark. It's dark where
they are, no lights.
He is crying and praying
and begging for his life.
And I hear him yelling,
"Not here! Not like this!"
I saw several disturbing things
on my walk,
but the demon projecting
itself is an old woman
to a living child
had me the most concerned.
This negative,
evil thing is coming up.
And it's wrapping itself
around her,
acting like it's good,
but it's really evil.
Next, I described how the demon
showed itself to me.
It was very disfigured.
And it was reaching out.
And it had these long,
dagger-like teeth.
Is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready
to reveal our findings
to each other and our clients
for the first time.
So, Amy, this may look
like a living room,
but we're actually doing
the reveal right in the middle
where everyone
in this house sleeps.
It's that bad.
This is Andy, his wife, Donna,
her son, Tyler.
Also...
they have a son, Austin,
who's 15,
and their daughter, Abbie,
who's 11.
Now Abbie's the reason
we've been called in.
Donna believes whatever's here
is picking on her
and she's afraid Abbie
could be in danger.
Now that Amy knows a little bit
about who you guys are
and the rest of the family,
I'm gonna ask her to describe
her walk for us.
One of the first things that
came through very, very clearly
was a disturbing residual scene
I saw involving a young male.
I got that he was
in his late teens.
He was extremely frightened.
He felt like he was
going to die.
Somebody was after him.
It was dark out
at this time.
He was crying and praying
and begging for his life.
He was saying, you know,
"Not here! Not like this!"
He was being beaten,
by two individuals.
And the one that I really,
got a look at was tall.
He was chubby.
I did get the name "Steve"
with him.
And I got that this was
a fairly recent attack,
possibly 1990s.
That sounds a lot like
some, case
I came across on my research.
A mile from here, you guys have
a rock quarry, um,
that used to be part
of the original property.
Back on Halloween night, 1990,
a young guy named
Ramone Hernandez was down here
with two of his friends --
Charles Steven Sink,
who I happen to have a photo of,
middle name Steven...
...and his girlfriend,
Evelyn Holcolm.
Now Ramone had terminal cancer,
recently cashed
a disability check
and had a lot of money on him.
His so-called friends
took him to the quarry
and suddenly attacked him.
They knocked him unconscious.
And Holcolm and Sink pushed him
into the quarry.
- Why'd they do it?
- For the money.
Ramone has $700 in cash on him.
Cops wind up figuring it out.
They got a hold of these two,
and they wind up confessing
to it.
Sink spent 23 years in prison
and he got out.
He's out now. He's alive.
Now Holcolm got out
after a few years,
but is back in jail
for another offense.
Do you think that's what
you might have been seein'?
Well,
it sounds just like it.
The next thing was that I...
came into the house
and I saw this male.
He seemed extremely angry.
He was hurting people
in his life.
One of the things
I thought was
that you might
hear him walking around.
Everybody in the house
hears footsteps, correct?
Yes.
I hear footsteps
going up and down,
up and down, up and down.
That's him.
I got that he would
occasionally touch women,
possibly,
inappropriately.
I also got that he spends
a lot of time right here.
So in this room,
you may feel nausea and anxiety.
A lot of what you're sayin'
is what these guys
are experiencing.
Explain your health issues
to Amy.
There's lots
of different health issues,
kidneys and gall bladder,
back,
and just tired all the time.
Since we've moved here,
I've di--
been diagnosed
with a heart condition.
I've had stabbing pains
and back pain all the time.
Now this might explain
why we were called in.
Abbie has developed
an anxiety disorder
called selective mutism.
Any time she's feeling
threatened or anxious,
she's not able to tell me 'cause
she just -- she shuts down.
Interesting. Okay.
Typically,
on a normal investigation,
I will come across,
you know, one thing
that is of major importance
at a location.
You, in fact,
have several.
I actually came across
a portal.
It's upstairs
at the end of the hall
before you go into
the big room.
And what this is,
is a doorway for the dead.
The dead that were coming
through this
were indicating to me that
they literally feel like
they're stuck
and that they're stuck
in hell.
So let me get this straight
So there's a portal here,
the dead could come
from just about anywhere?
Yeah.
And there are a lot of people
that are coming through.
I'm sorry...
All these horrible things
that happened around this area,
that were negative,
are being sucked in here.
It tears me up.
I wished it was me
that was experiencing
as opposed to them.
The other thing
that's coming in
with all of these lost,
dead people roaming about
was upstairs in the hallway.
And it was shadow people.
And they were slithering
flat on the walls,
up and down
and on the ceiling.
These things have been here
for a very, very long time
and have somehow
figured out a way
to cross over from
possibly another dimension.
They are extremely dangerous.
They tend to center
their anger
around children,
the elderly,
and individuals
who are sick.
Now Tyler here, tell Amy
about the shadow figure you see.
It feels like
it's about 7 foot tall.
- Okay.
- And it's peering down on me.
And it has yellow eyes.
Really. Okay.
I see something,
like he says, very tall
with pale, yellow eyes.
And he's got these long,
creepy fingers.
It makes me think
that I'm goin' crazy.
Now Abbie sees them also,
right, Donna?
Right. That's something
that shuts her down.
It scares her.
If she's seen half the things
I've seen, then...
I can't imagine.
All right, so what do
these shadow figures want?
They want to abduct
or they want to kill.
I don't want you guys
goin' in the pool,
especially the kids,
because when I was outside,
I was seein' this shadow person
goin' into the pool.
And I saw that thing,
like, people swimming
and then yanking them down
by their feet
and tryin' to drown 'em.
Now this house sits on
what used to be a 250-acre farm.
And in the middle of that farm
was that huge quarry
where the murder took place.
The other thing I found out
about the quarry
is that two young people
drowned there under
very mysterious circumstances.
First kid was
on August 22nd, 1987.
A 14-year-old boy
by the name of Henry Oglesby
went swimming there
with some friends.
And I got a picture of Henry
right here.
He jumped into about 10 feet
of water
and he never came back up.
Almost 2 years later, in 1989,
a 25-year-old by the name
of David Wayne Ellison
did the same exact thing.
He went swimming, jumped in,
and never resurfaced.
These were
two healthy young men.
Now you said these shadow people
are all over the damn place.
Yes.
Is it possible they could have
caused these kids to drown?
I think so.
There's actually been cases
where individuals
have seen shadow people
and then have had things
like heart attacks.
The feeling of lethargy
because they will literally
suck the breath out of you.
Now that I hear it,
it's all fitting together.
I've had more
breathing problems, you know,
um, like that.
So, I mean, it -- it's just...
it's concerning.
Now, Amy, Andy might
be downplaying things,
but he was doing renovations
and got seriously sick.
It's bad. I think he was
attacked up there.
And he hurt for over a week.
He likes to play it down.
Now do you think that's from
the shadow people?
Or is that somethin' else?
That's more than likely
the shadow people.
Like, slowly,
they're draining,
literally taking the life
from you.
We're being held captive.
Yeah.
The biggest threat in your house
is a demonic presence.
It's very powerful.
One of the individuals
that I got
that it's influencing
was in the pink room.
That's Abbie's room.
I got that there was
a lot of issues
with the person in that room.
And that this thing
is really essentially
at the root of that problem.
And all those fears
and traumas
that are taking place
are being created by this thing.
It can change forms.
There's a lot of trickery
and faces it can take.
Where's it at? I mean, is it
here with us, in the house?
Or is it...
- Yes, it is.
I feel -- I had a feelin'
that it was.
So I'm not crazy.
No.
One of the sketches
that I had done was
of a moment when it was
tricking the living person
into thinking it was
a deceased relative.
Jeez.
It looks just like Abbie.
It makes me so mad.
I should've
done somethin' sooner.
I'm worried.
So now this is not how the demon
looked when you saw it, right?
So what did it look like
when you saw it?
I had a sketch done.
Another one? Okay.
God.
Well, this would scare
the **** out of me,
I'll tell ya that.
That's my -- that's my room.
At night, I saw the --
I saw it completely black out
the TV in my room.
It was him lookin' down at me.
It scared me to death. It took
the color out of my skin.
And till this day,
I- I don't forget it.
So, Donna, is this
the yellow-eyed thing you saw?
Yeah.
All right, so what does
this thing want?
I feel like, the, demon
has really attached itself
to Abbie.
And I think it's already
influencing her
to become depressed,
um, possibly harm herself.
And you guys aren't the first
to be influenced by this thing.
That sucker's old.
It upsets me, makes me mad
that something could
have that power, you know,
to do that.
That fits right in with what
they do -- self-harm,
harm to others,
divide and conquer.
It makes me just want
to put the family in the car
and not come back.
Now every once in a while,
a client has a portal,
and that's bad news.
Shadow people come up even less,
and that's usually
really bad news.
This is the first case
I've worked with Amy
where you have a portal,
shadow people, and a demon.
Honestly, I have no idea
what she's gonna say.
But unfortunately, I got
a feeling you won't like it.
As we were going along,
I'm like,
"Well this could be done
or that could be done."
And then, I went upstairs
to talk to the positive dead.
And what they said, very loud,
very clearly, was, "Move."
There's several things
that you would need to do
prior to moving.
You would need to have
a type of exorcism
of Abbie.
I don't recommend exorcisms
for -- for children,
um, but this is
absolutely necessary.
So the next thing
that needs to be done
is a blessing
for the entire family
before the move,
by a holy person.
And then all three of the kids
should see a psychotherapist.
There's a lot of PTSD
that's going on here
of things that they've seen.
They're gonna be terrified
that this is something
that's gonna happen again.
Do you think that that's...
this thing has probably
caused her condition?
Yes.
And I think her seeing
a psychotherapist will help.
I feel bad for puttin'
my children through this.
I feel like
I've let it happen.
Um, and then also,
I cannot believe it.
You gonna do what
Amy suggests you guys do?
- We'll move.
- Okay.
Wishing we would've
done it earlier.
I'm willing to do anything.
Well, the thing is,
you're gonna have a fresh start
and get your kids back.
You can live in a tent.
What-- whatever you need to do,
as long as your family's safe.
As long as I still have them,
that's all that matters.
Right.
Between a demon, a portal,
and shadow people,
the only way Donna and Andy
can protect their family
is to move as far away
as possible.
If they do that and exorcise
the demon attached to Abbie,
they should lead
a peaceful life.