A living person who lives here
was horribly abused.
This person has PK.
Something just jumped in me.
I think I would
have freaked out.
I think that she's seen it.
So you think whatever's here
is capable of killing your guys?
Oh, I think it is.
Is it trying to kill her?
Yeah.
I just see the word death.
I just hear death.
My name is Amy Allan.
It's like,
"I'm going to get you."
I see dead people.
Her face was all demonic.
I speak to dead people.
He's like,
"You think you can stop me?
Because you can't."
And they speak to me.
- What is he trying to do?
- Kill them.
But there's only one way
to know if my findings are real.
Something happened.
Bam, bam, bam.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
Am I seeing
what I think I'm seeing?
And I know every person,
every house, has secrets.
They're everywhere.
It's my job to reveal them.
This guy's got the markings
of a serial killer.
But Steve and I never speak.
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
This dead guy
doing that to her?
- When we uncover if it's safe
for you to stay... - That's it.
Or time to get out...
Somebody's gonna
die over there soon, yeah.
I'm in Santa Rosa Beach,
Florida, just east of Pensacola.
Now, this place
may look like paradise,
but I got a call from a guy
who says he's living in hell.
He says whatever's in the house
is scaring his family to death.
Even worse, he's convinced
it's going
after his grown-up daughter.
He sounded really stressed
on the phone
and said we're
his very last hope.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the house
of any leading information.
Family photographs
and other personal items
can influence her findings,
so it's important I cover
or remove them all.
When I'm finished,
the location'll be ready
for tonight's walk.
There's a male,
an older male grabbing me.
He's, uh, really not good.
And he, um,
is a big problem here.
They can physically feel him.
Uh, he can, like,
you know, touch 'em, grab 'em.
He's grabbing me.
So, Steve, I gotta tell you,
this is one of the few cases
in all I've done, that the man
of the house has called us in.
What the hell's going on here?
We were just bombarded
with activity here.
It's just to the point
we gotta get some help.
I -- I just feel
like without the help,
I think it would
kill somebody eventually
if we didn't get
something done to it.
So you think whatever's here
is capable of killing your guys?
Oh, I think it is.
Is it affecting everybody?
I think it's
affecting everybody.
Okay.
Who exactly lives
in the house with you?
- Well, this is my wife, Donna.
- Okay.
This is Steven Jr.
He's 18.
This is my step-daughter,
Brittney.
- Okay.
- This is her fiance, Jason.
And then Nikola
is my other step-daughter.
Okay. What exactly are you guys
going through?
What experiences are you having?
Well, we're having knocks,
whispers, uh, things moving,
um, shadows and some attacks,
physical attacks.
And the depression
is so bad around here,
it -- it's just hardly
any peace around the house
anymore whatsoever.
Lately, we're all separated.
And we -- we never
do anything together.
Everybody stays in their room.
It's really hard to live here.
So which daughter
are you worried about?
Brittney.
Okay, what's going on with her?
She's just totally
drained of energy.
She can't walk over 30 feet.
She can't stand for any length
of time at all.
We've gone to every doctor.
We've just not found
any answers we --
we're looking for.
I -- I assume she can't work.
She can't.
It breaks our heart.
With all the stuff you've been
going through, why call us now?
What -- what change?
The physical attacks
have just gotten worse.
And then my son comes to me
and he has a bite.
And that's when we decided
we have to do something
about it.
It's extremely hard
to see your kids
get tortured like this.
A living person
got hit here
by this man.
These living people,
they have a lot of pain.
He's always grabbing someone
at the neck.
That grip, he's got, like,
this **** grip
that'll make, like,
their ear hurt,
their neck hurt,
their, you know,
all in here, having,
like, major, like,
**** pain.
He has to have his hands on you.
Like, he has to have his hands
on you.
So why'd you bring me in here?
We're seeing shadows
all the time.
Okay, where are you
seeing them?
They're originating
from the middle of the hall
and they're coming down
through here toward the kitchen.
It seemed like its about
6 to 7 foot tall,
solid black mass.
- Is it shaped like a human?
- Yes.
This is a quiet block.
Nobody's walking by.
Very quiet.
You don't even have cars
coming by here very often.
Okay.
So anything else?
Well, we're hearing voices.
I'll get up, there again,
assuming it's one of the kids.
We get up,
I go down the hallway,
I look in every single bedroom.
Never any of 'em.
Okay.
I think that old dude
comes in here a lot.
He gets really mad in here.
I don't know why.
He, like, he pitches a fit.
The living might hear, like,
I don't know if he,
like, stomps around,
or yelling.
They would hear him go
**** ballistic in here.
Okay.
So anything else?
Yeah, I got poked twice.
I was laying in bed,
uh, early morning.
And I felt a poke
on my backside.
I get up and then
I got poked again in the bedroom
and it left a big bruise.
All right.
So is it possible
in the middle of the night
you might have poked yourself
or hit yourself against
something, caused that bruise?
No, I don't think so.
How are you living like this?
If this activity continues,
we're done.
I mean, there's no question.
We can't live like this.
The dude who was, like,
grabbing me, he's just
**** torturing everybody.
The thing is, is,
like, he's hurting people.
Head and neck and upper back
on the right side.
Bad guy.
Torturer, torturer.
So when I was talking to Steve,
he said to me he thinks
that whatever's in this house
is causing your illness...
...and it's trying to basically kill you.
- Yeah.
You agree with that at all?
It's hard
for me to agree with that.
I want it to be something
that the doctors
can physically find
so that they don't
think I'm crazy.
Okay. That's understandable.
All right.
What are the symptoms?
It's a lot like having
the flu all the time.
Blurry vision, headache,
stomach ache, just --
it's been tough just,
you know, standing.
It's almost like,
uh, something is squeezing
my spine or something.
And it's very intense.
So I've mostly just
been bedridden,
because it's overwhelming.
Have you experienced anything
paranormal in this house,
anything unusual?
I've been scratched recently.
So how deep of a cut
are we talking about?
I -- I took a picture.
Let me see your nails.
All right.
You could scratch yourself
but you don't think
you did it yourself.
I don't think I did it.
Okay. Anything else?
I've been having
these nightmares.
Okay.
What kinda nightmares
are we talking about?
It feels like I'm
leaving my body.
All I see is black.
And then when I do wake up,
I wake up startled
and I wake up gasping
and shoot up in bed.
Okay. How often are you
having this dream?
Um, weekly.
I can't say that what's going
on with you is paranormal.
Um, I kinda hope it is,
to be honest with you,
so maybe Amy can come up
with something to fix it.
Yeah, I want to be independent.
And it's very hard for me
to have to live like this.
I bet it is.
Somebody's in the bed.
Ew, aye-yi-yi-yi!
Oh, dear God.
I feel sick.
Nah, I hear a woman screaming.
She's gasping.
She's waking up
from a nightmare.
So yeah, they're having a lot --
a **** ton of issues here.
And I feel sick, horribly ill.
I don't like this bed.
I don't like
this area.
I just see the word death.
I just see
the word death.
♪♪
So, Donna, Brittney's gotta
be concerning for you.
She's a beautiful girl.
You wouldn't think she's sick.
And she's real sick.
She was active and she had
to give up her school
and file for disability.
Breaks my heart.
What kind of experiences
have you had, if any?
I was standing
at the stove, cooking,
and a magnet
flew off the fridge at me
and landed right by me.
It's like somebody picked it up
and threw it at me.
I can't see how the hell
that could have happened.
I'm amazed myself.
'Cause, I mean, I was in shock.
All right.
Anything else happen?
I was making coffee
and, uh,
I felt someone come up
and put their arms around me.
- Okay, I'm assuming you thought
it was your husband? - Yeah.
So what happened?
- You turn around and
there's nobody there? - Yeah.
I think I would
have freaked out.
I did.
After going through everything
that I've gone through,
I don't want my daughter to have
to go through it or my children.
What do you mean,
after what you've gone through?
Um, I was molested
when I was 7 years old.
It was traumatizing,
someone I trusted.
Yeah, no doubt.
Well, I'm glad
you, uh, opened up
to me about that.
That's why we called you guys.
We need help.
Okay.
I think that somebody
who is here
was horribly abused as a child.
Uh, a living person
who lives here
was horribly abused.
I -- I don't know
how they were abused.
This person has PK.
PK manifestations usually come
from a living person.
And when that person gets angry,
it subconsciously sends energy
to that entity.
And that's when all hell
can break loose.
How does
the PK manifest?
[ Rattling handle ]
Lots of this sh--
kind of crap.
Things disappear.
And, like, literally
they're disappearing.
Like, I mean, like,
into thin air.
I do see, like,
people getting hurt.
So she's essentially
torturing herself.
Okay, so, Donna,
this is your master bedroom.
Yes.
Mm'kay.
So I assume
you brought me in here
because you've had experiences.
Yes, I have, several.
Okay, what happened?
Um, my husband was laying here
and I was laying next to him.
But I saw a dark,
dark black mass just
hovering over him.
Kind of a swirly light,
but it was solid black.
And it was nothing
coming from outside causing
that that you could tell?
I looked.
Okay.
Anything else in here?
A few times when I would be
about ready to go to sleep,
I felt like something
just jumped in me.
So now, when Amy talks
about getting jumped,
she's talking
about a dead person
actually jumping into her body.
Is that the same feeling
you're getting?
- Yeah, that's what
it feels like. - Okay.
Just queasy feeling all over.
Doesn't feel well.
I'm afraid to ask
if anything else
is going on in this room.
Uh, yeah.
I've had something
crawl across my legs in the bed.
I mean, I could feel
the indentation in the bed.
Now you have a small dog,
so you know
what that feels like.
Oh, yeah.
But, uh, she --
she doesn't even
come in this room.
She won't sleep in here.
So she sleeps in with Brittney.
I mean, how the hell
are you sleeping at night?
We don't much.
This thing's, like,
laying like that.
And then it, like,
went like this and then
it went like that.
And then it had a head,
arms and hands.
I'm confused about what it is.
It's been attached to a female
since she was little.
I think that she's seen it.
I think it's caused a lot
of problems
throughout this person's life.
I think that there's been
struggles
with addictions manifesting,
OCDs on and off.
And it's because of this thing
that has been
latched onto her.
It takes your energy from you.
And so then you can't stand up
and you can't walk.
You have to just lay down.
Her and the ****
thing take energy.
And so that's bad for anybody
who, like, lives with her.
Is it
trying to hurt her?
Yeah.
It does, her whole life.
Is it trying to
kill her?
So I've already reached
out to a bunch of locals:
cops, journalists, historians,
anyone who might give me a lead.
I just got a call
back from a genealogist,
who says a previous owner
of the property
was a well-known
attorney general
who went after the mob
and may have paid
for it with his life.
So Diane, this guy
you were talking about
on the phone
to me sounds pretty interesting.
What's his story?
He was an interesting guy.
This is Robert Bushnell.
When did he wind up
buying my client's property?
In 1944, he bought it
with his mother, Mary.
And they were going
to develop it
as a business interest.
Okay.
So did he live here?
No, his mother did.
He would come down...
...and visit often.
- Okay.
And you mentioned he was
an attorney general.
Yes, he was, in the state
of Massachusetts.
Okay, so what kind of a guy
was he as an attorney general?
He had a reputation
of being really tough.
He was known to be very
short-tempered as well,
in and out of the court room.
Now, Diane, you mentioned
he went after the mob.
Uh, what did you mean by that?
Well, in Boston there was
a very popular nightclub...
...run by the mob,
called the Cocoanut Grove. - Okay.
And in 1942,
there was horrendous fire
there that killed 492 people.
Wow.
There were code violations,
clearly.
Doors were locked.
And Robert Bushnell
went after the owners
and got convictions
for 19 manslaughters.
In fact, there was
an article here.
The main owner was put away
for from 12 to 15 years.
Well, the way it sounds,
how this guy went
after the mob,
he might have, uh,
had some targets on him.
I'm sure he did, yes.
I'm seeing the old guy
who grabbed me again.
You know anything
about him in life?
I know he moved here.
I'm gonna say probably from back
east somewhere.
He's talking about ownership.
He owned, like,
a business, I think.
I feel like he was,
like, established.
He's gotta
control everything, I guess.
There was also something
important about a fire.
And so the fire,
that was a problem.
I'm getting the fire big time,
big time, again.
Whew!
****
Ooh-wee, it's hot.
So, Diane,
I understand his death
might've been
a little suspicious.
So what happened?
In 1949, he returned from
Washington, D.C. one night
and went up
to his residential suite
in a hotel in New York City
and gave instructions
to the front desk people
not to disturb him
for the weekend.
And a couple of days later,
he was found dead in his bed.
Okay.
So I got a few questions.
I mean, what was the cause
of death, number one?
They ruled it a heart attack.
Okay.
How old was he at the time.
He was only 53.
Any health issues?
Was he obese?
He was a little bit
overweight for his size,
but nothing that came out,
as far as a disease
or anything like that.
He had few friends
and many enemies.
It could have been
a number of things.
This guy who grabs people
is kind of...
chubby, overweight.
So he didn't eat well.
His heart, man.
Something with his chest
is so wicked bad.
Like, he can't let go of that
****.
He died from, I think,
a heart attack.
Any idea how old
he was when he died?
You know, uh, uh, I would say,
like, you know,
like 60s, 50s,
60s.
So angry that he died.
Maybe he was looking forward
to moving here.
So far, I've got a family
being terrorized
by bizarre activity
on a property
that was once owned
by an attorney general
who died mysteriously.
But I wanna see
if there's anything else.
Searching through old records,
I find Charles Cessna,
one of the original owners
of the property
and the town's founder.
Turns out he was also
a scam artist.
I don't think Donna
and Steve have a clue
the town founder
owned their property.
I'm heading over to meet
with a local journalist
who says Charles Cessna's life
was filled with fraud, lies
and violence.
So Jeffrey, before we get
to this guy, Cessna,
and his scams, uh,
what were you able
to find out about him.
Steve, here's the picture
of Dr. Charles Cessna.
He was a medical doctor
in Chicago.
- He was a legitimate doctor?
- No, he was not.
He also was selling placebos
through newspaper
advertisements.
Okay, so this guy was like
a snake oil salesman basically.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
All right.
How'd that work out for him?
He did get busted twice for that
and had
his medical license revoked.
All right.
So let's move onto the scams
in, uh, Santa Rosa Beach.
When does he come down here
and start doing stuff?
- He comes in 1910 and starts
purchasing property. - Okay.
Then, in 1911,
he purchases the property
that your client lives on now.
All right. So how's the scam
work for him down here?
Here's an advertisement here
that shows he is selling
10-acre farmland for people.
And when they get here,
much of looks like this,
which is not good farmland,
like is advertised.
- So he tried selling 'em
this crap? - Yes.
What about this scam?
Does he get caught,
go to jail?
Apparently he does not.
In fact, he makes millions
on selling the land.
All right. So, Jeff, you had
mentioned on the phone
about violence --
what'd you mean by that?
Well, 1917, Mr. Cessna
is a married man
with three children who's
carrying on an affair
with a young woman
that was working for him,
named Julia Murphy.
Here's a photograph of her.
As they were breaking up,
Cessna flips out, beats her
and drags her around the office
by the hair.
All right.
So what happened?
I mean, he just
gets away with it?
He does not.
She --
she ultimately sues him
for firing her.
Okay, so how's that lawsuit go?
He eventually has to pay
$30,000 to Miss Murphy.
That's a lot of money back then.
It certainly is.
I'm seeing a young woman.
This dead girl,
she got an impact
on the right side
of her head and neck.
There's something
about her being, I think,
on a date when she got killed.
She has, like, brown hair
to about here and brown eyes.
And she's pretty.
She's young.
I'd say, like, you know,
between, like, I dunno,
like, 17 and,
like, 25, maybe.
She's confused and lost.
But she's really angry.
She's always running
around the house.
She makes people
feel panicky here.
She makes them feel fear here.
And then they can hear her, um,
yelling out, yelling.
And, like, I'm having neck...
really bad.
Oh **** ****.
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity
in your home,
go to the "Dead Files" page
at travelchannel.com.
Click on help me, "Dead Files"
to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
So another thing
caught my eye in research:
The original owner
of Steve and Donna's property
seems to have suffered
a lot of tragedy.
I'm heading over
to meet a local historian
who says his story
will definitely help my case.
So Brenda, I came
across this guy,
Henry Reddick, uh, who lived
on my client's property.
And I know he'd lost a few kids.
But before we get to that,
what do you know about this guy?
Henry Reddick was born
in Macon, Georgia in 1833.
Sometime after that, he moved to
the northwest Florida panhandle...
...and -- and settled here.
- Okay.
What'd he do when he came here?
He was in the mill business,
the timber business.
All right.
So if he's born in 1833,
I assume he winds up fighting
in the Civil War.
Yes, he does.
He joins the Confederacy
and soon after
that he goes to fight
in his first battle at
what is now Fort Walton Beach.
Uh, how's the war go for him?
Doesn't necessarily
go well for him at all.
He ends up in one of the most
horrific battles
of the Civil War
in Franklin, Tennessee.
Over 9,000 are killed and 6,000
of those are Confederates.
He's assigned to burial duty.
He's in charge of burying
all those people.
There's, like,
this big, fancy graveyard.
I've never seen,
like, so many graves.
It's, like, packed,
packed, full of graves,
one on top of the other,
one on top of the other.
There's so many dead people.
This was all bad ****
that went down.
All right.
So I know he survives the war.
So does he come back here?
Yes, he does come back
to the area.
And he marries.
And he and his wife
have two children:
Ellen and Etta.
Shortly after Etta was born,
his wife died.
All right.
So I know he remarries again.
Uh, when did that happen?
In 1874, he marries a widow
whose name is Elizabeth.
Any kids together.
Henry and Elizabeth
have eight children together.
What happened?
Well, out of
those eight children
that Henry and Elizabeth
had together,
three of them died.
Three of the boys
that had died
are buried on that property.
There was a female.
And she has, like, short,
curly, brown hair.
And she's little.
This was back a ways.
And she's, like, freaking out.
She is banging
on a dining room table.
She, uh, lost her child.
Her child died.
I saw several disturbing things
on my walk.
But the creature
that's torturing
a living woman had me
the most concerned.
There was a gigantic bed
in the room.
And then this thing
lifted its head to look at me.
It had a human arm
and leg.
Amy, is this what you saw?
Yes.
STEVE: Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready
to reveal our findings
to each other and our clients
for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to meet Donna.
This is her daughter, Brittney,
and her husband, Steve.
Now everybody's having
a bad time here.
But Steve is convinced
that whatever's here
is trying to kill Brittney.
Now, she may look fine, uh,
but she's not doing well.
She spends most
of her days in bed.
Uh, it's actually
a pretty big deal...
...that you're even sitting here with us,
to be honest. - Yeah.
So, with that,
I'm gonna have Amy
tell us about her walk
and see where it takes us.
When I first entered the house,
I saw this enormous graveyard.
It was packed with bodies.
I kept being told
that this was
extremely important
and that it does have something
to do with the land here.
Then, I was shown this female.
And she was pounding on a table
and screaming that her --
I guess a child...
...of hers had just died.
- All right.
So there's a few things
that you should know about.
First off,
there's a graveyard nearby.
I think it's just over a half
a mile from here.
And it was part
of the original property line.
Oh.
Now one of the original owners
of the property
has a direct connection
to the graveyard here.
This guy, Henry Reddick,
he was around in the 1800s,
fought in the Civil War.
Now Henry
and his wife, Elizabeth,
had eight kids together.
Three of them,
including a young infant, died.
And they're all buried
in that cemetery.
The next individual
that I ran into was a male.
And he was older.
Uh, and he's kind
of a big issue here.
I saw him attacking
living people,
trying to physically
torture people.
Like, I encounter this guy
and he's got a grip on me.
Like, he's holding me.
I think he can possibly
jump people as well.
Donna, tell Amy
what you experienced.
Yeah, I'm getting
ready for bed.
And I'm just relaxing.
And I feel just
the weirdest feeling.
It's almost like choking,
nausea.
And I just jumped totally
out of bed.
I felt like somebody
just went through me,
just terrorizing me.
It's shocking.
The reason why he does
this is to dominate and control.
I think that the living
would experience this dead guy
in several different ways.
Uh, so I think
the head, neck
and upper back would be uh,
a issue when he's around.
- Now, you've also been...
- Touched...
Tell Amy how you...
In the kitchen,
I felt somebody come around
and grab me around my waist.
I gotta show you
something else.
Brittney here
has been scratched.
Okay.
Wow.
I woke up one morning,
looked into the bathroom
and I notice these scratches
here, uh,
along here and down on my leg.
And it's just...
I didn't have
an explanation for them.
And this is what happened
to Steve's son.
He came out of his room
and he was terrified.
Uh, we knew we had
to call somebody at that point.
Okay. Any idea who this guy
might be in life.
I think he moved here
at some point
or was about to.
I saw that he had
a business back east.
Uh, I got
that there was a fire, uh,
that played a very important
role in his life.
Uh, in fact, my --
my back caught fire
and I --
I could feel it burning.
Why'd you guys
have that reaction
when she told you
about this guy?
'Cause she's always
got burning pain.
I got that he dropped dead
in his 50s or 60s,
I think from a heart attack.
I got
that he was slightly chubby,
didn't eat very well.
And he's extremely pissed off
about his death
because he was really, really
looking forward to moving here.
There is somebody
that could fit the bill.
There's a previous owner
of the land
that comes to mind, actually,
this guy Robert Bushnell.
Uh, he was the attorney general
of Massachusetts.
Uh, in 1944, him and his mother
purchased your property.
He didn't live here,
but he came down a lot to visit.
Now this guy was a lawyer
that was known
for his hot temper.
His biggest case
that caught my attention
that killed over 490 people.
Now, this fire took place
at a nightclub in Boston
called the Cocoanut Grove.
Now Bushnell went
after the Mafia-connected owner
of the nightclub
and sent him to prison.
Now the other thing
was, you said...
...the guy died of a heart attack
in his 50s or 60s. - Uh-huh.
In 1949, at the age of 53,
he dies of a heart attack.
Wow.
Actually found a photo
of him in his 40s.
Is it possible
this is who you saw.
Yes.
The next thing was
down the hall, uh,
and then the right.
So the first thing that I got,
when I walked into that room,
was the word death.
Uh, I got that the living female
that is in that room, uh,
is dealing with a lot of issues.
And it's many different types
of issues.
I felt extremely sick in there,
stomach pain,
intense stomach pains.
I saw this female screaming, uh,
gasping, waking form nightmares.
It was a bad situation.
That's Brittney's room.
That's your room?
Interesting.
You know, I look fine,
but inside, it's torture.
Um, stomach pains, back pain.
That's what I go through.
And when I'm standing,
it feels like,
almost as if someone's, like,
choking my spine. - Mm-hmm.
I hate to say it,
but it feels like I'm dying.
Now you had nightmares
that we talked about.
Yeah, um, it's...
I dream...
I -- I almost feel
like I'm leaving my body.
And this fear overwhelms me.
And I'm yelling at myself,
screaming to wake up.
Mm-hmm.
And I wake up just
terrified, startled.
The next thing
that I encountered was
in the master bedroom area.
I got that there was
a living female in there
who was horribly
abused as a child.
I got that she has struggled
with addictions
and possibly struggles with OCD.
Uh, this living woman
is also a sensitive,
possibly a physical medium.
I was hoping we were gonna
have to bring this up.
But it's kind of important
at this point.
You had some abuse issues
as a child.
Yeah, I was
7, 8 years old.
And somebody I trusted,
uh, attempted to molest me.
And I thought that's something
I put behind me.
Obviously you didn't put it
behind you.
Probably not.
So the thing I'm most
concerned about
was in the master bedroom area
as well.
While I was in there,
I thought I saw, like,
a big throw blanket
at the end of the bed, um,
but no, it wasn't.
So I'm looking
and I'm like, "Huh."
And it raises its head.
And then it just slid
right off the bed.
It's attached
to the living woman.
Uh, it's been attached
to her since,
actually, she was very young.
And I saw a scene
of this thing with the --
with the female in bed.
And I had that sketched.
Well, this ain't good.
BRITTNEY: Oh, my gosh.
Oh, yeah.
- That's probably what I saw
hovering over you. - Yeah.
Probably what I saw that night.
At least I know I'm not nuts.
But I feel nuts.
I felt something
crawl across the bed.
So you think it might
have been that?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Looks like it.
That thing
is a PK manifestation.
What is so fascinating about it
is that this is something
that you've had attached
to you since childhood,
which I've never,
ever, ever seen before.
Because it has somewhat
formed a personality of its own,
it can now do things
separate from you, uh,
to living indi--
individuals.
Um, so if you get angry,
it gets angry.
So the scratch marks
and the bruises,
could that be coming from Donna?
From your subconscious.
And when she gets angry
or upset,
she's able
to make objects disappear.
Yeah, she's always complaining
that something's missing.
Well, that's something
that's common with --
with mediums in general.
But she's not the only one
with abilities.
So the thing is,
I sat down at the table,
the first thing I got with you
was psychic empath healer.
And the problem
with being a psychic empath
is that you're
in close proximity
with someone
who is a physical medium
who has flaring PK.
And so she's drawing
a lot of energy
from everyone in the house
to the point
where it's draining you
and making you sick.
Oh, God.
Like, a lot of people will refer
to it as psychic vampirism.
Did all this start because of
what happened to Donna as a kid?
Yeah.
So it's like you're
torturing yourself.
You blame yourself for a lot
of ****
that happened
when you were a kid.
Yeah.
Like, um, in a dream or...
It don't seem right.
That's for sure.
Surreal.
Well, guys, we got a lot
of answers tonight.
We know why Brittney's
been so sick, uh,
why everybody's been
so depressed and drained, uh,
and why things have actually
gotten so physical.
But what we still don't know is
whether you guys can stay here
and live together peacefully
as a family.
Uh, for that answer,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
This is something
that can be dealt with,
although it will require
lifestyle changes and things
that you'll have
to do consistently
for the rest of your life.
Donna, I would like you
to find a psychotherapist.
You need an outlet.
And that's going to be
a really good outlet
for you to feel comfortable
in a space
that you can share
anything and everything
that's bothering you.
And by you verbalizing it
and getting it out of you,
you're taking away power
from this --
this sucker that's formed.
Steve: Will that make this thing
that's manifested
start to dissipate?
Yes, yes,
absolutely, absolutely.
And the thing is,
is by doing all of these things,
um, it'll --
it'll lead you
on a very interesting path
in your life.
The other thing
now is for Brittney.
You need to learn reiki.
Uh, this is going to balance
your energy and your abilities.
You're never gonna be completely
back to normal.
But you'll start having
more better days than worse.
I am thankful, like, for this.
I -- I am so grateful, um,
just to better, you know,
even a little bit better.
That works for me.
The other thing is,
as far as the house and, like,
all the energy that's here,
you need a reiki master
to come in
and completely balance
the energy here,
remove what doesn't need to be
here anymore and bring in light,
love and positivity
and to set up boundaries
for the dead.
So I never heard you say
before reiki master
removing the dead before.
They're gonna remove
negative energy.
But what they'll do
is also set up boundaries
so that the dead
can't come in anymore.
So does that mean this guy
Bushnell will be out of here
or he'll be not allowed back
in the house?
Yeah, he won't be allowed
back in the house.
You gonna take
her advice, Britt?
Definitely.
Okay.
- Donna?
- Oh, yeah.
You're on board.
Now I just gotta make sure
they do what they're gonna do.
I mean, this is a big relief.
I mean, just the mentalness
of her knowing that something
can be done is a lot.
- It's hard to forgive yourself.
- Yeah.
All right.
But you're not doing just
for you now.
You're doing it for your family.
Yes.
That's important to me.
And you can't be guilty.
I mean,
my family's too important to me.
And I'll do what I gotta do.
AMY: I can't imagine
the pain Donna
feels, knowing
she's manifested an entity
that's tormenting her family.
But, with the help
of a psychotherapist
and a reiki master,
they can banish the dead
and weaken the PK,
allowing them to lead
a peaceful life.