For the living and the dead,
this is just a terrible place.
Something is tearing
my family apart.
This person is scary.
I just know,
whatever it is, it's bad.
It's physically painful
to be in here.
Sickness is everywhere.
I just hear death.
-Aah!
My name is Amy Allan.
God.
It's like,
"I'm going to get you."
I see dead people.
Her face was all demonic.
I speak to dead people.
He's like, "You think you can
stop me? Because you can't."
And they speak to me.
What is he trying to do?
Kill them.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
Something happened.
Bam, bam, bam!
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
Am I seeing
what I think I'm seeing?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
They're everywhere.
It's my job to reveal them.
This guy's got the markings
of a serial killer.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end...
Is this dead guy
doing that to her?
...when we uncover
if it's safe for you to stay...
That's it.
...or time to get out.
Somebody's gonna die
over there soon, yeah.
Aaaaaah!
I'm out here in Kaufman, Texas.
It's about 35 miles
southeast of Dallas.
I got a call
from a guy named Larry.
Now, this guy's got
a real problem on his hands.
He says paranormal activity
in the house
already broke up his marriage
and, now, his three daughters
are coming under attack.
He says we're his last hope
to bring his family
back together.
I really hope we can
help this poor guy out.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the house
of any leading information.
Family photos
and religious items
must be covered or removed.
When I'm finished,
the location'll be ready
for tonight's walk.
That's weird.
Something's wrong here.
It feels,
really horrible
and it's just like this
sickness is just everywhere.
And then, there's like this
depression, this depression.
And it's scary.
Something going on.
And it's huge.
It's so bad.
And you just wanna run away.
And you want to run
the **** away.
All right. So, Larry,
when we spoke on the phone,
you sounded pretty upset.
What the hell's going on?
Something is tearing
my family apart.
Relationships
have gone to hell.
My wife finally got
to the point
where she just asked me
to move out.
She was my golden girl
and I figured that we'd
live the rest of our lives
together, 'til we died.
That's just not
the way it happened.
Why would you think
it's the paranormal
that broke up your marriage?
Something is wanting
to take control
of the women in the house
and trying to get rid
of all of the men.
All right. So this is
a pretty unusual arrangement
you guys got going here.
Now, who's living where?
I'm living in this
house over here
and my wife
and my three daughters
are living in this
house over here.
Okay.
- Matter of fact,
I've got a picture
of my family
that's staying
at that house.
Okay. So who's this?
- This is Chelsea.
Next to her is Denise,
my wife.
Okay.
- Next to her is Brittany,
my oldest daughter.
And that's Ashley,
my middle daughter.
All right.
So, Larry, do me favor.
Give me a list
of what's going on here.
We hear voices.
We see shadows.
We're having physical
attacks on the girls,
that's causing
health issues.
I've got
rheumatoid arthritis.
I've got degenerative
bone disease,
suffering
from depression.
I had a heart attack.
My wife had
thyroid cancer.
So, Larry, I gotta ask ya:
how old are ya?
Sixty.
- I mean, the ailments
you're talking about are
for a much older man
and I can't help
but notice the walker.
What's with the walker?
Well, me and my
daughter Ashley
got into an altercation.
She downright kicked me,
broke the crap
outta my leg
in three
different places.
It was like
something took over.
What do you
want out of this investigation?
I want whatever
is here is gone,
so that me and my wife
and my family
can all be a family
again.
There's somebody here
who's having really,
really bad knee issues.
I see like a woman.
And she's like screaming.
And I'm seeing her like
running after a man.
She's beating him.
Very abusive.
It's very abusive.
Very bad, very bad.
He's running away from her.
She's screaming
at the top of her lungs.
I'm getting like chills
down my back.
It's so **** negative.
Okay. So what kind
of experiences are you having?
I got attacked.
I got slapped real hard,
twice, on the arm
and it made me bolt
out of bed.
It freaked me out.
I went
into the bathroom
and I lifted up
my nightshirt
and there was three
scratches on my belly
and my lower rib cage
on my right side.
Now, I know there's dogs
all over the place.
You sure the dog
didn't do this?
The marks were
so far apart.
It was bigger
than my dog's paw.
There's no way that my dogs
coulda made those marks.
All right.
So, anything else?
We see shadow figures
and they've gotta be,
I would say,
every bit of 10, 11 feet.
They're everywhere.
I feel somebody's
in the room with me
and I know that
there's no one there.
I need answers.
Something's just
tearing us apart.
Okay.
I see an old, old man.
And he's creeping about.
Living people with him
would feel watched.
Maybe they might see a shadow
like that on the wall.
He is a creepy mother****.
I think there's like a lot
of stuff going on here.
So, Denise,
I was talking to Larry.
He was pretty convinced
that the paranormal
broke you and him up.
You agree with that?
- No. I don't.
People's relationships
don't work out
all the time
and people walk away.
And I assume you don't believe
in the paranormal.
No. I do believe
in paranormal.
It's terrorizing my --
my family.
Have you had
any experiences?
Yes. We've had
a family photo
that fell on the floor.
- Where was it?
It's in the entryway,
on a like a mantelpiece
and it was sitting
up there
and it just fell off.
Got a bunch
of dogs here, right?
- Yeah.
- Sure one of the dogs didn't?
No. They had been
asleep on the couch.
Okay.
Well, talking to Larry,
he thinks the paranormal
is causing health problems here.
You agree with that?
- I do believe that.
Now, I, you know, I hate
to say this, but, I mean,
Larry's 60, right?
- Yes.
He doesn't look good
for his age.
No. He looks more
like 80.
If he keeps going
the way he's going,
he's going to end up dying
a very premature death.
I don't want his children
to have to go through,
you know,
what I've gone through.
What do you mean by that?
I had a stepfather
who raised me
and he died
25 years ago, so.
He was murdered.
It was very rough
'cause we were very close.
I would never
want my children
to have to go through that
'cause it was bad.
Horrible, horrible,
negative energy.
It feels like I'm walking
through sludge, like
Somebody lost someone.
Someone can't breathe.
Can't breathe because
they lost this person.
Whoever's here isn't
getting over that, at all.
He didn't die here.
He died far away, recent,
anywhere from 1990
to now, maybe.
This guy's a good guy.
He's trying to get away
from here, but he can't.
There's like
an energetic cord
that's formed
between this dead man
and a living person
he had a relationship with.
All I saw was them
pulling this cord
and he's like "Aaaaah!
No! No!"
Not a happy situation.
So, Chelsea, I understand
you're the youngest
of the three girls, correct?
- Yes.
- Okay. How old are you?
- I'm 20.
- Have you had any experiences?
- Yes. I had a experience
where I was sleeping
in my bed
and I heard something
like whisper, "Hey."
And I could feel the hair
move next to my ear
and I like woke up
out of a dead sleep,
like with shivers
down my spine.
You sure you weren't dreaming?
- Yes.
Okay. Anything else?
Lately, I've been getting
phantom bruising on my leg.
Where on the leg
would it hit you?
It's like the inner thigh
or sometimes, it'll be
on the back of my arms.
I actually have
a picture.
Jeez. No dogs
in that room with you?
No.
All right.
Anything else?
I've had dreams of a family
getting murdered.
Really?
- Yes.
And then, I also
had dreams of my sister
committing suicide
in our bathroom.
Which sister?
- Brittany.
She hung herself
from the shower stall.
She told me it was something
I had to let her do,
so I just watched her
do it, in my dream.
I mean, is that something
you worry about?
She's never been that way,
so, for me to just
have that dream
was really off the wall.
All right, so,
with dreams like that,
it's gotta be tough,
sleeping in your bedroom.
I actually don't sleep
in here anymore.
I sleep with my mom.
Why?
- It's so embarrassing, but,
I- I don't feel safe
to sleep in my room.
I'm seeing a dead woman in here.
I think she was murdered.
She comes
right through the wall.
She's trying to reach
whoever's in this bed.
I know she tries to talk
'cause she saying,
"Help me. Help me."
She's trying to get them
through dreams.
Feel like she,
can get physical?
I'm hearing smacking,
enough to wake them up.
I don't like it.
Seems like everybody in
the house is having experiences.
Now, what about yourself?
I've seen a massive
shadow in here.
Okay.
Can you describe it to me?
It was huge. It almost
touched the ceiling,
basically took up
the whole wall.
How are you sleeping
at night?
I do suffer
from anxiety.
So, my mind races
at night.
I think of everything
and nothing,
all at the same time.
What do you think is here?
I think whatever is here
just messes with us
in different ways,
brings out the worst
in people.
We were once so happy
and our family's
being torn apart.
Okay. It upsets you?
Yes.
You okay?
For the living and the dead,
this is just a terrible place.
I don't know how
they can be in here.
Like it's physically painful
to be in here.
And it's all depression,
depression, horrible,
horrible depression.
This room is completely
filled with it,
like just this black goop.
This black goop is literally
coming out of the walls.
- So what is this?
- It seems to be a collection
of negative thoughts,
feelings, and emotions
that are pushed out
of a living person.
This kind of negativity
can cause like
mentally illnesses,
physical illnesses.
It could cause them to do
and act irrationally.
It's really bad.
So, Ashley, you're the girl
that broke your dad's leg.
That right?
- Yeah.
Now, you know
he doesn't blame you.
He blames the paranormal.
Yeah.
Do you agree with that?
He was acting pretty
weird that day, so.
Okay. Your family,
you think they're in danger?
Yeah. I believe
wholeheartedly
that they're in danger.
You've had experiences,
I'm assuming.
Yes. I've had many.
Why don't you tell me
about some of 'em?
The night
that my boyfriend
had proposed to me,
when I came home
that night,
I was going to bed
- Okay.
and, when I got up,
about 3:00 am,
my pants were off
and they were placed
by my pillow.
So, was your boyfriend
here with you?
- No.
- So you were in bed alone?
Okay. You okay?
Yeah. I'll be okay.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
I couldn't even imagine
waking up and seeing that.
There were bruises
on my thighs, too.
I showed my mom.
They really
freaked her out.
Yeah.
And then,
you know, then,
that's when the blowup
with my dad happened.
What do you think's
going on in this house?
I don't know, honestly.
I just know, whatever
it is, it's bad.
Kaufman is small-town America.
This place is like Mayberry.
So, when I asked a genealogist
to look into
the property for me,
she said she already
knew all about it
and that one of the
original families
had a riches-to-rags story
I'm definitely gonna
wanna hear about.
So, Rebecca, before we get
to this riches-to-rags story,
who were the original owners
and when did they
actually purchase the land
I'm investigating?
The original owner
of this property
was Thomas Shannon.
He purchased over
1,100 acres in 1882.
So what did he do with it?
He farmed this property.
So, even though they didn't
have the easiest time,
they were able to have
a prosperous farm
in this place.
- Okay. So what do you mean by,
"They didn't have
the easiest time"?
Three of Thomas Shannon's
children, and his wife, died
in a very short
period of time.
While they were
on that property?
Correct.
Thomas Shannon, himself,
actually died on the
property as well,
in 1906.
Okay.
What'd he die of?
Well, we can see
in his death certificate
right here, basically,
he died of exhaustion.
Exhaustion?
So how old was he
at the time of his death?
- He was 66.
- All right.
So, now, Thomas Shannon is dead.
Who gets the property?
Well, it changes hands
a couple times
and it ends up with
his grandson Shannon Jones.
All right. So now, the grandson
has the property.
What's he wind up
doing with it?
Well, he's not able to
hold on to the property.
Unfortunately,
he doesn't seem to have
the capitalist gift
of his grandfather
and, from this date
in 1922,
we see him selling
the property off.
All right. So what winds up
happening with Jones?
Shannon Jones dies
of a heart attack,
actually, in 1948.
So he's 55,
which is young.
And the doctor mentions
it's from overwork.
Yeah. I see that on there.
Basically,
he worked himself to death.
Yes.
I see an angry man
in his 30s or 40s.
I would think it was
between 1930 and 1950s?
And he was out and there was
nothing, nothing, nothing,
except for dirt,
a lot of dirt,
and he's freaking
the **** out.
He started screaming and yelling
that he can't do it anymore.
He had money.
I just see the bank.
But then, I see all these papers
and someone -- on a desk --
and someone's taking a stamp
and stamping the word "Bank"
on these papers.
So it's one after the other,
Bank, Bank, Bank.
Then, he thinks, "I'm gonna
**** shoot myself."
So far, I've got a house
full of women who say
they're getting physically
attacked on a property
that's seen
at least five deaths.
But I wanna see
if there's anything else.
Searching through old records,
I find Charlie Ice,
one of the property's
previous owners.
Turns out Charlie had
some dirty laundry.
Weeks after his wife died,
he married her young caretaker.
I'm on my way to meet a local
who knew everyone involved
in this scandal and she says
the nurse was volatile,
unstable, and violent.
I understand that you grew up
in this town
and you knew Charlie Ice,
or knew of him.
Yes. This is a photo
of Charlie.
This is his first wife,
Opal.
So, when does Charlie Ice
wind up getting
my client's property?
1953.
So, take me through
this scandal.
What happened?
This is Mary and,
evidently, he had been
having an affair with her
for quite a while.
It seems as though
he had a love child.
A love child?
How do we know that?
Because his name is
on that birth certificate.
Okay. Yeah.
He's the father on here.
How old was Charlie,
at the time?
Charlie is 44.
Mary is 20.
When Opal gets sick
in 1968,
he employs Mary
to take care of Opal.
She and the child
move in.
You're kidding me.
All right,
so I know Opal dies.
When and what
did she die of?
She dies in 1968,
at the age of 58,
from a blood clot
in the lung.
Three weeks later,
Charlie marries
Mary Louise Winkler.
Okay.
How's that go for them?
Well, evidently,
not as he had planned.
She had a temper,
she had outbursts,
and sometimes,
she was violent.
All right. So, how long
are these two married?
Seven years.
He died suddenly
of a heart attack.
All right. So do we know
if Mary's still alive?
She died in 2013,
of Alzheimer's.
I'm getting a female.
And I'm hearing "mother,"
mother and grandmother.
I'm wondering like
if this is somebody
who just lived here
and recently died here.
I wanna say like maybe late 30s
to like, you know, 50.
This person is scary.
They're extremely abusive.
There's a physical
illness, though,
that is involving
their head, that's bad.
One other thing
caught my eye in research:
a young schoolteacher
who was brutally murdered
on the side of the road
right near Larry
and Denise's property.
Now, I don't know if this
is gonna help my case,
but I'm meeting with
the Kaufman County Sheriff
to see exactly what happened.
So, Sheriff, before we get
to the actual homicide,
what do we know
about the victim?
Her name was
Linda Jane Phillips
and I have
a picture of her.
She was 26 years of age.
She graduated from
North Texas State
University in 1966
and subsequently became
a schoolteacher in Dallas.
Okay.
- She was teaching in Dallas
and living in Dallas,
but still, apparently,
had a very close relationship
with her family
and would still spend
the summers here.
I'm seeing
the murdered woman again.
And I got the name either
Linda or Lily with her,
something with an L --
Leelee?
She was between 25
and 35 years old, very small.
She was superthin
and she's all kinds of
scared and pissed.
So, take me through
the night of the murder.
What happened?
August 8th of 1970,
she attended a wedding
party in Dallas
and subsequently
called her parents
at about 10:30
and told them
she would not be
coming home.
She was gonna stay
with a girlfriend.
She never arrived there.
The car was found
during the search
on the 9th of August.
Okay.
And then,
approximately
20 hours later,
her body was found,
approximately
3 miles from there.
26 stab wounds.
"Lacerations of Neck
& Abdomen."
Jeez.
Subsequent investigation
and autopsy revealed
that she'd been
sexually assaulted.
Anybody arrested for this?
14 years later, in 1984,
the self-confessed
mass murderer
named Henry Lee Lucas
confessed to it.
I know Henry Lee Lucas.
He confessed to a lot
of murders, this guy.
He did.
What was your impression?
He was a liar.
What's your opinion on it?
Do you think Henry Lee did it?
I don't believe he did.
Okay.
- There's no evidence
that he did it,
other than his word,
and obviously, his word
is not not good.
So the killer
could still be out there.
Yes.
Okay.
She's so wrapped up
in how she **** died.
It was somewhere in Texas.
And she was wearing
a really pretty dress.
Boyfriend comes in
and then, these two big like
strong-arm dudes come in
and they took her.
They throw her in this old car.
-Aaaagh!
One's in the back
and he's **** beating
the **** out of her.
There's also
sexual stuff happening.
And she sees her arm
being cut off.
With what?
I think it was like
a **** knife.
I know they did
something here, too.
You know? So this is all
**** up, like cut open.
And then, she passed out
and then,
they did something to her
neck or head, or something.
Then, they scattered her body
parts along the road.
I saw several disturbing
things on my walk,
but the bedroom filled
with big, black, negative goop
has me the most concerned.
There's this little hallway.
The bedroom door is open.
The room was filled with black,
gelatinous stuff.
It's like spilling
into the hallway.
Amy,
is this what you saw?
Yes. That's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients,
for the first time.
So, Amy, this case
is a bit unusual.
This is Larry.
He lives next house over.
This is his estranged
wife, Denise.
She lives here with Brittany;
Ashley; and Chelsea,
her youngest daughter.
Now, Larry thinks
the paranormal activity
ripped his family apart and got
him kicked out of the house.
The ladies aren't buying that.
But everyone agrees
the activity
is getting worse and more
violent and it's gotta stop.
So, now that Amy knows
a little bit
about your family
and what's going on,
I'm gonna have her
describe her walk for us.
Initially, when I got here,
I encountered a female
and her situation is
that she was murdered.
She is pretty consumed
with the way that she died.
I connected with her
in the bedroom on the right.
All right,
so that's Chelsea's room.
That's the youngest
daughter.
Okay.
And I got her specifically
trying to make contact
with the individual
in that room.
One of the ways she's
trying to make contact is
through the living
person's dreams.
The other thing is she tries
to get physical.
One of the things she was
showing me doing was
smacking the person on the bed,
trying to wake them up.
She also tries
to talk to the person
and is constantly
whispering and yelling,
"Help me. Help me. Help me."
Chelsea's
so scared to death
of being in that room alone
that she sleeps with me
every night.
She's also heard someone say --
I can't remember if it was --
- "Hey." "Hey."
- "Hey"? Or "Hello" or something.
Now, she can get physical,
you were saying, right?
Yes.
So I have a picture here
of Chelsea's leg
and the bruises
she wakes up with.
Yeah. She'll go to sleep
and there's nothing there.
and then, she wakes up and
there's bruises all over her.
Denise, tell Amy about
the nightmare she has.
She's been having
a recurring dream
of a murder of a family
and she sees this murder
over and over and over.
Interesting. Okay.
If people are coming
to her for help,
then she's most likely
a physical medium.
She probably has a lot
more people that show up,
that she's not aware of.
My god.
So this murdered girl
who comes to Chelsea,
did you get anything
on her in life?
She looked young,
between 25 and 35.
I got that her name
was Linda or Lily.
I saw her getting into a fight
with her boyfriend.
Then, two men grabbed her,
threw her in a car,
and they beat her
and they also
sexually assaulted her.
They had a knife.
They cut open her stomach,
slit her throat.
And then, they took her body
and they scattered it
all over the place.
This is a tiny town.
There's not that many murders.
They have one murder
that sounds similar.
Almost 50 years ago,
a young woman was murdered
only a couple miles from here.
You said her name
was Linda or Lily?
Well, the victim in this case,
her name was
Linda Jane Phillips
and she was 26 years old.
Her parents live
right down the road from here.
So, on August 8, 1970,
Linda went to a wedding
party in Dallas.
10:30 that night,
she called her parents,
said she was gonna spend
the night at a friend's house.
Linda never made it.
A day later,
they found her body,
totally stripped naked.
She had been sexually assaulted
and stabbed 26 times.
Now, I got
her death certificate.
You talked about the stomach?
She was stabbed
in the neck and abdomen.
The sheriff I talked to
gave me Linda's picture.
Now, do you think that's
who you might have seen?
Yes.
The other thing I saw
was an elderly male.
He's active in both houses.
I called him the lurker
because he's always behind you.
Like you're always feeling
someone's right there
and they're watching you.
He doesn't particularly
care to be seen,
but if he is,
it's more like a black shadow.
The most concerning things
is that he seemed to be attached
to someone
in the master bedroom
and it's almost like
he's obsessed.
And I saw him like sitting
on the side of the bed
and like just really lightly
caressing the person's face.
Chelsea has seen that.
She has woke up
and she has told me.
One night, she said,
"Mom, I saw someone
at the end of our bed"
and she said,
"I pretended to be asleep
because I did not want
to move."
Larry, you've seen
shadow figures as well.
The shadow figures
that I've seen is
more dark than translucent,
where you couldn't
hardly see through it.
Now, you said this guy
likes to touch
inappropriately?
Brittany, I want you to tell the
story about your sister Ashley.
Yeah. She was
asleep in her bed.
She had long
pajama pants on
and she woke up
and they were off of her
and she has no clue
how they came off of her.
Okay.
- When I spoke to her,
she broke down,
talking about it.
Now, is that this guy,
doing all this?
Yeah.
He would be the one.
He's being a little bit more
inappropriate than I thought.
Anything else?
I encountered
another deceased male.
I got that he did die
far away.
I got that he died
between 1990 and now.
I got that there was
a deep family connection
to a living person
in this house
and it felt like there was
kind of a cord,
an energetic cord,
that was wrapped around him.
So he's being dragged
back in unwillingly.
This means that
a living person here
is inadvertently trapping him
and they can't really let go
of him emotionally.
So we're talking about
a dead man with a connection
to a living person here,
died around 1990?
Yes.
- I hate to even bring this up,
but --
- My stepdad was murdered.
I mean, have you gotten
over it?
I've moved on, but,
they've never caught
his murderer, so,
it's been kinda hard.
I was afraid
this was gonna come up.
I think it's a really
difficult situation to be in
because you have an open murder
and you want justice for them
and that's something that,
unfortunately,
can sometimes keep them
kind of earthbound.
So how do I let him go?
Because I wouldn't
wish that for him.
So the thing I'm most concerned
about was the bedroom
at the end of the hall.
It was really bad.
I was only in there
for a few minutes.
One of
the interesting things
was that the dead
even refused to go in there.
That's Brittany's room.
It was physically painful.
Like pain in my ears,
head, headaches,
stomach, nausea.
She's always
had stomach problems.
I've always had nausea.
I also got depression in there,
a lot of sadness.
And the other thing I got
is that, when you're in there,
your brain is like
fully activated.
Like it's going 100 miles
a **** hour.
And, honestly, like
I couldn't even think straight.
I go through that
every single night.
I think about
everything and nothing
at the same time.
All this negative energy
has collected on the walls
of your room and formed
into this black goop.
And then, I saw it kind of
spilling out of that room
and going through the house.
This negative energy is coming
from a psychic empath.
So you're the psychic empath.
Everything that you feel, like
your emotions and stuff, you...
are having a hard time
keeping within you.
It's something that spills out
from you energetically.
It can create negative thoughts
and negative thought patterns
and it can cause
irrational behavior.
Well, talking about
irrational behavior,
I mean, he did get his leg
broke by your daughter
Ashley.
He did. Yes.
He was talking to her
and she didn't wanna hear
what he had to say
about her fianc.
- Okay.
- So she got up to leave
and he pushed her down
and she fought back
- Okay.
- and she broke his leg.
Wow.
It's like something
in this house
is trying to drive
all the men
out of the house,
so that they
can have their way
with the women.
And, you know,
me and Denise,
something came between us
and drew us apart.
Have you guys gone
for counseling?
- We did, for --
- Yes, we did.
- You did?
- We did, three times, and --
Three times?
Just three sessions?
- Just three sessions.
- Yes, three sessions.
What really made me quit
doing counseling was because
Larry had told me that,
regardless of what
I was gonna do, basically,
he was gonna keep on drinking
and I just knew.
I was like "I'm done."
26 years, down the tubes.
You are killing yourself,
plain and simple.
Your drinking
broke up the marriage
because she loves you
and she doesn't want you to die!
So, you need
to get help for that,
if you want your family back.
I mean, you worry about him.
Don't you?
Every day.
Man the **** up
and knock it **** off.
It's that simple.
The key is stop drinking,
take care of yourself,
because these people love you
and they don't want you
to be dead.
Is this black goop making
Larry's condition worse?
Yes.
Now, this gelatin thing
you described,
does it look that way
to you, or to everybody?
I had a sketch done of it.
My god.
You don't see it that way,
but you feel that way?
What exactly
is this thing?
It's emotions.
Her emotions?
Well, she collects emotions.
- So she's absorbing
everybody else's ****,
all their energy,
and it's led to this stuff
spilling out
all over the house?
Yes.
Aw, honey. It's okay.
So, Larry, you called us in
because you thought
the paranormal
broke up your marriage.
Well,
that's not the case.
But, turns out, it's a good
thing you did call us
'cause your kids are
under attack.
Now, to find out
what you can do about it,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
There's family issues and then,
there's paranormal issues,
which do go hand-in-hand,
oftentimes.
There are dead that are attached
to this location,
for one reason or another
and for them, let's go ahead
and move them on.
What I would like to see
happen is a medium come out
to move on the dead
that are attached
to this specific location.
What about
Denise's stepdad?
What I would like to see is
you have a medium reading
just for him.
- Okay.
The second thing is
for Brittany.
To prevent any more
of that stuff from forming
around you or in your
physical environment,
start journaling
every single night.
Well, the other thing is
for you to put these
in your bath.
It's a mixture of herbs
and crystals
and this is going to cleanse
away negative emotions,
the stuff that's accumulated.
So, for Chelsea,
at least one time a week,
she has to let the dead
come through, has to.
It's not fun, but, the dead
need to have access to her.
She's a medium and so,
she's gonna learn
setting appropriate
boundaries with them.
But if she doesn't do the once-
a- week thing with the dead,
they'll slam her,
and they'll slam her hard.
The last thing
that I wanted to say:
I would like the entire family
to go for family counseling.
Ev-er-y-one.
This is extremely important.
I think it'll lead you
on a very interesting path.
So, Larry,
I know you wanted us
to try to help your marriage,
with that, but,
we did help
your daughters out.
I mean, I can't blame
everything
on everybody else.
I gotta look at myself,
too, you know.
Did we ever get more
than I thought we would get.
We were just hoping
to not be crazy.
It's overwhelming,
but, at the same time,
I'm relieved.
The dead are causing
a lot of issues
for Larry and his family,
but I believe their problems go
much deeper than the paranormal.
With the help of a medium,
the dead will be set free
and, with the help
of counseling,
so will the living,
as this dark,
negative goop
will begin to dissipate.