You're in trouble,
big, big trouble.
Tell us
what we need to do
to make this safe
for my girls.
She's getting
bashed in the head.
It's turned out to be
the house of horrors.
They're living
here in danger?
Yes.
This is not good,
not good at all.
I just hear death.
My name is Amy Allan.
God.
It's like,
"I'm going to get you."
I see dead people.
Her face was all demonic.
I speak to dead people.
He's like, "You think you can
stop me? Because you can't."
And they speak to me.
What is he trying to do?
Kill them.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
Something happened.
Bam, bam, bam!
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
Am I seeing
what I think I'm seeing?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
They're everywhere.
It's my job to reveal them.
This guy's got the markings
of a serial killer.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end...
Is this dead guy
doing that to her?
...when we uncover
if it's safe for you to stay...
That's it.
...or time to get out.
Somebody's gonna die
over there soon, yeah.
I'm in the small town of Medina
between Rochester
and Buffalo, New York.
I got a call from a young
mom named Kelsey.
Now, she was sobbing
saying the dead
are going after her babies
and brainwashing her mom.
I'm not sure exactly what
the hell she meant by that.
But she sounded
so scared for her kids,
I had to take the case.
Before Amy arrives,
I sweep the house
from top to bottom
looking for
any leading information --
photographs, family heirlooms.
Even a baby's crib
can influence her findings.
So it's important that I cover
or remove them all.
When I'm done, the location
will be ready
for tonight's walk.
Boy.
This isn't good.
So there's, like, you know,
some dead people here who...
I think that maybe
they can ****
with living people.
And they're bad.
They're very bad.
And they want to do things
to living people.
I don't know why there's
so many **** dead
people in this house.
Maybe it was a hospital
or maybe it was
a crazy house at one time.
Maybe it was a boarding house.
And then, I hear there
are demons lurking.
So, Kelsey,
I'm glad I'm here because
when we spoke on the phone,
you sounded pretty upset.
What's going on
in this house?
My main concern
is my daughter Zoey.
Um, she's 3 years old.
She's seeing things.
She's afraid.
She won't go into
her room by herself.
And you have,
another child as well?
We have Lucy.
She's 2 months.
Two small kids.
Looks like it's
affecting you, too.
Yeah.
It's a daily struggle
just to keep the girls safe.
The girls
are my main concern.
And I have to stay
strong for them.
As far as activity goes,
give me a --
kind of a list
of what's happening.
There's been loud screams,
things moving,
shadow figures,
apparitions.
And now
it's gotten physical.
Okay. So how long have
you guys been here?
We've lived here
18 months.
Now, when I pulled up,
this place looked like a --
a huge factory.
Um,
how big is this place?
It's 6,200 square feet.
And it has 12 rooms.
Wow.
Now, do you know any history
about the house?
We just know that it used
to be an inn.
- And how old is it?
- It's about 200 years old.
So who exactly
lives here?
Myself,
my daughter Zoey,
my daughter Lucy,
my mom.
You mentioned on the phone
your mom's got some kind
of strange connection,
obsession with the house.
What's that all about?
She seems to be
really attached to it.
She doesn't seem to ever
want to leave the house.
- That's strange.
- Since we've lived here,
her health has just
declined rapidly.
Is she the only
one getting sick?
We're all exhausted
all the time.
We all are sick
It -- it feels like home.
But it feels like
we're sharing our home
with something nasty.
I don't even know
how anyone can stay here.
There are just so many dead.
I feel very dizzy.
Very sick,
horrible, horrible...
We can't focus.
I think that the living here
would experience
extreme sadness.
When I first walked in,
I literally wanted
to start crying,
extreme depression.
All right, Kelsey.
This is a pretty big room.
Why'd you bring me
in here?
Well, one night I was sitting
right outside that door.
All of a sudden,
I heard footsteps
walking towards the door.
And the door just slammed
right in my face.
And so you hear, like,
footsteps like this?
Yep.
Any doors and windows
open for ventilation
that this might've
slammed shut on its own?
No, this happened
just a few weeks ago,
when it was winter.
Like that?
Exactly.
That must've scared
the hell out of you.
Yeah.
Living people, they have
a problem with the doors.
The doorknob's always...
tch, tch, tch, always rattling.
And all I'm seeing is --
is, like,
the doors had blood on them.
There was blood
on the floor.
Something is trying
to get inside.
Anything else?
I looked up and saw
a woman walk
from our dining room
into our kitchen.
She was wearing
this long, white dress,
looked like from
a long time ago.
So did you go
into the kitchen
to see
what the hell it was?
The fear overcomes me.
And I just can't bring myself
to walk in and see.
Well, okay.
Anything else?
Um, one night, I was sitting
down here on the couch.
All of a sudden,
I heard this ear-piercing,
horrific scream
of a woman.
And it sounded like
she was being hurt.
That was what was
startling about it.
I'm hearing a woman screaming.
Is she trying to get in?
Or is she trying to get out?
They could see her, like,
as a full-body apparition.
What would they see?
Like a white dress
or something.
I guess maybe, like,
a nightgown.
Freaking out.
Her heart's pounding.
I think she was murdered.
So this is Zoey's room?
And the reason
I took the case,
um, what's going on
in here?
She would wake up,
start crying,
refuse to lay back down,
refuse to go back to sleep,
talking about shadow figures
and, mean men.
One day, Zoey had got away
from us and took off.
And we found her at the top
of the stairs
holding what looked
to be someone's hand.
My heart dropped.
I -- I stopped.
I froze.
It was one of
the more scary things
that have happened here
for me.
Okay. Anything else?
Um, yeah.
I will be walking up
the stairs,
walking past this room.
And I'll look
in the room.
And there'll be
a black shadow figure
standing right
in the window.
It's happened three times.
And I was literally
afraid for my life.
So could there be
somebody standing outside
and a car going by
with the lights
and it reflecting
in here?
No. It was very solid.
Looked like an actual man
was standing there.
What are you hoping
to get out of all this?
Answers.
Tell us
what we need to do
to make this safe
for my girls.
Okay.
This person's
in big trouble,
big, big trouble.
This is not good,
not good at all.
And I feel like
these dead people
are very focused on this person.
Violent, very violent...
...anger, hatred,
being surrounded by these
very bad dead people.
And the only reason why they
would be focused on this person
is because they think
they can make
this person kill yourself
or kill everybody.
This living person is in danger.
So I was talking to Kelsey,
and she basically said
that you're kind of
obsessed with the house.
I guess that's fair.
I knew
three steps in the door
that this
is where we should be.
It's turned out to be,
at times,
the house of horrors.
I understand you've been having
some health issues, too.
I had to have
two back surgeries
and a hip surgery.
And I just can't seem
to heal here.
Have you had experiences
living here?
Yes. I've had experiences
with the walk-in closet.
I thought to myself,
"Maybe this is some
kind of a portal."
You hear
a woman screaming.
I mean, guttural,
painful screams
come out of that closet.
Well, how the hell
do you sleep in here?
I don't sleep in here.
I sleep in what
would be Zoey's room.
I started sleeping
in there,
thinking I would get
a better night's sleep.
But it has not worked
out that way at all.
Why not?
I'm having
these horrific nightmares.
Okay, what
kind of nightmares?
Every single dream,
it has to do with somebody
in this house
who is in peril.
What do you think
is going on here?
It's like this house
is,
a paranormal highway.
The living person
in this room gets sick a lot.
There is a Satanic vortex
that's in their closet.
Everything in this room
that happens is due
to this **** closet
and this ****
vortex in there.
I think that they would
see things in there.
Like what?
I don't know,
maybe having dreams.
Lots of stress.
I see somebody, like,
crying so much
they puke kind of thing.
So scared, so scared,
crying and crying and crying.
So anything else?
The most significant
and the most
frightening experience
that I've had here
so far has to be
walking over to the window
and looking out.
And there were, like,
8 or 10 shadow figures.
They were shaped
like a human form.
But they were solid black.
And they were just
staring right at the house.
And just one by one,
they turned around
and walked down
towards the river.
It terrified me.
You sure these were
shadow people
and not a bunch of people
that were dressed in black?
No. No, there's a street
light out there.
And it was lit up.
And you could see they were
this solid black forms.
They weren't people.
No.
It's like you're
constantly anticipating
what might happen next.
And it's really difficult
to live like that.
It takes its toll
on everybody.
There's not a lot of life left
in this house anymore.
I just saw, like, a really tall,
dark shadow man.
And he just walked
straight right back
and right into there.
He was **** tall, too,
'cause he must've been
right up on that tree there.
He says that there's more.
So those shadowed...things,
they've been here
for a long, long time.
I think that living people
would see them.
But it doesn't seem like
they're much interested in them.
Any idea how the living
would see them?
Like human-shaped shadow people.
Are the living here
in danger from them?
I can't say 100%
that they're safe.
Okay, Cindy,
why'd you bring me over here?
I was walking down
this set of stairs.
I got probably six
or eight stairs from the bottom.
And it felt like somebody
took their arm
and just swooshed
and knocked my knees out
from underneath me.
And I flew and hit hard.
- All right.
So when I came up these steps,
these seemed pretty sturdy.
They are.
- You could've got killed.
- It's possible.
And you're still
in this house?
And you're gonna say
you're not obsessed by it?
I don't want to leave it.
Okay.
There's a man.
I think it's a man.
But he sounds inhuman.
He doesn't want us here.
He grabbed my wrist and, like,
pinched it between
the bones, you know?
It, like,
almost felt like a ice pick.
And then, he was grabbing
my neck here like,
you know, this,
my shoulder,
and then my jaw.
He is very physical.
As far as being able
to touch people.
And then, I saw somebody
get shoved,
a living person, a female,
get shoved from behind.
So he's somebody
I would worry about.
I think it's dangerous.
I feel like he's, like,
trying to attach to me.
My God.
**** Get off of me!
So I made some calls,
and Kelsey's right.
The house is almost 200 years
old and used to be an inn.
I'm heading back there
to meet a local historian
who says the guy that built it
had such a tragic time there,
he probably wishes
he never laid his eyes
on it in the first place.
Sounds like my clients
were right.
This place was built
about 200 years ago.
Very close.
We found, um, that the house
was actually constructed
around 1837.
It's regarded as one
of the largest cobblestone
buildings
in North America.
She also mentioned
that it might've been an inn.
Yes, that is correct.
It was an inn.
Um, and it was there to cater
to the stagecoach traffic
that was traveling from Buffalo
to Rochester at the time.
And we actually have
a photograph here
from 1870
that shows, um,
what it would've looked like
from that time period.
And this picture makes it
a lot more bustling
than it is today.
- Absolutely.
- What do we know about the guy
that built this monster
of a house?
The inn was constructed
by Zachariah Spencer.
He was a wealthy farmer
from Connecticut.
So you mentioned
on the phone
that he's probably
even sorry
he set eyes on this location.
Why was that?
Yes, um, he turns the business
over eventually
to his son Henry,
um, in 1843.
Henry was about 28 years old
at the time.
And at that point in time,
he is a loner.
Um, he's not married.
And he has no --
no children to speak of.
That's kind of strange
for that time period.
Isn't it?
- Yes.
Okay. So now,
Henry's got the business.
What happens?
Um, from the best we can tell,
he runs it quite well.
And then, two years later,
he kills himself.
Okay, and how do
we know that?
We do have
a deed transfer
that reverts the property
back to Zachariah
that says, um,
Henry died at his own device.
- All right.
Could we assume he committed
suicide on the property?
Yes.
Now that Zachariah's
got the property
and the business back,
does he run it again?
Or does he sell it?
This time, he transitioned
the business to his other sons,
Burrall
and Samuel Spencer.
All right.
So how'd these guys do?
Um, they overextended
themselves.
And eventually ran
the business bankrupt.
Burrall started,
forging checks
about to
the extent of $270,000
at that point in time.
What are we talking about today?
What would that be?
By today's standards
of about $6 million.
Wow. Okay.
So this poor guy, Zachariah,
comes over, successful guy.
He's got all these kids.
One kid, Henry, who's 28
and winds up killing himself.
Yes.
And then,
the other two knuckleheads
wind up running the business
into the ground.
- Yes.
- All right.
There's, like, two guys.
It feels like
older teens maybe.
And they're bad.
They're very bad.
I don't like these guys.
I don't know
if they're human.
They might be
pretending to be human.
Like, I don't know
if they're really dead kids
or if they're demons.
And they're, like, talking about
Satanism and ****
Them, you got to
bargain with them.
Like, if you agree
for them to do something,
then you're gonna ****
pay a price.
That's all I know.
What sort of things
will he do?
They can scare them.
They can harm them,
cause accidents,
cause accidents
where people die.
And I think also that they
influence the living very much.
And I think that they could
influence a living person
into harming themselves
or somebody else.
It's not a good situation.
If you need us
to investigate
unexplained activity
in your home,
go to "The Dead Files"
page at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help me, Dead Files!"
to submit your story.
And we'll help if we can.
So far, I've got
a family worried sick
over their children's safety
on a property
where a former owner
committed suicide.
But I need to see
if there's anything else.
Searching through old records,
I find a disturbing
article about a local farmhand
who murdered a 13-year-old girl
right next to
my client's property.
Now, for some reason,
the local cops
won't talk to me
about this case.
So I reached out
to a local author
who says this was one
of the most gruesome crimes
in the town's history.
Were you able to find out
anything about this farmhand
that killed
this 13-year-old girl?
Yes, the man we're talking
about is Eugene Emory.
He was a farmhand
local to the area.
And there's no known
photograph of him,
but we did find
a sketch of him.
Okay.
He was described
as 5'8", clean-shaven.
You have any idea how old he
might've been in this sketch?
Yes, at the time that sketch
was done, 40 years old.
40, okay.
This guy have
any priors?
Not really.
But farmers in the area
had said that he liked
the young girls.
Okay, so do we know when
he starts working for the people
that live next door
to my client's property?
He started working
for the Grimes family in 1888.
Immediately was attracted
to their daughter, Cora,
then about 12 years old.
What do we know
about her?
Described as
a very pretty girl --
brunette with curly hair,
brown eyes.
Supposedly, quite
a brilliant girl.
He was actually
trying to court her.
And they had been
seen out in the area
in the horse
and carriage.
He had brought her
a few little gifts.
And the family knew
about all this?
Well, they did.
I don't think, at first,
they realized
it was that serious.
I, feel weak,
real weak.
Really, really,
really, really,
really weak.
Hard to walk.
I'm seeing the panicky girl
who was murdered again.
And she's starting
to show me flashes
of who she was
and what happened to her.
She has dark brown hair,
white nightie,
hourglass figure,
about 5'2", no shoes.
It's warm, hot even,
sticky hot.
Something's wrong here.
My God.
Take me to the murder.
What happened?
Well, on June 24, 1889,
summer evening,
Cora's parents
leave the premises.
Okay.
Well, Cora and Eugene
were having a discussion.
And she's trying
to let him know
that their relationship
isn't gonna go forward.
And he's not liking this.
She's trying to make it
clear to him
that she thinks there's
too big an age difference.
And he's not
the boss of her.
She leaves to go
into the house.
But in doing so,
she turns her --
her back on him.
He picks up a piece of firewood.
Using it like a club,
he bashes her in the head.
That first blow
probably killed her.
But he strikes her
two more times.
She's getting bashed
in the head.
Like, I'm just seeing
her head explode.
And I'm seeing, like,
brain and hair.
Something about
the evil that men do.
I don't know who this is.
They're in me.
That **** hurts.
- Who's jumping you?
A chick who's being murdered.
****
Get out.
All right.
So now what happens?
Well, Emory takes off
through the woods.
And the men form a posse.
He sees 'em in the night
with their lanterns.
And he knows they're
in pursuit of him.
He turns himself in,
confesses to the sheriff
that he loved this girl.
He's weepy.
He's sobbing.
But he doesn't know
why he did it.
This was big news
at the time.
What happened at trial?
They do convict him
of second-degree murder.
And he's sentenced
to life imprisonment.
He ended up
dying in prison
of natural causes,
kidney failure,
after serving
almost 13 years.
I saw several disturbing
things on my walk.
But what has me the most
concerned are the dead
coming out of the vortex
in the closet
and then surrounding
a living person in bed.
There's dead people everywhere.
There was a man on the left.
And he's in his early 60s.
Then there's a lady.
And she's tiny.
She's probably, like, 5'2".
And then, at the end of the bed,
just completely black.
Amy,
is this what you saw?
Yes, that's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients
for the first time.
Now, Amy, this is Kelsey.
And this is her mom, Cindy.
It's like these ladies are
in a dysfunctional relationship
with this house.
And what I mean by that
is it tortures them
physically and emotionally.
But they're drawn to it like
they're obsessed with it.
But there's a reason Kelsey
called us in.
This is her 3-year-old
daughter, Zoey,
and Lucy, who's a newborn.
Kelsey's convinced that the dead
here are picking on Zoey.
And she is not sure if
it's safe for them to be here.
Now that Amy knows just
a little bit about you guys,
I'm gonna ask her
to describe her walk for us.
Something
about this location
is that there were
a lot of dead people here.
And I could not
figure out why.
I was speculating maybe
it was an asylum or a hospital.
Maybe it was
a boarding house.
So I was extremely confused
as to why there were all
these random dead people here.
Some of them can
affect the living
because I felt a lot of
depression and anxiety.
Obviously, the house
is really old.
Um, a lot of people
have been through here.
It was built in 1837.
Originally, it was an inn.
We actually have a photograph
of your place from 1870.
Geez, it looks
about the same.
- Yeah, there's nothing...
- That's crazy.
Not much has changed.
Now, as far
as depression goes,
tell Amy about that.
Since moving in here,
I think we all are
drained and tired.
And I think our attitudes
are different.
Yeah.
I mean, there...
I am always on edge, always.
If it wasn't for Zoey,
there would be no life
in this house.
So I was outside.
And I saw this thing,
this really super-tall
dark shadow man, like,
probably 30 feet tall
just glide,
like, across the yard
and then went
into the basement.
And I saw just
all these shadow people.
They were
kind of human size.
I think that the living
might be able to see them.
And they
didn't honestly seem
at all interested
in living people.
But you never know,
that could change.
Well, Cindy's seen them outside.
There were, like, 8 to 10
just solid black mass figures
facing the house.
And one by one,
they just turned around
and walked right back down
to the river.
Scared me half to death.
I saw them three times.
Um, each time, it was when
I was walking past
Zoey's room.
The third time, I got angry
and just stared at it.
And that thing
didn't back down from me.
It kept staring.
Finally, I just got so scared,
I walked away.
So what else?
Then I went into
the master bedroom.
- That's Cindy's room.
- Okay.
And I saw
somebody crying.
And they were scared
and hysterical,
under a ton of stress.
Yeah. I've shed my fair share
of tears here
and just been moments
of just true despair.
I also got that
the individual there,
does get sick a lot.
And that person sees
a lot of strange things.
Um, and the reason
why is because
when I went
into the closet,
I saw this
dark, black hole.
I really got evil
from it.
And I said that it was
the Satanic vortex.
I hate that closet.
I hear women screaming.
And it sounds like
it's coming from that closet.
Tell her about
your illnesses as well.
I've had several back surgeries
and a hip surgery.
I have had maybe six or eight
other procedures
since we've been here.
- What?
- I just can't heal.
I'm just exhausted
and anxious and depressed.
And I'm just fighting
to get my life back
after these injuries.
But at the same time, you don't
want to give up the house.
I love this house.
I got three steps in.
And I knew that we were
supposed to be here.
Interesting.
In the master bedroom,
I also saw a person
in the bed terrified.
You talking 'bout Cindy?
Yes.
There were all
of these dead people,
that were kind of
around the bed.
So what did this look
like to you?
I had a sketch done.
I don't know
if I want to even open this up.
There you go.
My God.
Wow.
Well, that's awful.
Knowing that they're
targeting my mom,
I mean, I just get angry.
It's overwhelming.
Did you see anything else?
Yes.
I met a dead male that is
very active in this house.
And he is
a serious problem.
He grabbed my arm
and was pinching
through both of the bones.
And it felt like an ice pick
going right through there.
He absolutely did
not want me here.
And I felt he could do
physical harm
to living people --
pushing, shoving,
hitting them.
And I think
he could be dangerous.
Well, dangerous is
an understatement.
You could've been killed.
I was coming down
the stairway.
All of a sudden, it felt like
somebody took their arm
and just knocked my legs
right up from underneath me.
And I went down,
I mean, hard.
Does that sound like this --
this scum bag would do that?
Yeah.
All right.
So did you get anything
on this guy when he was alive?
I saw
he was a white male.
I think he was
in maybe his 40s.
The other thing that I got
was that he had murdered
a woman.
I saw her briefly.
And she was
in a complete panic.
She was screaming.
She was wearing
a white dress,
dark hair,
she looked young.
She was petite.
And she wasn't
wearing any shoes.
And it was hot
and sticky.
Then I saw that she was
bashed in the head.
And then
her head exploded.
And I just saw the brain
and hair
and everything
just go,
Then I walked
in the kitchen.
And she jumped
into my body.
The pain was
absolutely excruciating.
In the last 120 years,
there's only been three women
that have been murdered
in this town.
One of them was right next door.
And it happened in 1889.
The victim was
a 13-year-old girl
named, Cora Grimes.
And she was a beautiful girl,
dark hair, dark eyes.
Now, the year before
she was murdered,
the parents had hired
a farmhand named Eugene Emory.
The guy became
obsessed with her.
The guy was basically
a pedophile.
She's 13. He's 39.
You said the murder
probably happened
when it was sticky and hot?
Well, the murder took place
on June 24, 1889,
so the hot time of the year.
Now, Cora's parents
left for a bit.
Emory approached Cora
and professed his love to her.
She said to him,
"You're too old for me,"
and turned her back on him.
And this guy went into a rage.
He picked up
a club-sized piece of firewood
and took a shot at her head
and cracked her skull open.
He wound up turning himself in.
And, he ended up confessing.
He basically said
he lost his mind over the girl
and can't explain
why he killed her.
Um, he ended up getting a life
sentence and dying in prison.
Now, we don't have
a photo of him.
But I did track down the sketch
somebody did in the courtroom.
Um, I mean, it's a sketch,
but...
...is it possible that's
the guy you might've seen?
I don't know.
Possible.
It's hard to tell
from that picture.
But the case
sounds very similar.
Everybody just says
I look so young,
which is still creeping me out
that he's in this house.
Anything else?
When I went into
the living room,
I saw
two teenage males.
They're a big problem.
They're here.
And I keep going back
and forth on, like,
are they really these kids
or are they demons?
Their little mission
is to create this havoc --
torture people,
scare people.
And they can influence
the living
to harm themselves
or others.
How would they get here?
The freaking vortex.
Now, you had mentioned
that they can cause people
to harm themselves and others.
There was a suicide on the
property you should know about.
This place was built by a guy
named Zachariah Spencer.
Come 1843,
Zachariah turned his whole
business over to his son Henry.
Two years after taking
over the business, 1845,
Henry killed himself
right on the property here.
Boy.
I don't even want to ask her
if there's anything else.
But did you see anything else?
The room that I am
extremely nervous about
is the blue room.
Which is Zoey's room.
Now, you sleep in Zoey's room?
Yeah.
I don't sleep in the master
bedroom anymore.
So does Zoey sleep
in there with you?
- No.
- She never did.
Got it. Okay.
Interesting.
The individual that
sleeps in that room
is someone who is
in grave danger.
Those specific dead
are very focused
on that living person.
So what the hell
do they want from Cindy?
You've been subject
to that room
where that horrible
vortex thing is.
And they followed you.
I think that they are
trying to possess you.
I mean, they can jump you
and mold you into a killer.
My gosh.
They're probably
trying to get you
as close to death
as possible
'cause that would be
the easiest,
time for them.
That's scary.
Goodness.
I wasn't expecting that.
So, Kelsey,
you called us in
'cause you're worried
about your kids.
But it turns out,
your mother's
the one that's in danger.
To see if there's any way
you guys can stay here safely,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
It just isn't
the right place.
My goodness.
And I think, honestly,
as quickly as possible,
you need to get out
of the house.
And once you leave,
you then also need
to go for an exorcism.
Once that's done,
all the attachments will go away
so there'll be no more desire
to return
and things like that.
As far as this location,
I don't think anyone alive
should live here.
Kind of figured
something like that
was gonna be
what the outcome was.
Well, I wasn't.
I love this house.
You might feel differently
once you're away
for a few months
after you have
your exorcism.
If she gets the exorcism
done right...
...do you think she'll start
to heal a little bit better?
Yeah.
Once you leave the location
and you have the exorcism,
I think you'll see
a dramatic change --
your emotional state,
your mental state,
your physical state.
And if they stay?
I just...
That's just not
an option to me.
I'm sorry.
But it's just not.
Um, absolutely would
not recommend that.
Well, I'm a little concerned
about you, though.
I know what she's saying
that you need to do.
But I'm wondering
if you're like,
"I'm not giving up this house."
No, I'm going.
No ifs,
ands or buts about it.
- Okay.
- Yep.
Yeah.
This is so much bigger
than what I thought.
No house is worth this.
- No.
I just didn't realize how
big of a nightmare we were in.
The only way Cindy and
Kelsey can save their family
is to move as far away
as possible.
If they do that and get
an exorcism for Cindy,
all of the attachments
to the dead will be broken.
And they can begin to lead
a peaceful life.