I don't feel okay here.
I feel like I wanna run.
We've had customers
walk in the door
and stop dead
in their tracks.
Those things are here.
I saw several dead people
standing amongst the diners.
To me, they feel like a threat.
I am extremely creeped out.
I just hear death.
My name is Amy Allan.
God.
It's like,
"I'm going to get you."
I see dead people.
Her face was all demonic.
I speak to dead people.
He's like, "You think you can
stop me? Because you can't."
And they speak to me.
What is he trying to do?
Kill them.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
Something happened.
Bam, bam, bam!
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
Am I seeing
what I think I'm seeing?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
They're everywhere.
It's my job to reveal them.
This guy's got the markings
of a serial killer.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end...
Is this dead guy
doing that to her?
...when we uncover
if it's safe for you to stay...
That's it.
...or time to get out.
Somebody's gonna die
over there soon, yeah.
I'm in Sedona, Arizona,
about 2 hours from Phoenix.
We got called in
by a guy named Joe.
Now, he moved out here
from the East Coast
and opened up a restaurant
to live the good life.
Problem is,
the activity's so bad,
his employees and customers
are scared to death.
And he says, if we can't fix it,
he may lose
his entire life savings.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area of anything
that might influence
her findings.
This is a large space
with a lot of historical items
and signs that need
to be covered.
When I'm finished,
the location'll be ready
for tonight's walk.
Agh, I really
don't like it here.
I feel really, really,
very sick.
A lot of anxiety.
And stress.
I think that, if the living
spent enough time here,
you know, they would
develop things like ulcers
or stomach problems.
I'm getting feelings
of being abandoned, unwanted.
I don't feel very good here.
So, Joe, when we spoke
on the phone,
you sounded really
concerned about things.
What's goin' on?
Well, there's been
a lot of reports,
by both my employees
and customers,
of things happening here
in the restaurant.
Okay, so that's costin'
you business.
It is, indeed,
but the most important
concern, in my mind, is
the safety of my guests,
my customers,
and my employees.
Okay. How long have you
owned the building?
13 years.
Okay. When did you start
havin' experiences?
I haven't had
any experiences.
I haven't had any
experiences here,
or anywhere else
in my life.
Okay. Not to be rude,
but what the hell
am I doin' here, then?
I believe
it's really happening.
I certainly
did not believe it
in the beginning,
as a skeptic,
but we've had customers
walk in the door
and stop dead
in their tracks.
These are real people
- Right.
that are having
genuine experiences.
All right. Joe, I know
you've had no experiences,
but what's been
reported to you?
Things moving
on their own.
Shadow figures
in different forms.
Full-body apparitions.
And also
mood changes.
With all this concern
you have,
why don't you just
sell the place?
I'm too invested
in the place.
It's a gorgeous
building.
I've put many years
in improving it
and in restoring it.
Let me show you a photo
of what the facility
used to look like.
So, Joe, this must've
cost a pretty penny,
for you to restore all this.
It did. It cost me
my life savings.
Okay.
Sometimes, my partner,
she'll tell a client that
it's not safe to stay here.
How would you take
that information?
I don't know how
I would deal with that.
That would be
devastating news for me.
A lot of the things that
are here are not welcoming.
Everything in this room,
I despise.
I don't like the flooring.
I don't like this bar.
It adds too much chaos
to the environment.
There's not many places where
you can go here and feel okay.
I think that, for people
who are slightly sensitive,
to be here would be
a **** nightmare.
I don't think they would last
too long, honestly.
I think it would be
a real struggle.
I think they would see
a lot of stuff all the time.
I think they would feel
physically horrendous.
I don't wanna ****
be here right now.
I- I don't feel okay
here.
I feel like I wanna run.
So, Karyn, I was talkin' to Joe
and he was tellin' me
that you guys are partners
and he's concerned
for the employees,
as well as the customers
that come here.
You agree with him?
Yes, I do agree with him.
My concern is that,
customers and employees,
that they are not
fearful to be here
and/or in
any type of danger.
So I know Joe's never
had an experience before.
What about you?
Well, I did have one
back here,
with one of my cooks.
Okay.
- And a cup like this
flew off
of that middle shelf
toward us,
at the steam table.
It bounced off
and broke on the floor.
And nobody else was
in the kitchen at the time?
- No.
- And nothin's gonna fall
and fly all the way across,
at least 5-, 6-, 7-feet span.
No. Not with the laws
of physics.
Doesn't work that way.
Well, it sounds like you had
a close call back here.
That coulda been a knife
and you could've been
seriously hurt.
Boy.
There's so many accidents here.
It's abnormal.
It's not normal.
It's freaking people out.
People falling down, burn.
You know, stupid ****
that's so constant,
over and over and over again.
Yeah, it's bad. You know,
it's not good, you know?
It's a lot, a lot.
So, have you had
any other experiences?
Yes, I did, in the front
fine-dining room.
Something brushed up
against the back of me.
Did you get the sense it
might've been a man or a woman?
No. I didn't get a sense
of an actual gender.
I felt like it --
it was almost
as if it was just
checking me out.
All right, was the door open,
like maybe the wind?
Nothing.
No staff. No one.
what are you hopin' to get
outta this investigation?
- I'm concerned for
the customers
and employees.
I want them
to feel safe.
We really want you guys
to figure out
what it is that's here
and get rid of it.
What is that?
There's a dog.
But it's not a good dog.
It's a bad dog!
And I hear this is what they
need to be concerned about.
They all feel things
brushing against them.
This is this animal.
It causes bad things to happen.
Is it what's doin'
the stuff in here?
Yes.
I do think it's a possibility
that, other than just
causing accidents
for living people here,
I think that,
if the living have
some kind of interaction
with the dog,
they are possibly,
somehow, marked.
To die.
So, Deborah, I understand that
you're the office manager here.
Yes. And I'm a healer,
a psychic, and a medium.
Have you had
any experiences?
Well, we had
a stretch of time here
where people
were argumentative,
irritable, depressed.
How do you know
that this just wasn't
employees bein'
in a bad mood?
Well, it went on for
such an extended period
and seemed to involve
so many different people,
even people
who are normally,
you know, even-keeled.
Whether that's paranormal
or not, I don't know.
Anything else?
Yes, actually.
I was walking through
the front dining room
Okay.
- and I saw a man sitting
at a table.
I turned back around
to introduce myself
and there was
no one there.
Can you describe him for me?
A little bit tall.
The hair
was a little long,
parted in the middle,
with wings.
I could feel
his intense ownership,
like he was looking
over the place
or taking care of it.
Okay. So now, if you saw
a sketch or a photo,
would you be able
to identify him?
Well, yes.
I already have.
And, actually the
photograph's over there.
Who is this guy?
He's Henry Frank Gibson,
the former owner.
That photo
is the guy you saw?
Yes. And I had not
seen that photograph
until several days after
I had seen the apparition.
I'm seeing this larger male.
He's in his 50s.
His hair, a little longer,
a little.
It feels like he had a lot
to do with this place.
Feels like a...owner.
Something weird is going on
with the dead here.
There just seems to be an issue
with the dead finding rest
in this specific area.
The living are sensitive
and they will feel their deaths
and they might not understand
what they're feeling.
They would feel the sense
of dying, the dying process.
I think they would also feel
fear and sadness and anxious.
So, Jane, I understand
that you work here.
Yeah, for 5 years.
Any experiences
you could tell me about?
Well, yes.
When I was hosting,
I sat four lovely ladies
at this very table
and then I went
to the kitchen
and came back and there
were only three,
so I said, "Shall I wait
for the fourth one?"
and they said, "No.
There's only three
of us here."
You sure that a fourth person
didn't come in right behind 'em
and they were just
a single customer?
I knew. I knew
there were four ladies.
All right. So anything else?
Entering the bar,
one night,
an enormous, pitch-black,
triangular cape
came flyin' at me from
the uppermost ceiling,
down, straight at me,
to the point where
I physically jumped.
And then it was gone.
Did it look like it was
intentionally going at you?
It did, sir,
and it was frightening.
There are a group of beings
out here
and they are like smoke.
They're not solid.
You can see through them.
And their eyes are lights.
They made me feel uncomfortable.
What?
Just those things are here.
- The smoky things?
- Yeah.
How many of these
things are there?
Four or five,
I'm thinkin'.
Do you know what
these things are?
I'm leaning towards
some kind of elementals.
Elementals are entities
created by nature.
They are not
necessarily dangerous.
But these are.
To me, they feel
like a threat.
Heather, I understand
that you used to work here.
Yes, I did.
I was a hostess, server.
So, I assume you've had
experiences, then.
Yes.
- Okay. Can you take me
through some of 'em?
I did feel some anxiety,
just a tightness,
being in here.
I can hear and feel
energies around me.
I'm very sensitive
if there's another being,
apparition, or energy.
Okay.
So, anything else?
I was in the bar area,
carrying trays,
and telling a gentlemen,
"Excuse me,"
standing in my way,
wearing a plaid shirt.
And I look.
There's nobody there.
Okay. So can you
describe that person?
Gruffy,
rough-looking, dirty.
Have you seen him again
since that time?
Yes.
In the kitchen area.
I don't know,
'cause it's being New Age,
or this is a woo-woo
type of town,
but everybody seems to take
what's goin' on here kinda
"We got ghosts, they throw
things, no big deal."
This is what
goes on here.
Okay.
So, anything else?
When I would go and serve
in the dining room,
I saw several
dead people
standing
amongst the diners.
How many people
you talkin'?
5 to 12.
How many times
has this happened?
A few times, serving
in the dining room.
I would almost
drop my tray,
trying to move
around someone,
thinking
that they're there,
and then, all of a sudden,
they're gone.
I- It made me
pretty uncomfortable,
to encounter
something like that.
I am extremely
creeped out.
What's happening?
Anybody who's died here
is set up like mannequins.
There's people
in these chairs.
But they're dead.
It looks like their
physical bodies are here
and their soul is stuck
in their physical body
and they've been like
propped up like mannequins.
They can't talk or move.
I think the living
would maybe see this.
This is
cree-ee-py.
I don't like it.
Joe didn't know much history
about his restaurant,
so I made some calls
and, it turns out, a guy
named George Nelson got shot
and ended up dyin' in his
parking lot back in 1957.
I managed to track down
the victim's nephew,
who says, even though
this is still an open case,
he's got his own theory
about what actually happened.
So, Dan, before we get
to your uncle's tragic death,
what can you
tell me about him?
Here's a picture of him,
probably from when
he was a senior
in high school.
He was just friendly,
nice.
Not an enemy
in the world.
All right, Dan,
so, if you can,
take me through the night
of the murder. What happened?
It happened
May 25, 1957,
by the bar that
you're investigating.
Rainbow's End was what
it was called back then.
My uncle was with a couple
of his friends,
a couple of his buddies,
then there was
two younger girls
that they had picked up.
They all piled
in the car.
My uncle was in the
passenger seat up front.
Okay.
- And one of his friends
was driving and then
the other guy was
in the backseat,
between the two girls.
One thing you should know
is the friend
who was driving
was married
and the guy who was in the
back had a girlfriend.
They'd just left
Rainbow's End
and they passed by a car
that was sittin' on the
side of the road.
All of a sudden,
the car pulls up bes--
behind 'em,
started following.
George turned around
to the guy in the backseat
and said,
"You'd better duck down,
'cause your girlfriend's
followin' us."
So your uncle
recognized the car?
Yes. All of a sudden,
boom! Gunshot.
The back window shattered.
It hit my uncle in the head.
There's brains everywhere,
total chaos.
Witnesses told me that
they saw my uncle
"gurgling" on the
floorboards of the car,
so, even though his brains
were blown apart,
he was still alive.
You know, his body
was still alive.
He was breathing.
And they turned around
and went back
to Rainbow's End,
but, by then, it was
too late. He was dead.
I have a copy of
my uncle's death
certificate right here.
So do you think
this girl intended
to kill somebody
in that car?
I think she was actually
just trying to scare them
and my uncle died
because of it.
So, officially,
George Nelson's murder
is unsolved, to this day.
There's some kind of
gunfight.
I feel like somebody
got shot with a shotgun.
It's a guy and he's young.
It takes him a while to die.
It hurts.
It horribly hurts.
It hurts so **** bad.
So far, I've got
a restaurant owner scared
for the safety of his employees
and guests, on a property
where a man died of a gunshot
wound to the head.
But I wanna see
if there's anything else.
Searchin' through old records,
I find an article
about a local man
who died in 2006.
Turns out, he was run over
by a car
right outside
my client's property.
I'm on my way to meet
with the county sheriff,
who says the victim used to be
a regular at Joe's restaurant.
So, this guy that got killed
right outside
my client's restaurant,
did you find out
anything about him?
Actually, I have a photo
of him right here.
Randy Lee Austin.
54 years old.
He was kind of a drifter.
Came to Sedona in 2005.
He would spend
a lot of time at Relics.
What about the day of his death?
What happened?
April 4, 2006,
he went to Relics,
spent some time there
at your client's
establishment.
Okay.
- And, as it got dark,
he left the bar.
A couple witnesses
had seem him
crossing the street.
Another witness said
he saw him gettin' down,
actually just laying down,
facedown, on the street,
when an oncoming car
skidded right over
the top of him,
killing him instantly.
Here is a copy
of the obituary
in the newspaper.
Why would he be laying down
on the road, though?
Well, he was
an alcoholic.
I'm getting another death here.
There's something
about a car accident.
Somebody **** up
their back, bad.
So **** bad.
My God.
I think the dog foretells
accidents and stuff,
that it likes to do that.
I think that, if the living
encounter the dog,
in some fashion,
like it could be
like a harbinger
of death.
If the living see
or hear this dog,
it means they're
going to die soon.
But it doesn't mean
they're gonna die here,
like the car accident thing.
But it seems like some people
who start their dying process
here or who die here,
you're either stuck
in your death state
or you're like turned
into a mannequin.
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity
in your home,
go to the "Dead Files" page
at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help me,
Dead Files!"
to submit your story
and we'll help if we can.
You could pretty much
throw a dart
at a map of the U.S.
and you'll hit a spot
where the Native Americans
got the shaft.
It's no different here.
I'm on my way to meet
with an author who's going to
tell me about what the locals
call The Removal.
So, Melissa, thanks for
helpin' me out with this case.
Before we get to The Removal,
who were the
Native Americans here?
Okay, there were two
basic tribes in the area.
They were the Yavapai
and the Apache
and they both came in
about the same time,
about the mid-1400s.
After the Civil War,
late 1860s,
people started pushing West,
so, first, the miners
came in, looking
for gold and silver,
and then, right after them
came white settlers.
Okay. So how'd that go?
Well, it didn't go
very well.
There were minor clashes
here and there,
until 1872 and the
Skeleton Cave Massacre.
Okay, so what happened there?
The soldiers were told
to round up
all the Yavapai
and Apache
and bring them
to the new reservation.
They heard that
there were some Apache
held up in a cave.
They went to get them
and they fought back.
How many did they kill?
Well, they killed
75 Indians
and they captured
probably 30.
That's brutal.
That was brutal.
As a matter of fact,
this picture is
of the cave in 1908.
So these bones were there
this whole time?
They were there
the whole time.
And, of course,
a lot of the bones
were scattered
by wild animals.
So the next plan,
in 1875,
was to march them
180 miles south to the
San Carlos reservation,
close to Phoenix.
For whatever reason,
they decided to do this
in February.
1,500 people
started the march
and hundreds died
along the way.
I'm curious 'cause,
Native Americans,
the way they bury people
is pretty sacred.
What happened with the dead
along the trail?
They were not allowed
to stop and take care
of the dead.
They were forced
to just leave the dead,
or probably
sick or injured,
where they lay
and just keep marching.
That's pretty nasty.
It is, yeah. And,
unfortunately, the whites
didn't have much empathy
for the Indians, you know?
They had trouble
seeing them as "human."
A Native American
came up to me.
I'm feeling
a lot of people,
being disturbed.
They're not
being able to rest.
This isn't right.
This is wrong.
They're very unhappy.
They're very sad.
There's a lot of crying.
Do you know what happened
to the dead here?
It was over a period of time
and they were happy, dead,
and then something happened
and they woke up
and then they were disturbed
and they're unhappy and crying.
Do you have any idea
of when this happened?
It was dirt.
Long time ago.
There's so much illness
and mental anguish.
I'm feeling a lot of panic
back here, a lot of chaos.
I feel like the living
who are here a lot,
they could form disorders.
And I mean like
full-on disorders,
like general-anxiety disorders.
Severe stomach issues
would develop.
Esophagus issues would develop.
This is bad.
I saw several disturbing
things on my walk,
but the dead people
propped up like mannequins
in the dining room
had me the most concerned.
It's dark
and they can't move.
They're trapped
inside their bodies?
And their eyes were
very scary to me.
They were extremely intense.
Is this what you saw?
Yes, that's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients
for the first time.
So, Amy,
I want you to meet Joe.
You wanna know how many
experiences he's had?
Zero. None.
Reason he's called us in is
because of people like Deborah,
who's his office manager;
and Heather, who worked here
for a few years.
They've had a lot
of experiences.
Joe thinks the paranormal
is costing him business,
but his biggest concern
is the safety
for his customers
and his employees.
He wants to know
what the hell is here
and how to get rid of it.
So now that I told Amy
a little bit about you guys,
I'm gonna have her
describe her walk.
When I arrived,
I was very distracted
by a lot of chaotic
and confusing energy.
It had to do
with random objects.
Specifically, the wood
flooring was bothersome.
The bar and some objects
on display in the back room,
these items were
emitting chaotic energy
and it just added
to the overall
intense energy
of this location.
Amy, there's a few things
you should know about Joe
and this place.
Now, you were talkin' about
the floor and the bar.
Joe and his business
partner, Karyn,
did extensive renovations
on this place
when they bought it
about 13 years ago.
Joe sank his life
savings into it.
This what the bar
used to look like before.
This is circa 1980.
- Wow.
Obviously,
just from comin' in here,
you can see the huge amount
of work that was done.
Interesting.
That makes a lot of sense.
So, during my walk,
I'm getting sicker
and sicker and drained.
I do think that living
individuals here
might feel some
of that at times,
because there's a lot of stress,
a lot of anxiety.
And what I got,
in extreme cases,
so if you're here consistently
or if you're really sensitive,
you could develop some
stomach problems, like ulcers.
Amy, there's something
you should know about
the two ladies
on both sides of Joe.
Both of them are sensitives
and both of them have
spent a lot of time here.
Now, we didn't discuss sickness
when I interviewed
both you ladies,
but anxiety and stress
was definitely a thing.
I agree with the stress
and the anxiety.
Just so much pressure,
so much energy coming
at you all at once.
Deborah, you talked to me about
the bad vibes in this place.
There was
a extended period
where there were
a lot of dissension,
a lot of arguments, a lot
of customer complaints,
and it was going on
amongst many people
for a prolonged period,
and even among people
who are normally
eventempered.
Interesting.
Okay, so what else
on the walk?
So, I went into the kitchen
and what I saw happening
in the kitchen
were a lot of ridiculous
accidents
and the thing that was causing
these accidents was a dead dog.
I got that it
is extremely negative
and it's been here
for a very long time.
The living might feel it
brush up against them.
They might feel weight against
them, causing them to move.
If people encounter the dog
and they see it or they hear it,
that could actually indicate
that that person might die.
It doesn't cause
someone to die,
but it could possibly
foretell their death.
You're talkin' about
accidents in the kitchen.
Joe, tell Amy
what happened
to Karyn with the cup.
Karyn actually experienced
a cup fly across the room
and she was in there
with one of her cooks
and they both saw it.
Now, she also told somethin'
'bout her gettin'...
Brushed behind her,
that's correct.
She was just walking
through
the dining room up front.
and she experienced
something behind her
that she could sense
very clearly,
but nothing was there
when she looked.
Boy.
That's not good.
So what else?
There were a couple of people
that I encountered
who seemed to be stuck
in their death states
and reliving their deaths
over and over and over again.
I encountered one individual
in the bar area.
This was a younger male.
I got that this person was shot
and it felt like my insides
were just ripped apart.
It was extremely painful.
I know that it took quite
some time to die from this.
Somethin' I came across
in my research,
there was a guy who was shot
and then died
in the parkin' lot right here.
This happened
on May 25, 1957.
19-year-old
George Nelson came here
with some friends for a drink.
I actually have
a picture of him.
So, now, when they finished
drinking here,
George, two guys, and two girls
piled into a car
and started to leave.
Guy in the front seat
that was driving was married.
And the guy sitting
in the back had a girlfriend.
During the drive, George noticed
that there was a car
following 'em
right outside here.
Before he could do anything,
a shot went through
the back windshield.
He was struck in the head
by the bullet,
but it didn't kill him
right away.
They drove back here
to the parkin' lot
and he wound up goin' DOA here.
gunshot wound to the head.
Now, the case is still unsolved,
but I spoke to George's nephew.
He thinks that the car
that followed them belonged
to the girlfriend
of one of the guys in the car.
According to him,
the girl was jealous
and she mighta been
tryin' to scare them,
wound up killin' a guy.
But she was never questioned
about the shooting.
Wow.
So I'm back in the kitchen
and I felt that there
was another death.
It had to do with something
with the dog.
I got that there
was a car accident,
their back
was horribly damaged.
I was in so much pain at the
time that I had to kneel down.
I got that this happened
very close to this location.
I think I know
what she's talkin' about.
I'm pretty sure you do.
There was a car accident
that happened
right on the street here
next to Relics back in 2006.
Randy Austin, he was
a regular customer here.
I've got a photo.
Now, he drank here all the time,
pretty much every day.
We found out he was a drifter,
kind of a homeless guy,
here and there.
On April 4, 2006,
after a long day of drinking,
he walked out of the bar
and laid facedown on the road,
for some reason.
What?
Now, it's pitch-black out there.
Oncoming car didn't him
until it was too late.
It ran right over him.
- My --
He died at the scene.
Now, the driver was cleared.
It was obviously an accident.
He was known
by a lot of people
and it was a very sad
incident when that occurred.
No one really understood
why he did that, either.
So, Amy, do you think
that's the same guy?
It could be.
Which is awful.
If it is him,
it's unfortunate
because he would be stuck
in his death state.
Okay, so we've got accidents.
We got shootings.
What else?
I went into the area that is
kinda like decorated Victorian.
Which is that front dining room.
And there were these
smoky, grayish, blackish,
foggy things
that had light for eyes.
Aaaaah!
What?
Just, those things are here.
I kinda pride myself on not
being afraid of too many things
and this just really
caught me off-guard.
What are these things?
They're elementals, which means
they were never alive.
And then, at the tables,
I saw like
what initially I thought
were mannequins
and there were
about 10 of 'em.
And then I hear the screaming
and I'm like "Okay."
What I got was that these
entities had, over many years,
collected several
deceased people
and, unfortunately through
that collecting process,
they have trapped them here,
their souls and their bodies.
- All right.
- Walking into the dining room,
- Yeah.
- what did I see?
- Yeah, tell her.
- People just --
between 5 and 12,
just standing
amongst the diners,
for no reason.
It was
an uncomfortable feeling.
I did have a sketch done.
Frankly, I did find it
very disturbing.
I would not spend
a long time in that room.
It absolutely creeped me out.
I don't know if you guys
wanna go back in that room
after seein' this.
I recognize it.
Really?
Yeah.
I've seen
this sort of thing
many, many times,
over and over again.
It's like something
from a horror movie.
This means a lot,
that you've seen this,
because I can't share this
with other people.
So what do these smoky creatures
want with the dead people?
They're collecting them because
they think they're beautiful.
Like they're dolls.
They just put 'em
where they want 'em.
- Like a toy to them.
- Yeah.
And you believe
that those individuals
may be these individuals?
I think it's highly likely.
So, Deborah, I noticed
you got a little emotional.
Well, I think
the suffering
of those souls needs
to be addressed.
Joe, it looks like you
called us in just in time.
It is bad.
It's really bad.
So, Joe,
I know you're a skeptic,
but you gotta be pretty blown
away by what you heard tonight.
- Absolutely.
- Now comes the hard part.
We're gonna find out
what it's gonna take for you
to make your restaurant
safe again
and, for that, I'm gonna
turn it over to Amy.
The first thing
is the residual energy.
The entire location needs to be
cleaned, from top to bottom,
I'm thinking about one time
per month, for 6 months.
I know that's a big job,
but this is the best thing
to remove all of this
collected energy.
And then, once that's done,
a shaman and a medium need
to be contacted,
who are willing
to work together.
What I would like the shaman
to do is to perform a ritual
to reach out to the elementals,
to appease them.
Once that ritual's completed,
the medium needs to step in
and help any
of the deceased individuals
who don't go on their own.
Many will probably just leave,
but some might be a little
stunned, confused,
and the medium may need to
assist them in moving them on.
Will the dog go, too?
Yes.
So, when the shaman
comes in,
is he gonna get rid
of these smoky things?
No. What he or she
will do is
a ritual that will send
a clear message and intention
that they are being
acknowledged,
that respect will now be given,
that we understand
what they've been through,
and things of that nature.
All right.
So they'll stay here,
but they're not gonna trap
any more souls.
Correct.
They'll leave, but these
guys are still here,
with the scary eyes,
shootin' down
in my dining room?
Unfortunately, yes.
So people may see these
things, living people?
I think, if they're
sensitive, yeah.
Then, after that,
at least once a week,
you need to make an offering
to the elementals.
And my suggestion is to go
to one of the local
metaphysical stores and,
whatever you feel pulled to,
that's them letting you know,
"This is what we want."
So you bring that object
back and you say,
"This is now for you"
and you can select an area
to place the object in.
So as far as the cleansing,
once a month for 6 months,
how will it feel
for them?
Yeah.
It's gonna be good.
Good energy.
I'm very pleased that all
of this came out.
I'm willing to try it.
So, Joe, I know
you put your heart
and soul into this place
and it means everything to you.
As far as all this stuff
Amy suggests to do,
are you gonna
take that task on?
Absolutely.
It's too easy.
Joe has a lot of work to do,
if he wants to keep
his employees and guests
out of harm's way.
With the help of a shaman,
the elementals will stop
trapping the dead;
and, with the help of a medium,
the dead can move on,
allowing Joe to run
his restaurant safely
for many years to come.