Tonight
on "Dead Files Revisited"...
They're pissed.
...a second look
at some of Amy and Steve's
most terrifying cases.
That's got to
scare the hell out of you.
New information.
I had to have some answers.
Startling revelations.
I'll fight to the grave
for my child.
In this week's episode...
I don't like
coming down here myself.
...a return
to Fort Wayne, Indiana...
This thing might be into
torturing people.
...where painful memories...
I feel like it violates her.
...plague a family.
It's the scariest thing
in the world.
But first, we travel back
to Flint, Michigan...
I felt a hand
reach around my throat.
...where a demonic presence...
It's not something you want
to **** with.
...rips a family apart.
I got to protect
my family.
And in a "Dead Files" first...
You got
a serious problem.
...the battle for Kathy's soul
caught on camera.
In the name
of the Father and of the Son
and of the Holy Sprit, Amen.
No! No!
It's really bad in here.
My name is Amy Allan.
Something is not right.
I see dead people.
This person might have been a
serial killer.
I speak to dead people.
You get those chills.
And they speak to me.
He is darkness.
He is evil.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
I think she broke her neck.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
Telling me the truth?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I think the devil is down here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who the hell would do this?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
Who is he looking to kill?
We uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
You need to get out of here
right now.
Or time to get out.
It was, like, endless darkness.
Our investigation
at a home in Flint, Michigan,
was intense.
The family that called us in
were living through hell
before we got there.
But what happened after we left
is without a doubt
one of the most shocking things
any of our clients
have ever faced.
Kathy, things are pretty bad
here, it sounds like.
Yes.
My husband and five kids.
Five years,
we've been here.
There's people
being scratched, clawed,
things thrown at,
and it hits the kids
extremely hard.
You okay?
Yeah. Just --
It's a hard subject.
The things that's happened
here -- I call it a black life.
I don't have
what we used to have --
the joy, the laughter,
anything like that.
It's pure dread.
Okay, so,
what's going on in here?
We see black masses
and a headless man.
He'll say, "Get out. It's mine.
My house. Leave."
Well, that's got to scare the
hell out of you, I would think.
Yes, it does.
As usual, I had no previous
knowledge of the location --
who lived there,
who died there, nothing.
But as soon as I walked
onto the property,
I sensed this case was going to
get very serious very quickly.
I'm hearing growls.
It's, like, not an animal.
It's not human.
It's very, very dark.
It went right through the wall.
Was this the thing
that was growling? - Yes.
I think that some people
have seen it as a blackness,
but, like, it definitely morphs.
It ended up taking hours
to figure out
what that creature was.
And the fact
that it could change shape
only made things worse.
I just saw it, like,
turn into a big spider thing.
It's not something
you want to **** with.
There was a time
when I went out here
and I felt a hand
reach around my throat,
and I couldn't breathe.
Wow.
That's probably
the most physical interaction
I've heard about.
I haven't even told you
the worst of it.
One night, laying in bed,
I was grabbed.
And, of course, I check
on my one son, Mikey,
And somebody had his leg and
was pulling him off the bed.
What were they
gonna do to him?
With all that's happened here,
I don't think about myself.
What comes first is my husband,
my children.
I mean, they are the ones
I'm protecting.
I don't care, kind of,
what happened to me,
as long as they were safe.
How do you live
like that?
It's not living.
You just pray
for a fire.
It'll be the relief
that you can actually breathe
a little bit.
I see this woman
who...
she just sees everything
in her life...
falling apart --
And she's tough,
but, you know,
she's broken now.
She's just broken.
Like, I think she's had thoughts
of burning down the house.
It's pretty bad.
I spoke with Kathy's son Zach,
who claimed
that a male apparition
was watching him at night,
and over time, things got worse.
I was scratched
in the bedroom.
What do you mean?
You got scratches?
I had the word "LEAVE"
scratched on my stomach.
That sure as hell
does say that, does it?
That was a serious red flag,
and I went
straight to Kathy's husband.
But after hearing
some of his violent encounters,
I realized
this wasn't just a case
of their kid acting out
for attention.
One day I was out here
working on the truck,
and pretty soon,
something hit me in the back.
It was a piece
of broken concrete.
Anything else?
I had a one-inch wrench
thrown at me.
The kids were all in bed.
Made a believer out of me.
What's your biggest fear?
My biggest fear is somebody's
really gonna get hurt.
Right.
So, there's been a lot of chaos
in this area.
I think the thing is in here
quite frequently.
It gets really,
really physical --
moving things
very harshly around,
like it doesn't like it.
I chased that creature
all over the property,
trying to get some idea
of how to stop it.
And when I managed
to corner it in the garage,
it finally lost the disguise and
unveiled its horrific true form.
It's a demon,
and it creates
this sick, twisted environment
for everyone.
Next...
It looks like brains
are coming out of their mouth.
...a grisly entity
loses control.
"I've got you ****"
And in our
second investigation...
A lot of bad things
happened there.
...pure evil...
It's the scariest thing
in the world.
...hides in the shadows.
Whatever's here,
get the hell out.
Our clients had mentioned
the previous owner
of their house, Bill,
died in the living room.
And for some strange reason,
they kept his furniture
and even slept on his mattress.
And now knowing what I know
about this case,
that was probably a bad idea
because according
to one of the neighbors,
that guy Bill had a dark side.
I used to call him
old Wild Bill.
Now, I was told that he had
a mean side to him.
Is that true?
After his wife passed away
and that,
I think he started
drinking more.
And I think he got a little bit
more cantankerous and that.
How did Bill feel
about his house itself?
Well, they kept that place
immaculate there.
Inside the house,
everything was real nice.
I know
if anybody was in there
and they was messing with his
tools or anything like that,
he'd probably roll right over
in his grave.
I believe that
with all my heart.
You do?
Yeah.
Okay.
I just see people fighting,
and this man comes in
from the closet.
He says, "Ha ha.
I've got you ****"
And he, like, tries
to sleep in the bed.
I couldn't put my finger on it
at first,
but something about that man
was off.
They're not making any sense.
I can't get the thought process
out of him.
His actions appeared malicious,
but his ability to communicate
was completely impaired.
It looks like
intestines or brains
are coming, like,
out of their mouth or something.
I can't communicate
because their brains, literally,
are scrambled.
Unfortunately,
what ever happened to that man
had left him as nothing more
than a shell of his former self.
Can you
describe him at all?
This person's white, male.
I feel like his body is frail.
The guy
could have been on drugs,
and it's almost like
it's a lost cause or something.
This person is here
most of the time in this room.
Aside from
an accidental death in the 1930s
and the previous owner
dying of natural causes
in the living room,
the records were pretty clean
for a home
that was over 100 years old.
I figured that was the end of
the road for my investigation,
until I stumbled
onto a piece of history
that I just couldn't ignore.
It turns out,
the property I'm investigating
used to be
Native American land.
Pretty horrific stuff
went on there.
What can you tell me
about it?
Well, this was the land
of the Saginaw Chippewa tribe.
They were a very fierce,
very warlike tribe.
The United States government
was terrified of these guys.
Most of the Saginaw Chippewa
warriors
were very much aligned
with the British,
who were coming
to fight the Americans
in the War of 1812.
This is a picture
of United States troops.
Okay, so, what happened with
them during the War of 1812?
The Native Americans
would take hostages.
They would capture soldiers
in battle,
swoop down
on a settlement,
and literally
ransom them back
to white representatives
for money.
When they were POWs,
what were they treated like?
It would have been a very, very
tough thing to be a prisoner.
The winter season would have
been very, very difficult.
Food would have been
at a premium.
There are accounts of people
being tortured to death.
There's, like,
a lot of dead men over there,
and they're all a mess,
and it's very, very muddy.
Like, their clothes
are just kind of tattered.
They have long, gray,
wool coats on.
In that sea
of residual entities,
10 stood out in the crowd
because they were
still conscious
and unaware they had died.
And now they're just stuck
in an endless loop
of trying to interact with
people who are not really there.
I think a lot of them are sick.
They haven't had, like,
proper meals in a long time.
They're just, like,
pretty miserable.
I just think
they're trying to get home.
Next...
You got
a serious problem.
In a "Dead Files" first...
In the name of the Father
and the Son and the Holy Ghost,
Spirit, what is your name?
No! No!
...the moment no one saw coming.
I'm not going anywhere!
Amy, I'd like you
to meet Mike and Kathy.
The night of the reveal,
it was the first time I met Amy.
She was scary because if
she could see these things here,
could she see
something within me?
They're actually afraid
for their lives,
and they feel like
we're their last hope.
So, I'm outside
and I saw these 10 men.
They were wearing, like, torn
and tattered long, gray coats.
And they were very ill.
That's interesting.
The land
that your property sits on
used to belong to the Chippewa
Saginaw Indian tribes.
During the war of 1812,
they would kidnap
American soldiers.
These guys
lived under the worst conditions
when they were hostages.
Take a look at that.
You see the uniform colors
on the American soldiers?
Wow.
Amy confirmed what I see --
people walking across the hills,
walking across the property.
I didn't know
they were soldiers,
so that was neat
to find out about that
but sad
because they're stuck here.
I saw an individual
in the master bedroom
jump out of the closet.
He was ripping covers
off the bed.
That happens.
Several times,
I've felt being grabbed.
He was white
and he was on some kind
of substance.
The man that lived in your house
before you guys bought it
was this guy named Bill.
Back in the '90s,
his wife passed away,
and from that time,
he took a downward spiral,
started drinking heavily.
Eventually,
he did die in the house.
The odd part is,
when they bought the house,
they bought most
of the furniture with it.
And they're actually sleeping
on Bill's mattress.
Would them keeping his furniture
make things worse?
Yeah. Beds hold a lot
of residual energy.
I'm not gonna be settled
until it's gone.
We thought
instead of having them move it,
we would take the furniture
with the home.
Now I regret it a lot.
We kept it his place,
not our place.
What else you see?
So, there's one entity
that's actually interacting
with the family,
and it's extremely
powerful.
And pretty much
all of the problems
is generated
by this thing.
One of Kathy's boys
showed me these pictures.
Now, I don't know if you can see
what's scratched into his chest.
It spells "LEAVE."
Yeah.
Could this thing do that?
You know,
I wouldn't discount that
because it is
an advanced entity.
It knows
what scares you.
"Leave" -- that one word.
One word haunts me.
How can it tell me to leave
when it should be gone?
Well,
I had the sketch artist
sketch
the most disturbing scene.
She's kneeling down.
On the wall,
I would like there to be
the outline
of just a shadow.
Who's the kid?
God.
Mikey.
She's the one I called
the babysitter.
And you see
who she really is.
It's the entity.
When I seen the sketch,
I knew who it was.
It was just an automatic
kick to the chest.
But I'm not gonna let it
touch my kids.
I'll fight to the grave.
I will fight for my child.
There was someone
who was into dark magic
add conjured up
this entity, this demon thing.
- It's a demon, then?
- Yeah.
It sought out living people
to begin gaining more power.
It's making people fight
in the house.
When Amy was telling me
about the demon here,
I knew what the outcome
was gonna be.
I knew she was gonna tell us
that we couldn't be here.
Well, Kathy,
my big question is,
can you stay in this house
safely?
I believe the best thing
you could do
for yourselves and your children
is to relocate.
If they do decide to stay
and can't afford to move,
what can they do?
There is definitely
PTSD here,
and that's something
that needs to be addressed
through counseling.
While that's happening,
the Catholic priest must do
an exorcism of the property
and then remove the dead man
from the location, as well.
Would that get rid
of the demon?
Yes.
It's not too often that
this is the advice Amy gives,
but for her to give it, it must
mean you got a serious problem.
After the investigation,
I felt defeated.
The house defeated me.
I was hurt
because this was the house
that we wanted to call home.
So I decided to fight it off as
much as we can -- call for help.
Lord Jesus Christ,
have mercy on me.
When the priest got here,
we went from room to room.
Walk in your ways
and in your truth forever.
Burned the incense
and put holy water in all
four corners of every room...
♪ Christ God
has appeared to us ♪
♪ And glory to thee ♪
...and tried to bless
the house to eliminate Bill.
After that, the priest done
a baptism on the family
to bring God
back into our lives.
Surround her with your angels,
that she may be clean,
that she may walk in your ways
and in your truth forever.
But when
the priest baptized me,
it felt like stabs
to my own body.
And that's when he told me that
an exorcism had to been done
because a demon's
attached to me.
And without it leaving me,
it's gonna continue.
In the name of the Father
and the Son and the Holy Ghost,
Spirit, what is your name?
No! No! No!
I remember
bits and pieces of it.
I'm not going anywhere!
Sprit,
what is your name?
My land!
Mine!
I was being held down by two
of my kids and by husband.
Spirit,
this is no longer your land.
You must go to Christ.
Go to the place
that Christ has prepared
for you.
It was so many emotions -- hate,
agony, anger -- a lot of anger.
And this demon
is doing his bidding through me.
Bring her radiant
guardian angel down.
Be gone!
Looking back on it now,
I think,
"Why did I have to
go through this hell?
What did I do
to deserve this?"
She may walk
in your ways.
In the name of the Father
and the Son and the Holy Spirit.
How are you feeling?
He's gone?
What my family went through --
that's always going to haunt me.
Since the exorcism, it was
a new day -- a new day born.
The kids have already
been seeing a therapist,
and we are actually
on a waiting list to see one.
But with all that's
happened here, we're moving.
We have actually found a house
far away from the hell
that's there.
I'm not
gonna go through this again.
In my experience,
it's rare for a living person
to become possessed.
But if that demon
took control of Kathy,
then I can only imagine
what she went through.
I know it's been a difficult
journey for this family,
but hopefully they can put
this chaos behind them
and begin
rebuilding their lives.
As soon as I met Mark,
our client
in Fort Wayne, Indiana,
I knew he was in trouble.
He said that paranormal activity
was tearing his family apart
and he no longer had a way
to protect them.
And he had every right to be
concerned because looking back,
this household
was in more danger
than anyone
could have anticipated.
Mark, what's going on?
I've seen an apparition.
I've been touched,
hit with things.
We'll go sometimes
for like a month or two,
and nothing will happen.
And then it'll be continuous
for weeks.
I started out,
I was scared of it,
and now I'm at the point
I hate it.
It was crazy.
It was affecting my work,
my wife, and my daughter,
and I had to have some answers
and figure out
what I was gonna do
because
I just couldn't live here.
Why don't you just sell
the house and get out of here?
You know, it's finances,
and the thing is, it's my house.
There is something
definitely not right
about the land.
The second I set foot
on that property,
I could sense the residents
of that home were in danger.
It would end up taking me
most of the night
to identify
what they were up against,
and unfortunately,
this wasn't going to be
an easy problem to fix.
A lot of bad things happened
there with that family.
There was also, like,
a murder that happened.
I feel weak, like something's
trying to jump me.
This thing might be
into torturing people.
Next...
I felt fingers
running through my hair.
...the danger becomes real.
I feel like it violates her.
Listening to Mark's stories
about the activity in his house,
the guy was definitely scared.
But his biggest fear
was his basement,
and knowing how this case ends,
Mark should have listened
to his gut
and stayed
the hell out of there.
I was sweeping
the floor down here.
A fairly decent-sized bolt
hit me in
the center of the back.
- You were down here alone?
- I was down here alone.
I don't like
coming down here myself.
It creeps me out.
I was worried that someone
was gonna eventually get hurt --
get pushed down the stairs
or God knows what.
I mean, if these things
can move large objects,
what else can they do?
Have you experienced
anything else down here?
Yeah. Yeah, I'll see shadows
down here a lot.
What kind of shadows?
They're like a solid black mass
or something.
You'll catch them
out of the corner of the eye.
It feels sometimes almost like
things hide down here.
There is something very bad here
that's not a human.
This big gigantic black blob.
There is a lot
of physical phenomena
that this thing can do --
throwing people down stairs
or smacking them.
It's a pretty powerful thing.
A mass
of negative energy like that
is never good for the living,
but I felt confident I could
find a way to contain it,
at least that was
until I turned around
and saw that the black mass had
a reach far beyond the house.
And there is, like,
definitely a pathway here.
I think it goes possibly
next door or underground.
This thing might be
into torturing people.
Mark's wife, Kim, had
experiences similar to his own,
but unlike Mark, the effect
on her sanity was severe.
Ever since I've been here,
it's like I've just been
totally drained of energy.
I would assume this has got to
take a toll on your marriage.
Yeah, it does.
But the breaking point for me
was when Mark's daughter
revealed how the activity
in their home
was un-bottling
her difficult past.
Shaela, I was talking
to your dad earlier,
and he mentioned
that you're uncomfortable
being in the house alone.
Okay, how long
have you been living here?
I've been living here
about five months now.
Mark's my dad,
and we just found each other
when I turned 18.
What kinds of things are you
experiencing in the house?
I get this, like, weird vibe
of, like, sadness and anger.
I was not a believer
of anything paranormal
until I moved here.
But it felt like something
was out to get me.
I was absolutely shocked
and frightened
because it really reminded me
of my past.
Now, what's the most frightening
thing in the house for you?
I've felt, like, fingers running
through my hair.
It just absolutely
just mortifies me.
What do you mean by that?
I had a rough past.
I was abused...sexually.
And when I feel
these things,
it reminds me
of my childhood.
Like, I'll hear
the door handle turn.
And then...
So, that doorknob turning
brings you back
to when you were...
molested.
It's the scariest thing
in the world.
The pain that you felt
just plays over and over
in your head
and next thing you know,
you're just in tears.
Something paranormal's
bringing back that memory,
and it just hurts.
This older woman, she is
concerned about someone --
like, a girl
who lives in this house.
And this woman
feels like she's a protector
from this black shadow thing.
The situation
is really, really dire,
and that's why she's here.
From what I could tell,
the older woman
was doing everything she could
to protect the living
in the house.
Unfortunately,
going up against that black mass
was a losing battle.
I feel like it violates her.
What do you mean?
Like, kind of sexually.
It's not good.
She stabbed him
in the back.
Next...
He doesn't like the people here.
...resentment builds to rage.
I feel like I'm being attacked.
The only lead
I had on Mark's home
was that one of the prior owners
might have been murdered.
Apparently,
this happened recently,
so I found
a local retired detective
who used to patrol the area
to give me the full story.
So, A.J.,
my client said
there was a possible murder
in his house
back in the '90s,
Right.
Back in December of '96.
This was the victim,
Alberto Lopez.
He looks like a young guy.
How old was he?
He was only 25.
So, how'd the homicide
go down?
He had a live-in girlfriend.
They got
into an altercation,
and he took off running.
She had a knife,
and she stabbed him in the back.
It was a fatal blow,
and he died right there
on the floor,
right in front
of the stove.
A.J., what do we know
about the victim?
Not much of anything.
Nobody even knew him.
No next of kin stepped forward
to shed any light on who he was,
and nobody even claimed
the body.
Now, I'm assuming
she gets collared for this.
- She gets arrested, right?
- She gets arrested.
Ends up taking a charge
of aggravated battery
and got 10 years.
Now, what's her story?
She was claiming
domestic abuse.
She had
told people that,
"The next time he hits me,
that's it.
I'm gonna kill him."
She was
at a breaking point.
I feel like
there's a younger male here
who doesn't want to be bothered.
And he'll lash out.
Do you know when he died?
I would say like...
'90s.
Do you get an age on him?
25 maybe?
He's creepy.
He doesn't like
the people here.
Sometimes, an entity may want
to isolate themselves
from the outside world
while they're trying to accept
the fact that they're dead.
That young man could not
come to grips with reality,
and his denial
was building into resentment.
People are not
leaving him alone.
So, he is distraught over this.
He has so much anxiety,
so much stress, so much anger.
It wasn't long
before I uncovered
that the family who owned
Mark's property in the 1800s
had practically built
the town of Fort Wayne.
Money and power
usually get you ahead in life,
but according
to a local genealogist,
that's what ended up
destroying them.
John, when I did
my research,
I came across
the Olds family.
What can you tell me
about them?
They were
one of the top families
in Fort Wayne
in the 1800s.
This is Henry G. Olds.
He inherited the property
back in 1876.
He had a lot
of mercantile interests.
When did Henry die?
He died in 1902.
He was 62 years old.
He died at his house,
leaving a widow, Caroline,
and several sons
who took over his businesses.
So, what happens to Caroline
after he dies?
I'm just seeing, like,
these two dead old men
talking a lot.
They weren't paid well.
They had no rights.
And...they're pissed.
They're just **** pissed.
Well, there was
a series of lawsuits
that really harmed
the family.
Well, why is that?
They're mad about
their living conditions.
how they died.
It was not a safe place.
People were
really unprotected,
and one of the workers
was killed.
And his widow sued
the company for $10,000.
That was a lot of money
back then.
A lot of money, yes,
and that certainly took
a big chunk out of their wealth.
The coal company also got hit
with a big lawsuit in 1913.
Like, I do feel like
they worked underground,
like they were miners
or something of that nature.
And the one said,
"I died with my boots on."
A man was killed
when some coal was being
unloaded from a train.
Okay, so they wind up
losing a lot
between lawsuits
and accidents.
Yes.
All I see is earth
rushing in on him.
God.
Next...
It can get physical
and violent.
...the clients...
All hell broke loose in here.
...confront their demons.
Whatever's here,
get the hell out.
Amy, this is Mark,
this is his wife, Kim,
and this is his daughter,
Shaela.
I was scared
because I wanted to find out
if there's a way
of correcting the problems
that were happening here.
I was mainly worried
about Kim and Shaela
because if Amy said
they can't be here,
I don't know
how they would have handled it.
They feel
we're their last hope,
and that's why
they called us in.
So I encountered
two old, angry men.
They're very pissed off about
how they died,
which seemed to be
in some kind of an accident.
A family called the Olds family
owned this property
before it was developed.
Now, they owned factories here,
and the way they mistreated
their employees
wound up being
the demise of them.
So when Henry Olds
dies in 1902,
his wife, Caroline,
got hit with a few lawsuits
from the families
of mistreated workers.
I thought
it was very interesting
that she found the two men
in the basement.
There are times
where you can hear kind of like
a whispering voice in the house,
and I think that put an answer
to those noises
that we'll hear.
What else did you see?
In the garage,
I met a male,
probably between
18 and 25 years old.
He, frankly,
doesn't want to be bothered.
And he feels like his space
is being violated.
In my mind, it sounded like Amy
was talking about Alberto Lopez,
the man whose girlfriend
killed him in the house.
She stabs him
one time in the back,
and he winds up dying
upstairs in the kitchen.
Wow.
When they first revealed to me
about Alberto being stabbed
to death in the kitchen
and his spirit
staying in the garage,
I really wasn't sure
how to take that,
but I made up my mind that I'm
gonna have to address it myself.
Down here in the basement,
I saw,
this funky, nasty thing.
It's rather large,
very powerful,
and...negative.
Sometimes, I could see it
as a dark blob
I've seen
a black blob.
It was like it was alive.
It just took off.
So I had a sketch artist
sketch the scene I saw.
Is he looking at you?
Yes.
A very solid black.
He is like this.
Okay.
My God.
Wow.
I'm just horrified.
When Amy pulled out the sketch
of the dark entity
that's living in the basement,
my heart kind of stopped.
I was definitely really upset.
This thing
is really what's causing,
you know,
havoc within the house.
Frankly, I'm surprised that
it hasn't become more violent,
It just really scares me,
because
I don't want it
to get more physical.
At this point in the
reveal, Amy's demeanor changed.
I've seen that look on her face
many times,
and I knew our clients
were about to hear
something powerful.
There was a woman
that I met.
And she's very concerned about
a girl who lives in this house.
She's afraid
that this girl
might be getting sexually
assaulted by the entity.
God.
I really wanted her to say
that there's nothing wrong
and everything was okay
because I can't take
any more of that in my life.
When I was a kid...
I was sexually assaulted
repeatedly
for about
six or seven years.
My gosh.
Now that I'm here,
I feel safe, but I hear things
in the house that...
...will get me flashbacks of my
childhood. - Right.
I don't want, like, something
paranormal violating me.
Describe the finger
going through the hair.
It just feels like
someone, like,
just kind of, like,
caressing.
Sometimes it's lovingly.
Could it be
this woman that showed up?
Could be, yes.
I'm not sure
who she is,
but you do have a female here
who's looking out for you.
When Amy said the thing
about the older woman,
I find that comforting to know
that something
is looking out for her.
If there's something else
on the other side
that's messing with you,
it's nice to know
you got a little bit of support
on that side.
The question is,
can you guys live here together
as a family?
Dealing with
the negative entity --
get a warlock in here.
This needs to be a male witch
who's very masculine.
This individual
would do a banishment ritual
to send him
to where he belongs,
which I believe is Hell.
So why does it have to be a
masculine male witch or warlock?
Because this entity
is intimidated by you.
That's why he picks on women,
because he's a coward.
What about this guy
in the garage?
Have a very short, to-the-point
conversation with him.
And give him
the time and space
for him to work
his issues out,
as long as he doesn't bother you
or your family.
Now, I want youse all
to look me in the eye
and promise me you're gonna
listen to Amy's advice.
After Amy and Steve left,
all hell broke loose in here.
It's almost like we agitated it,
pissed it off, maybe.
So we had to get things
taken care of.
What Amy had told me to do
was to address the spirit
in the garage, which I did.
Okay, Alberto,
here's the deal --
I'll let you have your space
until you do what you got to do.
I told him he could stay
as long
as he wasn't raising hell
or doing anything
he's not supposed to do.
If you come in the house,
I'm gonna do something
to get you out.
I feel that it worked
and that Alberto left.
Whatever's here,
it can be released.
When the warlock first got here,
it was kind of like the calm
before the storm.
There was, like, a tension,
almost like
right before a fight.
I've seen some strange things
in my life, but that was crazy.
This has a bit
of dragon's blood.
I'm gonna literally nuke it and
neutralize the house as it is.
Once he's out,
he can't get back in.
As the warlock got doing
his thing in the basement,
it was like there was, like,
a battle of wills going on.
I felt like there was
a dark entity in the basement.
Whatever's here,
get the hell out.
And then he started using
this Tibetan singing bowl.
I protect and seal this off,
and get the hell out.
And the energy
did seem to graze,
but it was a very angry energy,
like it didn't want to leave.
Get out.
After the warlock left,
so far,
things are holding pretty good.
I feel, like, more
comfortable being in the house.
It's something
that's really helped me
move forward in my life
and not fear anything
that's happened in my past.
Things feel better
than they were,
but I don't know
what's gonna happen.
I'm not set up to leave,
and if something
came back again,
I don't really know
where I would go.
After what
that family's been through,
I can understand
why Mark's still worried.
But it sounds like
they've taken the right steps
to cleanse their home.
So at this point,
I'm hopeful things
will get better with time.