Subs created by: David Coleman.
I think they see him.
We have a gremlin crawling
up on the ceilings.
It's kind of like a shadow person.
He's bad.
I see a lot of blood.
I'm not gonna let something
drive us out of our home.
I feel very panicked.
This is a terrible place. I hate it.
It's really bad in here.
My name is Amy Allan.
Something is not right.
I see dead people.
This person might have
been a serial killer.
I speak to dead people.
You get those chills.
And they speak to me.
He is darkness. He is evil.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I think she broke her neck.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
Telling me the truth?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I think the Devil is down here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who the hell would do this?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Who's he looking to kill?
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
You need to get out of here right now.
Or time to get out.
That was, like, endless darkness.
Amy and I work the same case,
but from two separate angles.
I interview living witnesses and look for
secrets buried deep in the property's past.
While Amy talks to the dead.
I'm in the tiny town of
Cressona, Pennsylvania.
It's a couple hours outside of Philly.
I got a call from a man named Randy.
Randy and his fiancée
are both Army veterans.
And they both know what it's
like to be in a war zone.
They just never expected to
find one in their own home.
I'm hoping Amy and I can help them out.
Before Amy enters a location,
I need to remove anything that
could influence her findings.
This house is filled with family
photographs and military memorabilia.
So I need to conceal all
of it before tonight's walk.
There's this really
tall, really skinny...
Weird...
Crazy...
Guy.
He has, like, a long cape.
And a hat.
He is very excited for
us to be here tonight.
Because he...
Thinks he's all that as far as...
Being able to mess with
people and scare them.
He said, I'll see you
soon. I can't wait.
Like, you'll know when
you get there. Uh...
You know, what I'm all about.
Now, Randy, I understand you and
your fiancée, Angela, have got
some pretty serious things going
on here for you to call us in.
- Yes.
- Give me an idea what's going on.
There's apparitions. There's shadows.
There's been things moved from one
area of the house to a completely
different area of the house
that I know nobody has touched.
Now, is everybody in the
house being affected by this?
- Yes.
- Who lives in the house?
Myself, Angela, my two
daughters... 8 and 11...
And my stepson, who's 9.
- Are they frightened to be in the house?
- Samantha is.
Samantha actually lived here with me last
year for the school year and moved out
because now she's so afraid,
she doesn't want to move back.
- That's got to be heartbreaking for you.
- It is. It is.
That's my little girl.
It's hard to be a father and protect
your children when you can't...
How do you protect them
against something like that?
Do you guys ever consider
moving out of here?
It's not an option.
Monetarily, we couldn't afford to move.
Secondly, this is the best
school district in the area,
and we want our children to grow
up in a secure, safe environment.
- Okay.
- And this is it.
Okay, do you know
anything about the house?
A little. I know that
the houses were built for
the employees of the rail road
by the owner of the rail road.
Now, are there any parts
of the house you can
show me where you've
experienced or seen things?
Actually, there is.
This area right here.
- You've seen stuff here?
- I have.
What did you see?
It's kind of like a shadow person.
Okay, so how often do you see it?
- A few times a night.
- A few times a night?
Could it be lights coming in from
outside or some kind of reflection issue?
No. Not in that
direction. It couldn't be.
Do you know if this tall guy
interacts with the living here?
Yes, he does.
I think they see him.
He makes them scared, he stares at them.
Is there any particular
reason that he does this?
He's bad.
Okay, Randy, so what's going on in here?
I'll get migraines for a whole day, and
I've never, ever had headaches before.
One evening, I had a headache so
badly that I couldn't even walk.
And that was followed by a tightness...
Almost like a constricting of
my chest like I couldn't breathe.
I had to leave the area, and once I
left the area, it started to dissipate.
- You think you were having a heart attack?
- Honestly, yes, I did at first.
It feels almost as if something is sitting
on you, at the same time, squeezing you.
Okay.
Like, it hurts, and I can't
breathe because of the pressure.
This is the tall, creepy guy.
And he's like, I'm gonna suck
the [Bleep] life out of you.
He doesn't want me to
get anything about him.
He's getting really mad.
Ah, and he's really loud, too,
and he's like blowing in my ear.
The people feel that.
He said, oh, yeah, I
thought you could handle me.
And I said, I can [Bleep].
Randy, you got a lot going
on that you're experiencing.
I mean, is there anything else?
Sounds like there's
things up in the attic.
There's loud bumps,
bangs, noises in the attic.
It's just a really weird, eerie feeling
like you're constantly
being followed or watched.
In fact, I make sure I take my steps very
carefully when I go up and down the steps
because I feel like something
will push me down the steps.
You know, Randy, I got
to ask you. I mean...
Stuff you've told me so far, I don't think
I would stay here, to be honest with you.
- I don't know. How are you doing it?
- Because this is our children's home.
I'm not gonna let something
drive us out of our home.
This is the home that
we've always wanted.
Has this taken a strain
on your personal life?
Yes, Sir. Yes, Sir.
We've been getting
further and further apart.
- Really?
- Yeah. She's my soul mate.
I've always believed for the last
20-something years she's my soul mate.
Okay. Do you think it's
because of the house?
I believe so.
I truly believe it has
a lot to do with it.
These stairs are so bad.
- Why?
- They are an issue.
They're a [Bleep] problem.
- What happens?
- I think they fall down them.
I got to say this is up there
with my top 10 of hatred places.
I feel panicked, confused...
Scared, overwhelmed.
It's a terrible,
terrible, terrible place.
I hate it.
- This is your youngest daughter's?
- Yes, this is the 8-year-old's room.
Okay, what's going on in here?
She had described to me a large, dark
figure with a cape and a hook hand.
That's scary for anybody,
let alone an 8-year-old.
The way I understand it,
she sees it pretty often.
Okay, anything else in this room?
She's deathly afraid of the closet.
She had me draw crosses on her closets.
All right, so what is she
afraid of about the closet?
She never went into detail. She
just doesn't like the closets.
She won't even go in
the closet by herself.
How do you protect somebody like that?
I'm supposed to be the protective
figure. That's my role as a father.
I don't even know the kid, and
my heart's breaking for her.
If I think about it, I get
emotional. That's my daughter.
You can feel the fear
that these people feel.
He likes the closets.
It doesn't really care for children.
They're easy mark.
The tall, thin man is making
his presence felt in every room.
He likes to torment adults, but now
I see his real issue is with children.
Why do you say that?
He's like, oh, I'm gonna [Bleep] with your
head if you're gonna [Bleep] with my head.
And what is he doing?
He's just making me dizzy
and feel like I want to vomit.
I want to puke.
I feel like someone's
pushing my throat in...
Just smushing me right here.
Right here.
Like that.
Just smushing it in really hard.
Randy mentioned you guys fight a lot.
But at the same time, he says you're
his soul mate, so what's the story?
I think it's something
in the house trying to...
- Come between you?
- Yeah.
So, what are some of the
things you're experiencing?
Every night, we have a gremlin
crawling up on the ceilings.
- A gremlin?
- Yep.
2 feet tall, dark green with black
scales going down the back of him.
I've heard a lot of bizarre
stories working cases with Amy.
But when a witness tells
me she's seen a gremlin,
I need to know where her head is at.
I got to ask a question you may not
like, but are you on medications?
No.
Anything else going on?
I get the occasional poking in
the back, hair pulling at night.
- Okay.
- And it's not Randy.
No, Randy's downstairs.
- How the hell are you sleeping at night?
- I don't sleep.
I have a reoccurring nightmare.
I'm laying in bed, and...
the Devil comes up and puts his arms around
me and is pulling me through the bed,
through the first floor, and
once we hit the basement...
He turns around and he
says, I finally got you.
By then, I'm usually screaming,
and Randy wakes me up.
Wow.
I see this woman.
And she's screaming.
And I'm seeing...
The tall, creepy guy.
But his face is always changing.
This tall, creepy guy is
able to read people's minds
and project back their
most horrible fears.
He's very advanced and has
mastered his physical environment.
I think they feel like he might be poking
them, but he's actually grabbing them.
He makes them have nightmares.
Bad... he's bad.
You all right? I saw you grab
your rosary beads on the way down.
What are you feeling
when you come down here?
I just get the overwhelming feeling
like you don't belong down here.
I just feel evil.
Look, I understand you having that
dream makes you not want to come into the
basement, but is there anything else down
here that wants you to keep out of here?
Yes, one night, I was
home alone, and um...
I heard banging and growling and
scratching coming from the basement door.
I grabbed my rosaries,
I put them on the door,
and I went out and I sat
outside waiting for Randy.
Could it have been an animal that got
into the house and was trying to get out?
No.
The back doors... both sets of back
doors were locked from the inside.
And once you go down into the
basement, my rosaries were gone.
Really?
I found them a week later, and
they were broken in the closet.
I almost had a heart attack.
And what do you think's down here?
I think the Devil is down here.
There's, like, this old woman,
and she's, like, crying and...
Oh, no, no, and so sad.
She's creepy. Like, she puts
her hand on me and it's ice.
She knows this house, and this
house is full of people who...
Are really running
away from their lives.
There is something else I
wanted to explain to you.
One of the things that I
feel may be behind it all...
Is my mother.
- My mother passed away in '98.
- What did she die of?
She died of bone-marrow cancer.
- She was 36.
- She was 36?
I had some issues with my mother.
We'd try to make amends,
but it didn't happen.
I feel tremendous guilt.
I absolutely understand
what you're talking about.
Same thing happened
to me with my father.
I didn't get to say goodbye. We
had an argument the night he died.
That was 33 years ago, and
I still have guilt about it.
And if I can do that night over...
I'd do that night over in a minute.
Unfortunately, before she died, we never
had a chance to say goodbye to each other.
So I do believe that my mother is here.
I want to say that this
old lady is somehow...
Related to the house or related
to the people in the house now.
She keeps saying that
she's very sorry...
About everything that's happened.
Somehow, she feels responsible.
I think she knew someone bad... a male.
He was trying to hide it... but
she knew she could've stopped...
It from happening, but she
didn't do anything about it.
Oh, my God.
Something about cancer.
I think she died from it.
Do you know when this was?
Late '90s.
I don't know.
She might be death come to this house.
She's coming to take the lady.
Randy mentioned that one man
owned the entire town of Cressona.
That actually sounds like a pretty
good place to start my investigation.
I'm on my way to meet
with a local historian
who says the town's father
left a very mixed legacy.
John Chapman Cresson was
the founder of Cressona.
In 1847, he became the President of the
Mine Hill and Schuylkill Haven Railroad.
Which ran through Cressona.
This is his picture.
His contemporaries describe him as quite
a tall man with very expressive eyes.
Now, Rick, did he get rich just from
being the President of the company?
No, he made the lion's share of his money
through land and property acquisition.
We have a sales agreement here.
Where in 1847, when he became President,
he purchased 200 acres for $9,000.
He was a very shrewd businessman.
And how's it go from
the land into a town?
What John Cresson did is he broke
the land up into individual plots,
and had homes built on the plots.
And then what he did is he sold
them to the rail road workers.
So, on one hand, he was
putting money into their pocket,
and on the other hand, taking it out.
So, what wound up happening with this
guy? What, did he stay in the area?
Well, as much as he built up
the economy of Cressona, he also
pretty much ruined it in 1864.
What he did was he leased the
rail line to the Reading Railroad.
And by doing that, it outsourced a
lot of the employees from Cressona,
and the jobs weren't
here as much anymore.
So, during all this recession time,
he's still making a lot of cash.
Yes, he is.
So, it sounds like this
guy's kind of ruthless.
He was. He was a true
capitalist of the day.
I think that this is
the tall, creepy guy.
He does not want...
Anybody to know who he is.
Do you know how he looked in life?
Well, he was taller than average.
I think he had, like, kind of a
slender face, a kind of a hook nose.
Dark eyes.
He's saying, stop, stop!
Because I'm, like, trying
to get into his head.
Able to get any more
about what he did in life?
I think he sells a variety
of merchandise, I think.
And I know he's bad.
And I know he was a
very, very bad person.
I need to find out everything I
can about my client's property.
So I head to the local library.
Digging through the archives,
I discover a deadly rail road crash in
1892 involving a man named John Gray.
Turns out he used to
live in my clients' home.
So, I've reached out to
a local train historian,
who tells me this tragedy
could've been prevented.
Now, Dale, you mentioned
that this guy John Gray was in
the middle of this train
wreck that I had read about.
What did you mean by that?
Well, he was responsible for
maintaining equipment as a Foreman.
And foremen generally
were involved with making
sure locomotives were repaired properly.
Dale, can you explain exactly
how the train wreck went down?
It happened at 2:00 in the
morning on a cold November night.
And this is especially
tragic because the crew
brought this train to
Cressona from Reading.
And another crew had gotten on to
replace them to take the train North,
so instead of having three men
on the locomotive, there were six.
And just two minutes later,
the locomotive exploded
and killed five of them, and the
other man died later in the hospital.
- So, two sets of crews gets killed.
- Correct.
In connection to my clients' property,
how far away from that was the explosion?
Basically, just down the hill.
This is what a boiler
explosion looks like.
That's not that actual locomotive but,
a photograph of a steam locomotive
that had a boiler explosion.
Okay, we don't have any photos
of that explosion itself?
No, we don't.
- Okay, was anybody ever charged?
- No.
So, Dale, I got to assume,
in a small town like this,
this had to be the biggest
accident they ever had.
Well, it was up until that time.
But in 1918, the Spanish Flu hit.
Interestingly, John Gray's son, James,
was a Doctor in the town at that time.
Something doesn't want me back here.
I'm, like, hearing yelling.
I feel panicked... very panicked.
I am seeing, like,
all of these men dying.
I don't know if it's 1870
or something. I don't know.
These men are yelling and screaming and
they're jumping up and falling down...
And there's, like, dust everywhere,
and nobody can see anything.
Like, I'm totally not ready to see
this [Bleep] that's happening around me.
And it makes me sick.
You know, I made some calls,
and Dale's story checked out.
The Spanish Flu devastated Cressona.
So, I'm headed over to see a local
Doctor who says some of those victims
may have died right in
Randy and Angela's home.
Before we get into the Spanish Flu,
can you tell me anything about Dr. Gray?
He was the only Doctor in
Cressona during the Spanish Flu.
And his clinic and his residence
were in the same building.
Okay, so did he practice out
of the house I'm investigating?
Yes.
Okay, so how bad really was it?
The Spanish Flu was about 200 times
as lethal as our typical flu virus.
50 million people died worldwide.
Wow.
That being said, how
bad did Cressona get hit?
Cressona was absolutely
hammered with death.
They normally had about
10 people die each day.
Okay.
But it spiked around
the 20th of October.
There were 30 deaths
in a small community.
The Spanish Flu itself,
how contagious was it?
Nationally, 28% of the U.S. population
came down with the 1918 influenza.
And there were a great
number of people that died
four or five days after
coming down with the illness.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
So, the beginning symptoms,
what would they be like?
Well, initially, you'd develop a headache
and body aches and cold symptoms...
Runny nose, sore throat, coughing.
And how does it progress
to where they die?
Well, in most cases, fatalities
were from bacterial pneumonia.
Okay.
You would feel like your chest
was being compressed or squeezed.
It would be like starvation of air.
Oh, geez. So, basically,
they suffocated to death.
Yeah. It was absolutely scary.
Dr. Gray had to be
overwhelmed by all this.
Yes. They would've been convalescing
in his house and dying there.
Wow.
It's ridiculous how many
dead people are here.
Something happened.
What the [Bleep] is it?
There's, like, illness in here.
Oh, my God, it's bad.
The amount of dead in this location feels
like it's sucking the life out of me.
I've been sick this whole time,
but I can't figure out why.
Oh, God.
I can't breathe again.
I just want to vomit.
I feel...
[Bleep] Terrible.
During my walk, I was harassed
by a tall, thin man in a cape.
So I'm meeting with a sketch artist
to draw him as he appeared in life.
He had a long, thin, pointy nose.
His eyes are rounded on
top, straight at the bottom.
Okay.
His hair came down to
about the collarbone.
Next, I described his favorite
place to torment the living.
There's a closet along the wall.
It needs to be open halfway.
All right.
He's facing the side of
the bed from the closet.
Is that what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations.
We're ready to reveal our findings to each
other and our clients for the first time.
Amy, I want you to
meet Angela and Randy.
They live here with Angela's
son and Randy's two daughters.
Now, the thing about this couple, unlike
any other couple we've dealt with...
They're both Army veterans.
And they've been trained to
deal with high-stress situations.
But the activity in
this house is so intense
that it's literally
ripping their family apart.
With that, I'm gonna ask Amy to
tell us a little bit about her walk.
And see what we come up with.
This is seriously one of the
worst places that I've walked.
There were just so
many dead people, and...
They were all trying to talk at once.
I was physically and
emotionally just trashed.
Pretty much every room
upstairs made me sick.
Some of the symptoms I felt that
night was dizziness, vomiting...
Um, and I did, in one room, felt
like somebody was crushing my throat.
Okay, so you were sick
throughout the whole walk?
- Yes.
- With those symptoms?
- That's why you sound sick?
- Yeah. Mm hmm.
- From that? That's interesting.
I might be able to explain
why she probably felt that way.
Back in 1918, the Spanish Flu hit here.
30 people died in one day from
the Spanish Flu in Cressona.
Approximately 20% of the
town died from this flu.
James Gray, the guy that owned
this house and lived here,
happened to be the only Doctor in town.
And he treated a lot of those Spanish
Flu patients right here in this home,
where a lot of them
probably passed away.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh.
Can the children get sick because of that
or us get sick because of that or anything?
Have you shown any symptoms?
I went through exactly what you
just described on many occasions.
It's like Steve had mentioned...
it's like a flu-like symptom.
But all of a sudden, I got
a debilitating headache.
I mean, I couldn't even walk.
I crawled to the bathroom
because I felt like I was gonna vomit,
and I was super, super nauseated.
- I couldn't even stand up.
- Yeah, I get sick a lot.
- Same type of feelings?
- Headaches, migraines.
Yeah, that makes sense.
The residual here is very thick.
Like, it hangs on to...
The memories and, you know...
Everything that transpired here.
So, how did the rest of the walk go?
This guy shows up.
He was extremely tall, extremely
thin, had a hat on, cape...
Shadowy.
He's very creepy, very powerful.
I met him when I walked through here.
And he's like, I'm gonna suck
the [Bleep] life out of you.
He doesn't want me to
get anything about him.
He's getting really mad.
He was a businessman.
I know he bought and sold things.
And I know he had a
hook nose and dark eyes.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, I mean, it's a long shot.
I mean, but what she's describing
kind of reminds me of somebody
who's kind of actually
pretty important to this town.
Okay, well, it turns out it's a guy named
John Chapman Cresson, hence Cressona.
This guy ran the rail road here, owned
the rail road, and bought the land here...
And basically built the town.
Now, he had some shady dealings.
He built homes for the rail
road workers that he employed.
Okay, now I got a photo of
some of these rail road workers.
It'll give you an idea of
what these guys looked like.
So, what he was doing is he built homes
like this one for his employees to live in.
So, what he did was
he paid them at work...
Then sold them the house,
and they just paid him rent,
so the money that he was
making went right back to him.
Come 1864, he leases his rail
road company out to Reading,
so now all his workers,
they were out of a job.
It basically decimated the town, where they
went into a recession for over 20 years.
- Wow.
If you look at his nose...
He's got this hook nose that she had.
Interesting.
And he was considered tall for
his time, from what I was told.
Do you think that they had the same
characteristics as the guy you ran into?
Definitely.
I did do a sketch of the man.
Wow.
Take a look at that.
Wow, his eyes are pretty close. His
eyes and nose are almost identical.
Identical, right?
Wow, that's freaky. I would
say that's the same guy.
It looks spot on to me.
So, basically, the guy that built
Cressona is hanging out in our house.
- Yes.
- Wonderful.
So, Amy, in your opinion...
Do you think this gentleman is
the evil presence in our house?
I think he's an evil
presence in your house.
He likes to mess with people.
One of the things that he did to me in
here was, like he was standing on my chest.
What I saw was him, like,
pushing down on someone's chest.
When I was in here, I felt,
like, your ear will thump.
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah, I know exactly what you mean.
And he'll try to whisper in your ear.
You'll feel pokes.
I get poked and my hair
pulled almost every night.
He gives people nightmares, and
he also likes to stare people down.
And I have tremendous nightmares.
- Really?
- I am sleeping upstairs...
And...
Um...
I get a set of hands that
come up through the bed.
Pull me all the way down,
and I can feel myself
going through the layers of the house.
And when I get to the basement, he
says, I've got you. I finally got you.
She sees a gremlin-type creature.
He could manipulate how he's perceived.
And it knows what scares you.
The other thing that I got was, uh...
He hates children.
He hates kids.
And then I saw one of
the things he was doing,
which I thought was very disturbing,
and I did sketch it, so...
- You sketched it?
- Yeah, I did.
- Where did you see this?
- This.
Oh, so it's Samantha's room.
I don't even know if I
want to show this to you.
That's the closet.
I want this guy.
I'm gonna get this guy.
I'm confronting this little bastard.
That John Cresson [Bleep] him and
I are gonna have some dealings.
I'm gonna sit down, and I'm gonna square
off with that son of a [Bleep] on his own.
He wants a piece of
something, come and [Bleep] me.
- You all right?
- Yep.
I know a few people
that won't be, though.
Problem is you're not
dealing with the living here.
I know.
Samantha is deathly
afraid of the closets.
Because of that, she had me draw
crosses on every one of her walls.
And a huge three-foot cross
on the one closet door.
Wow.
Do you have any idea
why he doesn't like kids?
He's just a jerk.
And he's just a coward.
Very much so.
A sick, sick, sick coward.
I hate to even ask this right now,
but was there anything else you saw?
I saw an old lady.
And I got that she might have been
a relative of someone who lives here.
That she died of cancer, and
she died in the late '90s.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Her mother died of cancer.
I told you she was here.
If it's Angela's Mom,
why would she be here?
She had a lot of
regret. She felt guilty.
And she kept saying that she felt
responsible about everything that happened.
She...
Knew that there was a bad male.
She felt like she could've stopped
it from happening, but she didn't.
My stepfather was a very evil man.
And towards the end, before she
died, I tried to make amends,
and he would not let me speak to
her on the phone or come and see her.
And she died a week later.
She's back to take
the woman of the house.
Death was gonna come to the
house, but she came instead.
Whoa.
When I was leaving, she said, my
job's done. Tell her I'm waiting.
What?
Somebody's coming to kill her?
No.
But someone's coming to
take her when she dies.
Okay.
I mean, for her to take death's
place so that she'll be comfortable.
- So, it's out of love.
- Yeah.
Is her mother really feeling guilty?
Yes.
And you feel guilty, as well.
Why do you feel guilty?
Because I didn't say goodbye.
I didn't get to say that I forgive her.
I knew she'd be there when I died.
Well, listen, it's been a tough night.
And I think you guys got a lot
more than you bargained for.
- For sure.
- Definitely.
But the reason we're here and why
you called us is to see if you...
And your family can live here peacefully
and straighten out what
the hell you got going on.
Yes.
I can't answer that,
but I'm gonna turn it over to my
partner, Amy, and hopefully, she can.
Me, personally, I don't
like this house or this area.
If it's at all within
your means, I would move.
I won't let it beat us.
If we made it this far, we went through
everything we went through so far,
I'm not gonna just roll over and say go
ahead and take it I'm fighting for what's
mine this is our house this is where our
children are gonna grow up this is where
we're gonna be safe whether they like
it or not they're getting the hell out.
You know, monetarily, they can't leave.
It would devastate them, so is
there anything else they can do?
Basically...
Because it seems to be
encompassing the town,
like, you need to build your fortress.
So, the first thing being
for you to get bags of salt.
And go around the
entire property line...
Thick so you see the line on the ground.
When you can do it, I would suggest,
building a fence surrounding
the entire property.
And when you purchase
those building materials.
Have them blessed.
- Wow.
- So, who should do the blessing?
Any real...
Holy person.
Then, with a holy person,
again, of your choice.
They're gonna bless the house.
While this person's
blessing the house...
I want you to take this...
Follow them around, and after
they're done in each room...
Blessing each room...
sprinkle this in the room.
What is this?
This is brimstone.
And it's used in exorcisms.
Oh, my God.
And what will that do?
It'll get rid of the dead people here.
- What about her Mom?
- That woman will stay.
That process cannot stop.
It's natural, organic.
I'm mortified.
I thought there was...
Maybe four things here
and one of them was evil.
But not to this extent.
- Okay.
- We're gonna be fine.
I'm not gonna let nothing
happen to the kids.
Now, I'm gonna ask you, are
you gonna follow Amy's advice?
- Without a doubt.
- Angela?
Yeah.
This is one of those investigations, I got
to tell you, especially because I'm a vet.
The fact that we were able to hopefully
help you here makes me feel good.
I know it makes her feel good.
But from the bottom of my heart, I
really appreciate it from both of you.
- Well, thank you for letting us come in.
- Mm hmm.
Thank you for coming.
I still believe Angela and
Randy would be best off moving.
But since they can't, I really
hope that they follow my advice.
So that their home can be freed of the
dead and their kids will remain safe.