Subs created by: David Coleman.
He murdered somebody, and
he's laughing about it.
There's something here
that wants me to die.
It seems like a devil.
I refused to believe it.
This thing is the possessor,
people worshiped it.
This is the worst case I've ever heard.
I just want to not be afraid anymore.
It can take souls.
It's really bad in here.
My name is Amy Allan.
Something is not right.
I see dead people.
This person might've
been a serial killer.
I speak to dead people.
You get those chills.
And they speak to me.
He is darkness, he is evil.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I think she broke her neck.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Dischiavi, I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
You telling me the truth?
I know every person,
every house, has secrets.
I think the Devil is down here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who the hell would do this?
But Steve and I never speak.
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Who's he looking to kill?
Then we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
You need to get out of here right now.
Or time to get out.
It was like endless darkness.
Amy and I conduct our
investigations separately.
I interview living witnesses, experts,
and dig through the property's dark past.
While Amy communicates
with the other side.
I'm in Williamsport, Pennsylvania,
heading over to see a woman named Jodi.
The activity in her home is so bad,
she and her husband are getting
attacked on a daily basis.
She wants to sell, but he
wants to stay and fight.
She says if Amy and I can't help her
out, she thinks her marriage is done for.
Before Amy arrives, I look
for any leading information.
This home has a lot of family photos
that have to be covered or removed.
Once they're gone, the location
will be ready for tonight's walk.
I just see, like, a
woman off in the distance.
She has very, like,
Native American features.
I don't think she's well.
She has a lot of anger.
So this woman that I was
talking about earlier...
Says that she just wanted
everyone to understand...
Like, she didn't betray them or
mean to hurt anyone, but that,
at the same time, they
needed to learn a lesson.
She feels like they deserve it.
So Jodi, I'm glad I'm here, because
things sounded pretty bad on the phone.
It's rough.
It's really rough.
Because I feel like
nobody believes me, and...
You try to tell people, and they
look at you like you're crazy.
Listen, we're here to help, okay?
All right? We're here to help you, so...
It's gonna be okay, okay?
We're gonna see what we can do.
All right?
Okay, so who lives here
with you, your husband?
Just me and my husband.
- How long have you guys been here?
- We've lived here since 2004.
I didn't even want
to live in this house.
Okay, why'd you call us now, though?
Because of the attacks.
They are more frequent now.
I'm touched every day...
It's just constant.
I'm hearing things
throughout the house, I...
See shadows...
And it's gotten...
To the point where I just feel like
I'm being followed everywhere I go.
I go take a shower...
And it actually feels like somebody
has climbed in the shower with me.
I feel like something
has attached itself to me.
I worry about what's gonna happen to me.
I never know what's gonna
happen from day to day.
I just don't know.
The Native American woman,
she follows this person around.
Can you talk about the person she's...
- Talking to?
- Um, living person...
Seems to be a female...
Um, probably about...
Forties?
I'm not sure what she wants from her.
I just know that she is with her a lot.
Because, I mean, I see them,
like, in the kitchen together,
I see them showering
together, I see them...
You know, her in the room at night.
The dead girl is not
helping the living woman.
What's going on in here?
I saw an apparition
walk past the doorway.
And they were wearing
blue jeans and boots.
So what are we talking about, like
cowboy boots, or like work boots?
They look like work boots.
- Now, was it a man or a woman?
- It was a man.
Okay, so have you seen
anything else like that?
I've seen, like, a
dark shadow of a figure.
I just see it out of the corner of my
eye, and it's like you turn, and it's gone.
Now, let me ask you a question, what
do you think is going on in this house?
I feel like there's
something here that...
Wants me to die.
The thing that I'm seeing
looks like what's depicted
in the Catholic religion as a devil.
To me, it looks like it has
long nails, and evil and [Bleep].
It's saying that it can take
as many souls as it likes.
Like, I'm like, "what are you?"
And he's like, "I am the darkness".
How would people experience him?
It's solid, she's definitely seen it.
Can it hurt people?
It's saying it can and it will.
It's a trickster, it's a
liar, it's a manipulator.
So, Jodi, why'd you bring me in
the basement, what's going on here?
I've seen an apparition of
an Indian sitting right there.
Talking about like a
Native American Indian?
Yes. It looked like he was
dressed, like, ready for war.
Okay, are you experiencing
anything else down here?
Um, yeah, I hear...
What sounds like...
Hammers...
Boards being moved.
I want to describe it as almost
like somebody working on the house.
You have that feeling of uneasiness down
here, I can see it just looking at you.
Yeah, I... don't even
want to be here right now.
Okay, all right, so why
don't we get out of here?
You've spent enough
time down here with me.
One of the things it likes to do is...
That.
Yeah, [Bleep] Around with the doors.
I think this thing is the possessor.
The thing says that, you
know, people worshiped it.
The Native Americans, they
would allow it inside of them
to do things because that
was the way to keep the peace.
I think it would oftentimes
kill the person it possessed.
Okay, Jodi, so what's going on up here?
As soon as I turn my light off to try
to close my eyes and go to sleep...
That's when it gets worse.
Are you getting
physically touched up here?
I've had some stuff
happen to me up here.
Like, almost like somebody's...
Trying to wake me up in
an arousal kind of way.
Okay.
And you toss, you turn, you move, you...
you know, you say, "get away from me"...
And before you know it, something
is over me that you can't see.
- Okay.
- And I was, um...
Attacked.
Sexually.
Have you told anybody this?
I tried to tell my husband about it,
and I don't feel like he believes...
What happened to me.
Um, it's just real hard to talk about.
I imagine that's gotta be the most horrific
thing for a woman to have to deal with.
When I was a young girl,
I was sexually assaulted.
How old were you when this happened?
Um... I was about 12 years old.
Okay, look at me, okay?
So you can trust me, alright I'm listening
to everything you're telling me, okay?
I just want it to end,
I just want to not...
Be afraid in my own house anymore.
It's so hard, because I spend so
much time in this house, alone.
I'm gonna make this okay, all
right? Come here, I promise.
I'm gonna make this right,
we're gonna figure it out, okay?
- Mm hm.
- Don't worry about it.
I think it can do vile things.
- Like what?
- Inappropriate...
Sexual things, sometimes.
And it's very traumatizing and
scary for this person, as I...
Understand.
I hear somebody in this room, a female.
She's mad, she's very
angry, she feels attacked.
She's being messed with
by the... uh, the thing.
It's found her secrets, and it's like...
Messing with her mind through
her secrets or something.
And she's like, can't take
it anymore, she's like...
She's very stressed out.
I feel like it's saying, like,
"you know I'm a part of you,
you know you're a part
of me, I'm gonna get you".
She's very stressed out.
I feel like it's saying, like,
"you know I'm a part of you,
you know you're a part
of me, I'm gonna get you".
So it's mentally abusing her, I guess.
Is this thing targeting her?
Yes, it is.
Patrick, let me ask you a question,
do you know any history of the house?
A little bit, I did read
a few things about some...
The American Indians in this area.
There was a lot of fighting
with other tribes in this...
This particular valley.
- So Patrick, I talked to your wife, Jodi.
- Mm.
And I've done a lot of
these cases, and she...
She's having a tough time here.
I mean, at first, I really...
Didn't believe any of it,
I refused to believe it.
Are you still refusing to believe it?
Um, I can't.
What do you mean you can't?
Me and Jodi was in the
living room talking, and...
We decided to turn the TV off.
So when I turned it off...
I saw a man sitting on
the arm of her chair.
And I told her, I said,
"Jodi, do you see this?"
She says, "what?" I
said, "look in the TV".
And I looked over at her, and
I looked back, it was gone.
There was nothing there,
just her reflection.
What'd he look like?
He had... I want to
call it a farmer's hat.
It looked like he had a beard.
He looked angry, and it scared me.
So what you're telling me is that
you're not a skeptic of what's
going on, you believe there's
something going on in your house.
Yeah, I know there's
something going on here.
But yet at the same time,
your wife seems to think
you're not believing
anything she's telling you.
- When Jodi was attacked...
- Right.
And I came home...
She was...
In, I would say, a state of shock,
I mean, she was just white as a ghost,
she was trembling, she was upset.
Well, I went off, and
I called 'em all out.
I said, "look, if you're this bad
and you're this tough, show yourself".
Okay, so what happened?
I woke up with bruises on my lower back.
And I can't figure out what he is.
It seems like he keeps that form,
like, that look of, like, a devil.
He also likes to make
people feel trapped.
I don't know, like, he's up in the...
Up, up...
He's saying, like, he
murdered somebody or something.
And he's laughing about it.
My main concern right now is my wife.
She sobbed when I
spoke with her, sobbed.
I can't give her answers,
and she keeps asking me,
and, you know, when I can't
answer, what do you do?
- Right.
- That's why I spend so much time out here.
It's breaking my heart,
the both of you, I mean,
it sounds like you two
aren't communicating.
You want to help, you
just don't know how.
It's went downhill, it's went
downhill fast, faster than we want.
But we don't know what to do to fix it.
She's concerned that the
house is gonna kill her.
Wow.
She's been attacked, and attacked in
ways that nobody should be attacked.
I think it wants... whatever
it is wants to hurt her again.
Like I said, I'm not...
I don't want to say dead, because I
don't want to see that happen, but...
This is the worst case I've ever
heard as far as paranormal stuff.
- Can we take a break?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
Patrick told me there were some violent
Native American wars on his property.
Now, most times client leads
turn out to be a dead end,
but this one I want to check out.
I've reached out to a
local historian to see
if there's any truth
to what Patrick said.
So my client told me that the land
I'm investigating, where his house is,
at one time there was warring
Native Americans, is that correct?
That's correct.
There was a treaty signed in 1768.
And that delineated Native American
property from white settler property.
But the white settlers didn't
always obey those guidelines,
and so they were squatting
on Native American property.
And that includes the
property I'm investigating?
- That's right.
- Okay.
Well, the Senecas went on a rampage.
In part because the British had
prompted them, they had given them guns,
they had given them ammunition.
And the Native Americans
began these attacks to
antagonize the white settlers
to move them off the property.
How many white settlers did get
killed during these conflicts?
There are at least 370 documented.
Now who was in charge of these guys?
They were led by Chief Cornplanter.
He was a very peaceful man.
He didn't sound so peaceful
after what you just told me.
I think, perhaps, he
was a reluctant warrior.
He loved his nation, he
loved his tribe, and so...
He decided to go along, of course, with
the majority, and the majority ruled.
So now I'm seeing this guy.
I think it's a Native American.
Um...
He has feathers in his hair.
I think he feels guilty.
There's only so much that you want
to see your enemies fall to revenge.
I think he thinks he
needs to make things right.
This Native American knows
all about the Devil creature
I've been seeing throughout the house.
And he's telling me his people
had to deal with it, too.
He's saying people
worshiped it, and, um...
But not anymore.
You know, you have to
do things for this devil.
Otherwise, it will do
uncontrollable things.
Now let me ask you a question about
the property I'm investigating.
Any of those attacks
happen right on my property?
- Well, June 10, 1778...
- Okay.
The Plum Tree Massacre, as
it's widely known, occurred.
Okay, what happened?
There was a wagon-load of 16 settlers,
and there were Native
Americans of the Seneca tribe.
They were concealed in
a group of plum trees.
And so when the wagon passed through,
the Native Americans attacked.
So 16 settlers go through, and they
get ambushed, were they all killed?
Twelve were massacred... there
were two children who were killed.
Two of the people were women, they
were both scalped and stabbed...
Tomahawked, and left for dead.
And two of the girls were kidnapped.
Do you know what happened to them?
I know that they were taken to Canada.
I don't know the rest of the story.
Okay.
I'm hearing a lot of...
Gunfire nearby.
And this man, he's hiding.
He's crouched down, and
he's, like, shivering.
And he's hearing all of the...
The fighting and gunshots.
It was unexpected... whatever
happened was completely unexpected.
Women are screaming and running,
people are running all over the place.
Men are yelling at each other and
shooting each other and shooting people...
Somebody's yelling about the apocalypse.
I definitely want to follow
up on what happened to the
two young girls kidnapped
on my client's property.
I'm heading over to
meet with a local author
who says the story had
a very dramatic ending.
So I understand there was this Plum Tree
Massacre on the property I'm investigating
and that two young girls
were actually kidnapped
by the Native Americans
that did that massacre.
What can you tell me about that?
The two girls' names were Ruth
and Sarah King, age 2 and 4.
Their father's name was William
King, he was a member of the militia,
the colonial militia, and he was out of
the area when the massacre took place.
But the mother, Rachel, was gruesomely
killed in front of her two daughters.
But, for some reason,
these girls were spared
and taken up the
Sheshequin Trail to Canada.
- Okay.
- The younger child, Ruth...
Was sold to the wife of a British officer
who apparently couldn't have children.
And we don't know for sure what
happened to her sister Sarah,
but she did survive, and
she was in the area there.
Okay, so now, William King comes back
and found out his wife was murdered
and his two kids were missing.
That's correct.
There's this man...
I feel like he's alone.
I think maybe his wife is dead.
Uh, and maybe his children are far away.
There's also, like, a
woman off in the distance.
Like, I kinda get "escapee" with her.
She has a lot of anger.
Definitely a lost soul, that's for sure.
So what happened with the kids?
Well, their father never totally
gave up hope that he'd find them.
And seven years after
the massacre happened he,
found out where they were, and
so he set out to retrieve them.
He found an Indian guide to take
him north towards Fort Niagara.
Okay.
Somehow, he recovers the two children
and brings them back down
to the Williamsport area.
And led what appeared to
be a fairly normal life.
'Til, in 1802, he had an accident
on the river, a creek, he fell in,
got paralyzed, and it lingered
for several days, and died.
- Huh.
- At the age of 57.
I'm heading to the local library to find
anything else I can about
my client's property.
Searching through the archives...
I discovered the Lord family
lived there for generations.
Turns out, a lot of the family
members died on my client's land.
But a local genealogist tells me
a couple of those deaths
might help my investigation.
Now, the Lord family owned the property
I'm investigating for a pretty long time.
Yes, nearly 80 years, from 1882 to 1961.
Now, of all the deaths on this property,
you said a couple of them are unusual.
Oh, yes, there were two sisters.
The first was Sarah Bricker...
She lived in the house
out back of the property.
And, in 1903, she came over
to visit her sister next door.
- Okay.
- And just fell over dead.
From what?
What we would now say is
stroke or a cerebral hemorrhage.
Okay, so Sarah was 40 years old,
which was young, even for back then.
Yes.
Then, ten years later,
her sister, Amanda Lord,
passes away suddenly of the same thing.
Wow.
Okay, so ten years apart, two
sisters die from the same illness...
- On the same property.
- Yes.
That is unusual.
It's a sickness here.
Someone died in this room.
Very ill, female.
This woman, she crawls...
Into the ceiling and disappears.
So she doesn't have any
interaction with anybody.
Her pain is still
something that is here.
In a physical way.
She's like, "oh, you know,
bad, bad, it was bad".
There were several entities
that stood out during my walk.
But what has me the most concerned
is the Devil creature that's
tormenting a living woman.
This thing was coming out of a closet.
And it was pitch black, but
its skin was, like, glossy.
And there was a woman
who was yelling at him.
Is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations...
We're ready to reveal our findings to each
other and our clients for the first time.
Well, Amy, I gotta tell ya,
this is probably one of the
hardest cases I've ever worked on.
I want to introduce
you to Jodi and Patrick.
They're a married couple that live here.
Listening to their stories was
pretty gut-wrenching for me.
Bottom line, Jodi thinks there's something
in this house that's trying to kill them.
And kill her specifically.
It's tearing their marriage apart.
They called us in because we're their
last hope so, with that being said,
I'm gonna ask Amy to tell us
a little bit about her walk.
I'm definitely aware that there's
a lot of issues here, and, um...
We'll get into everything
slowly but surely.
I went to the back yard, and...
I saw a lot of...
Really odd, like, violent
and chaotic images.
I was hearing gunfire.
It wasn't just men, you
know, I heard women screaming.
I think I saw a woman get shot.
Whatever was happening had
just come out of nowhere.
A lot of what you're saying
is something I uncovered
and that you had pointed
me in the direction of.
You gotta know something about
this property we're on, Amy.
It was the scene of fierce battles of...
Native Americans against white settlers.
On June 10 in 1778,
right on this property...
There was an event called
the Plum Tree Massacre.
And when that massacre
was over, men, women,
and children were murdered,
all shot, stabbed, and scalped.
Where did the Native Americans live?
Here, this is their land.
White settlers were breaking
a treaty that was set in 1768.
Well, a lot of other stuff I got
is totally making sense now, so...
Okay.
At one point, I went
into the basement, and,
I encountered a Native American man.
He said that he feels guilty.
And he feels like, you
know, you can only want
so much agony for your enemies.
Now, Jodi, you saw a Native American
man in the basement, as well, right?
- Yes.
- Describe that for Amy for me.
He was sitting... what looked
like he was sitting on top
of the pipe in the back
room of the basement.
The brown pants, um, I
could see the white feathers.
I turned to walk away and turned
back around, and he was gone.
Who I think both of you might
have encountered is, um...
This guy Chief Cornplanter.
He was the war Chief
for the Seneca tribe.
This is a portrait.
Cornplanter is his
Indian name translated.
Wow.
He was considered a peaceful man.
He didn't want to be part
of any kind of fighting.
But after his tribe made a treaty with the
British Army, he became a violent killer.
He's responsible for killing at least
370 men, women, and children in this area.
Even though he was a peaceful man, he
turned into one of the bloodiest killers...
- Which makes sense.
- So, is this who you think you saw?
- I think it could be, yes, I do.
- Okay.
I also ran into a Native American woman.
Unfortunately, the other
thing I got was that
she actually had
attached herself to you.
Like, I literally kinda saw
her, like, holding your arm.
She even, like, goes
into the bath with you.
Like, she just doesn't really leave you
alone, she's always kind of by your side.
And I would think that you would feel
her presence, because she's always on you.
Everywhere I go in this house, I feel...
It feels like somebody else's
energy around me, constantly.
Anywhere I sit, it just feels like
somebody is with me, sharing my body.
It's just everywhere I
go. I go to bed at night...
Somebody's there.
I'm just not ever alone.
I tried to tell my family
what was going on in my house,
and they all laughed at me.
And ridiculed me.
I don't go to family functions, because I
know what they say about me behind my back.
Plus she doesn't think that Patrick
actually believes anything she says.
I understand people who
are skeptics because,
I think that when they
lash out like that, it's...
Based out of fear and ignorance.
I've gotta see things
in order to believe it.
It's been a tremendous
strain on our family.
It's been almost three years that
we've been putting up with this, the...
The ridicule.
But this is your wife and
your partner in your life.
You need to stand by her side and...
Screw the people who
are calling her names.
I get so angry, because he goes...
He goes and he leaves me sitting here.
Knowin' how they feel about me.
And it's very hard to sit here alone.
And I can't do anything with them.
Because, because they think I'm crazy.
You see right now, I mean,
it's tearing me up right now.
Because she's so tore up.
I know this has been a
pretty tough night already,
but I think, Amy, you have more stuff?
I also came into contact
with another entity.
It...
Showed itself to me at one point
to look like a traditional...
Out-of-the-Bible devil.
The truer self of it was,
like, this very tall...
Um, completely black but
with, like, shiny skin.
And it had long, like,
fingers and nails.
And little horns, and, um...
It can show itself in different ways.
A Native American female
told me that this...
Thing had been here
for a very long time.
How would they see it is
what I'm curious about?
I would think some kind of blackness.
I see a lot of dark figure
shadows moving through the kitchen.
And a lot up in my bedroom.
It seemed to me that
he was focusing on you.
He had found whatever weakness
he perceives from you, about you.
He was psychologically abusing you.
He was grabbing and licking you and
doing inappropriate sexual things to you.
I was sexually assaulted
several times in the house.
I've been traumatized and basically
terrorized for three years.
I feel something standing over
me when I'm in my bed, and...
I'm scared.
How you doing over there?
The day that she was
attacked, that I came home...
I went through this house, screaming.
And I called whatever it was...
"You want something to
deal with, come get me".
And I woke up with bruises...
On my back.
That's one of the things I can't...
Debunk.
It's hard for me to be intimate
with my own husband because...
Of what happened to me.
She shared with me, when she was
younger, much younger, she was...
- I was gonna ask, right.
- Sexually assaulted by a family member.
- She doesn't have a support system.
- She does now.
I did do a sketch of what I saw
upstairs in your room, and...
It seemed to be that you were...
Very angry and stressed out at the time.
Oh,.
I just want my life back.
Jodi, come here.
I did do a sketch of what I saw
upstairs in your room, and...
It seemed to be that you were...
Very angry and stressed out at the time.
Oh,.
I just want my life back.
Come here, Jodi, come here.
Put your arms around me, Jodi, please.
Nobody believed me.
Who cares? [Bleep] 'Em.
Look at me...
We will take care of this, okay?
I love you.
You okay?
What is this thing?
This thing says that...
It has taken souls before.
It says that it has
and will hurt people.
And it stated, you know
that he's a part of you
and you're a part of him and
that he's going to get you.
He was also trying to project bad images
or dreams or something to you
to try to make you hurt yourself.
And that's part of the
manipulation that he was doing.
Now listen, Jodi, Patrick,
this has gotta be...
One of the most extremely emotional
nights you've ever been through.
I know it has been for me when
it comes to working these cases.
But Jodi, now you know you're not crazy,
and you're actually in a fight
against something that's real.
Now, the big question, is there anything
you can do about it? And can you live a...
Normal life and get your
marriage back on track?
For that, I'm gonna turn it over
to Amy and see what she has to say.
After the walk...
I did some research.
Because I came into contact
with so many Native Americans...
I wanted to see if there
was anything in their history
that would clarify
maybe what this could be.
What I came across was...
Something that tribes
referred to as the clown...
The trickster, and heyoka.
It was a human.
But they also felt that it
was half man and half spirit.
It's very possible that this entity...
Was a human being.
At one point and was part of a tribe.
And when he died, he
became the embodiment of it.
So how do they get rid of this thing?
First thing is, you should contact
your local Native American tribe.
That would be the Seneca
tribe for this area.
And you want to connect with the Shaman.
Let them know everything
that's been going on,
and then allow them to do whatever
ceremony they think is necessary.
Being raised Catholic and listening
to everything and seeing what I saw...
Part of me wants to still...
Follow the train of thought
that this is some type of demon.
The next day, I would like you
to have someone from your church
come to your home and perform
an exorcism of the house.
What about this woman that's attached
to her, what happens with her?
As you start doing an exorcism this...
Native American male will remove her.
I don't think I have to ask you
if you're gonna take Amy's advice.
I'm definitely gonna do
everything she told me to do.
I just want this gone, I want...
I want to be able to
live in my home in peace
and not have to worry about this
when I lay my head down at night.
I can't say I'm a skeptic anymore.
I'm not sure whether it will
be the Shaman or the exorcism
that will get rid of
these evil entities.
But if they follow my advice
and perform these two rituals...
Jodi and Patrick will finally be
free and able to live in peace again.