Subs created by: David Coleman.
I think this girl's being murdered.
She's terrified.
There's something here.
Objects being thrown at people.
She can't breathe.
- Scratches up here on my arm.
- That could be a problem.
Oh, my God. What's happening?
Something terrible's happened to her!
It's really bad in here.
My name is Amy Allan.
Something is not right.
I see dead people.
This person might have
been a serial killer.
I speak to dead people.
You get those chills.
And they speak to me.
He is darkness. He is evil.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I think she broke her neck.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
Are you telling me the truth?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I think the Devil is down here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who the hell would do this?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Who's he looking to kill?
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
You need to get out of here right now.
Or time to get out.
It was like endless darkness.
Amy and I never communicate
during an investigation.
I learn about the dead through
interviews and research.
While Amy speaks directly to them.
In the end, we meet up and reveal
our findings to each other...
And our clients for the first time.
I'm in Waxahachie, Texas, about
20 minutes south of Dallas.
I'm heading over to meet
with a woman named Shawn,
who owns a family restaurant in town.
She says things have
gotten so out of control,
she's worried about the safety
of her employees and her guests.
She says Amy and I are her last hope.
I can't hide the fact
that this is a restaurant.
But I still need to be careful
to remove or cover any pictures,
signs, or decorations that
could influence Amy's findings.
In my opening, a Sheriff came up.
And he pointed to four graves.
I think he knew some of these guys.
And said that...
Those men had...
Caused a lot of fear at the time.
I'm getting a really weird smell.
What a weird smell! What is this?
Blood, it's blood.
I'm tasting it, yeah. Yeah, it's blood.
Ugh.
So, Shawn, you sounded pretty concerned
on the phone about what's going on here.
Yeah, we are... we are very concerned.
My daughter works up
here, she's 16 years old.
My mother, my husband,
and my dad are up here.
And we, you know, want
to make sure everything is
perfectly safe for everyone
that comes through that door.
Okay. So, give me an idea what kind
of experiences you guys are having.
Well, we've seen
apparitions, shadow people...
Things moving around, so it
pretty much runs the gamut.
- So, how long have you been here?
- I've been here for seven years.
Okay. And how long has
the activity been going on?
Forever, as far as I know.
So, why're you calling us in now?
Things have seemed to
kind of start picking up...
Like objects being thrown
at people in my kitchen,
and my daughter Amelia
was physically slapped.
So we're worried about her.
What do you hope we can do for you,
as far as the investigation goes?
I would like my children to be able to
pass on this legacy to
their children, and so on.
This is part of who we are.
Shawn, what about your customers?
Are they experiencing anything?
They have told me about a lot
of the things that are happening.
In fact, I have some ghost
logs that I'm gonna show you.
- Whoa, geez!
- These are some firsthand accounts...
That we have received
from some of our guests.
We have two more like that.
You're kidding?
Wow!
Now, what do you know about the history
of this place, I mean, it is pretty old?
Well, there's a legend about a love
triangle that occurred near this location.
Where a young lady was murdered.
Wow, okay. Why don't you
show me around the restaurant?
All right. Come on. Let's go this way.
I'm seeing this little
lady, like, about this tall.
And there's a male.
Her son, I think.
He's younger, 40s.
He's not nice.
It's really strange.
She feels so much stress.
Why?
Cause she can't leave here ever.
What's going on in this room
that you brought me in here?
There are all sorts of descriptions
in that log book as far as apparitions.
We get lots of reports on an older lady.
Any description on her?
That she wears glasses,
that's the only thing
that people have all
consistently said... glasses.
Okay.
And one of the things that
I have seen in this room is
some sort of shadowy figure
that appears under this table.
Really?
- It's like a solid figure.
- Okay.
And it's shaped like a person.
And we're positive it's not something
coming from the window, making it look...
- Yes, I'm absolutely, 100% positive.
- Why is that?
Occasionally, guests will say that
they felt something touching their leg.
Wow.
It's very upsetting.
The older woman and the son...
You know if anybody might have
experiences related to them?
I think that they might both be
seen um, as, like, apparitions.
Okay.
Her, though...
I definitely think she
would try to talk to people.
Okay.
And if she doesn't like something, I
think she would let people know somehow.
Are there any areas in particular
that they might be more?
In here.
Well, this is a busy kitchen, obviously
getting ready for the dinner crowd.
So why'd you bring me in here?
Just today, we were actually
standing over there and,
this glass just inexplainably broke.
- And nothing fell on top of it?
- No.
Did you hear the crack?
Yes, that's why we looked over there.
Wow. Anything else?
I have had what appeared to
be scratches, like three...
One, two, three, scratches
up here on my arm.
I was cooking, and I
thought I'd burned myself.
Well, that's my obvious question,
right? Did you burn yourself?
No. That's like a burn mark.
In my experience working with
Amy, that could be a problem.
Anything else in the kitchen?
I was here one day, and I'd see
something like a white apparition.
And it looked just like
a person walking back...
You know, like walking back and forth.
How tall would you say it was?
Probably about six feet tall.
It had arms and such.
Okay. What if Amy did tell you...
It's a little bit too dangerous here
to be here, for you and your guests?
That would just be sad, if it
was not something that I could...
Pass on to my daughter.
So I'm hoping that there's a solution
that will allow us to stay here.
All right.
This area's not good.
I'm seeing a weird shadow.
Of a female.
Her arms are long and thin.
She's stretching out.
Mm!
- Are you okay?
- No!
She can't feel her arms or legs.
And she can't breathe.
No... like [Bleep]!
Why are my arms so long?
Oh, my God. What's happening?
Oh!
I'm not right.
She's not right anymore!
Something terrible's happened to her!
This woman is desperate
to tell her story.
So I'm doing something that I almost
never do because it's so dangerous.
Ow, my arms!
Oh, my God!
I'm letting her jump
me, or enter my body,
so she can speak through
me and I can feel her pain.
She can't find what she's looking for.
She's a mess. She's a mess.
Um, she does not understand
what's happened to her.
When you bought this place, did you
have any idea it might be haunted?
- No, I was a total skeptic.
- Okay, so what about now?
A lot different now. I
totally believe it now.
There's something here.
What changed your mind?
Well, I have a daughter,
a younger daughter.
- Right.
- She's eight now.
She was in the front
dining room one morning,
and I heard her talking to somebody.
So I asked her, I says, hey,
baby, who you playing with?
And she turned the other way and looked
up and then says, what's your name?
She asked somebody there what their
name was, and she wasn't talking to me.
- So, did she tell you a name or anything?
- Yeah.
- What'd she say?
- She said Eliza.
She said she wanted her
to stay with her tonight.
Okay. Anything else?
One time, I came in
through the back door,
and passed one of our... just a
manager who was working there...
And all of a sudden this loud bang
crash happened right behind me.
Well, what we call our fish racks...
Flew over his head and landed
in the middle of the kitchen.
I mean, I was shocked. I
didn't know what to think.
Now, do you think
whatever's here is dangerous?
Oh, yeah. It's very concerning,
you know, it's very upsetting.
Well let me ask you this,
would you be comfortable turning
this over to your daughter
right now and then walking away?
No, I don't think I would.
- You wouldn't?
- No.
She throws things.
In here, in the kitchen.
I think that she...
Is talking all the time.
I think that they would feel...
The pains.
I think that...
She looks...
Scary.
To people.
She's trying to understand what...
Is going on.
She...
Keeps...
Seeing things that...
Frighten her.
She's getting panicked again.
It's okay...
It's okay.
So, Doctor, you're Shawn's dad.
- Yes.
- You're also a former Marine, like myself.
You're a scientist,
as well as an engineer.
That's correct.
Straight out blunt, is there
something going on in this place?
The unexplained events that
occurs in this restaurant.
Well, give me an idea
what we're talking about.
There was one situation in which I was
in the back, and I was cutting fish...
And someone says something to me, so I
laid the knife down on the cutting board...
- And I turned around to talk to him.
- Okay.
When I turned back around...
The knife was falling
from in front of me...
And stuck in the board.
I could see no explanation for it.
I can't even try to debunk it for you.
I find it very disconcerting.
There's a entity here.
Whether that entity is good or bad...
Is unknown...
But we don't take it lightly.
She has to figure it out.
Because when she figures it
out, it will all make sense.
Please tell me what you remember.
She's... And then I can't breathe.
The woman that's jumped
my body is struggling
to piece together
what's happened to her.
She's gasping for air, and
I'm feeling all of her pain.
And it hurts!
Like, she can't breathe.
I think this girl is being murdered.
Shawn told me there was a
legend about a love triangle
where a young girl was
murdered on the property.
So, I'm on my way to meet with the
local Police Chief to see if it's true.
My client said that there
was a female that was
murdered on their property,
some kind of a lover's quarrel.
Is there any truth to that at all?
Yes, actually there is.
April 30th of 1929, there was a young
lady murdered on that property area.
Okay, so it doesn't sound
like it happened in the
house I'm investigating,
but on the property.
Yes. The victim is this young lady here.
She was a 19-year-old
divorcee...
Miss Lola Roller, and this
Doctor, Dr. Harry Dowling...
Is apparently interested
in her in a romantic way.
Chief, do we know if they actually
ever had a relationship together?
No, indications are that they didn't.
I mean, he was 48 years old, she was 19.
She'd already told
members of her family that
she did not want a
relationship with him.
So, what does she wind up doing next?
She leaves the Temple area, comes
to Waxahachie to get away from him.
She comes up here, where her
Uncle lives, a Mr. H.L. Hempkins.
And she stays with him in his house.
He's a local grocer up here.
So, Hempkins lived on the plantation
property I'm investigating.
Correct.
So, she's at the house, and Dr.
Dowling finds out where she is.
And he is told by Mr. Hempkins that he's
not welcome, he's not gonna let him in.
Well, Dr. Dowling forced his way in.
So, Mr. Hempkins went
next door from his house...
To his grocery store
to retrieve his weapon.
And he also gets a hold of the Sheriff.
So, Chief, when the Uncle and the
Sheriff come back to the house...
- Is she already dead, what's going on?
- No, she's not dead at that time.
They find that Dowling and her
are involved in a physical
altercation going on at that time.
She feels like something's missing.
There's something missing.
A person, she's trying to find a person.
I hear the men, they're talking.
But it was too late.
There's, like, three... three of them.
I feel pain.
Some kind of pain.
The Sheriff can see that
Dr. Dowling has a weapon.
The Sheriff tries to get the
gun away from Dr. Dowling.
But he's unsuccessful.
And Dr. Dowling fires three
shots at the victim, Miss Lola.
Okay.
Hits her once in the
head, twice in the body.
Oh, God [Bleep]!
She can't move. She's so angry,
she can't move her [Bleep] legs.
I see...
How much it hurts.
Uh, and then I can't breathe.
I can't get the breath into my body.
And it hurts.
She thinks that she might be dying.
What happens next?
Well, Mr. Hempkins, from behind
the Sheriff, shoots Dr. Dowling.
And hits him in the head.
But there's also some question
that the good Doctor...
Had intended something, or
knew something might happen.
Because in his wallet was found a note,
that in case something happens,
contact either one of these two people.
Because I'm going to go get
the only woman I've ever loved.
Chief, this sounds like this must've
been some huge case back then.
Well, it was a pretty good-sized case,
obviously at that particular time,
but it's not the only one involving
ladies that have been killed in that area,
within one mile of the place
that you're talking about.
The story of Lola's murder is like
something right out of a movie.
It's hard to believe
there's several other cases
similar to that within a
mile of Shawn's restaurant.
I'm heading over to meet with
the County Sheriff, who's done the
research on those cases, and he
said it will definitely help my case.
You mentioned you found some
more cases very close to the
property I'm investigating,
similar to the Roller homicide.
- We did.
- Okay, what were you able to find out?
Ernest Feray, a 56-year-old
man, shot his wife, Amanda.
He shot her in the head
for throwing a vase at him.
Here's a picture of him in an article.
How far from the Catfish
Plantation did this homicide happen?
It's approximately.8 of a mile.
- Okay, so pretty close.
- Yes, Sir.
- Was there any other cases?
- Yes.
In 1914...
Thomas Hastings shot his 18-year-old wife,
mable, and then turned the gun on himself.
And they were both found in the
kitchen area of their apartment.
And how far from the plantation is this?
- This one was.7 of a mile, I believe.
- Okay.
Then, we had another one that was
approximately two blocks
from the Catfish Plantation.
On this one here is Charles
Allverson and his wife, Maggie.
Maggie was taking
medication for an illness,
and her husband, Charles, decided
to mix strychnine in the medication.
She died of a stomach poisoning.
This is another female
murdered by the husband.
You find this unusual
when you read about this?
Yes.
We have between 8 and
10 homicides a year.
And that's 990-square-miles.
Right. And these are four homicides
within a mile of the Catfish Plantation.
- Yep.
- That's interesting.
There's, um, a lot of people.
Um, and it's not safe.
Letting the murdered girl jump
me took almost all of my energy.
But now that she's out of my body,
there are other dead here
who are trying to communicate.
Something's happening, and
this woman's freaking out.
There's a lot of stomach pain.
Someone's saying, self-inflicted.
There was some kind of
love going on or something.
And it was horrible,
and it ended horribly.
Ugh.
Now that I know four women were
murdered within a mile of my
client's property, I need to see
if anything else went down there.
So, I head to the local library.
Searching through the archives, I
discover a former Major League ball player
named Paul Richards who used
to live on my client's land.
Turns out, he suffered a great
deal of loss in his time there.
So I reached out to a local
genealogist who says his
story is filled with fame,
tragedy, and family feuds.
The property I'm investigating was once
owned by one of Waxahachie's
most famous residents.
Well, that's true.
Paul Richards was a baseball player.
And I have a photo here of him.
In that photo, he's a
manager of the Orioles.
Now, you had mentioned on the phone
that he had some hardships in his life.
Sadly, he lost a
brother, a half-brother.
He was only 24 years old.
And then, later, he
lost his father, in 1937.
And then, Paul Richards lost
his six-year-old daughter.
Just three weeks before
his mother passed away.
So, I would imagine
it's got to be tough.
Very hard, but he and his mother
sometimes weren't on the best of terms.
I want to show you this photograph
of her in her later years.
Right after his windfall of winning
the pennant and getting some money.
He had indoor plumbing
installed in his mother's home.
- Okay.
- And, um, so...
I'm sure he thought that she would be very
pleased with that, but when he asked her,
she said to him that she would've
just as soon had a new dress.
To him, it was very serious,
and they were on the outs with
each other for a long, long time.
Her son.
She says that he's like...
Money-hungry.
She says she spoiled him badly.
And so she's kind of, like, upset.
Because he turned out that way.
And isn't a better person.
She says he definitely...
Exploited people for money.
And she's like, cause
I think he's the Devil.
You have any idea how he died?
He was playing golf.
At Waxahachie Country Club,
and he died of a heart attack.
At the age of 77.
I am getting a lot
of physical pain here.
Now, I'm getting, like... I'm getting,
like, maybe this is heart attack.
Yeah, definitely a heart attack.
I think this is her son.
I'm having a sketch artist draw the two
entities who stood out
the most from my walk.
First, the old woman.
She was...
Probably...
In her late 60s...
About 5'4.
She had smaller eyes.
Almond-shaped.
Next, the woman who jumped me, and
how she projects herself to the living.
She's kind of disfigured.
Her arms are...
Too long.
And her hair is like
sticking in clumps...
Out away from her head.
Is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
finished our investigations,
it's time to reveal our findings to our
clients and each other for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to
meet Shawn and David.
They're married.
They're part owners of the
Catfish Plantation restaurant.
It's a family business.
Actually, her parents work there,
as well as your 16-year-old daughter.
And that's where the problem comes in.
There's a lot of activity in this
place, and their concern is...
Is it safe for them, their
family, and their guests?
And, they would like to eventually
turn it over to their kids.
They called us in to see if
there's a solution for it.
So, with that, I'm gonna have Amy
tell us a little bit about her walk.
When I went in, these two dead
people met me right at the door.
It was an elderly little lady,
and a male who might be her son.
And she told me...
That he is...
Not a very nice person.
He was very money-hungry.
And then, I was feeling
symptoms of a heart attack.
As far as interactions with the living.
People might see them as apparitions.
One day, we were at the restaurant, our
youngest daughter was up there with us,
and she was in the front
playing, just being a kid.
And I came around the corner,
I could hear her talking,
and it was an imaginary
friend, I'm sure.
And as I listened to her for a few
moments, some of the things she was saying
made me believe that it was almost like
a motherly or a grandmother-type figure.
Wanting her to spend the night.
Interesting.
Now, I wanted to tell you
about the Richards family
that lived in this
house for about 45 years.
Paul Richards was a
mediocre baseball player,
but a pretty good manager
in the Major Leagues.
And he lived here in
this house with his mom.
- Oh.
- I actually have a photo of him.
This is Paul Richards.
He had some heartbreak in his life.
He had a 24-year-old half-brother
who died from Tuberculosis.
In 1951, his six-year-old daughter
died from a tear in the heart.
Three weeks later, his mother
fell, and she died a few days later.
Hmm.
Now, Amy, you mentioned
that the older woman
kind of thought he was
money-hungry in life.
Well, the mom and Paul
Richards had an argument...
Over money and didn't talk after that.
But after he wins the World Series,
and comes into some money, obviously...
Um... he goes ahead and buys her
indoor plumbing for the house.
She turns around and says, well, why,
you should've just bought me a new dress.
- You also mentioned a heart attack.
- Yes.
He did die of a heart attack, on
a golf course right in Waxahachie.
Geez, wow.
Now, I have a picture of his
mom, Sarah, when she was older.
It couldn't have been too
long before she passed, either.
I have a younger photo of her.
What a difference.
- We've seen her.
- Really?
Mm-hmm.
That's giving me chills.
I saw her in between these ages.
And I did do a sketch of her.
All right.
Well, you guys take a look.
- Mm hmm.
- Holy smokes.
Wow.
They're very similar.
The hair is, you know, right on.
The brow, and the ridge line right
there, right above the nose...
All seem to be very right on.
- You think this is who you might've seen?
- Probably, yeah.
She was showing me a
lot of different scenes.
Or situations that she
had seen in her life.
What I could see and make out of
them, ended, like, with people dead.
The one that I could make the most...
Sense out of was about a female.
I started getting really
bad stomach pains, and...
Someone out of these dead people
said that it was self-inflicted.
There was love involved, and
that it ended just horribly.
From 1914 to 1929, there
were four women murdered...
- What? What?
- Within a mile radius of the restaurant.
Now, I think the murder you're talking
about is this woman, Maggie Allverson.
She had been sick with
some stomach ailments...
- Okay.
- And she was taking medication.
Her husband, Charles, decided to
mix the medication with strychnine.
And wound up killing her with it.
Now...
- Nice.
- Yeah.
This is her death certificate
here, Maggie Allverson.
She was about 40 years old when she died.
He was a little bit younger. He was 34.
This only happened two blocks...
- Oh!
- From the restaurant.
It was close. So she probably knew her.
I mean, it's a small town, everybody
knows everybody in this size town.
- Yes.
- Wow. Hmm.
Makes so much sense to me.
What else you see?
I was in the bathroom area.
And I started to get this
really intense, negative feeling,
like when you're almost
in a car accident.
I felt a woman near me.
And then I did something
that I very rarely do...
And I let her jump me.
She stayed with me for
about a half an hour or so.
Wow.
So, were you in control
or you don't remember?
Um, initially, I was not.
Is she trying to communicate
through you, or what was going on?
Well, I can show you, because...
- We have Matt's cameras.
- Let me see it.
Oh, my God, what's happening?
Ow, my arms!
Oh, my God!
I'm not right!
She's just not right anymore!
Something terrible happened to her!
I don't even know what
to say about this, I don't
like that you did it,
to be honest with you.
What is this woman's deal?
What's the story with her?
She's very confused and scared.
She's constantly reliving her...
Her death.
She doesn't understand
at all what is going on.
She was waiting, I think, for
somebody to come and get her.
She saw some men...
Um, come in towards her.
- She said, I think I'm dying.
- Oh, no!
Um, and then she was like trying to
make her body breathe, and it couldn't.
I got a lot of pain here, in my neck.
Um, and the front of my chest.
So, I think at that point she was
probably dead but still inside her body.
That's awful.
I think I have an
answer, but I'm not sure.
Remember I told you there
was four women murdered?
- Right.
- Okay.
One of the women that was murdered, died,
not in the house, but on the property.
Back in 1929 on April 30th.
Her name was Lola Roller.
She was 19 years old.
This is her.
She lived in Temple, which
is about 100 miles from here.
She came up here to get away from a
48-year-old Doctor. He was a veterinarian.
His name was Dr. Harry Dowling,
who fell in love with her, and
she wanted nothing to do with him.
They never even had a
relationship together.
She comes up here to
stay with her Uncle.
Somehow, he finds out she's up here.
He drives up, finds out the house she's
in, goes to the door, knocks on it.
The Uncle answers, says, you're
not allowed in here, get away!
He had a grocery store
next to the house.
He went there to go get his
gun and then get the Sheriff.
When they come back, somehow
Dr. Dowling got into the house.
And when the Uncle
and the Sheriff arrive,
he's got her and they're
in a physical altercation.
The Doctor, he's got a gun in his hand.
The Sheriff tried to gun away from him, a
fight ensues, there's a big fight going on.
And the Doctor he puts one
in her head, two in her chest.
Whoa.
The Uncle, he puts one into
the Doctor's head and kills him.
The thing that really
bothers her is that she...
Sees herself very strangely.
She does not know that she's dead.
To her, she's still fighting.
- It's very confusing.
- It's sad.
The way that she sees herself...
Is basically like a shadow.
And her limbs are...
Extremely long and thin.
I kind of thought that that's maybe
how living people would see her.
Okay.
Like a female shadow
that's kind of distorted.
I'm having a little trouble understanding
how that would actually look.
Well, I did do a sketch.
That's odd.
Take a look at that.
Wow, I've seen that.
I did do a sketch.
That's odd.
Take a look at that.
Wow, I've seen that.
This is very upsetting to me.
It's a dark figure.
That crouches underneath the
tables in the burgundy dining room.
So, is it possible that the
shadow thing she's seen is Lola?
Yes.
What does she do? I mean...
Well, she...
Will break things...
She'll throw things around,
especially in the kitchen.
She is always screaming
and yelling and crying.
Wow.
- Can she become frustrated?
- Oh, yeah.
We have our racks that
we use for cooking.
And I was almost out of the
kitchen, and they flew off the shelf,
and flew over our assistant manager's
head and landed behind... right behind me.
Oh, wow.
Now, one of the biggest reasons
we're here is she's been scratched.
On her left arm.
Show Amy where you were scratched.
It was just right like that.
Just like three fingernail marks.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's her.
The scratches, I think, are...
Something that occurred
during the struggle.
Okay.
I'm very sorry for her.
I knew these things weren't
just happening for no reason,
that someone was trying
to tell us something.
We still haven't answered
your most pressing question...
Is it gonna be safe here for
you, your family, your guests?
And, even more importantly, is it gonna
be okay for you to pass it on to your kids?
Right.
For that answer, I'm
gonna turn it over to Amy.
We'll start with the mother and son.
A local medium needs to come in.
And talk to...
Her.
You know, she has so much anger.
She needs to talk about,
you know, her life.
And the things that
are keeping her here.
Okay.
Once these two have spoken.
Let the medium do whatever they need to.
Um, to make sure that they move on.
As far as she's concerned, this
is a little bit more detailed.
There are two people you need for this.
You get another medium,
and a grief counselor.
So, they have to come together,
the medium and the counselor?
Yes.
Okay.
The medium might get jumped.
So, they should take
this slow and steady.
Um, with several meetings.
Okay.
By the third meeting, the
start of therapy begins.
This is when the grief counselor...
Will really take over as far as
counseling this person who's dying.
We're dealing with somebody,
again, who is extremely traumatized,
because she's never moved on.
And at first, you know, things
might become more active...
Because she might be pissed.
But that should just be
temporary until she leaves.
I've got to ask the question
I ask all my clients...
Are you gonna take Amy's
advice and do what she says?
I think that we need to
help Lola, definitely.
Absolutely, cause, I mean,
it's almost terrifying
just to think about
what she's going through.
We feel compelled to help.
Lola continues to suffer in death.
But if Shawn and David follow my advice,
I'm confident she will be set free.
And they'll be able to safely pass
their restaurant on to their children.