Subs created by: David Coleman.
There's a lot of anger,
towards the living.
I was thrown to this doorway.
It was kind of brutal.
Aw, geez.
They're banging on the walls...
Wanting to leave.
He went totally
ballistic and killed her.
She's being assaulted.
I'm not alone inside of my body.
It's really bad in here.
My name is Amy Allan.
Something is not right.
I see dead people.
This person might have
been a serial killer.
I speak to dead people.
You get those chills.
And they speak to me.
He is darkness. He is evil.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I think she broke her neck.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
You telling me the truth?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I think the Devil is down here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who the hell would do this?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Who is he looking to kill?
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
You need to get out of here right now.
Or time to get out.
It was like endless darkness.
Amy and I conduct our
investigations separately.
I dig into the history of the location,
and interview witnesses about
their paranormal experiences.
While Amy deals directly with the dead.
I'm in the small town
of Radford, Virginia.
It's about an hour outside of Roanoke.
Amy and I were called in by
this woman named Marcelle.
She saved a huge historical
building from the wrecking ball.
But she says ever since, her life's
been nothing but a living hell.
She says Amy and I are her last chance.
Before Amy arrives, I look
for any leading information.
Even though this
building seems abandoned,
I still have to cover or remove anything
that could influence her findings.
When I'm done, the location
will be ready for tonight's walk.
There are a lot of people here...
Layers of people.
There's about four women.
They don't want to be here
anymore, they want to leave, and...
They can't.
So, they're all up there, these people.
It's very physical.
I can't breathe.
Marcelle, you sounded really upset on
the phone about what's happening here...
What's going on?
We've had people who have seen
apparitions in the building.
We have volunteers who have
been picked up and tossed...
Hair pulled.
Visitors come in that have
left with scratch marks on them.
And seems that the activity
has become more and more.
So, with a list like that of
things that are happening here,
why would you stay here?
For the love of the building.
There's just something about it.
Well, Marcelle, I've got to say, this
is probably one of the biggest buildings
we've ever investigated, how big is it?
It's over 68,000 square feet.
Wow. Okay.
What's the story as far as
history goes? What do you know?
In the early 1900s,
it became a Sanatorium,
and it stayed a
Sanatorium until the 1980s.
We'll, you know, looking around,
this is definitely a work in progress.
What are your plans for it?
We would love to restore the
building and turn it into a museum...
With history about the Sanatorium.
And we'd also like to
put a research library in.
Do you do anything with it now? Is it just,
basically, you're in the repair stage?
In order to pay for the repairs,
we've had some conferences here.
We've had a wedding here recently.
We're doing some parties.
Okay. What are you hoping we can
do for you with this investigation?
I'm hoping you can help
us to find a solution.
It's not only a passion in my
heart, we're run by volunteers,
and we don't want the people
coming in to be harmed or injured.
Okay.
Living people are not
supposed to be here.
Dead people push themselves up against
the walls to get out of their way.
They don't want to be bothered.
They don't like the living.
They're just pissed off and exhausted.
And they feel so, like, tired.
What made you bring me down here?
This is one of the rooms where I
had one of my first experiences.
One of our volunteers had...
It was like... something
jumped into her.
Okay, so, take me through what happened.
She became, like, in a trance.
When she was talking, her words
were all jumbled and garbled,
and just was not making sense at all.
Okay, so, how did you get her out of it?
We pulled out Bible scriptures
and read Bible to her.
Okay, now, did she come
out of it eventually?
Yes. It took a little
over an hour, but she did.
- Do you know this girl personally?
- I do.
Okay, is she on any medication
that would make her demeanor change?
- Nothing like that?
- No, not at all.
Anything else down here?
A woman screamed at me.
Kind of like I'd startled her.
You sure it wasn't somebody
playing games in here?
There's no way.
And you weren't open for any
kind of business or anything?
No, we were not.
There's, like, a woman
running up to me, screaming.
She's freaking out.
She just says that...
It's time to go.
And she's panicked.
A living person would feel this...
This, like, panic.
You feel like...
Something really bad is going to happen.
You feel like you need to leave.
I didn't expect to see
a bowling alley in here.
Was this used by the patients or was
this for the people that worked here?
Primarily, it was used as reward
for good behavior from the patients.
They were allowed to
come down here and bowl.
All right. So, why'd
you bring me down here?
Well, I had my first
paranormal experience in here.
Okay, what happened?
I had this large, white mist
come through the door behind you,
and go down the bowling alley...
And then make a hard right
turn and go through the wall.
What was odd... is the
temperature dropped.
Okay, anything else?
My most horrifying experience
happened just next to the file room.
I got very dizzy, short of breath,
went to the emergency medical area.
Come to find out, it was my pacemaker.
It went haywire and was
beating at 143 beats a minute.
Wow.
And my blood pressure was 164 over 112.
Now, Don, did the doctors ever come up
with an explanation as to what happened?
No, they couldn't
even tell me one thing.
There was nothing to
show what happened at all.
Do you think people could live here?
No.
I wouldn't live here.
- I don't think it's healthy.
- What would happen?
I think that they would get sick.
Just let the dead have it.
I just don't think living
people should be here.
It's probably not a good idea.
So, Chuck, I was talking to Marcelle.
- You're the head of Security here?
- Yes, Sir.
You're probably law
enforcement, I assume?
- I'm a retired deputy Sheriff.
- Okay.
Have you ever had any
experiences yourself?
Oh, yes, Sir, I had one right here.
Standing on this lower step one
night, I felt myself levitate.
It was like I just became
weightless and started coming up...
And thrown...
Over to this doorway.
I could just feel like
something gripped me, okay?
Okay.
And had a hold of me to the point
that I had no control over my body.
I've got to tell you, Chuck, if
you weren't prior law enforcement,
that's not a story I would
probably believe right away.
Well, I can totally understand that.
They don't really want
us to be back here.
Because this is their...
Quiet area.
I see...
This man, and he's getting...
A little frustrated.
He's like their protector
for the dead here.
And I think he's trying to set up, like,
a safe zone, or something, for them.
He says he's going to make me sick.
If I don't leave.
Now, did anything else like
that ever happen to you?
Yes, Sir.
I left our gift shop area.
There's some steps that will
bring you up to this first level.
As I got about the sixth stair...
I could see something standing there.
I could see, like, the chest of it.
Okay.
You can see the muscles
just rippling through there.
As soon as I saw that,
I was picked up...
And not thrown straight back.
But I was thrown over, like, the rails.
Whatever it was had to be strong.
Okay, did you get hurt?
I mean, that's a big fall.
It just really shook me up.
Felt like a bear got a hold of me.
- Okay.
- Just that much strength.
How do you wrap your head
around what's going on here?
I couldn't even fathom
what this thing is.
Okay.
I don't even know what
that guy's capable of.
But I think he's pretty
capable of quite a bit.
Did you see him at all?
He does project himself.
He is white, tall.
And feels very young. But
he's not, he's very old.
And he's not happy.
He doesn't not want
me to talk about him.
So, Chuck, why'd you bring me down here?
When I come in this room, I have
seen one face on several occasions.
Describe it to me.
- His face is very round.
- Okay.
I'd say that he would
have been a big man.
Okay, does it looks like he
knows you're looking at him or
like he's looking at anybody else?
Oh, he definitely knows
you're looking at him.
Anything else happen?
One lady during an investigation.
She was hit between the breastbone.
She was hit so hard
that it left a bruise,
and they told us the bruise
was there for almost two weeks.
Okay, so, when you say an investigation,
we talking about, like, a paranormal group?
Paranormal group, Sir.
Any other thing, physical, happen here?
Women have been touched inappropriately.
They find, usually, the woman
who has the weakest emotions.
Okay.
And they just start
there and just drain them.
And for that reason, we don't allow
any women in this room by themselves.
Whatever's in here has just...
Got something out for the women.
So, now I'm seeing there's this new
guy, who tells me to call him Uncle.
He...
Likes it down here.
He's a big guy.
He's pervy.
He likes to touch women's hair.
I suspect, like, it doesn't just stop
with the hair, you know what I mean?
And there are people...
Maybe four...
That are banging inside.
And they want out.
This dude... the Uncle dude
trapped all their asses in there.
It has something to do with money, like,
if he keeps them in there,
he'll get more money.
He's flooded this place with...
Just nastiness.
Marcelle told me that St.
Albans used to be a Sanatorium.
Now, that seemed like a pretty good
place to start my investigation.
So I reached out to a local
psychiatrist who tells me
that a lot of sick people
lived and died on the property.
So, the current owner
of the property I'm
investigating told me that
it had been a Sanatorium.
- Is that correct?
- That is correct.
It actually started out in the early
1900s as St. Albans school for boys.
Okay.
That closed in 1911, and Dr. John
C. King, with his own funds...
Bought the facility and opened
it up, then, as a Sanatorium,
or a freestanding private
psychiatric hospital.
What kind of patients
would have been there?
Anyone from people that might
have just exhaustion from overwork,
all the way through some of
our severe psychiatric illness
such as Schizophrenia, manic psychosis.
So many different...
People.
- What do you mean?
- I'm seeing, like, people dressed...
In suits and [Bleep].
Like, professional people.
Some guy is saying something,
like, about emotional trauma.
He's like, I suffered emotional trauma.
He's very dramatic.
Walking from room to room, I keep seeing
all of these different dead people.
Some are depressed, some are angry,
and they're all trying to speak to me.
There's so much commotion and movement.
They're banging on the walls...
Wanting to leave, wanting
to leave, wanting to leave.
There's some, like, little
old lady, and she's like...
Oh, you know, it's a processing plant.
They process you.
And then the guy says...
Oh, don't talk to them,
they're [Bleep] lunatics.
So, with these types of patients there,
what kind of treatments
would they have had?
It could have been anything
from cold, wet wraps, all the way
to things more evocative and
potentially more powerful as well.
Such as psychosurgery including
lobotomies, Insulin coma therapy,
electroconvulsive therapy.
Now, is that the same
as electroshock therapy?
Yes.
So many were done at St.
Albans during a stretch of time,
they actually had one machine
that they called Mighty Mouse.
And they would just wheel
it from room to room.
It was kind of brutal to have done
because no general anesthesia was offered.
And so you would be fully awake
when you were administered an
electrical current that would
induce a fairly significant seizure.
I mean, it had to be pretty painful.
I actually have a film
I'd like to show you
to give you an idea of
just how it was done.
Oh, geez.
My feet, my hands.
It's like burning. I
feel like I'm burning.
I'm, like, shaking.
It hurts.
There is a female.
She's scared. Very,
very, very frightened.
She's shaking. She
feels like she's burning.
Now, Doctor, this place
is 68,000 square feet.
So, how many patients
would have been in there?
Thousands over the years.
Now, a place that big,
with that many patients,
I got to assume there had
to be a lot of deaths there.
You know, I think so, too. I
was able to find 10, for sure.
But I think that would be
a gross underrepresentation
of the deaths that likely
would have happened.
Now, did they have a Morgue there?
- Yes.
- Really?
So, Doctor, I got to assume there
had to be a lot more deaths there,
because you don't build
a Morgue for 10 people.
- That's right, you would not. Absolutely.
- Okay.
I see a group of people
sleeping on the floor here.
It's just, like, a big heap of people.
They're kind of covered up.
Like, it's a mess.
Dr. Scheiderer told me that St.
Albans was an all-boys school.
Now, it didn't sound like much to me until
I called a local historian to check it out.
He told me that the story
of the school's founder
will definitely help my investigation.
The school was actually started
by Professor George Miles.
He was an educator, a
well-connected businessman.
And he was also a wealthy individual...
he had married into a wealthy family.
Okay, so, what purpose
did he open it for?
It was a preparatory school for boys.
Here's actually an advertisement
from 1892 when he opened the school.
The idea was to train these
young men to be good gentlemen,
and also to prepare them for
a track to go to university.
Okay, now, what kind of guy was he?
That depends on who you ask.
He had this reputation of being
respectable and dedicated to his work.
But he was also scheming and abrasive.
Really?
Now, what happened to the school, because
I understand it became a Sanatorium?
Yeah, his business interests took
him away from the school in 1902.
- And it kind of floundered without him.
- Okay.
And in 1904, they shut it down.
All right. So, what
winds up happening to him?
Professor Miles actually
met a pretty tragic end.
Early in 1905, he admitted
himself into a hospital,
and they found that he had liver cancer.
And within two months, he passed away.
- He was only 42 years old.
- Okay.
I'm seeing the man who
calls himself Uncle.
And he was in charge...
very, very, wealthy.
And he was the start...
Of this.
And at first, there was good intention.
And then it went bad.
Can you describe him?
He's probably in his 40s.
He's bald and he's pale.
He's dying.
He feels guilty.
Now that I know my client's property
used to be a prep school and a Sanatorium,
I need to see if anything
else went down there.
So I hit the books at the local library.
Digging through old records, I discovered
the murder of a girl name Gina Hall.
Turns out, her car was last
seen near Marcelle's property.
So, I'm headed over to meet
with a local police Lieutenant.
Who says that the
connection between that case
and St. Albans runs
much deeper than that.
Lieutenant, I came across an article
talking about a homicide that happened
that has a connection to the
property I'm investigating.
What can you tell me about it?
On June 28, 1980, Gina
Renee Hall, age 18 years old.
Wanted to go dancing
at a club in Blacksburg,
and met a guy named
Stephen Epperly, age 28.
And he ended up talking
her into going back to a
lake house that his
friend was taking care of.
Okay. What did the original
investigators theorize happened?
That Epperly made some advances toward
her, and she rejected those advances.
There was something
with a female in here.
And there's, like, an older man.
She's kind of being messed with.
I mean, I think he was trying to
kiss her or something, and then...
It went bad.
We believe that he just went
totally ballistic and killed her.
And put her body in the
trunk of her own car.
Drove her somewhere,
disposed of the body,
and parked the car just down from where
you're investigating with the trunk open.
Wow.
What do we know about this guy
himself? I mean, what's his background?
Epperly was a charmer to the ladies
thought very highly of himself.
He was known to have
a very violent temper.
And was actually charged
previously, before this happened,
with a couple rapes in the community.
You're kidding.
So, he had all the characteristics of
a guy that would do something like this.
Yes.
First it was, like, teasing,
then it wasn't teasing.
He got... he got mad real quick.
And he, like, punches her.
She's being...
Kind of assaulted.
He get's life in prison,
first-degree murder.
Now, what about the body?
Was it ever recovered?
No.
First case in Virginia that someone was
convicted without ever finding the body.
Wow. Where do you
think the body might be?
Some believe that it may be at the lake.
And some people believe that she's buried
on the property you're investigating.
The rumor was that he worked at
St. Albans for a little while.
Really?
There's, uh...
Something really, really wrong.
Um...
I'm not alone inside of my body.
As I'm seeing this brutal
attack, I feel a woman jump me.
She's entered my body.
Whoa.
Mm. That does not feel good. [Bleep]!
And she's not the only one here
who can do this to living people.
Hm-mnh, no. Hm-mnh. Hm-mnh, no.
For one of the few times in
my life, I can't finish a walk.
This woman refuses to leave my
body, and I fear for my own safety.
Are you okay?
No. She won't [Bleep] leave.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations.
We're ready to reveal our findings to each
other, and our clients, for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to meet Marcelle.
Few years back, she saved this
building from a wrecking ball.
Her dream is actually to
turn this place into a museum.
Hmm.
The problem is the
activity here is so bad,
she's afraid for any guests or
any volunteers that work here.
Now, speaking of
volunteers, this is Chuck.
He's retired Police Officer.
He runs the Security here.
He's been through some stuff
I've never even heard before.
Marcelle wants to know if
there's any way that she can
safely turn this place into a museum.
So, now that Amy
understands why we're here,
I'm going to ask her to
tell us about her walk.
I...
Got here, and it was very confusing.
And I got just layers and
layers and layers of dead people.
I got that a lot of the
dead are extremely angry.
Pissed off, and exhausted, and that a
lot of them do not care for the living.
There was one location
that I went to upstairs.
The dead said that it was their quiet
area and they didn't want me there.
The person that I encountered...
He basically was this
group of people's leader.
And he is trying to
enforce a safety zone.
For some of the dead here.
He was kind of white-ish and tall,
and he was projecting himself as
being younger than he actually is.
And he told me, you better
leave or I'm going to hurt you.
He definitely has the capability
of doing whatever he wants.
Could that person, that's that advanced,
take a man that size and throw him?
Um, yeah.
I was asked to meet someone
at the grand staircase.
As I was on about the sixth step.
Something grabbed me...
And threw me over...
- The rail.
- Whoa.
Describe what you saw.
The chest... huge.
- Like something's on steroids, okay?
- Mm hmm, okay.
I can see the muscles,
like he's very ripped.
- Mm hmm.
- Does that make sense to you?
Yes, absolutely.
What else did you see on your walk?
I met a lot of strange people.
It was kind of interesting,
because at one point
I was seeing a lot of
professional people.
And it was a weird contrast.
Then I ran into this other guy who was
just, like, so out of it and so lost.
They were just bashing,
banging on all of the walls.
So, then, I saw, like, a
bunch of little old people.
And one of the little
old ladies said to me,
she's like, yeah, this is
just like a processing plant.
And then the guy I was with
turned to me and he goes...
Don't listen to them,
they're all bunch of lunatics.
This is easy enough to explain to you, you
could take your pick on who you ran into.
Because this place operated as a
Sanatorium from the early 1900s till 1980.
And it was started by this
gentleman right here...
John C. King.
They treated people here
from depression to drug abuse,
alcohol abuse, up to
full blown Schizophrenia.
Really?
Does it make sense to you about why you
ran into all those different... yeah.
Now, that's part of your draw,
that this was a Sanatorium,
and you're trying to bring back
the whole grandeur of this building.
- What it was at one time.
- Yes.
Once you come into the
building, you're drawn to it.
You just, you want to restore it. You want
to bring it back to its original glory.
So, what else did you see?
I, physically, had a
very difficult time.
I felt like my head was being
crushed in, I couldn't breathe.
A lot of the people I
encountered were also having pain.
There was one young girl that I saw
who was having seizures and vomiting.
Then there was a woman that I met
downstairs who felt like she was burning.
She was also shaking,
and I do think that living
people who spend a lot
of time here would...
Be prone to having
symptoms of illnesses.
Marcelle, this is probably
a good time for you to
tell Amy about the incident
with your husband Don.
Don has a pacemaker.
It's set to go at 60 beats.
And it was racing into
the 130s beats per minutes.
The doctors couldn't explain it.
He has problems with his
pacemaker every time he comes in.
Now, you've got to know
something about the Sanatorium.
Back in the day, it had some pretty
primitive ideas of treatment here.
You mentioned somebody who
was shaking, and felt burning,
and all this other stuff,
and this was a woman, right?
They had an instrument
here called Mighty Mouse,
that they'd wheel from room to room
and they did electroshock therapy.
Okay.
Now, do you think that's what
that woman was going through?
Yeah, that I think so.
I'm trained in psychology, so I'm very
familiar with electroshock therapy.
And now that I know what
this building used to be,
I realize that's what it must feel like.
There's a lot of dead
people here who feel trapped.
And they were banging on
the windows because they
want to get out, they want help.
I had them sketch that.
They were very pale.
And extremely thin.
Skeleton-ish.
- Is this what you saw?
- Mm hmm.
And you wanted to come back in here?
You've got more guts than I do.
I wouldn't want to come back in.
Oh, my gosh.
- Sad.
- That's amazing. Very sad.
Do you think it could have possibly
been patients that were here?
Now, I'm thinking yeah, probably.
Very sad.
Now, is there any reason
why they're trapped?
Yeah.
So, when I first got here,
there was a male...
Who was having me call him Uncle.
I know he was in charge, he
was very powerful, very wealthy.
When he started this, he
started it with good intentions.
And he was very odd-looking himself.
He was completely bald.
The other thing with this Uncle
was that he was kind of a pervert.
And he really likes to do
things inappropriate to women.
Let me ask you a question,
does he touch women?
- Oh, yes.
- Okay.
Well, explain the boiler room to her.
Women who enter, they're drained.
Down to the point that
they're just ready to pass out.
And there's inappropriate touching...
In there as well.
And that's the reason we do not
allow women by themselves in there.
You know, a lot of things you
said reminds me of the guy that
actually built this place in 1892,
the original founder of the building.
Now...
This is George Miles now, you mentioned
that he started out with good intentions.
He opened this up as a boys school.
And it was basically a
preparatory school for...
Um, young men to lead them on
to a good path, so to speak.
This guy was well-connected,
knew a lot of influential people.
Many people said he was
scheming, ambitious, abrasive.
This is the way they described him.
People thought he was a
little bit money-hungry.
Oh.
Now, three years after he left the school,
he got diagnosed with severe liver cancer.
He was given early forms of chemotherapy
and radiation, and he
lost all of his hair.
And he died within a couple of months.
What else did you see?
In the boiler room, when I walked
in there, I saw a male and a female.
And it seemed like she
was kind of teasing him.
He went in to kiss her. She
wasn't going to let it happen.
And then he started hitting her.
And she was screaming and crying.
And I believe there was
a rape that followed that.
Do you think the girl that was
raped was killed, that you saw?
Mm, yeah, I think so.
Back on June 28, 1980, this girl...
It breaks my heart to
even talk about this story.
Her name was Gina Hall.
She was 18 years old.
Look at this kid. She's
everybody's daughter.
She went to one of
the clubs here in town.
She ran into a guy, Stephen Epperly.
She went dancing, this guy was
a charmer, good looking guy.
He convinces her to drive
him to a friend's lake house.
That's the last time she's ever seen.
Here's a picture of him.
The guy in the middle...
this is at his trial.
They believe what happened is
she went back to the lake house,
he made some sexual advances
that she didn't like...
And he killed her.
Probably raped her.
Her car that she drove him in was
found literally yards from here.
Her body's never been recovered.
There's two theories as to where she is.
She was either thrown in the water, or
she's buried somewhere on this property.
Oh, my God.
Geez.
Pretty impressive walk you already did.
What else did you see?
Towards the end of the walk, when I was in
the basement after all that, I got jumped.
What happened has only happened a
handful of times as a professional.
I couldn't finish the walk because
this woman got inside of me.
And how long did it take
you to get rid of her?
Maybe, like, six to eight hours.
Now, we've done over 50 cases together.
This is the first time I'm hearing
her not being able to finish a walk.
Yeah.
So, she continued to stay with me.
We left, I was in the
car crying hysterically.
What she told me was that there's a
lot of dead people here who can do this.
Uh, that they can do it to
people who are open or closed...
Who have abilities, don't,
or they can follow them.
And they can influence a person to make
anything from just simple bad decisions to,
you know, harming themselves
or harming somebody else.
Is it possible...
For someone to be jumped...
And not realize it and change
their whole demeanor, their whole...
Personality, and change
their relationships?
Absolutely.
I think it's changed my life.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
It's just a tough subject to talk about.
You're talking about
you or somebody else?
Someone else.
Speaking with Marcelle, I feel
she's holding something back.
And knowing that her husband,
Don, refused to come to the reveal.
I started putting together why.
If they have an ailment, are they
more susceptible to being jumped?
Yes.
I have an idea of who
you're talking about.
I need a few minutes.
If they have an ailment, are they
more susceptible to being jumped?
Yes.
I have an idea of who
you're talking about.
I need a few minutes, guys. I'm sorry.
Guys, I want to apologize for becoming
so emotional a little while ago.
I don't know how else to explain it.
Since I've become involved in this
building, I've seen people's lives
that have kind of changed,
relationships that have changed.
And it's caused some
problems in my own home.
Nice people became...
Angry or unhappy.
And, hopefully, you can
give us some answers.
You've been hit with a lot of
disturbing information tonight.
But the biggest question
is can you turn this
historic building into
a museum and be safe?
For that answer, I'm going
to turn it over to Amy.
This cannot become what you want it.
With what's going on here.
It's far too dangerous.
As far as what to do here...
Go into the largest room you
have here and do a mass funeral.
Get several different
types of holy people.
That way you're hitting as
many religions as possible,
so that the people who are dead here
who feel an affinity for
that religion, they'll go.
This has to happen three
times over a one month period.
One month later, you're going to have
to have an exorcism of the location...
The entire location.
Because unfortunately, you do
have, now, these nasty people.
They're going to jump
people, they've gone bad.
- Will that get everybody out of here?
- Yeah.
I'm just amazed.
We knew there were things going on here.
- Yeah.
- You've answered a lot of our questions.
The next question is the obvious one...
Are you going to
listen to what Amy says?
Well, we asked her to come
in to give us the solution,
so I think we need to
follow through on it.
If they don't do it, is
it going to get worse here?
Well, I wouldn't come back.
She ain't coming back, you've got
problems. I've got news for you.
With all of the dead
inside this location...
Marcelle and Chuck have
their work cut out for them.
But I'm confident that if
they follow my advice...
They'll be able to keep their
guests and employees safe from harm.