It's awful, awful in here.
This wolf-looking guy -- He went
"Raah!" right in my face.
I felt real fear.
In front of two witnesses,
he stabs him to death.
"I'm dying.
I'm dying."
I know what I see.
Something's wrong.
And I know what I hear.
He wants them to go.
He wants revenge.
It's really bad in here.
My name is Amy Allan.
Something is not right.
I see dead people.
This person might have been
a serial killer.
I speak to dead people.
You get those chills.
And they speak to me.
He is darkness.
He is evil.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
I think she broke her neck.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
You telling me the truth?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I think the devil
is down here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who the hell
would do this?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
Who's he looking to kill?
We uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
You need to get out of here
right now.
Or time to get out.
It was like endless darkness.
STEVE: I always head to our
locations before Amy arrives.
I dig up facts
about the property's dark past
while Amy speaks to the dead.
I'm in Potsdam, New York.
It's about 30 minutes south
of the Canadian border.
We got called in
by a woman named Donna.
Like me, she's a retired
homicide detective.
She actually sounded embarrassed
needing our help,
but as a cop, I understand that.
Bottom line --
She and her family
are being terrorized by spirits
in the house.
And all her experience
can't help her solve this case.
MATTHEW: Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area
of any leading information.
This home
has a lot of family photos
that need to be covered
or removed.
When I'm finished,
the location will be ready
for tonight's walk.
I saw these men who were walking
like monkeys, like gorillas.
It just looks like
their, you know, skin
has been painted on black,
and they're barking
and growling.
One was saying that
they get used up or something,
and then they fall
into little dust.
He was a living person.
I don't know about the others.
They are protecting
certain things from being known.
STEVE: Now, Donna, you sounded
pretty upset on the phone.
And you're a former
homicide detective like myself.
I know it had to be tough
for you to even call us.
I've tried everything
I can do.
We've been terrorized here
with the things
that have been happening here.
Okay. So why don't you
tell me what's going on?
Well,
our son has seen things,
I've been woken up
and seen things,
and my skeptical husband
has even seen things
and been touched.
And how old is your son?
He's 17.
Latest apparition he saw,
he ran into my room screaming,
and that's why
I wrote you guys a letter.
I need a solution
'cause it's got to stop.
- You were a detective down
in south Florida, right? - Yes.
What brought you here?
I was born and raised up here,
and I left for 32 years.
And my son,
at the time, was 10.
And living in south Florida
with a child,
I wanted to bring him back
to a peaceful place.
You don't have to worry
about the criminal element here.
Right.
But you have to worry
about some other element now.
Oh, yeah.
I'm pissed off,
and the fight's on.
There's this living woman.
And she's saying that this home
is not working for her.
She hates it,
and she feels like this house
is, like, closing in on her.
She's probably an empath.
MATTHEW:
Why do you say that?
Her emotions --
She pushes them out of her.
There's a lot of anger
in this room from her.
Something's wrong.
So, Donna,
why'd you bring me in here?
We've had
a lot of bad luck.
A lot of freaky things with
the appliances breaking down.
They're all new appliances.
And we've been hit by lightning
here
not once, but twice
in seven years.
The odds on that
got to be astronomical.
It's like a magnet
or something.
We had a chimney fire
that caught the whole front yard
on fire.
That's crazy.
Anything else going on?
I sit over there,
watching TV,
and I see this blob
of a black shadow,
and I look to make sure
I'm not seeing things,
and it just moves so fast.
I've seen that
about five times recently.
When it moves,
it's pretty massive.
And you're sure it's not
something from outside coming in
to make you see this?
I'm positive,
'cause my dog has --
When he sees it,
he starts growling and barking.
And you get up to investigate,
and it's gone.
It's gone.
This is a very bad area.
Things happen here
to the living people
with these things.
And this family --
I think they think it's
shadow people, but it's not.
The painted creatures who were
acting like monkeys outside
are now projecting themselves as
shadow people inside the house.
Whoever's in control
of these things
wants them
to torment the living.
They, like --
They'll see them like that,
but then
they'll see them get up.
There's, like, this panic.
Like, I hear a woman screaming
and running out of here.
So,
what's going on up here?
This is the worst of it.
I get woke up a lot
in the middle of the night.
Give me a for-instance.
Well, the other night,
I was sleeping,
and, all of a sudden,
right in my face
was this wolf-looking guy,
and he went "Raah!"
right in my face.
- You're not on medication
or anything, right? - No.
If you were back on the job,
talking to people,
and somebody told you
this story...
- I would think they're crazy.
- Right.
Which my husband probably
does think I'm crazy for.
And then another time,
I woke up about 3:00
in the morning for no reason.
I see this huge, big guy
standing on the side of the bed,
looking at me.
He was about
at least over 6 feet tall.
He didn't look like
he was happy.
He was kind of menacing.
I saw an older man
who was hiding things.
He's very condescending.
He has an elitist attitude
about everything.
He's very scary.
MATTHEW:
Is there any connection between
him and the painted people?
AMY: He put them to work
for him.
He painted them all black
and creepy-looking,
and he makes them
show themselves to people
and scare them.
And he does
take their energy.
When they're all used up,
they become like dust.
And what happens, then,
when they turn into dust?
They cease to be.
STEVE:
Now, is there anything else
you've seen up here?
Yeah, one night, I was up here
with a few friends,
and I felt something
behind me.
And I look,
and I see this arm.
It had a black sleeve,
the skinny old-lady fingers
with nails.
So, you just saw the arm,
not the --
Just saw the arm.
Where was it coming from?
It was coming
from behind me.
Okay, so, it was as if somebody
was behind you going like this?
Yeah, trying to get my attention
or, like, cutting me off.
Did you see the lady?
No.
Do you think there's evil
in this house?
I don't think
it's on the good side.
It wants us out of here.
Okay.
I think that this guy
has a little bit of a problem
with the people in this room
because they know about him.
He hates it.
So he wants them to go.
Ooh!
This is...Mmm.
This is not good, all right?
Oh, I don't like it.
Okay, just a sec.
[ Clears throat ]
[ Moaning ]
MATTHEW: Are you okay?
I felt really, really scared.
It's, like, real fear.
STEVE: Andrew,
I was talking to mom,
and she told me about the things
that are going on in the house,
and she told me
you're having a tough time here.
Yeah. I've experienced
some things here.
In seventh grade,
I saw a shadow figure
dart across my front lawn.
Describe what you saw.
I saw, like,
a black-figured human being.
Okay.
Had you ever seen this thing
again?
Yeah, recently, actually.
I was coming home
from football,
and I came in the driveway,
and I saw it.
Really?
It kind of, like,
lifted its head up and ran.
Okay. So, now,
what about the house?
What have you experienced
in the house?
I was sleeping on this bed,
and I woke up,
and I saw a man dressed in an
army uniform standing over me.
- And he was just
staring at you? - Yeah.
Now, how long did this thing
last in front of you?
About two seconds,
and then I thought it was
a human being standing there,
so I kicked him in the face.
My foot went through his face,
and he disappeared.
That was it?
I ran out in the hallway,
and I kind of, like,
hyperventilated a little bit.
I don't like being here
alone.
All right, so, what do you
think's going on here?
Something doesn't want us here,
or I don't know.
Okay.
AMY:
This older man I saw --
He is pissed,
because when he died,
he kind of lost control
over everything.
[ Sighs ]
He talks too **** fast.
This angry man is following me
around the house,
bragging about the power
he holds over the dead here.
[ Scoffs ]
And he calls me a dimwit.
[ Grunts ]
He's like, "Keep up."
Okay.
He says
that most of these people
were men when he met them.
I mean, they were dead men,
but they were men.
And he made them
what they are now.
He says, because he is superior
in every way,
that's why he's able
to dominate them.
When he was alive,
I think he was haunted by them,
and he flipped
that whole **** around.
I was talking
to your wife.
She said
that you really don't
believe in any of the stuff
that's going on here.
50/50.
I'm kind of a skeptic.
Okay.
I don't think
they're lying,
but I'm not seeing
what they're seeing,
and I don't know
what to do about it.
Okay. So you think
there's something going on.
You just haven't
experienced anything.
Uh...
Up in the room up there,
there's a cord with a tag on it.
One night,
I went up there to go lay down,
and before I went to lay down,
it flapped rapidly.
- Kind of like a finger flapping it
back and forth? - Yeah.
[ Imitates flapping ]
Like that.
So was any wind or any windows
open or anything like that?
No.
That's the whole thing.
All the windows were closed.
All the doors were closed.
Okay.
And I thought to myself,
"Well, Donna might be right."
And before I went to sleep,
I said, "**** you,"
'cause I was aggravated.
Okay.
I had one other instance.
I was laying on the sofa,
trying to take a nap,
and I felt a vivid touch
on my face,
and it felt like this...
Okay.
Like a finger?
Yes.
And I opened my eye,
and it was nothing.
And I remember feeling
some kind of a --
I don't know -- a presence.
Whatever was there that caused
that, I couldn't explain.
Okay.
I feel a lot of pain,
but it's not really --
No, pain isn't the right word.
It's pressure.
I feel a lot of pressure.
Somebody pushing.
It kind of --
Now it's starting to hurt.
I want to say this is the leader
and his little posse.
But he'll push on people, like,
squish them or shove them.
He doesn't like living people.
They violated him...
and he wants revenge.
The first thing I usually do
in these investigations
is try to find out
who lived on the property.
Turns out
one of the former owners
actually passed away
of a heart attack in the house.
I'm on my way
to meet with his daughter,
who's still upset
by the way he died.
Betsy, when was the last time
you were in this house?
20 years ago.
Okay.
How long did you live here?
From 1978 until 1983.
During your time here,
did you ever experience anything
you couldn't explain?
Not a thing.
I can't recall anything
ever strange happening here.
Your father died here,
and what'd your father do
for a living?
He had been in the service,
you know, in the Korean War.
I brought a picture
to show in his uniform.
Then he was an insurance man
for a great many years,
and before he passed, he was a
manager at an auto-parts store.
Okay.
So, what kind of a guy
was your dad?
He was a tough guy.
It was either his way
or the highway.
Didn't show
a whole lot of emotion.
He was basically
a very strict dad.
What kind of a relationship
did you have with him?
I was always cautious.
He would get heated
pretty quickly.
Makes you be on eggshells.
I was, like, on eggshells a lot.
AMY:
I see that older man in here.
He doesn't like it
when people know about him.
It freaks him out.
It disturbs him. He hates it.
When he was alive,
he had control
over everything, every aspect,
and then he died
and, like, "Oh ****
He's dead."
I think it was unexpected death.
He didn't have any control,
and he got really mad.
What the **** is that about?
What kind of relationship
did your mom and dad have?
Well, they were together
a very long time.
They were
high-school sweethearts.
Okay.
But I think, you know,
before he passed,
it was probably a low point
of their relationship.
She wasn't home.
She wasn't here
when he had passed.
She was in Florida.
I don't think
that he was happy
about her going away
on vacation.
And before she went away,
he said, you know,
"I'm not gonna be around
that much longer, anyways.
I'm not gonna be living
that long."
Just like that?
Just like that.
Three days later, when she was
gone in Florida, he died.
She felt horrible.
It was so tragic
and such a shock.
Now, where did he die
in the house?
He died in the garage.
Okay.
Would you mind showing me?
Does it bother you
being in here?
It's very strange
being in here.
This is where
he took his last breath.
It was very hard
to come in here
and know that
this is where it happened.
Right.
And what year did he die?
He died in 1992.
Now,
was there any indication
that he had a heart problem
or a heart condition?
There was no signs.
There was nothing.
Who was the first family member
to come home?
I was.
You were?
Mm-hmm.
What did you see?
Well, I found over in this area
a small round circle of blood
where he had hit his head.
Did you clean it?
It's the first thing I did
after I pulled myself together.
It was important to me.
That's all I could focus on
was to go into the house
and to clean it up
'cause I didn't want my mom
to see that when she got home.
He died alone,
and that's just really tragic.
That's how my mom died, too,
and it bothered me
thinking about her dying alone.
When I came out here
and I found the spot of blood,
it just was --
It hit me full force.
Right.
He's gone.
MATTHEW:
Do you know how he died?
Some kind of, like,
aneurysm, sudden heart a--
you know,
sudden death, whatever.
You know, it was something
completely unexpected.
Do you know
when he was alive?
'80s, '90s.
I feel a pain -- back and
my neck -- pretty **** bad.
I feel anger and stress.
[ Sighs ] ****
When I'm hearing his thoughts,
I'm thinking I'm dying.
"I'm dying. I'm dying."
If you need us
to investigate
unexplained activity
in your home,
go to "The Dead Files" page
at travelchannel.com.
Click on
"Help me, Dead Files!"
to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
STEVE: I need to find out
what else might have happened
on my client's property,
so I hit the books
at the local library.
Digging through old deeds, I
find a man named Frank Bancroft
originally owned Donna's land.
Turns out he was hit and killed
by a car
while walking back home.
Now that I know
a former owner of Donna's land
died in an accident,
I reached out
to a local genealogist.
He tells me that that tragedy
was only the beginning
of the Bancroft family's
problems on that property.
So, Dennis,
I came across this article
about this guy,
Frank Bancroft.
So, I was wondering, what do you
know about what happened to him?
He was intoxicated,
and he was
wandering down the road,
and he was struck by a car.
He died as a result
of a skull fracture
and some hemorrhaging,
of which
we have some information,
including
his death certificate.
This happens in 1937.
Yes.
This was actually
the second time
he was hit by a car
within two weeks.
Okay.
But he really didn't sustain
any injury that first time.
Well, what's the matter
with this guy?
He's walking down the street
and keeps getting hit by cars?
I think a lot of it has to do
with the passing of his wife.
In 1934, his wife passed
with pneumonia.
He just really
never got over it.
He got sort of despondent
and began drinking.
You weren't kidding
about bad luck with this guy.
Yes.
Later on, in 1932,
his horse barn
was hit by lightning
and destroyed.
Then, in 1935,
his house burned to the ground,
and he barely made it out
alive.
So, now, once Frank dies,
what happens to the property?
The property goes
to his only daughter, Hazel,
which we have a picture of her
when she was 12.
What did she do
with the property?
Do you have any idea?
In 1946, she had a boarder
named Frank Reninger
that was living there,
and one day,
he started beating on her,
and he almost killed her.
She finally escaped
by going down through the cellar
and out the side door
to the neighbor's to get help.
Now, is there any reason why
she got beat up by this guy?
I don't know
if anybody really knows.
Like, he snapped.
I would say that probably
would be what happened to him.
It's awful, awful...
awful, awful in here.
A lot of emotions in here --
desperate.
I heard screaming, too,
like, a female screaming.
I do see a woman,
and she's from a bit ago --
100 years ago, 125 years.
And she sits and cries.
She's in a nightdress,
she's got a nightcap on,
and she's just weeping
and weeping and weeping.
While she was gone, this Frank
set fire to her house,
and it destroyed the house.
We have
a little bit of information
on that particular fire.
I tell you, Dennis,
this is pretty wild stuff
because two houses
burned on their property
before my clients
even got there.
Their house was hit by lightning
twice in the last seven years.
Plus,
their chimney caught fire.
So you got two lightning strikes
in the last seven years
and two houses that burned down
on the property before that.
Actually, four houses.
Four houses?
One in 1901
and the other in 1911.
So, four times
houses burned down.
Yes.
STEVE: During my research,
I also uncovered a murder
that took place
just a short distance away
from Donna's house.
I'm on my way
to meet with a local historian,
who tells me
the crime was so brutal,
it had the whole town
in a frenzy.
So, now, this murder I came
across during my research --
It looked like
it was pretty prominent.
Yes.
The Donavan/Rowley case,
which was in 1852.
John Donavan and James Rowley
spend the evening drinking.
They start arguing
and get into a fight.
Friends kind of
calm them down,
make them shake hands
to be friendly,
and they depart
each other's company.
Donavan goes back in a bar
and starts drinking again.
A friend of Donavan's
starts telling him
how he should not
have apologized.
Okay, so, this guy
is instigating Donavan?
Yes.
And as Donavan drinks more,
he gets more worked up
about Rowley,
so he actually leaves the bar
with his knife
and goes
and hunts James Rowley down
and, in front of two witnesses,
stabs him to death
and kind of
disembowels him.
Ooh! Okay.
He's apprehended
that night,
and, the next day,
finds out what he did.
He has no recollection
of the murder,
so he showed a lot of remorse
after this in a trial
but was convicted
of first-degree murder.
All right, so, what winds up
happening that night?
He was hung
just outside the jail.
Between 1,200 and 1,500 people
attended the hanging.
AMY: Someone's talking
about the murders,
and I'm seeing someone
getting stabbed to death.
There's someone wearing
a white button-down shirt,
a male,
and he's getting
stabbed to death.
Where is he being stabbed?
In his abdomen and chest.
During my walk,
I saw an angry man
who was in control of
the painted people in the house.
I'm meeting with a sketch artist
to draw him.
He's between 55 and 65.
He is balding.
He has deep-set eyes.
Next, I described a scene
where the painted people
were tormenting the living.
There's a thing.
He's been painted black.
He's using his hands.
And he was reaching out
for her.
It was just
a very freaky kind of scene.
Is this what you saw?
Yes.
STEVE: Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready
to reveal our findings
to each other and our clients
for the first time.
Amy,
I'd like you to meet Donna.
Now, Donna is a retired
homicide detective like myself,
so when she called us in,
I knew things had to be serious,
and, actually, they are.
She's being terrorized
by the things
that are going on in this house.
This is her husband, Millard.
He's had a few experiences,
but he remains a skeptic.
One thing they both agree on
is they're fighting mad.
They're not gonna let
whatever's here
drive them out of their house.
With that,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy
and have her tell us
about her walk.
AMY: So I was out
in the front yard,
and I overhear two women
gossiping.
One woman is saying,
"Oh, my," you know,
"Did you hear
about the murders?"
One of the victims that I saw
was a male,
and someone
was stabbing him to death
in the abdomen/chest area.
Now I didn't think
this would have came into play,
but there was a homicide
that took place in 1852...
...on your property.
- Okay.
Two guys got into a fight
in a bar.
People that see it break it up,
and they make them shake hands
and quiet down.
One guy's name
was John Donavan.
The other guy's name
was James Rowley.
Rowley leaves the bar,
and John Donavan stays
and continues to drink.
A friend of his comes up
and starts egging him on,
saying, "You know what?
You should have never
apologized to that guy.
You should have
stood your ground."
Now, he eggs him on to the point
where he goes out,
finds him on the street,
and he stabs him a few times
in the chest and the stomach.
He stabs him so bad,
he disemboweled him.
Donavan was actually hanged
for that homicide.
Wow.
What else did you see?
I came inside,
walked around the first floor,
and I got
that a living woman here
was mad and angry,
and I was hearing her say
how much she hates the house
and how she feels trapped,
like the home
is crushing her.
And this female
seems to be empathic.
So this anger and hatred
actually fills the atmosphere.
Well,
does it sound like you?
It does sound like me.
Yeah.
Like, sometimes,
I can feel when people are sick.
And it comes
without any warning.
Okay.
Not good.
Oh, my gosh.
What else was going on
during your walk?
At one point,
I went upstairs.
I went into, I guess,
the master bedroom.
And I felt extremely intense
feeling of fear.
After the fear came in,
sadness.
Then I saw this old woman,
and she was just rocking
and, like, moaning and crying.
It seemed like it was
about 100 to 125 years ago,
just by the way
she was dressed.
Tell Amy what you saw.
You were talking about
the old woman's arm.
Well,
I felt something behind me,
and then I saw this skinny arm
with a black sleeve
with these long nails,
just going like this
behind me.
I'm like, "What the heck?"
And I turn around.
There's nothing there.
This may be a long shot,
but a woman that used to
live on this property
had a pretty tragic time here.
Her name is Hazel Bancroft.
Her mother, Harriet,
died of pneumonia back in 1934.
Now in 1937,
after the mother died,
her dad, Frank --
He gets hit by a car one night
and ends up dying, as well.
Oh, my God.
So, now, the daughter winds up
taking over the property.
1946, she's got a boarder
who's 68 years old,
and she just comes home
from the market or something.
He meets her at the door,
and he starts beating the hell
out of her for no reason.
She literally escaped
with her life
by running out
the back of the house,
down in the basement
and then and out.
Once she escapes,
the guy burned the house down.
Wow.
Now, could the woman
you were talking about
been either her
or maybe her mother?
Possibly her mother.
By the way, that was the fourth
house to burn on this property.
I mean,
these are some of the articles.
1901, 1911, and 1935,
houses were all burned down
on this property.
Did you know anything
about these fires at all?
Absolutely not.
No.
They've had their house
hit by lightning twice
in the seven years
they're here,
and you also had a chimney fire,
right? - Yes.
So, now you have four houses
burnt to the ground...
...on this property.
- Right.
Your house has been hit twice
with lightning,
and you had the chimney fire.
And if we weren't home,
it wouldn't be here today.
[ Sighs ]
There's no such thing
as coincidence
when you have this many.
Yeah, I agree with that.
So, how'd the rest of the walk
go?
Well, the most powerful entity
that I met in the house
was this older dead man
who was very condescending.
[ Sighs ]
He talks too **** fast.
[ Scoffs ]
And he calls me a dimwit.
He's like, "Keep up."
He was very controlling.
In fact,
he's a control freak.
But here's the thing --
The way that he died
was maybe an aneurysm
or a heart attack,
and this really upset him
because it was something
that was out of his control.
And this was probably
in the '80s or '90s.
[ Scoffs ]
He is upset
with living people
because he feels like
when he died,
he was very disrespected.
Well, I think I know
who you're talking about.
There's a guy
that died in this house in 1992.
The name of Cleave Lytle.
He died unexpected, died
of a heart attack in the garage.
Great.
Now, I talked to his daughter,
Betsy.
She described him as a "My way
or the highway" type of guy.
He was not very warm,
not affectionate.
Now, I got photos of him.
He was actually in the army.
He was in the army.
Wow.
Your son said he saw somebody
in an army uniform
standing over his bed, right?
He sure did, plain as day.
Our son,
he's always scared.
Just the other night,
he was yelling in his sleep
and came out walking
like he was in a daze,
and he doesn't
even remember that.
That was just the other day.
Oh. I'm glad he's not sitting here
to look at that.
And here's a couple of pictures
of him years later.
Wow.
I did do a sketch,
but I saw no hair on top.
Wow.
Take a look at that.
Oh, my God.
Mm.
It could pass for him, yes.
That's definitely him.
The eyes are right on.
What's this guy's story?
He is kind of a leader
of about 25 other dead men.
Oh, boy.
And what he did to them was,
he painted their skin black,
and he makes them
kind of move like a gorilla,
and they'll bark
like a dog.
It's very strange.
He uses their energy,
and he'll use it so much
that he literally uses them up,
and then they turn to dust
and cease to even be
anymore.
Oh, my God.
He makes them
frighten the living.
The living people would probably
perceive them as shadow men,
but they're not.
Oh, my God.
Now, you've mentioned...
...you've seen shadow figures
in the kitchen. - In the kitchen.
You look out
of the corner of your eye,
and you see something
about 6 foot tall,
and I go to look, and it...
Away it goes.
And I've seen that several times
recently.
I did a sketch
of what I saw.
Ooh.
What the ****
I don't know if you're gonna
want to see this.
Oh, my God.
This is exactly
how I see that.
**** exactly
AMY: I did a sketch
of what I saw.
What the ****
I don't know if you're gonna
want to see this.
DONNA: Oh, my God.
This is exactly
how I see that.
**** exactly
So, they're not shadow people,
like you --
No.
Real people.
Yeah, they're enslaved.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
That's crazy.
So, where are these people
coming from?
Well, they're -- I don't know.
He collected them.
He just makes them kind of
**** with the living people.
Can we **** with him?
Yeah,
can we **** with him?
I think so.
- Good.
- Yeah. - Game on.
They just make you
anxious and scared,
and they'll mess around.
But he got that he could
interact with the living.
He can blind you
through migraines,
cause hallucinations,
fear and panic.
He likes to bother and/or scare
children.
Nice.
He can touch
by, like, shaking, pushing down,
feeling smothered --
things like that.
Now, you said he could
cause hallucinations, right?
Yes.
Tell Amy what you saw
in your bedroom.
When I first moved in,
I got woke up
by this horrible wolf thing.
Now, is that what he's capable
of doing, what she's describing?
I think so, yeah.
Absolutely.
You got touched.
I felt I did, yes.
Tell Amy what happened.
MILLARD: On the sofa,
I couldn't go to sleep.
I felt a vivid finger.
Poke you?
Not hard, not painful,
nothing -- Just, it was there.
STEVE: What does he want?
He wants control
and to dominate.
He would probably prefer
no living people around here.
Now, how's it feel knowing that
somebody doesn't want you here?
**** him.
So he can move out
to the **** yard.
Well, you two said
you were up for a fight.
Looks like you got one
on your hands.
The big question is, is it safe
for you guys to stay here?
And is it safe for your son
to stay here?
For that,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
So, there's a few things
that you're going to have to do.
The first thing
is to get rid of the people
that are inside the house.
This is their chance
to leave nicely.
So, what you're gonna do
is take this.
This is, like,
quick-lighting charcoal.
So, you can break it up
into four pieces,
put it in something
that's obviously fireproof,
and then
take the yellow sandalwood
and sprinkle it on
so it'll smoke.
Mm-hmm.
This is used in exorcisms.
State the following
while you burn this --
"I am allowing you to follow
this smoke out of my home.
If you do not leave now,
you will be removed.
I am granting
all the power.
Leave now."
And what will that do?
Basically, she's opening a door
for the ones who want to leave.
Most of them
will want to go.
Yes. I do believe that.
Whoever chooses to stay,
they're gonna be pissed.
They know what's coming.
So, do you think this guy is
gonna be the last guy standing?
Yes.
So, the next thing
that needs to be done is,
you need to find a medium
and a holy person.
Hmm.
First, you're gonna
have the medium come.
Have that medium
do whatever they want
to remove
the remaining dead.
Okay.
Once the medium's done,
the next day,
you need to have a holy person
come
and bless the house
and then the ground.
You down with it?
Well,
if it'll help my wife.
Why don't we discuss
your skepticism?
Let's say I'm not as skeptical
as I claim to be,
I guess, but...
I don't like acknowledging it.
That might give --
If it does exist,
gives it more strength.
- Is that true?
- No.
We have a lot of work
ahead of us.
Just treat this guy
like another perp.
He is. He is.
He's a burglar in the house.
You know, you want to bring
the fight to them, bring it.
Yep. Yes.
We're gonna do it.
Good.
AMY: Donna and Millard have
a tough fight ahead of them,
but I believe
if they follow my advice,
they'll be able to expel
the controlling man,
free his slaves,
and live a normal, peaceful life
with their son.