Somebody here is watching them.
They just look creepy.
I've been physically touch.
Things like touching.
Ooh.
They're cutting apart people
with swords.
I just want a safe spot
for my family.
I don't want my kids
experiencing
anything that I have.
They have their sights set
on the children here.
It's really bad in here.
My name is Amy Allan.
Something is not right.
I see dead people.
This person might have been
a serial killer.
I speak to dead people.
You get those chills.
And they speak to me.
He is darkness.
He is evil.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
I think she broke her neck.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve DiSchiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
You telling me the truth?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I think the devil is down here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who the hell would do this?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
Who's he looking to kill?
We uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
You need to get out of here
right now.
Or time to get out.
It was like endless darkness.
The Dead Files 5x12
Innocent Blood - Rome, NY
Amy and I work each case
independently of one another.
I interview living witnesses
and uncover secrets
about the property's past
while Amy communicates
with the dead.
I'm in Rome, New York.
It's about an hour
east of Syracuse.
Amy and I got called in
by a young married couple,
Sue and Joe.
They didn't sound very good
on the phone.
The activity's so bad
and so physical,
Sue had moved out
with the three kids.
But now she's back.
She says if we can't help her
find a way
to make the activity stop,
it may end her marriage.
I'm really hoping
Amy and I can help them out.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area
of any leading information.
Family photos
and other personal items
need to be covered or removed.
When I'm done, the location will
be ready for tonight's walk.
So in my opening,
I saw all of these thick trees,
and there were all these
native American warriors
standing there
with their bow and arrow drawn.
They're waiting
for something to happen.
They were put there
by this leader guy.
He says it is some kind of,
like, spirit warfare.
He says that there were problems
before the white man,
that they had a lot of battles,
many battles,
with these spirits.
Sue, you sounded
clearly upset on the phone.
Give me an idea
of what you're going through.
We hear banging, knocking,
footsteps.
I've seen apparitions.
I've been physically touched.
I've tried to rationalize
with myself
a million times over again.
I have tried to make up
every excuse in the book
other than it being paranormal.
Now, do you
believe in this stuff?
What really made me
believe in it
was when
my 8-year-old daughter,
you know, she heard people
talking, whispering.
- Is this your kids here?
- Yes.
Now, who's who?
This is Madison.
Okay.
That's Brooke Lynn and Joey.
You had actually left with
the kids at one point, right?
Yes.
I moved out for 11 months.
I just couldn't take it
anymore.
They do not like to be alone.
- So did you take them out
to protect them? - Yes.
I don't want my kids
to grow up experiencing
anything that I have.
What made you come back home?
I wanted my family back.
I don't want them
to be from a broken home.
But you came back to hell.
Yeah.
The same as it was
before I left.
Have you guys ever thought
about just moving?
That would be last resort
only because
my husband inherited it
from his grandparents,
so he's got
an emotional attachment.
This native American guy
says that there is some kind
of a family of beasts,
and they think
that they're ghosts.
These things are occasionally
trying to enter the house.
They're very dark,
and they look kind of like
human beings,
but they're definitely not.
Were they living?
I don't know yet.
They just look creepy.
Okay, so why'd you
bring me in the kitchen?
Well, we hear knocking
at the door.
Okay.
Get up, answer it,
nobody there.
Okay.
So, is anything else going on?
Banging.
It's a... bang! Bang!
Bang! Bang! Bang!
Where does it sound like
it's coming from?
The far right corner
of the living room.
If something's wrong
with the pressure in the pipes,
that would bang.
All of our pipes
are in the basement.
And does it happen
at any given time?
Mainly at night.
Well, that's got to scare
the hell out of you.
Startles you.
I mean, you'll jump out of
your skin when you hear it.
These things are pretty tall.
How tall?
Well, see where
that dent thing is?
About that tall.
Their head kind of jets forward
on a long neck,
and they're hunched,
and you can really see
their shoulder blades.
And also, they have, like,
a spine thing that sticks out.
And then really long arms
with the long fingers.
It's like a weird dragging sound
against the house.
Do you have any idea how
the living might perceive them?
Making noises
on the outside of the house,
looking in through windows,
growling.
Do you know what they want?
They definitely have their
sights set on the children here.
Maybe these are what
the native American warriors
- are fending off?
- Hm.
Maybe they are trying
to protect kids?
I hear footsteps
walking in here at night.
So it sounds like
it's in the room with you?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
You have the TV in here now.
- Do you keep the TV on?
- No.
And there's no sounds
coming from upstairs,
- like the kids walking around, or...
- No.
Is anything else going on?
Aside from being touched
a few times, no.
What do you mean "touched"?
Well, there was an incident
in the shower one time
where I felt like
somebody had rubbed
the outer part of my right arm.
And there was another time...
in the living room,
on the couch.
Okay, what happened?
I felt this... grope.
So I'm assuming
it was forceful.
Okay.
Being touched,
it's a violation.
Not only for me,
but for my husband.
I will do whatever I have to do
to make sure that my kids
do not experience
what I have experienced.
They definitely messed
with the boy who lives here.
In this one,
I just hear crying.
Crying and things like touching.
Ooh.
This is not good.
Oh
Like, trying to hide,
and those weird [Bleep]
finger [Bleep] or whatever.
He was crying
'cause he was scared.
So, you mentioned you
were worried about the kids.
What's going on with them?
Well, Joey...
he's more of just...
Scared to go upstairs alone.
Brooke Lynn
also is the same way,
but she seems to be
a little bit more sensitive.
She's hearing voices.
I wonder if she's being affected
more than I know.
I don't want them to grow up
and be scared.
You know, my worst fear
is that they might get worse.
This is home to them,
and they shouldn't be afraid.
Well, for some
[Bleep] up reason,
dead people come here.
I see this dead woman.
She's kneeling on the floor
right here.
She's only one of many...
many of them.
I think the creatures here
have never been human,
but now I'm seeing dead people
lined up,
and they're seeking help
from a living person.
This person here might have...
ohh... an idea
that they are a medium.
Dead people
coming to get moved on.
This is not good for them.
No, this kid's got to go.
Joe, your wife, Sue,
said that you actually grew up
in this house as a kid.
My grandparents used to live
in this house when I was a kid.
- I grew up across the street.
- Okay.
So, I was always over here.
Did you have experiences
as a kid here?
You know,
a couple different times,
but I kind of blew it off as,
you know, it's no big deal.
So your grandparents, I assume,
- the way you're talking now,
they both passed away? - Yeah.
My grandmother passed in 1997.
She had developed emphysema,
and then the emphysema
led to bone cancer.
She passed away in the house,
under hospice care.
Okay.
What kind of woman was she?
She treated me like, you know,
her little prince,
to be honest with you,
and that's how she always
made me feel.
She made me feel loved.
Very kindhearted lady.
Loved to cook.
I mean, I miss her cooking.
You know,
she was my role model.
When Grandma passed on,
it was very hard for me.
I'm getting this older woman.
She was always cooking
and cleaning in here.
She was little.
Tiny, little lady.
Very frail.
And she's putzing around,
putzing around.
She's, I don't know, related
to somebody here or something?
Living?
Yes.
Now, Joe, when did
your grandfather die?
He died September 10, 2001,
the day before 9/11.
Wow.
I'm not sure how he passed on.
There was never
an autopsy done.
I think that he had
a massive heart attack.
He was a hard-core smoker,
three packs a day.
He actually passed away
right here in the kitchen,
and he was, you know,
dead on the floor.
Okay.
Do you know how old
grandpa was when he died?
75.
Okay, so what kind of a guy
was your grandfather?
He was a Sicilian-American
immigrant.
He was very tough, hard-nosed,
old-school Italian.
Somebody that I looked up to.
I actually have a picture here
of him and I
from when I was a little guy.
Joe, you obviously
knew your grandparents
- better than anybody.
- Right.
Would they want you
to stay here and fight
whatever the hell is going on?
They wouldn't want me
to give up.
Right.
They would want me to fight
for what is mine.
And they instilled in me,
you know, you never give up.
I see, like,
some kids running by.
A little girl
and, I think, a little boy.
They're probably
between, like, 5 and 8?
Somebody here is watching them.
I think that this is a male.
He's pretty dang old.
He's probably like 70 maybe.
Yeah, I think he's Italian.
A heavy, heavy smoker.
He's not a bad guy.
Do you know when he's from?
Maybe he died
in, like, the '90s?
1990s? Early 2000?
Do you know how he died?
I think he had a heart attack.
Maybe it was emphysema,
'cause I can't [Bleep] breathe
for [Bleep] from him.
So, Joe, what made you
bring me out here?
I was inside, and I noticed,
off to the right-hand side,
over here,
there was two mirrors,
and I noticed
that both of 'em cracked
and was just stunned.
Kind of really frightened me,
to be honest with you.
So, did anything hit it that
would have caused it to crack?
There was nothing that
could have been thrown at it,
nothing that hit it.
It wasn't broke
when I looked at it
three minutes
prior to this happening.
Okay.
Let me ask you a question, Joe.
What are you trying to get
out of our investigation?
What's the best thing
we could do for you?
I don't want the kids
to be affected.
I don't want to have to keep
things from them.
You know, as a dad
and as a father,
I just want to be there
to protect them.
I just want things to stop.
It's been tough
on your marriage.
Yeah, it's been tough.
It's weighed pretty hard.
You know, it's tough
to talk about those things
because she means
everything to me,
and without her,
I would have no family.
Since she has come back,
you know,
she's been touched and whatnot,
and I just want a safe spot
for my family.
That's all that I want, really.
I combed through
my client's property records,
and as it turns out,
a family lived on the land
for 50 years.
Most of the time,
this doesn't amount to much,
but I spoke
to a local genealogist
who told me the family
that lived on the land
suffered enough tragedy
to last ten lifetimes.
Kobler family...
they lived on my client's
property for almost 50 years.
From about 1874 to 1919.
Now, when we spoke
on the phone,
you said that there
were some terrible times
- on the property when they were there.
- There was.
It all seems to center around
this guy, Henry J. Kobler.
It started at the age of 9
when his dad died.
His father
was about 34 years old
and passed away
of unknown reasons.
34 is young.
- It is very young.
- Okay.
And as part
of his father's will,
Henry was actually to be given
to another family
as a valuable farmhand
as a way for the family to live.
I've never heard of that
before.
And this lasted for five years
when he was finally returned
to his mother.
Okay.
But it continues.
In 1901, his grandmother,
who was about 83 years old...
keep in mind, she was deaf...
was picking berries one day
on the property
and was attacked by a bull
and killed.
She was mutilated.
All right.
There's this crazy lady
who does run around outside.
She's just all over
the [Bleep] place.
And she did die poorly.
What do you mean?
Her head, you know, got...
it got chopped off...
or ripped off, more.
It's not a nice, clean cut.
Oh, my gosh.
It's messy, very messy.
I'm almost afraid to ask.
What else happened to him?
This is probably
the darkest part of his life.
He had a daughter.
Her name was Ella.
And in 1920,
she was 16 years old,
and she was coming home
from a friend's house,
and she was struck by a car.
Wow.
She was an only child.
Oh, geez.
- This guy can't catch a break, can he?
- Correct.
And actually, three years later,
his wife, Fannie,
she passed away
of a botched surgery.
You're kidding.
She was having a routine
stomach procedure,
and she just died mysteriously
and unexpectedly.
Wow.
He ended up passing away
at the age of 67.
The tragedy in this guy's life
is overwhelming.
This native American guy
is saying, like,
how it's not safe here.
There's no place
that's safe here.
Everyone's at risk.
He is saying that, um...
that everyone knew
that nobody should be here.
That people shouldn't live
in this area.
That it's just for ghosts
to live.
So, he just wants to help them
clear the area out.
Of what?
Living people.
So far,
I've uncovered multiple deaths
that are directly tied
to my client's property.
But I need to see
if there's anything else.
Digging through old records,
I find the Joslin family
originally owned
the land I'm investigating.
Turns out, they suffered a lot
of loss in their time there.
I'm on my way to meet
with a local historian
who did some digging for me.
She says she found
some information
that will definitely help
my case.
Now, Mary,
when I did my research,
I came across
a couple of deaths
associated
with the Joslin family,
- but you said there was a lot more.
- There was a lot more, yes.
- Okay, how many are we talking about?
- They had ten children,
and four of those children died
as babies.
And then they had
two young adults die
from tuberculosis,
which was very prevalent
in that era.
Now, Mary, out of the remaining
kids that lived,
did any of them
stay on the property?
Yes, Foster did.
Okay, so what happened
with him?
He lived to be
about 60 years old.
He was a very busy man.
He married at the age of 58,
and they had one child,
who died as a baby.
Shortly afterwards,
not even a year later,
Foster dies on that property.
I'm seeing
those weird creatures again.
A lot of children
they would eat.
I do see, like,
the kids are being bit.
Open their chests.
The leader
of the native Americans
is showing me a horrifying scene
where the tall creatures
by the side of the house
are killing small children.
Kids?
Kids.
It's pretty gross and sad.
In my research, I also found out
that my client's property
was near
the site of a bloody battle
during the French-Indian war.
I'm heading over
to meet with a local historian
at the actual battle site.
He tells me
it was the most violent fight
in the region's history.
This is where the actual
Battle of Fort Bull took place
in March 27, 1756.
What was the French-Indian war
all about?
It was between
two superpowers...
the British and the French.
The British
were building forts here,
and the French felt that it was
getting too close to their area,
so they sent the men down here
with the Indians from Canada,
and they ended up
surrounding the fort.
And who led these people?
The Lieutenant Gaspard de Léry.
Okay.
And he had with him
the Indian...
Colonel Louis Cook,
who was from Canada.
Okay, so now what went down
with this fight?
- The British were inside this fort here.
- Okay.
The French come up
to the holes in the fort
and were shooting in there,
then they started chopping
at the door.
And finally,
they got through it,
and they're cutting apart people
with swords,
and then they were
scalping them.
Wow.
It was a bloodbath.
The British ended up losing
approximately 60 men.
So, what wound up happening
to the fort?
The French burned it down
with he bodies right in it.
Okay.
Somebody says something
about the dead man down there.
I guess they were settlers.
For whatever reason,
they seem to be stuck
down there.
I do see one of them getting
their head bashed in.
I think they got ambushed,
were brutally murdered.
Yeah.
Do you know who ambushed them?
I think
it was native Americans.
I saw many entities
during my walk,
but two stood out the clearest.
First, the old man
watching over the kids.
He was probably 60, 65.
Heavyset.
Very long eyebrows, very thick.
His nose is rather large.
Next, I described
the tall, dangerous creatures
by the side of the house.
It was hunched.
The shoulder blades
were kind of popping out.
It didn't have any features.
Yes, that's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
finished our investigations,
it's time to reveal our findings
to our clients and each other
for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to meet
Joe and Sue.
They're a great,
down-to-earth couple,
but the activity in the house
is ripping them apart.
It's got so bad last year,
Sue actually left
with the three kids
and moved out
and stayed away for a while.
She's been back
around, what, five months?
Actually, the activity's
gotten even worse now.
They needed our help,
and they want to know
if they can actually stay here
and be safe with their family.
So now that Amy knows
a little bit
about what's going on
with you guys,
I'm gonna ask her to describe
her walk for us.
When I first opened,
I saw native Americans,
and they had
their bows and arrows drawn,
and they were
just in that stance.
I got that they were alive
around 1740, 1750s.
What they're doing is attempting
to protect the area.
There was some type of...
and still is... some kind of,
like, spiritual warfare
going on for them.
I met this older
native American man.
What he said
was that this place
was not meant
for the living to be in.
It is meant for the dead.
I'm not surprised you saw
native Americans
because the British had set up
a fort on the land here.
It was called Fort Bull
back then,
in March 27, 1756,
the French and Canadian Indians
came down here
during the French-Indian wars,
and they attacked the fort.
It was known as
the Fort Bull Massacre.
Now, the guy I spoke to said
it was probably
the bloodiest battle
that was fought
during the French-Indian war
near your property.
Now, the native American
you spoke to
said it wasn't safe
for the living here.
No.
Doing the research
on your property, I went back.
The first white settlers
on your land
was the Joslin family.
They settled in the 1840s.
Hosea and Louisa.
They had ten kids.
Six of them died.
1874, the Koblers
moved into your property.
Most of the tragedy
surrounds a guy named Henry J.
I actually got a photo of him.
He moved onto your property,
he was about... he was a kid.
Three years after he gets there,
his father drops dead,
- 34 years old.
- Oh.
In the will, he's willed off
to be an indentured slave
for some other farm family.
- What?
- Took the mother five years to get him back.
Now, a few years later, 1901,
on your property,
his grandmother, who is deaf,
gets gored to death by a bull
on the property.
Next thing you know,
he gets married,
lives on your property.
His 16-year-old daughter
is coming home on a bicycle.
- She gets hit by a car and killed.
- Oh.
I got a picture of her.
Wow.
Three years after that happens,
his wife goes in
for a simple stomach procedure.
She dies.
So, it's like
there's nothing but death
surrounding this property.
Are you surprised to hear
about all this tragedy?
No, not really.
The location,
it's not healthy for the living.
When I went into the kitchen,
I encountered an older woman,
and from her specifically,
I got that there was
a relationship
with someone living
in the house now.
She prefers the kitchen area,
and then a bit later,
when I went upstairs,
I encountered an older man.
And both of them seem to have
strong ties to the house.
And he was watching
two children playing.
He looked Italian.
He was wearing suspenders.
He definitely did
a lot of work outside.
And when I was around him,
I couldn't breathe.
Like, I felt
that he was a very heavy smoker,
and he either died
of a heart attack or emphysema.
And I think that he died
in the '90s or early 2000s.
I would say that those would be
my grandparents, for sure.
Both of them were smokers.
Grandma was a light smoker.
Grandpa was a heavy smoker.
Worked construction
his whole entire life.
Grandma's favorite spot
was the kitchen,
and I remember,
as a little kid,
Grandpa used to spend
a lot of time
at the top of the stairs.
So, for you to say that,
it hits home, big time.
So, my grandmother
passed on of...
it started with emphysema,
and the emphysema
led to bone cancer.
- Oh. - And that's what
she passed on from
- was bone cancer.
- Oh, wow.
And she did pass away
in the house.
Yes, both of them passed away
My grandfather passed away
in the kitchen,
and my grandmother passed away
in what is now our bedroom.
Would it be okay
if I showed Amy their pictures?
- Sure, sure.
- You sure?
Yeah.
It's be all right?
I'm all right with you sharing.
This is his Grandma.
Mm. Okay.
And this is his grandpa,
and that's him as a baby.
Oh, okay.
I did do a sketch
of the guy I met,
but just sitting up on the bed.
Oh, geez.
That's your grandfather,
trust me.
Oh, my gosh.
I miss him.
He watches the kids.
I'm just glad to know
that he, too,
watches over the little ones
'cause that's how he was with me
when I was a little guy.
And this is why
it's so important, really,
for Joe to make this house
work for him.
He just... he feels like
it's a tribute, really,
to your grandparents.
Yeah, and I just feel
that I have to pay
a debt of gratitude to them.
Okay, I have a few questions.
How old are your children,
and what are their names?
Madison, she's 10.
Brooke Lynn is 8,
and Joey is 6.
Okay.
Um, so...
My walk was very active.
So, I'm upstairs, and I went
into the room on the left.
So, I go in there,
and I see a little boy,
and he's crying
because there's something
in the room,
and it was touching him.
This was obviously
very disturbing,
and I don't feel that this
is a very good place
for children.
So, I went into the other room,
and what I saw there was, like,
a line of people out the door.
So, initially,
there's this one woman.
She's kneeling
at the side of the bed
trying to talk
to this little girl,
and she's begging her for help.
And then there's
a line of dead people
out the door
and going down the stairs,
and all of them want help
to be moved on.
And the young girl is living?
Yes.
Whether this child
knows it or not,
she's a medium.
And is actually helping people
in her sleep
to, you know, move on.
I Knew it.
That's why this is so hard
on Sue.
She actually thinks
Brooke Lynn's sensitive.
I know that this is crazy,
but Brooke Lynn wrote
this book a couple years ago
out of nowhere that was called
"Blood drops Everywhere."
And it kind of scared us.
- It was pretty graphic.
- Yeah, okay.
She was probably
in kindergarten, first grade.
I mean, talking about somebody
being stabbed with a knife.
Honestly, it's not unusual
for children who are mediums
to act these things out
via dolls or writing stories
that, you know, would be
more appropriate for an adult.
Apparently, she probably knows
more than I do.
You had a lot of stuff
on this walk.
What else did you see?
This is, you know,
one of the things
that really bothered me.
I saw this thing by the house,
and it was, like,
trying to get into the house.
It was odd.
It was very, very tall.
It was kind of hunched
by its neck,
but it had a weird, long neck.
It had, like,
a human-shaped head.
It just really bothered me.
It did not look human.
I feel, like,
this draw to the window,
and them being outside
and, like, looking in,
making weird noises
and scratches.
And I could see it had,
like, sharp teeth.
Can they make noises
that they'll hear...
like a knocking...
by any chance?
Yeah, I wouldn't be surprised.
- How about banging?
- Yeah.
Which we've had numerous,
numerous encounters with,
knocking and banging.
Ooh.
- I'm trying to figure out what the hell these
things look like. - Well, I did do a sketch.
I'm dying to see this.
Oh, get the [Bleep]
out of here.
- I'm trying to figure out what the hell these
things look like. - Well, I did do a sketch.
I'm dying to see this.
Oh, get the [Bleep]
out of here.
I'm never gonna get any sleep
in that house... never.
She doesn't want to look at it,
and I'll explain why.
When was it, last week?
Ugh.
Broad daylight,
and she says to me,
"did you just see something
walk across the lawn?"
I seen its head
up above the porch railing.
A couple days later,
she says to me,
"it must have been
pretty tall."
You know what, babe,
I'm gonna turn this around,
all right?
This way,
you don't have to look at it.
Let me ask you, what the [Bleep]
are these things?
I don't think
I've ever seen you
sketch something like that
before.
- Were they ever human?
- No. Mnh-mnh.
I think that these things
harmed children in the past.
- Geez.
- Like, way back when.
They're very old,
and they're definitely focused
on your son.
I think
it's what was touching him.
Sue's been
physically touched twice.
Describe that to Amy,
what it was like.
It was just a rub.
You know, like this.
Flesh on flesh.
The other one,
it's a little difficult
for her to talk about,
but they were together
on the couch,
and she was inappropriately
touched.
- Okay.
- There was nobody else there.
It automatically triggered
just pure anger.
Joe and Sue, I know you've heard
a lot tonight,
and it wasn't easy to hear.
But at least now you know
what's going on in your home.
Big question is, though,
can you continue
the legacy
of your grandparents, Joe,
and stay here safely
with your wife and children?
For that,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
There's a lot going on here.
Especially
because of Brooke Lynn.
She's a medium.
So what you're
gonna have there is, like,
a lighthouse, almost,
in your case,
where the dead are coming
to seek help
from the living sensitives
in the house.
Some of the dead on your
property don't want to leave,
that's why she's gonna need
to learn about her abilities
and to feel comfortable
with them.
I would suggest opening
a line of communication
with all the kids about
any experiences that they have.
My suggestion is,
let them all keep
dream journals,
as well as you guys.
I didn't even mention this
to nobody.
Brooke Lynn just said that
a couple weeks ago.
She wanted all of us
to get journals
and write our dreams down.
Honest to God.
It's so weird.
She wants to talk about it.
Sounds like she's
ahead of the game.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
All right, the next thing
is the need to protect.
Since native Americans
are guarding your land,
I suggest you contact
a local shaman
who can help you remove
the dead that have been
attracted to your property.
In the meantime...
this is black salt.
Take just a little bit of this
and put it at the entrance
of each bedroom door.
This will create
a protective barrier.
The next thing
I would like you to do
is to build a stone fence
following that property line.
So, this stone wall
you're talking about,
- is this keep the bad out?
- Yeah.
Is it gonna keep
that thing you drew out?
No, I don't think so.
So, no matter what,
they're gonna be there?
Yeah.
Well... ugh.
You have a potential situation
that I personally
have never encountered before.
When I was doing the sketch
of the thing that I saw,
I started to get really upset
by it,
and the reason why was because
I was being told that, in fact,
it was some type
of alien creature.
I know, it's a lot.
And they're trying,
through subtle ways,
to have the living people
get out of the area.
I've never encountered anything
like this in my entire career.
I'm not exactly sure
what these things are
or where they're from,
but it's possible
they're from another world
or another dimension.
I can introduce you
to some experts,
and it's very possible
that they'll have suggestions
as far as how to keep
those suckers away.
What about his grandparents?
They're good.
They're gonna hang out.
Mm.
What are you thinking about?
It's just craziness.
It's a lot of stuff, huh?
Yeah, no doubt.
No doubt.
So, Joe, I got to ask.
Are you gonna take Amy's advice
and do what she says?
Absolutely.
I mean, you know,
all I'm looking for as a dad
is just, you know,
keep my wife and kids safe.
I want to take her advice.
I want to do what we can do
to eliminate
all of this chaos...
And hope that those creatures
will go.
I wish I had better news
for Joe and Sue.
I know if they build a barrier
and work with Brooke Lynn,
their lives should improve.
But whether they can continue
to co-exist
with those creatures,
unfortunately,
remains to be seen.