She can go into people's bodies.
Said the ghost
has scratched him.
I yelled at whatever was here,
"Leave!"
Something is so physically wrong
with her.
The body was chopped up
and thrown into the harbor.
This is un-[bleep]- bearable.
So much pain!
It's really bad in here.
My name is Amy Allan.
Something is not right.
I see dead people.
This person might have been
a serial killer.
I speak to dead people.
You get those chills.
And they speak to me.
He is darkness.
He is evil.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
I think she broke her neck.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve di Shiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
Homicide detective.
You telling me the truth?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I think the devil is down here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who the hell would do this?
But Steve and I never speak...
we never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
Who's he looking to kill?
We uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
You need to get out of here
right now.
Or time to get out.
It was like endless darkness.
Amy and I conduct
separate investigations.
I hear what living witnesses
have to say
and uncover any secrets
buried in the property's past
while Amy talks with the dead.
I'm in historic
Winthrop, Massachusetts.
It's about 15 minutes
outside of Boston.
Amy and I got called in
by a woman named Cynthia.
Now, she was hysterical
on the phone.
She says
that whatever's in the house
is attacking her 14-year-old
son, who has special needs.
She says if we can't help,
she's afraid
what's going to happen next.
Before Amy arrives,
I look for anything that could
reveal information to her,
like family photographs.
Once I conceal them all,
the location will be ready
for tonight's walk.
I don't feel good.
There's some woman there.
She's making me so sick.
The dead know I'm coming
long before I do.
And one dead woman
from this location
is desperate
to have her story told.
Oh, man.
That is some pain, man.
She's jumped me,
entered my body.
And I'm experiencing her pain,
which is so intense
that I'm scared for my safety.
This is not good.
This woman that showed up,
she is very sick.
She's obviously inconsolable
and in so much pain.
This is un-[bleep]- bearable.
Cynthia, you sounded
really concerned on the phone.
We've had a lot of noises,
tapping, banging.
I've seen things, shadows.
But, really,
the reason why I've called
is my youngest son, Nathaniel.
He's 14
and is in the autism spectrum.
And I really feel
this is affecting him.
Okay. In what way?
Well, he's actually
been scratched a few times.
He's frightened.
And he's not quite the same
anymore,
since we've moved in here.
He was a fun kid,
really outgoing.
Okay.
I called him the mayor.
He would be all bubbly
and talk to anyone.
And he's just different.
There's no joy anymore.
I'm so mad to see him afraid.
And I yelled at whatever
was here to leave him alone.
"My home, my child.
Leave."
It didn't cut it.
I don't know what to do for him
anymore. I really don't.
This girl that jumped me,
she can go into people's bodies
very easily.
So, I had to, like,
disconnect a little bit
because she was
making me so sick.
She inadvertently jumps people.
And she is seeking help.
Unfortunately, her presence
can make people feel
very, very depressed...
And suicidal.
So, now, who lives in the house
with you?
Well, my husband lives here
with myself and Nathaniel.
And I have two older sons
that live here, as well.
Okay.
And this was my parents' house,
and I grew up here.
Oh, okay.
And I wanted to
come back to my home.
Well, did you have any
experiences when you were...
Yes.
As soon as my parents
bought this house,
we all had experiences.
Did you have any hesitation
about buying it, then?
Yeah.
I had a catholic priest
come in,
bless the house,
and pray for Nathaniel.
And I was confident that
that would be sufficient.
Now I do feel guilty.
Okay.
Your parents
have both passed away?
Yeah. This is my dad.
He passed away here at home
in '95.
He had pancreatic cancer.
Ah, geez.
So, now, he passes.
What about mom?
She passed in the nursing home.
When I bought the house,
she was very upset.
Okay.
Was there a reason for that?
I have no idea.
After it closed,
she left me a message
that she didn't want me
to have the house.
Yeah, but it's to her daughter.
She made it quite clear.
Okay. Did you get along
with your mom?
Um...
she was a very
irritable-type person.
She had a really bad temper.
Okay.
Did you ever
resolve your mother
being upset with you
buying the house?
No, not at all.
There is an old lady.
She watches.
She's always like this...
Her thing is that if
she showed herself for real,
nobody would be afraid of her.
Because who's going to be afraid
of a little old lady?
So, she makes herself tall.
Like, if she stands straight up,
she can put her head
through the ceiling.
She has, like, a long,
spindly, like, neck
and, like, skeleton legs.
It's a very strange composition
of pieces.
She's angry, bitter,
resentful, hateful.
And when this lady was alive,
she was very distant and cold.
She hates humanity in general.
And, you know,
she had to, like, hide that.
Do you know when she's from?
She says that she was alive
in the '50s.
Okay.
And she was a housewife.
Why'd you bring me
in this room?
Well, Nathaniel won't go in
his room -- frightened to death.
So, we had to trade bedrooms.
My husband and I
are now sleeping in his room.
That was my bedroom as a child.
The bedroom set
that's in there now,
that actually was
my parents' bedroom set.
Oh, really?
When they passed, I kept it.
Okay.
That's interesting.
Now, are things
any better for you
that you're in the other room?
No, actually.
I've been having
terrible nightmares, you know,
where someone gets injured
in a boating accident
or crossing the road
and getting hit.
It's just...
they're violent accidents.
And I'm not one
to dream like that.
Are you taking any medication
that may cause weird dreams?
No, nothing at all.
How are you living like this?
It's terrible.
Here I am, an adult, and I sleep
with a night-light in there.
I do feel like
a child is being chased...
and a woman.
Like, emotionally,
they're getting chased here.
What do you mean?
I don't know how to explain it.
Are they being chased
in their nightmares, maybe?
Oh, she likes this room.
Mm.
She does things in the bed.
She likes to stand right here,
slide down real slow,
and then, like, be on the floor,
all the way on the floor.
And then, she'll like --
you know, she'll strangle.
But when she touches her,
she takes her life.
What do you mean?
She is going to kill her.
So, Nicholas, I understand
that this was Nathaniel's room,
but you're sleeping in here?
Yes.
So, let me ask you,
what was the breaking point
for him to move out of here?
Well, one night,
in the middle of the night,
he came running into our room
and said,
"There's a guy in my room" --
a shadow man, shadow figure,
however he said it.
And he wouldn't
come back in his room.
He said,
"I'm not going back in there.
I'm not sleeping in there
again."
Got to figure out
what's going on here.
This is too much.
Your wife said he was getting
physically attacked.
Well, actually, one day,
he woke up.
And then he came and says,
"Mommy, look at my arm."
And we took a picture,
and that's what we saw.
And I said,
"What happened?"
He says, "A ghost did it."
He said the ghost
had scratched him.
Did you guys question him
about that?
Yeah. I mean,
my first thing is, like,
"Maybe you scratched yourself
when you're sleeping."
He said no, he wasn't.
He was pretty adamant.
He says,
"I wasn't sleeping."
There's no way he would ever
make up anything
or do that
and then tell us something else.
The old lady,
she likes it in this area.
She wants to freak people out
and make them leave
and not come in here.
She is very, very proud
of inflicting pain.
What kind of pain?
People get scratched here.
What about yourself?
Are you having any experiences?
Well, the first night I
came in here, I had a nightmare.
I thought it was real, the most
vivid dream I probably ever had.
I was looking up at a plane.
The plane started coming down
and, you know, exploded,
right into the ground.
Dreams, like, with screaming
people in it and violence.
It's kind of interesting
how you and your wife
are having
the same type of dreams.
Is it just dreams you're experiencing?
No.
One night, I woke up wide awake
about 3:00 in the morning.
I looked up,
and I saw a shadow.
And it was going back and forth
across the top of the door.
Like, you could see it
blocking the light.
It was about a minute,
at least a minute.
And then I got up,
and I started to come over here.
And there was nothing here.
This stuff is confusing to me.
We've prayed.
And the priest
across the street,
he came in and blessed the house
and prayed for Nathaniel.
What I've done, you know,
isn't the answer.
So, to me, this would be
like a last resort, even,
you know, you guys here.
I believe, like, pretty basic,
like, black and white,
like angels and demons,
you know, good and bad.
Right.
What do you think this is?
There's something wrong.
There's something else
that's going on here
with these doors, this hallway.
I'm thinking right now
it's the old lady.
Why is she so weird
about how she moves?
Mm. She says...
Oh, no, yeah.
That adds to, like,
the creepy, creepy factor.
She's a sociopath.
She's chasing them,
these two people.
One is the living woman.
And the other one,
I think it's a boy.
I was talking to mom and dad,
and mom was telling me
that you're having a tough time
in the house.
Oh, yeah.
When I go upstairs, it takes me
a while to fall asleep
because I feel like I'm being
watched for some reason.
And a couple times,
I saw this weird black thing.
It was just, like, an outline.
And what did it do?
It just stands there
for like five seconds.
And what happened?
It just completely disappeared.
I got so scared,
I actually switched rooms
with my parents.
Okay.
Dad showed me a picture
of a scratch on your arm.
Yes.
What happened?
I felt, like, a weird burning.
And I looked,
and it was a weird scratch.
Did the cat do it or anything?
No, definitely not
because it was perfectly fine.
And then,
like five minutes later,
there was a weird scratch.
Would you be afraid
to be alone in the house?
Yes, actually.
Okay.
What about your old bedroom?
That's the worst.
Old lady does weird [bleep]
up here.
What does she do?
She does weird stuff
on the floor up in here.
And then,
there's someone crying about it,
being afraid about it.
I think it takes her a lot
to murder someone.
So, she's focused on
offing a living woman
that lives here now.
She's just kind of trying to
get that done and over with.
And then, she'll move on
to the next person.
She's definitely, like,
screwing with the kid now.
You know you're in the northeast
when you trace the history
on a property
and it takes you back
to the 1600s.
Turns out, the first settlers
on my client's property
lived there
for a couple hundred years.
I asked a local genealogist
to look into it for me,
and he said he found something
that will help my case.
You know, Steve,
this is one of the oldest deeds
I've ever searched through.
It goes back to the 1600s.
And I came across
the Bill and Belcher families.
Mm-hmm.
What can you tell me
about them?
In November of 1635,
John Bill and his wife
came from England
with their family.
And by 1690, the family
owns most of Pullen Poynt,
today's Winthrop.
Okay.
So, how does the Belcher family
get involved?
Well, in 1697, Hannah Bill
marries Joseph Belcher.
Okay. So, these were two
pretty prominent families, then.
Exactly.
Now, you said there was
some information on the phone
that would help my case.
What were you talking about?
Well, I went through
over 200 years of records.
And, of course, there's deaths,
standard things...
That is
until the mid-to late-1800s.
Okay.
During that period,
a dozen Belcher children
under the age of four die.
Okay.
Do you know what they died from?
You might want to take a look
at some of these death records.
Most of it was common ailments
of the time --
cholera, consumption,
what we know today
as tuberculosis.
So, we're talking about
some kind of an epidemic?
No.
But in the 1700s, there was
an outbreak of smallpox.
And that was in the area
I'm investigating?
Exactly.
Okay.
I saw the old lady.
And then I saw
these three little kids.
And she was claiming
that she killed them.
Then I heard a man say
that she didn't kill them.
This is not a good room.
Pain and then pain, pain.
Blood and death and pain.
Now that I know there was
a smallpox epidemic in Winthrop,
I need to find out more
about it.
I'm heading over
to meet with a local historian.
He says
there's a direct connection
between the outbreak and
the property I'm investigating.
So, Bob, I understand that
there was a smallpox epidemic
related to the property
I'm investigating.
Correct.
When did it happen?
December of 1751.
So, how does this epidemic
start?
The ship The Bumper
came into town
and ran aground
here in Winthrop.
Captain Nicholas Cousens,
actually, he had a crew member
that was sick.
And he quarantined him on ship
prior to this crash.
He ordered everybody
off the ship.
And then he just basically
got townspeople
to help out him
unloading his ship.
So, that's how
it winds up spreading?
Correct.
That's a scumbag move.
It is.
Over 7,500 people got infected.
569 people died.
Wow.
Considering the time it was
and the amount of people,
that's a lot of people.
A lot of people,
especially around this area.
I mean, back then,
they were mainly farmers.
What do you know about
the symptoms of smallpox?
Well, you have a high fever,
body ache,
have open sores,
and stuff like that.
And if you'll look
at this picture,
you can see how painful
it can be.
This is what a guy
would look like?
That's what it looks like.
Oh, geez.
Yeah.
So, Bob, you mentioned
on the phone
there was a direct connection
between the epidemic and
the property I'm investigating.
Right.
Because a lot of the patients
were actually taken
to John Bill's house,
the owner of that property.
That took a lot of guts
for this guy to do that.
A lot of guts, yep.
I see all of these men
running up from over here.
They're all dying.
And they're all scared.
They're all white men.
There is so much pain.
All these dead --
these dead souls, these men.
There's so much sadness here.
I'm at the local library
to see what else I can uncover
about my client's property.
Digging through old records,
I find a young woman named
Suzanna Geary who died in 1905.
But what's really disturbing is
where her body was discovered --
washed up onshore
right by Cynthia's house.
I'm heading over to meet with
a local police lieutenant
who I asked
to look into it for me.
He says this story
is every parents' nightmare.
Lieutenant, came across
this gruesome case back in 1905.
Body washed up on the shore
pretty close to the property
I'm investigating.
What do you know about it?
Suzanna Geary --
20-year-old dancer
originally from Massachusetts
working in a performance
in Boston.
This is a picture of her
right here
taken from a newspaper
back in 1905.
She's a pretty girl.
Yeah, pretty girl.
She was going out with one of the stage
managers of her production company.
Okay.
She became pregnant,
wasn't married...
Ah.
...and things started to go bad
from there.
I know that this woman
is younger,
probably in her teen or 20s.
She has long hair about here,
brown.
She'd kind of skinny
for a pregnant woman.
The young girl who jumped me
at the start of my walk
has left my body.
And I'm now able to see
what she looked like in life.
I'm surprised to find
that she's pregnant.
Very pretty, large, brown eyes.
Very dark.
Um...
and obviously very sad.
So, what happens next?
Suzanna and her boyfriend,
Nathan --
here's a sketch of him
right here...
...they decide
that having this baby
isn't going to be the best for
either of them in their careers.
And they decide
to go have an illegal abortion.
They find a doctor
in the Boston area.
Okay.
That doesn't go so well
because she develop
septicemia and peritonitis,
two highly infectious diseases.
They're serious today,
never mind back then.
I've heard of it.
But what are the symptoms?
You have any idea?
Well, I know that a sepsis infection
is in your bloodstream,
and it can travel
throughout your body.
Causes excruciating pain.
It's a deadly disease.
Okay. So, now,
she develop this infection.
And I assume
she goes back to the doctor?
That is correct.
A second procedure is performed
by this doctor, Percy McLeod.
But they go back
to the same office?
Yes.
But this is a new doctor that sees her?
We don't know exactly who
performed the first procedure.
It could have been
Dr. McLeod.
He was trying to fix whatever went
wrong with the first procedure.
And instead of fixing it,
she dies a day later.
She was pregnant...
and she lost the baby.
And I think she lost her man.
Something is so physically wrong
with her.
This woman's physical and
emotional trauma is so severe
that I'm experiencing
all of the pain she felt
when she was alive.
I've never felt so much pain.
It hurt.
It was so painful.
Seriously, I would've [bleep]
just shot myself in the head.
Her loss is just...
Oh, it's really bad.
So, how do we end up with her
going DOA in a doctor's office
to being in the water?
I'm sure that the doctors,
realizing that they had
a dead body on their hands,
panicked and started to
try to cover up their tracks,
try to dispose of the body
so that no finger-pointing
would be made
that they were doing
any kind of illegal activity.
These two gentlemen here --
hired by the doctor
to dispose of the body.
The body was chopped up,
went into suitcases,
and thrown into the harbor.
So, what happens next?
Two young boys in a rowboat
saw the bag floating,
decided to bring it in.
God knows what's inside of it.
They bring it to shore,
they open it up,
and wrapped up inside
was a torso.
What did they do with the torso
at this point?
Well, it's right next to
the cemetery.
They bring it in
to the cemetery.
And that's right next to
the house I'm investigating.
Exactly.
Somehow, the mother
identifies it as her daughter.
So now we have a victim.
We found an article,
actually, of divers
looking for other evidence.
And that's when they
discovered her head.
Oh, wow.
Look at this.
So, now, what winded up
happening with the doctor?
Did he ever get convicted
or charged?
The people that helped the
doctor, they were convicted.
They were sent to
the Charlestown penitentiary
for seven years.
The doctor in this case,
he was charged,
but he was acquitted.
During my walk, a traumatized
young woman jumped my body.
I'm meeting with a sketch artist
to describe
how she appeared in life.
She was on the thin side.
Deep-brown colored eyes,
very large.
Very pointy chin.
Yes, that's who I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients
for the first time.
Amy, I want you to meet
Nicholas and Cynthia.
This is their home.
They've both experienced
a lot of things here.
But the main reason
they called us
and their main concern is their
14-year-old son, Nathaniel.
Okay.
He has special needs,
and it seems like
he's being singled out
and victimized
in a violent manner.
What they want to know from us
is if it's safe enough
to stay here.
With that, I'm going to ask her
to tell us
about how her walk went.
On my way to do the walk,
I was jumped by a female.
And I became violently ill.
It was extremely sudden,
totally unexpected,
and extremely overwhelming.
She felt so much loneliness.
Okay.
Getting jumped is
not easy for her.
I hate when it happens.
Hmm.
I can't even imagine
living with that kind of pain.
If I had been her,
I would have just taken a gun
and shot myself in the head.
The thing is is that
she doesn't mean to jump people.
But when she does, the people
can become violently ill,
extremely depressed,
possibly suicidal.
One of the things
you told me about your son
was how his personality changed.
Well, really shortly
after we moved in,
he just really changed.
I used to call him
the little mayor.
Talked to everyone.
Now, he doesn't want to
really go out
and do things with other kids
or enjoy school activities
like he used to.
Were you able
to find anything else about her?
Well, she's probably between
16 and 22, I would say.
Very little, thin, pale.
She had very long brown hair
and huge brown eyes.
And what I figured out
was that sense of loss
was because
she had been pregnant
and lost her child.
A lot of it's making sense.
It's not a story
you're going to want to hear.
So, a young dancer
by the name of Suzanna Geary.
She was 20 years old.
She was from Boston.
Her boyfriend,
who was the stage manager
for the dancing troupe
she was in got her pregnant.
Uh-oh.
And they decided to
get an abortion,
which obviously was illegal
back then.
And there's a sketch
of her boyfriend.
This is Morris Nathan.
Now, while she's recovering,
she develop
what they call septicemia.
She got very sick,
excruciating pain, apparently.
So, she goes back
to Dr. Percy McLeod.
They do another procedure.
Didn't go too well.
She dies the next day.
Now, the police at the time
believed he panicked.
He cuts her up...
dismembers her body,
then hires two guys to take
the body and get rid of it --
throws it into the harbor.
God.
A few days later,
her body washes up
very close to the house.
Now, I've got a picture of her.
And she's a pretty girl, too.
Oh, my God.
Well, I did do a sketch of her.
And this is the same girl
that jumped you?
Yes.
You take a look at that.
Without question, that's her.
Wow.
The eyes, the eyes.
Mm-hmm.
That's horrible.
I mean, I can't even
put words to that.
What else did you see
on your walk?
So, I came into the house,
and in the kitchen,
I see this elderly woman.
And she is filled with
resentment, hatred, bitterness.
She was very cold and distant
in life.
One of the things
that she expressed
was that she absolutely
disdains humanity
and that when she was alive
she had repressed that.
She told me that she lived here,
I think, in the '50s,
that she was a housewife.
You mentioned your mom wasn't
always that great, that nice.
Yeah, my mother kind of
didn't like a lot of people.
She kind of ruled the roost
a lot.
She didn't like anybody.
I'm trying to be gracious.
She actually said that she loved
the dog better than my children.
Really?
You said you got a good look?
Mm-hmm.
Wow.
Is that who you saw?
Yeah.
That looks like her.
But definitely older.
She didn't want you to
have the house, either.
No, mnh-mnh.
When she found out the house
was sold and the papers passed,
she just was really upset
and left me a voicemail.
She said
I stole the effing house.
And she doesn't give an "f"
what I think.
And "f" me,
and "f" everyone else.
And use your imagination.
Well, all I know is
that the woman I met
repressed a lot of stuff,
like did not really
give a [bleep] about anybody.
Mm-hmm.
Sounds right.
What is she doing
around the house?
Nothing good.
She wants to scare people.
She had made herself
about seven to eight feet tall.
Like, she was showing me
this monstrous, disgusting,
deformed thing.
And that helps her to frighten
and cause fear and all of that.
I know she can get physical
in the house to people.
Like,
upstairs in the master bedroom,
I saw her
coming through the wall.
And she'll, like,
slink down onto the floor
and then come up the bed
and, like, attempt to strangle
the female
that sleeps in the bed.
The other thing
that she tries to do is,
she likes to enter nightmares
and create them.
And what she'll do
is get in there
and literally make the people
feel like
they're being chased by her.
Now, you guys
are sleeping in there,
and you're having nightmares
every frigging night.
Yeah.
I've had nightmares,
vivid nightmares.
It's always something violent.
Last night, I had one
of a parachute jump go wrong.
There was also
boating accidents,
just horrible things like that.
Now, you mentioned that
it can get physical.
This is a picture of Nathaniel.
Oh, okay.
And he's been woken up
with scratches on him.
Wow.
It's happened a few times.
Another time, I put him to bed,
and he woke up in the morning,
and he had a long 8-inch scratch
right from the groin area
all the way down.
Is she capable of doing this
on Nathaniel like that?
Very possible.
Very.
Because what she's doing now
is just inflicting pain,
like, whether it's mentally,
emotionally, physically.
And now, she definitely
has her sights set
on two individuals
in the house.
One was the young boy.
And the other
is the lady of the house.
You're the only lady
in the house.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, boy.
What I got was that, you know,
she's trying to, like, you know,
really strangle you,
like, to death...
...and that she wants to get you
and then go after him.
I definitely got the sense
that she would go after him
big-time, too.
I feel sick right now.
She's trying to, like,
you know,
really strangle you,
like, to death.
And she wants to get you
and then go after him.
I feel sick right now.
You don't look surprised.
No.
I know the whole family,
and I saw what she did
to, basically, all of them.
You okay?
Yeah.
This is probably one of the
hardest reveals I've ever done.
Did you feel abused
when you were a kid?
Oh, yeah. Absolutely.
Oh, absolutely.
I'm just surprised
with Nathaniel.
She was always like that.
I mean,
does she really feel like
you guys just ruined her life,
or what?
Oh, yeah.
She had a hot temper, for sure.
Well, I know this isn't
what you wanted to hear.
I know it's something
I didn't want to hear, either.
The big question left is,
is it safe for you
to raise Nathaniel in the house?
For that, I'm going to
turn it over to Amy.
What you need to deal with
is getting rid of
unwanted visitors, so to speak.
So, therefore, we kind of
want to put her to rest
so that you're not going to
have to deal with her.
Because my fear is that if
you don't take care of her now,
it's going to get worse.
It could be so debilitating,
I don't know
if you could get her out.
My suggestion is
to get an individual
that is a mental medium.
A mental medium
is a type of medium
that does not feel
the individual's death.
Therefore, they won't be
as impacted by her.
So, what is this mental medium
going to do?
I would suggest
that they go in your backyard,
talk to her over two days.
What they're basically going to
be talking to her about
is letting her
tell them her story
to help her to move on.
Will she leave at that point?
Yes.
So, it sounds like the biggest
problem here is your mom.
Mm-hmm.
As far as she's concerned,
what I would suggest doing
is writing a letter to her.
In this letter,
I would like you to focus
on what she is no longer allowed
to do,
that she is no longer allowed
to control you, your home,
your family, or your dreams,
that you are taking back
the power and control
of your home and your family.
And then,
have a physical medium,
which is somebody like me,
come to the home.
And you and this physical medium
are going to deal with her.
Then, you're going to
read your letter.
I want you to yell.
I do.
I feel like you need to
fricking yell at her.
Don't let her stop you.
I don't care whether you feel
like you're going to throw up.
I don't care
if you do throw up.
I don't care what happens
as long as you finish
what you write.
Right.
Once you're done,
then you tell that physical
medium, "Get rid of her."
Are you afraid to do this?
Uh, anxious.
Once I get started,
I'll be on a roll.
I see how protective you are
of him.
Yes. I am very much.
What about you? Are you
going to take Amy's advice?
Yes, definitely.
I look forward to it.
Cynthia has her work
cut out for her.
But I believe if she's able
to stand up to her mother,
she'll free her family of
the evil that's tormenting them
and they'll be able to
live a peaceful life.