Stop it.
In this special edition
of "The Dead Files"...
I didn't really comprehend
what I was doing.
And I flipped out.
...Steve and Amy
answer your questions...
Do you ever worry about
being physically attacked?
- The banshee lady
wanted to kill me. -
...revealing
their most shocking moments...
She just wanted to die.
That's how bad it was.
- ...and their greatest fears.
Amy?
That week,
I ended up in the hospital,
having to have
blood transfusions.
A lot of physical mediums
die young.
It's Steve and Amy
like never before.
That first episode,
I was hesitant even
going out there.
She didn't strike me as somebody
that could talk to dead people.
You've asked.
Is there one case in particular
that hit you the hardest?
They answer.
That one entity
was so powerful,
he had caused
so much horror.
Hi. I'm Jim Casey,
the creator and one of
the executive producers
of "The Dead Files,"
and I'm sitting here with the
two stars of the show,
Amy Allan and Steve Di Schiavi,
who have taken a break
before their next investigation
to answer some fan questions.
Now, what I want
to know first is,
what question do you guys
get asked most often?
Did I ever have
a paranormal experience?
If I had a dollar
for every one of those,
we'd be on an island
doing this interview.
And what's the answer?
No.
I mean, everybody
wants to know why.
I'm like, "Not everybody has
a paranormal experience," right?
Some people are
more closed than others.
I'm pretty closed.
Amy, how about you?
What question do you
get asked the most?
People ask me what's going on
at their house.
I can't answer them
unless I do
an investigation there.
I can't give general answers
to those types of questions.
Well, we actually get
a lot of questions
about Amy's abilities.
Savannah wants to know,
"Amy, when did you first know
that you could see
and talk to the dead?"
I have been able to do it
since I was a child,
but I didn't really comprehend
what I was doing
really until I was maybe
in my teenage years.
It was like this moment
of complete realization,
and I flipped out.
And then I really went
on a quest
to figure out if I was insane,
if this was real.
Okay.
Nicole writes, "Amy,
at the beginning of the case
"at Plan B, the restaurant
in Asbury Park, New Jersey,
you start to explain how
you communicate with the dead."
When I encounter the dead,
I am seeing them
just like I'm interacting
with a living person.
But I might be communicating
with residual energy,
or I might be communicating
with dead people.
That's what I've always been
trying to find out.
"Can you tell me more about how
and what you see and hear?"
It depends on the location.
If there's a good, cool dead
person who's willing to chat,
then they look like,
you know, physical.
They're just there.
They're just talking to me.
They look like you.
You know, it's all good.
If there's not
or they're being jerks,
they might not look
as physical.
They might run away,
And then there's times
where there's no dead people,
and then it's more like,
you know,
I'll utilize some of my psychic
abilities, like psychometry,
and that's when, you know,
I might be touching things,
and then I see pictures
in my mind of what's going on.
There was a -- a big event.
Someone's lost...
and people are running all over
inside the house.
There's, panic.
Why are sometimes
things not not so clear?
Sometimes it's like I'm standing
there in the middle of a room
and I'm surrounded by, you know,
this throng of people
who are just yelling out
all of these various things
about themselves.
And, you know, I'm just trying
to do the best job I can
as far as figuring out
who is the person
I should be focusing on.
And I'm also typically yelling
at them to line up, and --
You know,
there's a lot more going on
than, you know,
what people see.
You had told me once before
that, like,
once they find out
that you can actually see
and talk to them,
they're kind of like,
"My God,
we've got somebody
we can actually talk to."
So, you know, it's like, "Hey."
You know, it's like --
It's like a mob.
Right. Exactly.
And you're trying to make sense
of what happened...
...and you're getting 50 stories
at the same time. - Right.
Steve, you're a former Marine.
You're a former cop.
You're a former
homicide detective.
Yes.
You've spent much of your life
helping the living.
Yeah.
Yeah, for the most part.
But I have a question for you
here from Laura,
who wants to know,
"It's unusual for a detective
"to be involved
with the paranormal.
How did you first
get involved with it?"
Well, you approached me
about doing this.
And you know
how hesitant I was.
I do.
You know, but I've always
been interested --
If there was a paranormal,
if there is supernatural stuff
going on.
Because I've never
had an experience,
I could never believe it.
But then we did the show
in Denver with Amy
called "The Lost Episode."
It's on the Travel Channel's
website for "The Dead Files."
It was like 2:00 a.m.,
and I felt this presence
right behind me,
right over my shoulder,
you know?
I could just tell it was --
It was some kind of energy.
- Were you alone in the house?
- Totally alone.
No one was here,
just this overwhelming feeling.
That first episode,
I was hesitant
even going out there.
Then when I met her,
you know.
Well, I'd never met anybody
that talks to dead people.
I've worked with a couple
of psychics on the job before,
but they didn't have
your abilities.
And I wasn't impressed
with them.
They, you know --
They were useless.
They never gave me a lead
or anything.
But then when I saw
her abilities,
I was, like, blown away.
Was there a single moment
in that case?
Well, the sketch
was huge for me.
Now, this is Amy's sketch
of the girl.
I haven't seen it yet,
myself.
Wow.
I mean,
the sketch was so close
to the girl that was murdered
in the house,
you know,
there was no denying it.
So, after doing the show,
are you still a skeptic?
I'm skeptical. I'm open-minded,
but I'm skeptical.
I believe in Amy's abilities.
She's as accurate
as anybody could be.
And I know for a fact
she doesn't know
any of the information
beforehand or where we're going.
Amy, at the Merchants Cafe
in Seattle, Washington,
you encountered an entity
that told you her name was Mary.
This religious woman,
she feels women are weak
and thus sickly.
What does she do?
I think
she **** kills them.
Do you get a name on her?
Mary?
Gina wants to know,
"Why don't entities
always tell you their names?"
Sometimes
they don't remember.
Names don't seem to be
that important
to a lot of dead people.
I'm not sure why,
but it's, like,
kind of not their --
who they are
or something.
It's a really strange thing
that I've been told by them --
by some of them.
But some of them who are still
very much attached to life
will, you know, still carry
their names with them.
You know, you have this much
time and it goes this fast,
and it's like, you know,
"I was murdered here with an ax,
and here I am,
and I can describe him," so...
They just want to tell you
what they feel is
the most important thing.
People wonder why
we're not hearing you,
you know, actually having
a verbal conversation
with somebody that's not there,
that we can't see.
- So it's actually going through
a thought process? - Right.
And I've always
wondered that myself.
- So it's like a telepathy.
- Yes.
Okay.
That answers that question.
Telepathy with the dead.
Now, Moses from the restaurant
in Asbury Park, New Jersey,
he was a special case,
because he was living,
yet you saw him.
How did that work?
His energy is here.
It's very, very solid energy.
But it's not like
I'm talking to him.
His energy is here,
but do you know
if he is dead himself?
I don't think so.
You know,
what had happened there,
whether he'll admit it
or not,
was an extremely emotional,
life-changing moment.
Part of him
is still there.
From the murder?
Because he killed someone
violently in that house...
...there's a piece of him
that remained? - Yes.
You also had him show up
at the sketch.
Yes.
He's right there.
And he's yelling at me
to shut the **** up.
****
Why did he show up?
He didn't want me
to sketch him.
What did he do?
How did he try to stop it?
Um, he was yelling at me
and calling me names,
trying to intimidate me.
And this is somebody
that's living.
Yeah.
That's the bizarre part
for me.
Was it tough for you
to sit across the table
and interview Moses?
Did you want to kill him,
or did you just
want to make a point
by hitting him upside the head
with a hammer?
Just make a point.
"Don't touch me."
You made your point
9 or 10 times.
You know that, right?
That was a tough interview
for me, doing the show.
Kind of got under my skin
a little bit.
It took a lot for me not to go
across the table at this guy,
because he's just so flippant
about the murder he did.
I think he gave us
the slightest glimpse
into what your life was like
when you were on the job.
Right. It took me back.
Made me miss it a little,
actually.
Next...
The banshee lady
wanted to kill me.
...can the dead
really harm the living?
I ended up
in the hospital,
having to have
blood transfusions.
And later, Steve shares
one of his darkest moments
from "The Dead Files."
It was just the worst
nightmare of a movie
that you can think of.
So, Ross wants to know,
"What are the common mistakes
that people make
when they're trying
to contact the dead?"
Well, the first thing is
you really shouldn't be
going out of your way
to contact the dead.
Typically,
you're gonna be getting
a whole mess
of crazy people
who have
nothing to do with you
and decide that they want to
mess with your life.
So, again,
the suggestion is,
please don't try
to go out of your way
to contact the dead.
If you're having a problem
getting over the death
of a loved one
and you feel compelled
to reach out,
go to a medium,
then try to go through
the process of grieving
and letting them go.
All right, Steve,
I got a question for you
from Frederick,
who wants to know,
"Do you wish
you had Amy's gift?"
No.
No. I don't even
have to think about that.
I got enough problems
with the real people.
I got to worry about
dead people, too?
No. I'm good.
You do have your own gift.
- You have a sixth sense
of your own. - Yes.
- You have this ability to really be able
to read people. - Yeah.
And how has that helped you
in paranormal cases?
I approach paranormal cases
like I would approach a homicide
or any investigation.
I don't believe anybody
till I talk to them,
and then
they got to convince me
that that they're telling me
the truthful statement.
I've been doing this
a very long time,
so I'm able to pick up on
when people are lying.
I can tell right away.
A perfect example is Logan,
in Olalla, Washington.
What's going on that you need us
to come in and investigate?
Well, I've heard whispering,
and I've been seeing things.
I had some friends over,
and we went to the other house
and did a séance
and we tried to communicate
with the spirits
and kind of talk
to them, but...
I'm afraid that
I set something in motion
that I don't understand,
and I called you guys here
'cause I'm hoping
you can put a stop to it.
He had done some séances,
or --
His first words were,
"a séance or maybe two."
And I knew there was something
not right with that answer,
so I pushed him
a little bit on it.
This is the room
where I did the séance.
And this was the first time
you did a séance?
Yes.
- You sure?
- Yes.
I did have a couple more
after that, though.
How many more?
I kind of lost track.
I think I did 10.
So, Logan,
let me get this straight.
You did 10?
Somewhere around 10,
15 séances.
Logan, you told me
you did one séance.
Then you told me
you did 10.
Then I got you to tell me
you did 15.
I can't help you
unless you tell me the truth.
So, what's the number?
I've done 17 séances.
- You're sure about that?
- Yes.
You might have bit off
more than you could chew.
So, that's how it helps us,
because me getting the truth,
the way I get the truth
out of people,
I can give her
the whole story,
and I think that's what
we both bring to the table.
So, Steve, how can you tell
the difference
between somebody
lying to you
and maybe just holding back
a little bit?
Well, it's almost
the same thing.
You know
that something's not right.
So, the tells are the same.
Whether --
Then I'll find out
if it was a lie,
or if it's just
they didn't to tell me,
they were afraid
to say something.
Like Marcus in New Orleans.
When I was here
in my bedroom,
I heard some footsteps
going up and down the stairs.
What other stuff
besides something like that?
You just heard footsteps?
- That's about it.
- Okay.
So, Marcus, listen.
I've seen and heard it all.
I've been in some scary,
scary places, all right?
Don't be afraid
to talk to me.
I'm here to investigate
and find out what's going on
in this house.
So, if there's something
you want to talk to me about,
you can tell me, okay?
So, um...
anything else
that happened up in here?
Um...
Yeah.
Once, I saw this woman
in a white dress,
like, walking
up and down the stairs.
He was a young kid.
I didn't think he was lying,
but then he opened up...
...and told me something he never
even told his mother. - Right.
I have a good way
of making people feel
comfortable talking to me,
which is very key
when you're doing interviews.
If you can't make somebody
comfortable
talking to you
about everyday stuff,
how are they gonna talk to you
about serious stuff?
Now, Amy,
you went head-to-head
with what you called a banshee
at Smalley's Inn.
You've said many times
that the dead will kill you,
the dead
will make you sick.
Kathy asks, "If an entity
or a dead person
"is trying to harm you,
will it sometimes show up
as something else?"
A heart attack, heart failure --
How does that work?
The banshee lady
wanted to kill me,
and that week,
I ended up in the hospital,
having to have
blood transfusions.
So yes, it can manifest
in a physical manner.
A lot of physical mediums
die young
from heart attack,
aneurysms,
cancers, you know,
various things like that,
because our bodies
are constantly absorbing
dead energy.
Do you ever worry about
being physically attacked?
Well, I don't
particularly like it,
but, you know,
it's just part of the job.
- I worry about it, 'cause I'm sending her
in there. - Right.
But I don't know about it
until I see it on TV.
I don't like that.
What's going on?
Like a little push,
a little nudge, on my back.
Okay.
Eee, I don't like that.
But we got a job to do,
and, you know,
it's like when I was a cop.
You got to go through that door.
What are you gonna do?
- It's your job. Go through it.
- Right.
Coming up next...
But they were never
living people.
...Amy faces
a childhood enemy.
I am seeing, like,
shadow figures.
They want to remove
living people or kill them.
We get a lot of questions about
paranormal manifestations.
Nancy wants to know
if the shadow people you saw
in Acampo, California,
were the worst
you've ever seen,
and "are they
deceased people
or completely different
entities?"
I feel like there's more
kind of going on in this area.
Wait a minute.
I am seeing, like,
shadow figures,
which makes me uncomfortable.
I do not like those things.
That case was surprising because
there were so many of them.
There's a lot of different
theories out there
in regards to them.
But they were never
living people.
Basically, though,
they seem to want to remove
living people or kill them,
typically elderly
or children.
There was a lot going on
in that house.
Yes.
I did not like that house.
- Even during the reveal, she was having
issues. - I didn't like it.
I'm actually terrified
of these things...
and I've had
my own experience with them
when I was a child.
It was actually my first memory
of an experience
was with shadow people,
and they actually
tried to kill me.
They influenced me
to bite my electrical cord,
and I was electrocuted.
That's when I also
kind of figured out
that they were not good.
And it was very unnerving,
you know,
and frightening for me.
- Frightening for me, too.
- Yeah.
Now, Tiffany writes,
"Amy, you encountered
a demonic presence
"that pretended to be
a little boy
at the house
in Belvidere, Illinois."
He likes really bad ****
He lets things in
that are really bad sometimes.
But he seems too **** evil
to be a 5-year-old.
I don't like him. Okay.
It's not a real kid.
It's something really bad.
Like what?
Demons will pretend
to be dead people.
How do you actually know
when entities are demons,
and what exactly are
demons?
Demons are things that
have never been in human form,
and what they want to accomplish
is to destroy the living
and to destroy
as many as possible.
But sometimes they'll trick you,
at first. They will.
If you stick with that entity
long enough,
they'll probably do something
like that one did,
like, seeing the morphing
and all this,
and then I was like,
"Man.
You know, "It's not a child.
It's a demon."
On that subject,
Angel writes,
"In the case
in Garrett, Indiana,
there was an entity that was
trying to possess you."
This thing
can go in your body.
Now it's, like, grabbing
and trying to get my heart.
It's gonna make me sick.
This thing is, like,
really attacking me.
"Can you tell me more about
how possession occurs?"
In a true possession case,
where an individual has been
taken over by a demonic entity,
I believe that person
would do as much harm
to as many people as possible.
Possession
is extremely rare.
So, I believe there's
different types of attachments
that are not necessarily
possessions,
where you may have dead people
who take over living people.
Have you ever had it happen
to you?
Yeah, yeah. Yep.
I- I mean,
I've had people jump me.
What does that mean,
jump you?
Enter my body.
Were you getting jumped in
Wichita, Kansas, with Herbie?
Is that what he was doing?
He's real grumpy.
Really grumpy guy.
Herbie's getting
a little aggressive.
Stop it.
Stop it!
Geez,
what the **** man.
This is weird.
It's like he knows how to, like,
do the electrical impulses
in your body
and your brain.
I don't like it at all.
He was very good,
actually,
at being able to manipulate
the human body
and had learned
how to go through
the central nervous system.
And at first,
he was kind to you,
but he thought you were there
for a different reason.
Yeah. I got a lot of ****
from the dead
who figure out
why I'm really there.
And if they don't want to go,
they get very upset at me.
"In Flint, Michigan,
you recommended
"the client get a priest
to exorcise the property.
On top of that, the client
had her own exorcism."
This is no longer your land.
You must go to Christ.
Go to the place that
Christ has prepared for you.
No!
"Do all possessions
require an exorcism?"
Like I said, it's extremely rare
for an individual
to be truly possessed
by a demon or devil.
They can have attachments
from dead living people
who might be jerks.
They don't need a priest
to remove attachments.
They can have
any holy man do that
or they can have a healer,
et cetera, et cetera,
to remove the attachments.
Very rare that
it's a true possession.
Steve, Danny asks,
"You've used sketches
"in your crime investigations
before, of course.
"How useful
and accurate are they,
and how did they compare
to the ones that Amy provides?"
Her sketches are about
as dead-on as you can get.
So, I did a sketch
that I think might be him.
Wow.
Look at this photo.
Now look at this sketch.
You tell me.
The same cruel mouth.
The same boxer-like nose.
And the ears.
Yeah, the long ears.
She has him.
I would say that's him.
If I had a witness like her
in my cases,
it would be a lot easier
to solve them.
Why are you
still surprised
when you see a sketch
that matches so perfectly,
when Amy knows exactly
what happened in the house?
It's 'cause
I've dealt with people
doing sketches for crimes.
What'll happen is, you'll catch
the guy who actually did it,
and then you compare it
to the sketch they did,
and you're like, you know,
"It's not even close."
And it's hard
to do a description.
It's like you had met a stranger
that walked into a coffee shop
and then you're like,
"All right,
give me a description of
the guy that you just
saw for two minutes."
That's difficult to do.
So then
when I see her sketches
and I realize how close
they are, I'm like --
And then she's
so down on herself --
"Well, I don't know.
I don't know."
It drives me insane,
because I know people are not
that accurate at all.
It's just human nature.
People aren't trained for it.
Right. Right.
- I don't think we're gonna
convince her. - No.
Coming up...
She had a demonic scratch.
I'll never forget it.
...the paranormal shocks
even the most hardened
homicide detective.
She just wanted to die.
That's how bad it was.
Broke my heart.
We receive
a lot of questions
about what it takes
to make the show --
to solve a case,
follow an investigation.
And Kathy asks, "Steve,
"I love the history
you find on the locations.
How much time does it really
take to do the research?"
It takes a lot of preparation.
A lot.
I have to have
everything lined up,
all my ducks in a row,
before I get there.
So, I got to have historians
lined up,
genealogists lined up,
archivists lined up,
where to get this information --
all lined up
before we get there.
Now I ask things
so differently now
than I did
our first investigations,
because I know what she needs
when we're at the reveal table.
Like, I would never ask
somebody,
"So-and-so lived here in 1920.
Did he have any kids
or daughters?"
I wouldn't care before.
Now I know she may need to know,
"Well, did they have any kids?"
So, she puts a lot more
on my plate than I already have.
And not only do you need
to know how someone died,
but you also
have to speak to people
to understand the symptoms
and what it feels like
to die like that,
because that's, a lot of times,
what Amy's feeling.
Right. Because she is
a physical medium,
she takes on
those pains and stuff.
So, I get experts in line
that'll be able
to articulate to me,
and to the viewers, obviously,
what those symptoms would be,
and then at least
I can bring that to the table.
Something similar happened
in Uriah, Alabama,
where Amy was seeing
young children
who looked like zombies.
They were yellow,
and it turned out to be...
Yellow fever.
So, the husband, Mr. King,
he comes back,
he contracts yellow fever.
And from what we understand,
he came home.
He was very sick.
During that time, they lost
two of their young children.
So, there's, like, intestines,
and there's, like, blood,
and it had something to do with,
like, the abdominal area.
Like, that's the focus,
is, like, the abdominal area.
They look ghoulish.
Like, they're, like, pale,
and, like, they have, like,
the dark circles in the --
around their eyes.
They look like zombies.
That's a perfect example.
Like, stuff I would never
have cared about before
is now almost
on my top priority.
What case was the most
challenging to research?
Well,
they're all challenging,
but the one that had the most
conflict in it for me,
where I couldn't tell
what was what,
was in Huntington,
West Virginia.
It says
she died from a fall.
But the articles are vague,
and they just...
The articles are not just vague.
They're contradictory.
Right.
I have here
her death certificate,
which actually says
that she died
from acute alcohol poisoning.
But the paper says she fell,
so...
who do you think's right?
I have no idea.
I didn't have a straight answer
of how it happened.
So, that was
frustrating for me,
because records from those
time periods just were unclear,
until we sat down
at the reveal.
Then everything became clear.
Steve, Brian wants to know
if you're ever concerned
about something
following you home --
something paranormal.
Um...no, not really.
Never tho-- never --
I don't even think about it.
You don't?
No. When I go
into an investigation,
I'm not thinking about
my own concerns.
I'm thinking about the client.
Do you think
Steve should be concerned?
I think if something
did follow him,
he would be oblivious
to it.
- So, I don't think it would matter much.
I don't think anybody's
gonna go out of their way...
...to follow Steve home.
What does that mean?
Why would they not
follow Steve home?
Do they not like
his apartment, or...
No, no!
Um, because, you know,
he wouldn't care.
He would --
- I got my own problems.
- Right.
Well, that brings up
an interesting point.
When you say
Steve doesn't care,
is the best way
to get rid of one to not care?
So, they're gonna
want to go with somebody
who is going to
deal with them.
Steve would not
"Deal with them," meaning
"interact with them"?
Correct. Yes.
And Steve would not
interact with them.
He would ignore them.
Correct.
More than likely.
Should it be a concern
among the crew,
being followed home
by some of the entities
from some of the places
that we investigate?
I think so, yes.
It just depends on if you're
sensitive to it or not,
and you may
or may not know that.
Now, there was
one case in particular
when a member of the crew
got followed by something
in Acampo, California.
I woke up this morning,
discovered I had
these scratches here.
It freaked me out,
so I called Amy,
and she met me here.
You do have
some indications here
for a poltergeist attack.
Like, specifically
around the cuts,
of a poltergeist-type
manifestation.
Very powerful.
- Okay.
- So, you okay?
- Yeah, I'll be fine.
- You're gonna be okay. I'm sorry.
I'm just scared.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What is a poltergeist
exactly?
A poltergeist is
energy that is emitted by
living people who have PK --
psychokinesis,
or telekinesis.
So, a kid gets upset
and a door slams shut.
And it can affect
their surroundings,
whether they are
aware of it or not,
in a physical manner.
Yeah, but was she picked on
for a reason,
or attacked
for a reason?
Um, I think that there were
some kind of religious issues
and lots
of religious undertones.
She had a demonic scratch.
I'll never forget it.
I think we looked for
every possible explanation
for that scratch.
There was no way
that we could figure out
how she could have gotten
those scratches
other than
something paranormal.
- It's not like she was looking for
attention. - No.
Next...
I'm sorry.
I'm very upset right now.
Helping the living and the dead
takes its toll
on Steve and Amy.
That was probably
one of the most overwhelming
experiences I've ever had.
Now, I know
these investigations
are physically tough
on both of you.
There are
a lot of demands.
But Renee wants to know
what it's like emotionally
for you both
when you investigate homes
where the people living there
are scared for their lives.
It's a huge responsibility
to take care of them
and to tell them what to do
and to make sure
that they're going to be okay.
And I know
it's especially hard for you
when kids are involved,
'cause you're a dad.
Yeah. I mean, you --
Nobody wants to see
kids suffering.
But when I see children
going through stuff
I couldn't imagine
going through as an adult,
and them not knowing
or understanding
what the hell's happening,
it tears at my heart,
not only for the kids
but for the parents
that don't know
what to do for their kids.
Imagine being a parent --
the father or mother --
and you cannot fight
what you can't see.
And I always think about,
for every family
that lets us in their front door
to investigate,
there are 500
that tell their kids,
"Shut up and go to bed.
There's no such thing
as ghosts."
We had that case
in Alabama
where the husband didn't believe
the wife was seeing things,
and he was raised
Southern Baptist.
They don't believe
in anything after life.
They believe you go to Heaven
or you go to Hell.
So he just couldn't comprehend
that she was seeing something.
Even though he was experiencing
these things as clear as day.
Which was contradictory.
I got out of my truck,
went up on the stairs,
and it was like I startled
a young girl.
She screamed.
Then I went inside and up
and come back down the steps,
and she screamed
two more times.
It was like I startled her.
And we see that a lot
with husbands.
I mean, sweet couple.
They were really nice people,
but you could see
the frustration on her face.
Amy, there was one case
in particular,
in Blackshear, Georgia,
that I think
really hit you hard.
It was Pearl,
the young girl who had been
burned to death there.
Pearl burned to death
in the house here.
My God.
She burned beyond recognition.
I got a picture of her.
This is Pearl.
She lingered
for like seven hours.
My God.
It had to be agony.
You all right?
I'm sorry.
I'm very upset right now.
My God.
I told you there were ghosts
in this house.
Why was that
so difficult for you?
You know, I had been
hanging out with her
for, like, about
a week and a half or so.
You know, she was
under the table at the reveal,
and she was going through
everything
and was becoming
extremely emotional,
just because, like, you know,
she was finally being heard,
and, you know,
things were being understood.
And then her death came up
and she was reliving that,
and so I was also, you know,
feeling her emotions and my own,
and it became overwhelming.
Steve, I have a question from
Kathleen, who wants to know,
"Is there one case in particular
that hit you the hardest?"
For me, probably Browns Summit,
North Carolina.
Carrie is special-needs.
She's had 19 surgeries,
and 14 of those
have been brain surgeries.
Geez.
But since a few months ago,
it's just taken
a very negative turn.
Okay, in what way?
It's becoming very physical.
Carrie
has been seeing things.
She kept saying
she was gonna be whipped
and she was
gonna be burned.
She has visions
of being nailed to a cross.
That was one of those instances
where somebody was mentally
handicapped and disabled
and was being tortured,
and the parents just couldn't --
didn't know how to help her.
She just wanted to die.
That's how bad it was.
I heard her weeping when
I was interviewing the mother,
and to hear that sobbing
broke my heart.
This is a mother
that hears this all day long.
So, I heard it for two minutes,
and I was ready to break down.
Couldn't imagine
living with that.
That one
really tugged at my heart.
Amy, how about you?
What location were you most
concerned for the client?
Cedar Park, Texas.
The next thing that I saw
was all of these people
in the trees.
I did get
the distinct impression
that they would like to
burn your house down.
The reason being,
they're disgusted by you.
The big question is,
is it safe for you to be here?
I would probably move.
They may accomplish
their mission...
She was deteriorating rapidly,
her health,
and there wasn't really anything
that could be done,
at that location,
to fix the problem.
It's tough.
Yeah. I think that left
an impression on all of us.
- Coming up next...
...find out which cases
Steve and Amy feared the most.
It was just the worst
nightmare of a movie
that you can think of.
Whole place is haunted.
Amy, Yvette wants to know,
"What has been the most intense
paranormal experience
"you've had
on 'The Dead Files'
that's impacted your life?"
I really did not enjoy
the Santa Fe investigation,
because it was extremely
physically damaging
as far as my body
was concerned,
and it was also
really scary.
I really feel sick.
Like I'm gonna vomit.
Is it you
or the location?
It's the location.
It's, like, haunted.
Whole place is haunted.
I feel like my neck
is breaking, and...
Everything, it hurts.
My head.
It's, like, all right here.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Amy?
That was probably
one of the most overwhelming
experiences I've ever had.
I was pretty much
rendered speechless.
You said it was scary.
What scares someone who sees
dead people on a daily basis?
You know, that one entity
was so powerful.
He had caused so much horror
to so many people,
even though
they were criminals.
I think it was just
comprehending that evil.
The first place we ever
investigated that involved
law enforcement
where teaching about hauntings
and ghosts
were in their curriculum
for the academy.
Did you ever hear stories
about paranormal stuff
going on here
before you started working?
They talked to us about
some of the paranormal
activity at the academy.
They just touched on it.
But they did mention it.
They did mention it, yes.
I was floored by that.
Yeah.
So, that alone
made you understand
that it had to be pretty bad
for them to actually put that
in the curriculum
for their training.
They told
the prison guards,
"Expect to see things
that you can't explain."
And it was just part
of the curriculum.
Yeah.
- And they weren't bashful about talking
about it. - No. They were not.
They were
pretty forthcoming.
What'd you experience
in here?
Just, like, a shadow
that you would see,
like, on a bright day,
someone walking by.
But there was nobody there
to make a shadow?
No.
No, no.
You also, Steve,
you had one of your more intense
interviews with Craig.
That's the name I gave him
was Craig.
That's not his real name.
Everybody and their mother,
from authors to news reporters,
wanted to get ahold of this guy
and speak to him.
He had done time for murder
in the prison there,
and he was there
when the riot happened.
He was actually part
of how it happened.
I know you've seen
a lot of horrible things,
but have you ever seen so many
horrible things in one place
happen in such a short amount
of time?
Not really.
I mean, not like that.
I've seen multiple, multiple
homicides at once scene,
but what he described,
the blood flowing through
the hallways like a river,
I'm picturing it in my head,
how this chaotic scene
must have been.
It was just the worst
nightmare of a movie
that you can think of.
Never mind the paranormal.
Just showing how evil
and how brutal
living people can be.
But my part of it was
I wanted to do
a good investigation,
find out
what the story was,
and coincide with her case.
Yeah. Yep.
So, here's a question
that we all want the answer to,
but Gloria was wise enough
to ask it.
"Can you get me the upcoming
Powerball winning numbers?
I tried that
the first time I met her.
It didn't work.
Especially --
I mean, I'm --
You know, my dominant ability
is mediumship,
and, you know, you don't use
your abilities that way.
Yeah, you do!
Usually if you --
If I had them,
I'd use them.
Usually, if you do that,
you lose them.
I'd only need it the one time
if it's a big Powerball, though.
So you're saying nothing good
comes from personal gain?
Right.
See?
It's back
to working hard again.
So, guys,
I just want to say thanks.
Thanks for all the hard work
you're doing,
and thank you for taking
the time between investigations
to answer
all these questions for us.
Thank you.
It means lot.
Thanks
for having us here.
This is something
we always wanted to do
was answer
some fan questions.
We love our fans.
- They're the most devoted fans
on the planet. - Cool.
Thanks for watching.
Keep sending us your questions
and keep watching
"The Dead Files."
All-new episodes coming up
on the Travel Channel.