Subs created by: David Coleman.
You got some crazy going on here.
I heard a man say,
I'm going to kill you.
Scared. A lot of fear.
I see a shadow.
I see a man go down the hallway.
Jumping all over the room.
Someone took a hot curling
iron to the back of my neck.
Sounds like you have a serious problem.
I just got grabbed.
Somebody died back here.
It's really bad in here.
My name is Amy Allan.
Something is not right.
I see dead people.
This person might have
been a serial killer.
I speak to dead people.
You get those chills.
And they speak to me.
He is darkness. He is evil.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I think she broke her neck.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
You telling me the truth?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I think the Devil is down here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who the hell would do this?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Who's he looking to kill?
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
You need to get out of here right now.
Or time to get out.
It was like endless darkness.
Amy and I look into
each case separately.
I interview living
witnesses and uncover dark
history that's been
buried and forgotten.
While Amy communicates with the dead.
I've just arrived in St.
Clair Shores, Michigan.
It's about a half-hour
outside of Detroit.
I received a call from a mom named Emily,
and she sounded pretty upset on the phone.
Her husband and two sets of twins are
being tormented by paranormal activity.
She says it's ripping the whole
family apart, and we're her last hope.
Before Amy arrives, I do a
complete sweep of the house.
Things that are common in most
homes, like family photographs,
can influence her findings.
So it's important I remove them
all before she begins her walk.
This is not good.
What?
There was, like, a man...
Crawling out from under here.
And he doesn't have any
arms or legs anymore.
So he's, like, a black
slithery, snaky thing.
He makes you feel...
Fear.
So, Emily, when we spoke
on the phone, you sounded
pretty upset about the things
that are happening here.
- Yes.
- Tell me what's going on.
We hear voices, footsteps.
We see shadows move, apparitions.
Okay. How many people
actually live in the house?
My husband, my 12-year-old
twins, my 7-year-old twins.
And we have two dogs.
Okay. How long are you living here?
- Seven and a half years.
- Why did you call us now?
In the last year, it's gotten physical.
- Really?
- Mm hmm. I've been scratched.
I have severe nausea every day.
And my youngest son has also
been showing symptoms of nausea.
Feeling sick to your stomach is
hardly proof of something paranormal.
But it's not my job to speculate
about that side of the case.
I leave that up to Amy.
Have you and him gone to a doctor?
Yes. But no one can
explain why it's happening.
Well, that's got to be tearing you and
your husband apart a little bit, right?
It is. Me and my husband
don't sleep together anymore.
I sleep up here on the couch.
Why?
To stay closer to my children.
I couldn't leave them up
here by themselves anymore.
I'm very worried that
they're going to be hurt.
Okay.
You got some crazy going on here.
And now I feel really sick.
I don't feel good at all.
What's going on?
It's a stomach thing.
[Bleep] I don't feel good in this place.
At all.
Phew.
- Like, mm.
- Just, your stomach in general?
It's like stomach and heart.
Terrible. Terrible pain.
Mm.
Okay, so, what's going on in this room?
I hear voices all night.
One night, I heard a man
say, I'm going to kill you.
- That had to scare the hell out of you.
- Mm hmm.
My daughter Katey came running out
of her room the other day, screaming.
Um, completely naked.
And she said a man whistled and...
Breathed heavy in her ear.
- It was heartbreaking.
- Wow. Anything else?
I see an apparition of an older man.
I would say he's probably in his 70s.
He wears a hat.
- It does have a brim on it.
- Okay.
Now, besides that guy,
have you seen anything else?
The first night that we
moved in, I saw a uh...
Huge, big, cloudy, black mass.
Hanging right over here.
I screamed.
And that's when it went away.
How often have you seen that?
It happened for seven straight
days the first week we moved in.
Okay.
I'm seeing this one guy
from outside under the car.
He's everywhere.
Plus, you've got some
weird [Bleep] on the wall.
- What do you mean?
- It's like, um, lines.
Squiggly lines, like this.
- That's what's on the wall?
- Yeah.
They're, like, more of an emotional
kind of a thing. Like an unsettled...
Feeling.
It might be coming from
someone who is still alive.
Sometimes when the living
experience intense negative emotions,
their energy can manifest things
like these bizarre lines on the walls.
And they have the ability to
affect the living in harmful ways.
It kind of gives me a headache
and makes me feel chaotic.
Whatever it is, is not good.
Okay, so, what's going on down here?
I've had my hair pulled from the back...
Very violently.
And there wasn't the
kids around or anything
like that that could've
possibly done that?
Nobody was down here. I was alone.
It sounds like you have
a serious problem here.
It's actually even worse than that.
I've been burnt.
It was like someone took a hot
curling iron to the back of my neck.
It happened four times.
Every time, I was taking a shower.
Wow.
You sure it wasn't
maybe the heat changing?
Absolutely positive.
Geez.
Now, what if Amy says this is only
going to get worse and you can't fix it?
What would you do?
I'm going to take my kids
and walk out that door.
Okay.
I just felt like
somebody touched my hair.
Like, there has been some
physical [Bleep] here.
Ah. I just got grabbed.
Like, behind my... right here.
Like that.
Okay.
And he said, basically,
get out of here [Bleep]!
Shut up.
And one would think
that it's a dead male.
But it is a fully-formed
uh, PK manifestation.
A PK manifestation usually happens when a
living person's energy creates an entity.
These manifestations are very powerful and
can physically influence their environment.
How advanced would you say it is?
Well, it's definitely capable
of causing physical injury.
Erich, I spoke to Emily.
Um, she told me about all the
stuff that's happening here.
What have you been experiencing?
I came down to take a nap one afternoon.
And I thought it was Katey and Erich
that came down and actually were...
Bouncing on the bed
and talking and whatnot.
- So you were sleeping on the bed.
- Correct.
And what, did you feel
like this, how did it?
Yeah, pretty much.
Kind of felt like two
kids jumping on a bed.
Okay.
But when I went to
look, they weren't there.
Have you seen anything?
Oh, I see apparitions
down here frequently.
- Frequently.
- Describe the apparitions for me.
There's a guy.
And he will walk behind me
and come into this bedroom.
It's pretty unnerving.
It's got to be tough on your family.
Sometimes, you got your kids and
they look at you and they wonder um...
Why did you do this to me?
- Well, that's got to break your heart.
- Oh, it hurts. It hurts.
There's just problems within the family.
And unfortunately, this family has
some emotional instability there.
There's definitely a
poltergeist going on.
Um, there might be a few...
Happening.
Do you know if they're aware
that they're doing this?
No. No, I don't think so.
You also have kids who
are... have abilities.
And they happen to be able
to create PK manifestations.
And there's so much energy,
it literally makes you sick.
So, I was talking to mom.
And your mom said
that you guys have been
having some strange
experiences in the house.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
Okay, so, Erich, why don't you
tell me what you've been seeing?
Sometimes, I see a
shadow in the hallway.
Okay. What kind of shadow
are we talking about?
Like, a man.
Was anybody walking around
that they made that shadow?
Or was it something,
I don't know, where...
- No one was there.
- Nobody was there.
- No.
- Okay. What about you, Sweetie?
When I go to bed, I always
see a man go down the hallway.
Is it the same like he sees it?
Okay. What else have you experienced?
Well, we both seen a girl.
- A little girl?
- Yes.
Okay. Do you know how she's dressed?
Sometimes, she has a big white dress on.
And it sleeps with me sometimes.
She just sleeps at the end of
there, and my head's back there.
- Okay. Does that scare you?
- Mm.
So, you've had a lot of things
happening in your room here.
Do you have trouble going to
bed at night because of that?
- Sometimes.
Me too.
There's a lot of
emotional instability here.
And people are...
Freaking out and...
Crying and hiding under...
Blankets and sheets.
Like, how many people?
Can you talk about them?
I would say there is four
people who are very freaked out.
Okay.
I'd say at least three of them have...
- Some PK [Bleep] going on.
- Okay.
I think it's really just
mainly a poltergeist.
Chad, I was talking your mom.
And she told me that she's
having trouble sleeping at night.
Mm-hmm.
Are you having any
problems sleeping at night?
Sometimes, when I go to
bed, like, I hear voices.
What kind of voices are you hearing?
Like, "hey". And like coughs.
What else are you seeing?
One time, I came in
from playing basketball.
And I was going to get
some water. I grabbed a cup.
And, like, the faucet
just, like, turned on.
- On its own?
- Mm hmm. Like, full-force on.
So when that happened,
did that scare you at all?
No, not really.
Let me ask you a question. Does
anything in the house scare you?
Um, usually, in the basement,
I see a shadow in my dad's room.
Like, it's a tall man in a hat.
Okay.
And just, like, peeks around
the corner and just goes away.
You act kind of cool about all
the stuff that's happening here.
You don't seem to be, I don't think you're
dealing with it about it the right way.
It's not normal for a 12-year-old not
to be able to go to sleep at night.
It's okay to be afraid.
It's okay to be upset or
scared about something.
You all right?
Okay.
Mm.
A lot of different emotions.
Like, definitely wanting to
cry, though, is the biggest one.
Where are they coming from?
The kid that's in this room.
The person in here hears voices.
People talking in the
room from the walls.
Causes, like, headaches.
It's, like, too much.
What's causing headaches?
The voices and the
noise and the buzzing.
This room is like [Bleep] chaos.
There's, like, nightmares
and screaming and crying.
And then, there's
these, like, light rods.
Like, jumping all over the room.
And it's so much, it hurts. It hurts.
It buzzes in your head. It's buzzing.
The energy in this
room is very unstable.
Whoever lives here has major abilities
but doesn't know how to control them.
Definitely, like, PK energy, for sure.
Just not good.
I usually start my investigation by
reaching out to the
property's former owners.
Most times, it's a dead end.
In this case, I found
a woman named Shannon.
She says she's got some information
that will definitely help my case.
She's agreed to meet me at the
house and tell me what happened.
Shannon, let me ask you a question. When
was the last time you were in this house?
I'm guessing the late '70s.
- Okay. So you grew up here.
- Yes.
During your time here did you ever
experience anything you couldn't explain?
- No. Mm mm.
- Nothing?
Now, you mentioned on
the phone that you had
some information that
could help my case.
Well, my grandfather passed
away here in the house.
Ah, geez.
Just of natural causes.
Did anybody else die in
the house that you know of?
Ah, yes. Actually, my other
grandfather's girlfriend.
What year did this happen?
1978.
In fact, here's the article
out of the local paper.
There was a coat rack next to
the stairway to the basement.
Okay.
And um...
Georgina went towards the coat rack and
probably didn't realize the
stairway was beneath her feet.
- Okay.
- So, she fell down the stairs and...
Um, she tragically, um...
Passed away that day.
How'd your grandfather take that?
It's the first time I ever seen him cry.
I haven't thought about it in years.
Somebody died back here.
- What happened?
- It was just, like...
It was very fast.
Like, everybody involved with it is...
Completely confused.
Um...
Scared. A lot of fear from these
people concerning this person.
And it's, like, a sudden...
man, it's like, bam!
I'm, like, very confused right now.
Like... like...
Here's the pain again. The pain again.
- Like, the grabbing?
- Yes.
Hurts so [Bleep] bad.
I'm at the local library to see what
else I can uncover about
my client's property.
While digging through old deeds,
I discovered that a man named Noah
Furton originally owned the land.
But what catches my attention is a tragedy
involving two of his young children.
So I've reached out to
one of his descendants,
who says there's a
lot more to his story.
So, Bev, it turns out that Noah
Furton actually owned the property that
I'm investigating and lived there.
But you're a descendant of his.
- How are you related?
- He was my great-grandfather.
What can you tell me about him?
Well, he was a sea Captain on
the Great Lakes for 35 years.
I have a picture of his boat.
Now, I saw in the census
that he lost two sons.
Yes. He lost two children.
One was two, and one was two months old.
And they died within a week
of each other of measles.
He also lost his wife.
- What did she die of?
- Tuberculosis.
- She was 49.
- So she was young.
Yes.
So, what ever wound
up happening with him?
Well, when he was 78, he passed away.
It sounds like he had
a pretty tough life.
Yes, he did. But he also had a cousin,
Adolphus, who also lived on the property.
And he had a very tough life.
- You know anything about it?
- No, I don't know much.
Okay.
The men here have problems.
You're talking about the dead?
Yeah. Dead and living men
have problems in this location.
Like, they don't act like their selves.
So a normal guy moves in and then he...
Gets involved with bad [Bleep] or...
Drops dead or goes crazy.
But it doesn't have anything
to do with the PK phenomena.
Is this anything that
might be dangerous?
Yeah.
Bev mentioned that
Noah's cousin had an even
worse time on the
property I'm investigating.
So I'm headed over to
meet with a local archivist
who tells me that the tragedy
this man suffered was unthinkable.
Cindy, you mentioned that this guy,
Adolphus, had a pretty tragic life.
But before we even get into that,
what can you tell me about him?
Adolphus comes from a long line of
French-Canadians who settled in this area.
Okay.
And the Furton family did live on the
property that you are investigating.
Okay. And then they settled
here to do what kind of work?
He started out, as a
young man farming and,
eventually went to the
occupation of sailing.
Either for commercial vessels, small
boats, or the larger company boats.
Okay. So they were considered,
like, merchant seamen at the time.
I know that's dangerous work today.
So how bad was it for them back then?
There were a lot of boiler explosions.
There were a lot of groundings
of ships on the flats.
It was very dangerous.
This black, like...
Slithery, snaky thing.
I'm trying to figure out what
he looked like when he was alive.
He's a big guy.
He's got, like, longer brown hair.
Has an accent and/or
spoke another language.
I think he's scared.
And there's a lot of violence
around him and in his life.
Now, Cindy, was Adolphus married?
Yes, he was. His first wife, Mary, was
married to him the 29th of January of 1886.
And they had seven children together.
Okay. Now you mentioned he had
unthinkable tragedy in his life.
What was it?
All of the children died as infants,
except for his daughter Julia.
She died as a teenager from
consumption at the age of 17.
But all the babies died.
Oh. So, what were the
reasons for their death?
Childhood diseases that we
didn't have any medicines for.
Typhoid, diphtheria, cholera, measles.
Wow. So, he buried all of his kids.
That's correct.
During my opening, I saw a graveyard.
So I go to go in, and I notice that
I have to, like, really crouch down
and walk through the opening
because it was super short.
When I was going through
it, my thought was...
That it was something that
was built for children.
And I hear a voice say, "it was
awful. It took so many of them".
So now, married this woman. Married,
they had seven kids. All seven kids died.
You said it was his first wife,
though. What happened with Mary?
Mary passed away in 1898 of consumption.
And here is her death certificate.
Consumption is Tuberculosis, right?
- That's correct.
- Okay.
In 1901, he remarried a relative
of Mary's named Elizabeth.
Okay. Now, did they have kids together?
No, unfortunately, they
didn't have children together.
She also died shortly thereafter.
Now, with all this tragedy in his life,
what wound up happening with Adolphus?
Adolphus, on November 21st,
1916, drowned in Lake St. Clair.
He was lost on the ice, and his body
was not found until the following spring.
- Okay.
- And they ruled it accidental?
Yes.
And how old was he when he died?
He was 55 years old.
This guy lived a pretty tragic
life for a man only 55 years old.
And a very tragic end.
I'm having a sketch artist
draw the two entities
who stood out the most from my walk.
First, the dark, slithering man.
He doesn't have...
Like, any legs.
He still has, like, his head and torso.
And he's wrapped in a black mist.
Next, I described the bizarre
scene I saw in one of the bedrooms.
There's a child.
Sitting, cross-legged.
So, what he's looking at is...
These rod-shaped...
White lights.
That are moving across his room.
Okay.
Yes. That's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations.
We're ready to reveal our findings to each
other and our clients for the first time.
This is Erich and Emily.
They live in this home with
their two sets of twins.
Things have gotten so bad in this house
that it's basically ripping them all apart.
It's at the point where
it got very physical,
and it looks like it's
directed more towards Emily.
But the concern is that it's going
to affect their children soon.
What they want to know is if they can
actually live here in a safe manner.
Now that Amy understands a
little bit about what's going on,
she's going to tell us about her walk.
In my opening, I did see
something that really stood out,
and it was a little disturbing to me.
There was a graveyard that
was built for children.
Then, I heard someone say that
there was a terrible accident.
And that many of them had died.
- So you saw a lot of dead kids?
- Yes.
Well, your house is not that old, but
the property goes back into the 1800s.
And the original owner of your
property was a guy named Noah Furton.
And he had lost, back in 1891,
two sons to measles within a week.
One was two years old.
One was two months old.
What's worse is he had a cousin
named Adolphus that lived with him.
All of Adolphus' seven kids died young.
Six of them died under the age of
one, and one died at the age of 17.
Wow.
It's like a curse.
The next thing that I got was that
this property is not good for men.
Whatever is here on this property,
can cause them to kind of go crazy.
Or even to drop dead.
It absolutely has killed in the past.
And it's, to me, very dangerous.
It's interesting you say that
it's bad for men because...
Well, this guy, Noah, that lost
two his children, right, to measles.
Now, his wife died at 49 of TB.
So he lost two kids and lost his wife.
And next, we talk about Adolphus.
Loses seven kids and then
two wives on top of that.
Lost his first wife
at 29 to Tuberculosis.
Remarries and loses his second wife
within a year or two after he got married.
So he never even had children with her.
Not only that, he wound up dying
under strange circumstances.
Even though Adolphus was
an experienced sailor,
he ends up drowning in Lake St. Clair.
Here's his death certificate.
They ruled it accidental drowning.
But who the hell knows?
The next thing that I
encountered was a dead person.
And I see him come out from...
Underneath the car.
He doesn't have any
arms or legs anymore,
so he's, like, a black,
slithery, snaky thing.
I felt like he lived here before.
The fear that I felt was really
overwhelming and powerful.
You know, when you get that really
tight sensation in your stomach?
And you almost feel like
you're going to pass out?
Yeah, that's kind of how I felt.
Have you seen this person?
I don't know if they're the same
person, but I see a man in a hat.
Is he intimidating to you?
He's scary.
- Okay.
- He just stares.
I did do a sketch of the man that I saw.
The way he moved for me was snake-like.
Whoa.
Mm.
Is there any chance that this guy
here could be one of the Furtons?
Very possible.
So, walking into the
house, it was chaos.
Very, very physically painful,
and it was just overwhelming.
What I finally figured
is that there's three main
experiences that you
guys would encounter.
The first thing is physical abuse.
And this seemed to
be directed towards...
Women.
I got grabbed by the back of my
neck, like, right under the ears.
And I could feel the
whole hand. Male's hand.
Very strong. Grabbing me.
It really hurt. A lot.
Um, I've had my hair pulled.
Three times.
Tell her what happens
when you take a shower.
- It's like a burn.
- Okay.
And it's happened four times.
All four times, I was in the shower.
I actually have a photo.
Whoa! Okay. Wow.
I mean, I'm overwhelmed with all of
the things that are going on here.
So you said people here are being
affected by three different things.
What else?
I pretty much had a constant headache.
Um, and nausea, feeling
sick to my stomach.
I also felt that my heart hurt.
You seem pretty upset
by what she's saying.
I had a heart attack
last year for no reason.
When we spoke, you didn't mention it.
Are you uncomfortable talking about it?
Yeah. It's scary.
I'm 38 years old. It's
not supposed to happen.
- Right.
- What happened?
The doctors can't explain it.
She's been through more tests than
any other person I know in my life.
And every day, I have
horrible, horrible headaches.
- How do you sleep at night?
- I don't sleep much at night.
Tell her where you sleep, so
you can be close to the kids.
- I sleep on the couch.
- Uh huh.
It's difficult, you know. You want
to have your significant other laying
next to you, and not
upstairs, away from you.
So, now you said there's three things
they're dealing with in this house.
Physical abuse. Sickness.
And what was the third thing?
The other thing was the voices.
When I got into the kids' room,
it was crazy out of control.
In that particular room, these
voices were not coming from the dead.
They were coming from the walls.
Yeah. We all hear it every day.
You guys are validated for
what you're going through here.
Definitely. More than I
could have ever thought.
So, there was another sketch that I did.
In the kids' room, where the
voices were coming from the walls...
I saw something else that disturbed me.
Have either one of you ever
seen anything like that?
We both see them.
I call them strings of light.
Where are they coming from?
This is one of the things that
happen in poltergeist hauntings.
And it's been going on for a while.
So it has developed into a
full-blown poltergeist haunting.
So, these strings of light that
we see, that's a poltergeist?
This has developed into a
full-blown poltergeist haunting.
So, these strings of light that
we see, that's a poltergeist?
And it was created by living agents.
I almost feel like it's my fault.
Well, you both seem to have abilities...
That have spontaneously been activated.
You had this heart attack, which basically
was kind of a near-death situation.
Highly stressful, and I
think that completely...
Did away with you being closed
in any way, shape, or form.
And I think that you are
in an active location.
So, inadvertently, were
made to open to some extent.
The other thing is, is that
we can become extremely ill.
Because of the ability.
Every physical medium that
I know has had heart issues.
So, what does the
poltergeist haunting do?
So, like, all of this
energy is out there,
and it's going and it's
going and it builds...
Spontaneously affecting the environment.
Then what can happen is it
can feed off of the dead.
So, with this guy here...
He's being absorbed and then becoming...
Part of this ball of energy.
And what can happen then is
when you're adding your abilities
to that ball of energy, it
can become a PK manifestation.
Which is a very dire circumstance.
Pk, from what I understand,
that can make things move.
- Like, objects move.
- Yes.
You'll have the objects
moving, emotional instability,
and some of the physical phenomena.
That's when you're getting
the deep cuts and...
You know, being thrown across the
room, and, you know, hardcore...
Physical...
Abuse.
I don't think it's gotten to that level
yet, but I think it is headed there.
Phew.
This is a lot of information
to take in one night and...
It probably wasn't the information you
actually thought you were going to hear.
But the main question is
can you live here safely?
Could the kids be safe? And
can you fix what's going on?
Hopefully, Amy may
have an answer for that.
We need to get the
dead out of the house.
So, to start off, you're going to be
doing home cleansings three times a week.
Go ahead and take your Sage.
Go around the house with the
Sage and just let it burn freely.
While you're saying...
"Only love, light, and peace may enter".
And any dead that are in
the home have to leave.
Okay.
Also, to eliminate this
poltergeist and to have everyone,
balanced and centered
with their energy...
I would suggest either
yoga, tai chi, or qigong.
At least once a week
as a family together.
Now, let me ask you a
question a poltergeist sounds
to a layman like me, it sounds
like a scary thing, right?
Oh, yeah.
But you're saying yoga's going
to kind of nip it in the bud?
Yes. It'll dissipate because
you won't be feeding it anymore.
You'll feel much healthier,
you'll feel much more at peace.
Because it will focus on
harnessing and balancing energy.
Okay.
So, what's going to happen to this guy?
Once the poltergeist is dissipating.
It's going to release him, and I think, at
that point, he's going to choose to leave.
And what can they do about
this thing that's bad for men?
There's something that comes
from the Earth here that...
Doesn't particularly care
for men for whatever reason.
So, I would suggest
bringing in a Shaman.
To do a cleansing ceremony on the land.
Okay.
Now, this whole thing of you having
abilities actually, the both of you.
When you woke up this morning this would've
been the last thing you thought of.
The last thing I thought of, absolutely.
So, the big question is, are you
going to listen to our advice?
Absolutely.
Definitely.
- Okay. Good.
- Okay.
I really hope Emily & Erich rid their
home of the poltergeist they've created.
If they do that and learn
to harness their abilities,
there is no reason they shouldn't live
in their home peacefully as a family.