Subs created by: David Coleman.
I don't know what this
dude's fully capable of.
I have nightmares about this house.
Aah! He's pissed off.
All of their bodies were
burned beyond recognition.
- Wow.
- Hates this person. Hates them.
- I had an exorcism.
- An exorcism?
I'm gonna get you. I'm gonna kill you.
I got to get away from this guy.
It's really bad in here.
My name is Amy Allan.
Something is not right.
I see dead people.
This person might have
been a serial killer.
I speak to dead people.
You get those chills.
And they speak to me.
He is darkness. He is evil.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I think she broke her neck.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
You telling me the truth?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I think the Devil is down here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who the hell would do this?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Who's he looking to kill?
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
You need to get out of here right now.
Or time to get out.
It was like endless darkness.
Amy and I look into
each case separately.
I interview living witnesses and
dig into the property's history,
looking for dark secrets
buried in the past.
While Amy communicates with the dead.
I'm in Chicago, Illinois, on my
way to the house of a veteran cop.
Thing is, he didn't call us in.
His daughter, Cristina, did.
She says the activity in the house is
so bad, she's afraid for his safety.
But she also says that he's such a tough
guy, he is not gonna leave his home.
I'm hoping Amy and I can help him out.
Before Amy arrives, I look
for any leading information.
This home has a lot of
photographs, religious icons,
and family heirlooms that
have to be covered or removed.
When I'm finished, the location
will be ready for tonight's walk.
I'm seeing this older woman.
She said that somebody opened a door.
And also is bringing dead
people home with them.
And she wants it to stop.
She says...
"I'm not gonna waste any more time because
you're not gonna do anything to help me"...
Just like the others.
Uh...
Ow!
What's wrong?
Oh, Cristina, I'm glad I'm here.
You sounded a little worried on the
phone about all the stuff happening
in the house here, and you're
concerned for your father, I understand.
- Yes.
- But what about you?
I've heard voices, footsteps...
And I have nightmares about this house.
I haven't lived here since I
was 18, and they still continue.
Okay, like what?
There was a boy, and he was trying
to force me to look at his head.
And half his face was gone.
Okay, so, you've been having
these dreams for a while.
For years.
Okay, so my question here is
why are you calling us in now?
My daughter is only 3.
And when she's staying
here, she's having...
These kind of bad dreams.
Cristina, the first person you mentioned
when we spoke on the phone was your father.
And you sounded concerned
for him. What's the story?
It's just my Dad and my stepmom,
Lori, here by themselves.
I'm concerned about their safety.
What are you looking
for us to do for you?
I'm hoping that my nightmares will stop.
That I'll be able to
bring my daughter here,
and that my Dad and Lori will
be okay here by themselves.
Ow.
So, I look, and there's a guy who...
Came from below...
The house.
He was punching me nonstop,
and he's got blood on him,
like, dried-up blood, and
he told me I should leave.
He's worried or something.
Well, right down
there. Right down there.
Mm.
This male...
Hides...
Down in here.
He gets up in their space.
There's someone standing, staring
at you. You know what I mean?
This is the same room you
grew up in having nightmares.
Yes, it is.
Okay. What have you
experienced in the room?
This is where I've seen the apparition.
Of what?
A woman dressed in white.
And she was actually right
here in front of my closet door.
- Okay, did you get a look at her face?
- No.
Her back was to me.
She was facing the door, and
then, she disappeared into it.
Okay. You sure it wasn't a
dream or anything like that?
I was wide awake.
Oh, interesting.
What's going on?
- The older woman...
- Mm hmm.
From outside likes to...
Hide in the closet.
And pop out like a witch.
Is this something that people see?
Yes. That's why she does it.
So, Mark, obviously, we're here
because your daughter called us in.
Mm-hmm.
She's concerned for your
safety, as well as your wife.
You got to be a little bit
worried yourself, I would think.
Very worried.
Now, do you know any
history about the house?
A little bit. I know that a doctor lived
here, and he was a T.B. doctor in the area.
- You're a cop.
- Yes.
- And how long you been a cop?
- About 27 years.
I'm sure you're like me. If you don't
see it or hear it, you don't believe it.
Right.
So, that being said, have
you had experiences here?
I heard my name be called once.
It sounded like my wife.
It sounded just like her,
like something's mimicking her.
- Was she home?
- No.
I jumped up. I grabbed my
gun. I ran down the stairs.
It did sound like
someone was in my home.
- And nobody was?
- Nobody was there.
Okay, have you ever experienced
anything else down here?
I see what appears to be, like, a
black mass coming up the stairway.
- Scared the heck out of me.
- It did, huh?
- It's very frustrating.
- Right.
It's hard to even accept it because
I can't prove it, and I can't...
I really can't understand it.
This is his preferred area in here.
Aah! He's pissed off.
He's angry. People
definitely see this guy.
Ow.
Aah. He hurts people.
Ow!
He's making my head hurt.
Yeah.
Ow!
Knock it off.
Okay, Mark, so, why'd you bring me here?
I seen a male apparition
and a female apparition.
Okay, describe the male for me.
He had a suit on, I
recall, a tie, and glasses.
- And you mentioned you saw a female, also.
- Yes, I did.
She appeared to be a little older,
had longer hair, it looked gray to me.
- Okay.
- And she was in some sort of dress.
You know, on the phone,
your daughter mentioned
something about inviting
other paranormal groups in.
- We did recently.
- And?
They definitely said that
there is something going on.
Was that the only investigative team or
proactive thing you've done in the house?
No. I had an exorcism of the house.
- An exorcism?
- Yes.
After the exorcism, did
anything improve at all?
I don't believe it has.
What are you hoping we can do for you?
I know now that my daughter had a
hard time here, she had nightmares.
- Yeah.
- Now I got grandkids.
I don't want my grandkids to go
through what my kids went through.
Oh, no.
I got, like, weird, Voodoo,
seance stuff happening here.
Somebody opened a [Bleep] door!
Where dead people come.
The old woman, she doesn't
like to come in here anymore.
Because it's too um...
Chaotic and hectic for her.
And she wants her house back, so
she's getting really desperate.
She said she swears to God
she's gonna poison them.
So, Lori, I talked
to your husband, Mark.
- Mm hmm.
- I talked to Cristina...
And they explained the experiences they've
had and what's going on in the house.
- What about yourself?
- I've had a few strange experiences.
- Okay.
- And...
One of them being one night I
thought Mark was home from work.
- He used to work midnights.
- Okay.
I heard footsteps coming up the stairs.
I kind of, like, froze.
And I never heard him come towards the
bedroom, so obviously, it wasn't him.
- Okay, so, he wasn't home.
- He wasn't home.
What about one of the other kids.
It wasn't the other kids.
They were all in bed.
So, that really freaked me out.
I see these two men.
Um, they have no skin.
They're rotting and they like that.
And they're tricksters.
They're tricksters.
Those two men, they're tricksters.
They look charred.
I feel like they got
burned or something.
And I hear roughhousing.
You know, they're banging in the walls.
Anything else going on up here?
I don't feel comfortable in the dark.
Why?
Not too long ago, I went to bed one night,
and all of a sudden, in a sound sleep...
I felt hands come up and grab my waist.
And, like, I'm facing Mark,
so it couldn't have been him.
- What did you do?
- I froze.
I kind of, like, put the blankets up,
and I was afraid to move or say anything.
Okay, so, you couldn't
mistake it for something else?
No.
Sounds like you were on
pins and needles living here.
Yeah.
Now I'm a little more
nervous of going to bed.
If I wake up in the middle of the night,
I'm afraid to, like, open my eyes or move.
Bad.
Lots of physical [Bleep]
He's like...
Beating on somebody in the bed.
He hates them.
Ah! Hates this person.
- Hates them.
- Why?
They're messing with his stuff.
Messing with his life.
- And this is a living person?
- Yes.
He's, like, up in their ear, and
he's like, I'm gonna kill you.
I'm gonna get you. I'm gonna kill you.
Just as I'm seeing what this
angry man can do to the living,
he turns his attention back on me.
He wants me out of this house, and
he has disturbing ways of showing it.
He is a [Bleep]!
[Bleep] Damn it.
I got to get away from this guy.
He's really hurting me.
He's very excited that um...
He can jump people or
get inside of people.
His energy is extremely
uncomfortable, like terrible, terrible.
I got scared because I thought, I don't
know what this dude's fully capable of.
Mark told me his house used to be
a doctor's office for T.B. patients.
So I made some calls around
town, and his story checks out.
But the historian I contacted says there's
a lot more to the story than Mark realizes.
So, it turns out that
my client was right,
that the house was occupied
by a doctor at one time.
Yeah, Dr. George Gindele.
Can you tell me a little bit about him?
Well, he was a general practice doctor.
There wasn't a lot of money in
medicine, and he had, like, 10 children,
so they had to start
various other businesses.
They opened up a candy store. They
had a newsstand that they operated.
Okay, and he did treat
T.B. patients in the house?
Yes, he did.
This guy sounds like he
put a lot on his plate.
He had a house with 10 kids
he was trying to raise...
Yeah.
His own practice,
several other businesses,
plus, he's treating a very
contagious disease in his own home.
Right. He must have been
terribly stressed out in his life.
That hurt.
But I know what he [Bleep]
looks like now to me.
Even though the angry
man violently attacked me,
he revealed himself to
me for just a second.
And I was able to get a glimpse
of what he looked like in life.
Very professional field.
Dark-brown hair, average
build, as far as I can tell.
He does have a coat on.
He had a very, very
[Bleep] stressful life.
Very [Bleep] stressed about work.
High stakes. High stakes.
Now, you had mentioned that he
had some tragedy in his life.
Yeah. Some years before, a couple of his
sons were going through an apple orchard.
Nearby the property, and this man suddenly
appears, and he starts yelling at them
in German, telling them to
get out of the apple orchard.
And he takes out a
shotgun full of buckshot,
and he starts firing them at the kids.
And one of the sons got hit in the leg.
And the oldest son,
George, got hit in the face.
And he didn't die, but it
disfigured him horribly.
I've seen shotgun victims before.
How bad was his face?
Well, George Jr. was hit 35
times in the face and the neck.
So it was obviously very bad.
You all right?
There's a lot of pain in his head.
He had a destination. There was
some kind of meeting with men.
And then, I see trees around me.
That's when things get sketchy.
But then, he came back here.
So, now you got this poor kid
shot in the face. He's disfigured.
- Whatever wound up happening to him?
- It's a tragedy.
About eight years later, 1926...
The doctor gets a house call, and he
decides to take George out with him.
And it's pretty snowy
for that time of year.
And the house call is
around the Des Plaines River.
And the doctor parks his car,
goes off on his house call...
And he leaves young George behind.
George got out of the car
evidently, and he went and he
sat on the edge of the bridge
looking down at the river.
Meantime, Dr. Gindele comes
back, and the kid's missing.
He doesn't know what
happened to him so...
He goes back home and files
a missing-person report.
They finally found his body a
couple weeks later downstream.
A few miles from where he had
evidently gone into the river.
Okay. So, did they
have a cause of death?
Well, they brought the
body in for an autopsy.
And that's the death certificate.
He drowned, and they're
saying it's accidental.
Right.
- This had to devastate him.
- Oh, it had to.
And it just broke him
up. It just destroyed him.
This guy, he fell down.
He slipped on the ice, and maybe he kind
of snapped a little when... you know?
Because he's not dealing with it.
I think it's just because
his brain is... he's confused.
It triggered his pain,
and he got really angry.
Uh, pretty quickly.
I want to know what happened to Dr.
Gindele after the death of his son.
For me, the best source of
information is from a family member.
I've managed to track down
one of his descendants,
who says the tragedy
destroyed the doctor's life.
Now, Jack, I know you're a
descendant of Dr. Gindele.
But what was your actual
relationship to him?
- He was my grandfather.
- Okay.
And this is a picture of Dr.
Gindele and his oldest son George.
- This was taken before he was shot?
- Yes.
You know, Jack, one of the reasons
I actually wanted to meet with you
is because I wanted to find out what
happened to the doctor after his son died.
He had a nervous breakdown, and as a
result, he stopped practicing medicine.
My understanding is that Dr.
Gindele was of such a state of mind
that he went to live in Oak
Park with one of his sisters.
And my Grandmother stayed in
the house with the children.
So, he just left them there?
Well...
Uh, yes.
I got to figure your Grandmother
had it pretty tough then.
Yes.
How old was the doctor when he died?
- Uh, 75.
- 75, okay.
And how old was your
Grandmother when she passed?
- In her 80s.
- Oh, she was an elderly woman.
- Oh, yes.
- Okay.
I feel very tired here.
Just...
Worn out.
This might be that old lady.
- Okay.
- But something...
Is not...
Right.
What are you talking about?
Something about their
family, it's broken.
She felt really lonely...
Confused.
I don't like it.
It's a little [Bleep] unnerving.
I'm at the local library to see what
else I can uncover about
my client's property.
Digging through the archives, I discover
that a poor farm operated right next door.
And according to the headlines,
the conditions there were terrible.
So I've reached out to a local reporter,
who tells me that the tragedies that
took place there are unthinkable.
The Cook County poor farm is
one of the dirty secrets...
In Chicago history.
The conditions there
were absolutely appalling.
This was where they sent people,
basically, to be forgotten.
And as you can see from this picture,
this is a fairly large institution.
What kind of people would
have been on this poor farm?
Quite a variety. There
were mental patients...
There were indigents, and
there were tubercular patients.
Pat, you mentioned on the phone
that there was a tragedy on the farm.
What was it?
In 1923, the main building
of the mental institution...
- Okay.
- Burned down.
And at least 17 people were killed.
All of their bodies were
burned beyond recognition.
Wow.
And as you can see, the
destruction was pretty widespread.
As a matter of fact, most of the people
who died there ended up being buried there.
You mean people who died there
before and after the fire?
Yes.
And what's the estimate of how many people
are actually buried on that property?
Conservatively, 38,000 people.
Wow.
During my walk, I got a quick glimpse
of the angry man who attacked me.
So I'm meeting with a
sketch artist to draw him.
His hair was very thick but cut short.
And kind of a longer chin.
How about his eyes?
Almond-shaped.
Next, I described a horrifying
scene in the upstairs bedroom.
There's a woman in the bed, and
I saw him, like, beating on her.
I'd have his left hand holding her arm.
And his right hand in a fist over her.
Is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our own investigations.
We're ready to reveal our findings to each
other and our clients for the first time.
Amy, I want you to meet Mark.
He's a cop, and he's
been a cop for 27 years.
This is his wife, Lori,
and his daughter, Cristina.
Now, Cristina's actually
the one who called us in.
But she doesn't live here anymore.
Even though she doesn't live here, she's
still getting tormented by nightmares.
Now she has a
3- year-old daughter...
Who's having similar dreams, and
she's getting very concerned about it.
These two live here, and they're
being tormented by the activity.
And they want to get their life back in
order and make this a safe place to live.
So, now that Amy knows a little
bit about what's going on,
I'm gonna ask her to
tell us about her walk.
So, I encountered two men.
And they didn't have any skin.
They were kind of like
mushy-looking corpses.
They were a little charred
like they had been burned.
Upstairs in the hallway in
particular, they like to horse around.
They're kind of acting crazy.
You'd hear the scuffling
feet in that hallway.
Now, you guys hear footsteps
all the time upstairs.
- Yeah.
- Correct.
I would think it was Mark
coming home from work.
And I would hear footsteps.
Well, this particular night, I
heard the footsteps coming up...
And I waited for him, you know,
to come back to, like, the bedroom,
and he never came back,
meaning it wasn't him.
Right.
Now, you mentioned these guys
looked like they were burned?
They got burned in a fire.
That's interesting you say that because in
the late 1800s, less than a mile from here.
Adjacent to the property was
the Cook County poor farm.
The complex housed poor people...
Had an insane asylum on it, and it had
a Sanitarium for Tuberculosis patients.
Wow.
1923, the insane asylum
burns down to the ground.
Oh.
17 people burn to death.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Oh, wow.
Now, this is a photo of the aftermath.
People that went there, they died
there, and they were buried there.
Could be as high as 38,000.
What?
- Right here?
- Right here.
Now, do you think these
guys came from that fire?
Yes.
What else did you see?
I encountered this older woman outside.
And she was just spewing hate.
She felt very alone and confused.
And was really, really tired.
One of the things that
she likes to do is...
Come out of the closets.
She's trying to assert
her dominance that way.
I saw the figure of a woman...
Upstairs in my bedroom
facing the closet.
And she disappeared into it.
I saw an apparition of a woman.
I could only see her from the back because
she was sitting on the edge of the bed.
The edge of the bed is
right next to the closet.
Let me ask. What is she pissed about?
She doesn't feel like...
This is her space anymore.
Because there was something about
seances and someone opening a door.
And she's getting desperate.
No one's listening,
and she swears to God,
if it continues she
wants to poison you guys.
Like, she wants to poison you.
- They did have a ghost group...
- Okay.
Of paranormal investigators come in.
Not only that, but they had a priest
perform an exorcism in the house.
- We did.
- Of the house?
Of the house.
This is where we
started the ritual here.
And he said that he was
chasing whatever it was
throughout the house
down into the basement.
While he was in the basement...
He's saying the final prayers and...
The stole got pulled off of his
shoulders and thrown to the floor.
Oh!
Now...
Is the woman pissed off because of
maybe the exorcism or all of the above?
I think it's all of the above.
I'm a little concerned about your saying
that she was going to poison the people.
- Mm hmm.
- Is she capable of that?
Yes.
This woman's so advanced she's
able to persuade the living
into harming themselves, and
she plans to do it with poison.
I got to protect my family.
This is not something that's
gonna obviously fly here.
What else did you see?
I'm outside, and I meet this guy.
He was trying to get me out of here.
He just didn't want me to
find anything out about him.
Definitely the most powerful
entity that's in this house.
Aah! He's pissed off. He's angry.
People definitely see this guy.
Ow.
Aah. He hurts people.
He looked very professional.
He was...
Obsessed with his work.
Extremely stressed-out man.
And he was extremely good
at whatever it was he did.
But it was high-stress and high stakes.
I'm not sure if this is the guy
you saw, but it sounds like him.
This house was occupied by a guy
by the name of Dr. George Gindele.
And he worked out of
the house, this house.
Um, starting in, I think, 1920.
He was a workaholic, this guy.
Back during that time period, Chicago
had a big Tuberculosis outbreak.
He treated a lot of those
patients right here in the house.
And he had 10 kids here.
That's a lot of stress.
I'm just curious if this could
possibly be the guy you saw.
I did do a sketch of him.
Well, you guys take
a look at the sketch.
Wow.
Wow, is right.
That's the apparition I saw.
100% definitely, that's the guy I saw.
Oh, my God.
If you imagine a mustache right here,
it really does look just like him.
I don't like the fact that...
He's here doing what he's doing
because I'd figure if he was a doctor,
he would be helping people,
not causing problems.
And did you get anything
else from this guy?
He had had two big
accidents during his life.
The first one I saw
was he slipped on ice.
The other one I saw, like, he
was walking to meet some men...
And then, something
really, really bad happened.
He was all bloody, and there was
something wrong with his eyes.
I have nothing that says Dr.
Gindele had any accidents but...
There were two events in his
life that basically destroyed him.
I actually have a picture of him and
his son, who he was very close to.
This is the doctor, and
this is his son, George Jr.
George Jr. was about 20 years old, and
he was walking through the neighbor's,
farm the apple orchard.
And the guy that lived on the
farm decided to take a shot at him.
What?
Shot him in the face and neck.
So this kid was disfigured.
My dream.
I had a nightmare one
night, and there was
a boy who looked like
he was in his late teens.
And it looked like he had been shot in the
head because half of his face was missing.
And he kept trying to
force me to look at it.
Because I have nightmares all the
time that are connected to this house.
I have nightmares all the time
that are connected to this house.
This is...
Hard for me to take.
You guys thought I was crazy.
I never even heard that, honey.
I didn't even know that happened.
She'll be all right.
Hopefully, this helps her.
- You all right?
- I'm okay.
Starting to make sense to you
now, though, a little? Yeah?
Now, this poor kid, George Jr., was
badly disfigured from this shooting.
Now, you mentioned falling into
the ice or falling on the ice.
George Jr., in April of 1926, fell...
Accidentally or he jumped
into the Des Plaines River.
And I have his death certificate.
Right here basically, you'll see,
it just says accidental drowning.
This eventually destroyed Dr. Gindele
because he gave up his medical practice.
He moved out of his house, left
his wife with the nine kids...
What?
Moved in with his sister,
and left her here alone.
Now, she stayed here
until she died in 1960.
This is his wife, Julia.
Oh, my gosh.
Could this be the woman you saw?
Yes.
Now, could this possibly
be the guy you saw?
- I think so.
- Oh, my gosh.
The main areas that he likes to be in...
Is the basement and then
the front room upstairs.
Would that be causing her nightmares?
I mean, it seems like they're... yeah.
With him, you'd experience him in
a lot of, you know, different ways.
Anyways, you might hear,
you know, things in your ears
making threats, touching people.
Most of the stuff he
does is in the dark.
I am very afraid of the dark.
And at night, there will be times
where I wake up in my sleep...
And I won't even open my eyes.
I'll just pray that I fall back asleep.
Why do you wake up?
- I don't know why I wake up.
- Huh.
I did do another sketch
of something that he does.
And it was in the main bedroom.
And he was getting physical
with a woman in the bed.
Well, I have to show this to you, so...
That's really freaky.
He's touching you.
Why don't you just explain
to Amy what you told me?
Well, not too long ago, I
was in a sound sleep, and...
I woke up because I felt
somebody grabbing my waist.
And I could feel the fingers.
But when I woke up, I did open
my eyes, and I was facing Mark.
So, my back would have
been towards the closet.
So, it couldn't have
been him touching me.
I'm getting angry.
Because this isn't his
house anymore. It's my house.
I'm going to tell you what
I believe is going on here.
After hearing everything, I kind of feel
like I was being a little too hard on him.
It's a heartbreaking story.
The woman, she's always been
here. I mean, she never left.
I think that what...
May have happened here is that...
He was probably pulled
back to the house.
When you had paranormal groups
come in and try to contact the dead.
It probably pulled him
back here from the darkness.
This is the place he ran from in life...
Too many memories, too much pain.
He's reliving it over
and over and over again.
I think he's angry at you
because you called him back here.
I think he's lashing out because
he wants to make you suffer, too.
He really can't leave now because
he's just in the thick of this chaos.
So, he's not able to leave on
his own, even if he wanted to.
Exactly.
So, when you saw the accidents
involving the ice and the blood,
was that him reliving
his son's accidents?
I think so. It's a very, very sad thing.
It is sad, and on the
same... I feel bad for him.
And on the other hand, I'm mad.
- Well, look what he's doing to your wife.
- That's the part I'm mad about.
And what he did to my kids.
I know you guys got overwhelmed
with a lot of information tonight,
and I'm sure it's not
what you wanted to hear.
But the big question is can you
live here without all the torment?
And can you go on without
having these nightmares
and protect your 3-year-old
from having the same issues?
I don't have an answer for that,
but I'm gonna turn it over to
Amy, and hopefully, she will.
It's going to sound unusual.
The first thing would be to
get a clinical psychologist.
Who practices providing therapy.
These are his conditions.
What do you mean his conditions?
- He's asking for this?
- Yes.
Earlier, we made a compromise.
This actually happens quite often.
When I got to the house for the
reveal, the angry man approached me,
and we worked out a deal
to help him to move on.
He needs to focus...
On talking out his life.
Because right now he's living in chaos.
So, we want to give him a
little bit of time to process.
And hopefully, he'll just
leave after that anyways.
The second thing is you need
to bring in a chaos magician.
What the hell exactly
is a chaos magician?
A chaos magician is an individual who...
Follows the philosophy that...
The Universe and the Earth and
everything is functioning within chaos.
So they utilize that
chaos within their magic.
So, when the chaos magician comes
in, that'll get rid of the old lady,
the two burn victims, and Dr. Gindele,
too, if he doesn't leave on his own?
Yes.
What of Cristina's nightmares at home?
Because she's having them
not here but at her house.
Right.
How do we fix that, or can it be fixed?
When you wake up, you need to
tell them, you get out of my house.
You leave me alone. You
leave my daughter alone.
Will it affect her daughter?
Well, that remains to be seen.
- She's only having stuff here, right?
- Right, yeah.
Yeah. So, you know, they're
gonna do all these steps,
and the house is gonna be locked down.
So, then, she'll be
fine to come over here.
Are you gonna do what Amy suggests?
I'll do my best, but that
psychologist isn't for us.
I got enough people in the house.
Even if we do the other
steps, he'll have to leave.
We'll force him to leave.
- Are you seriously gonna do that?
- I don't know.
Hey, you got to take some responsibility
here, he did not want to be here.
It's just the negotiation part
that I have a problem with.
I'm upset, too, you know? This guy
beat the [Bleep] out of me for hours.
I think that you should
go with what Amy...
Is saying.
And it's just that, you know,
as extreme as it is for Lori,
if it gets it all to stop,
then swallow your pride, and...
You have to do what you have
to do to get it all to stop.
- It's not easy for me.
- Because you're pissed off.
But you know what, two
wrongs don't make right.
I really hope Mark's frustration
doesn't affect his judgment
when it comes to following my advice.
I believe that if he follows
the steps I've given him...
He'll not only be helping his
family but the dead here, too.