Subs created by: David Coleman.
Some guy is yelling, ha,
ha, ha, you [Bleep] coward.
They told me if I knew what they
knew I would never buy the place.
Very, very sad.
When it happens it's
terrifying, actually.
There was somebody who
killed themselves here.
Shoots him in the back of
the head, kills him instantly.
I love this building. I'll
never walk away from it.
It's like a city of the dead.
It's really bad in here.
My name is Amy Allan.
Something is not right.
I see dead people.
This person might have
been a serial killer.
I speak to dead people.
You get those chills.
And they speak to me.
He is darkness. He is evil.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I think she broke her neck.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
You telling me the truth?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I think the Devil is down here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who the hell would do this?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Who's he looking to kill?
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
You need to get out of here right now.
Or time to get out.
It was like endless darkness.
Amy and I conduct
separate investigations.
I look into the history of the location,
digging up its secrets and forgotten past.
While Amy speaks with the dead.
I'm in the old Wild West,
Deadwood, South Dakota.
We got called in by a guy named Ron.
Now, Ron runs a bar and casino in town.
And for the past 20 years, he's
been trying to restore the building.
Only problem is, every
time he swings a hammer
the paranormal activity gets dangerous.
He says time is running
out and that Amy and I
are his last chance to
have his dream come true.
Before Amy arrives, I look for anything
that might influence her findings.
This hotel casino has a lot
of photographs and historic
information that has to
be covered or removed.
When I'm finished, the location
will be ready for tonight's walk.
There's more dead here than
the dead here would like.
It's hard to keep all of them in line.
There's five men here now.
They're, like, a team
of bad men that are now
trying to make up for their bad deeds.
And I think their crimes
run from stealing to murder.
You know, basically,
they're gonna escort me.
The one guy says, like,
it's like a city of the dead.
This place is amazing.
It's a great place.
When I walked in the door, I
fell in love with the place.
I just knew that I needed to be
here, kind of like I was here before.
And so, I want the place restored
just like it was in the past.
Now, did you have any
ideas that there may be
some stuff going on when
you went to go buy it?
Yes, I did.
When I talked to the previous owners...
They told me if I knew
what they knew or saw
what they had seen, I
would never buy the place.
Now, let me ask you a question, before
you bought this place were you a skeptic?
- Do you believe in paranormal?
- Sometimes yes, sometimes no.
But, after I've been here,
what I've seen, I believe now.
Can you give me, like, a broad idea
of all the stuff that's happening here?
Well, we've had things thrown around.
People hear noises, doors
are opening and closing.
You know, people are
feeling that they're being
touched and they get really frightened.
That's a problem.
Oh, yeah. I've had
customers run out the door.
Do you know any history
about the building itself?
It was a Brothel in the past and
there was illegal gambling here.
Let me ask you a question,
how long are you here?
- 23 years.
- So, why are you calling us now?
The more work we do, the
more the activity picks up.
Some of the investors get spooked off.
And I love this place,
and it hurts me not to
see the place of my
dreams come to fruition.
The dead don't care for the decor.
So, each dead person tries to keep it
the way it was when they were alive.
- Mm.
- Because...
It confuses them, and
that makes them upset.
It does hurt my head.
So, Ron, why'd you bring me up here?
I brought you up here because this
is one of the creepiest places.
What's the story?
Activity picks up as soon as we
start doing construction here.
So it's as if whatever's here
doesn't want you to make changes?
Yeah, exactly.
So now, have you ever experienced
anything yourself up here?
Yeah. There's this gray-haired woman,
and I don't know why, but she's
always laying on the floor.
Can you see through her?
No, like a solid apparition.
Does she acknowledge or
look at you when you see her?
Yeah, she looks at me.
And then, when I see her, I just turn
around and head right the heck out.
And you're sure this is
not some kind of maybe a
reflection coming from
outside or anything like that?
I've seen it too many times and
it's always in the same place.
How do you deal with this?
- Well, you got to deal with it.
- Right.
And so, every time I enter
a space that I haven't
been in for a while,
I'll say, coming in!
I feel more comfortable.
Okay, is there anything else?
I've seen a guy that's
clothed in dark clothing,
like a long rider coat, late at night.
- Okay.
- Dark hat.
And moves from the ladies' room area,
and then kind of vanishes
towards the back of the room.
Has anybody else seen it?
Yeah, most of my employees have
seen him, some customers, as well.
The dead Cowboy dudes, one's saying
a lot of good times over
here, drinking and gambling.
One of them says that
something bad happened.
They're not really letting me get it.
They're blocking it.
And I feel, like, an impact in my head.
I feel like it's male.
Either they got shot in the head
or they shot themselves in the head.
I lived here for five years.
- Was this your bedroom?
- Yeah, I moved out in '95.
Okay, so what happened?
Well, I was laying down over here,
sleeping, and I was laying like this.
And all of a sudden, I just went
up like this and, what the...
And I seen... right where you're
standing is where I saw this tall woman.
She was in a green dress with red hair.
And I couldn't move, and she just
stood there about four or five minutes.
And I just couldn't move.
Are you on any kind of medication
when you go to bed at night?
No.
That must have scared
the hell out of you.
Yeah, I moved out that next month.
Now, would you stay
overnight alone again?
No. No.
So now, is there anything else you
can tell me that might help my case?
Many people have had to stay here.
They've had the sensation of their
hand being moved off their chest.
Or away from their side
while they are sleeping.
And it had been a very
frightening experience to them.
If we don't get this paranormal problem
fixed, I might never get any investors.
I might never get the place fixed.
If my partner told you things
are gonna get worse here, or
you really shouldn't stay
here, how would you take that?
Well, I love this building.
I'll never walk away from it.
There's a male...
Who is not a happy camper.
At all.
Mm-mm. This grumpy guy,
he stays up here a lot.
I feel like up here is, like,
off-limits for living people.
And he gets pissed.
Makes him feel angry.
Do you know if he does
anything to the living?
I know he is working on
trying to physically harm them.
He's trying to...
Scare them to death.
Kathleen, I talked to Ron, and he
was telling me that you work here.
But he also said that you
actually lived here at some point.
Yes, I was here for a week.
And I am the only person on staff
who will come up into the 2nd floor.
So, none of the other
staff will come up here?
No, they send me.
- Have you had experiences here?
- I've had my hair stroked.
I've had a hand on my forehead, and
I've had a hand on my lower back.
Can you tell if it was a
man's hand or a woman's?
It seemed to be as if a man was
escorting a lady out for the evening.
When it happens it's
terrifying, actually.
The hair stands up on
the back of your neck.
You feel an electrical
crackling and you shake.
Okay, so is there anything
else you've experienced up here?
I woke up around 3:20 in the morning.
I heard footsteps outside.
I heard voices.
I opened my eyes, and there was a woman
at the foot of my bed wearing a blue dress.
I think her hair was red.
- And she was just looking at me.
- Somebody broke in maybe?
The alarm would have gone off and
the police would have been here.
I was scared enough to not only bolt
the door, but to pull the heaviest
piece of furniture from the room
and put it in front of the door.
There's a woman, and
she was always talking.
You can still hear her, you
know, going on and on and on.
People, if they don't see her,
that would [Bleep] shock me.
She worked here.
She was a busybody, who...
Was here a lot.
- She just always complains.
- What did she do here?
I think she did sleep with people.
The other dead people
don't appreciate her.
So, they'll, like, try
to keep her in a room.
So you might hear her yelling or
screaming to get out, or banging on doors.
And doors closing on their own, yes.
So, do you have experiences
down here, as well?
- Yes.
- Okay, like what?
Our gaming tokens, for instance.
They're kept far back from the edge of
the counter, so that they don't fall over.
And every now and again, you'll
just see one come up from the tray,
flip over and land on the floor.
- And you actually see it in the air?
- Yes.
I'm trying to figure out how that
can be explained, and I can't.
Is that the only thing
you've seen down here?
There's an old lady who
wears a long, white nightgown,
she walks up and down the hallway.
And then stops and just
sort of watches you.
Then she kind of dissolves.
Kathleen, how would Ron take
it if my partner told him...
Listen you got to get out
here, it's basically unsavable,
you have to sell it
and count your losses?
He's not going to give up. We
fight back for what we want.
All right.
There's an older woman
who putz around a lot here.
I'm hearing 65, but she
looks a bit older than that.
She is really tiny.
She is probably only, like, five foot.
On the heavier side.
She wears a full dress.
She definitely worked a lot here.
And she didn't care for...
The people that she worked
with or that worked for her.
She really didn't care
what happened to them.
- Richard I understand that you work here.
- Yes.
Okay. Now, how long have
you been working here?
Off and on for 20 years
or a little better.
What do you do exactly?
Well, I do a lot of maintenance work around
the place and I've also worked in the bar.
A little bit of
everything in this place.
It seems like everybody is having
experiences here. How about yourself?
Yes, I've definitely had
some experiences here.
Okay, tell me about some of them.
Well, one of them when I was working
floor and the cage in the bar.
- And I heard a door start creaking.
- Okay.
And I turn around and look at the
door, and the door is opening up,
and it opened wide like someone walked into
the place, and then gently went shut again.
Nobody was visible anywhere.
Have you seen anything else?
Yeah, at sometime later I was
back here stocking beer cases.
I had locked up, it's 3:00 in the
morning, there's no one in here but me.
And somebody walks by and then
disappears right out through the wall.
So, what exactly did it look like?
A black coat with tails on it.
Now, did you believe in this stuff?
I never did till then, but it sure
convinced me at that time, it was all done.
There's so many dead people here that
it is making my walk very disorienting.
Everyone's trying to talk to me at once.
But one guy by the bar
is demanding my attention.
There's a man. He likes to work here.
He feels very attached to the place.
So, he gets mad because
they're not doing it right.
And he wants to...
Help, but they're not listening.
So what will he do if
they're not listening?
Go and hurt people.
Ron told me his property
was built as a Brothel.
From what I know about Deadwood, it was a
mining town, so I'm not surprised by that.
But, when I reached out to a local
author, he told me there were two deaths at
the property I'm investigating, directly
related to the prostitution business.
So, you mentioned on the phone there
were two deaths that would help my case.
But, before we get to that, I have got to
ask you a question about prostitution here.
Was it pretty prevalent?
During the initial influx of
the population in Deadwood...
There were thousands of men.
And they were here for one
thing, that's to pan gold.
- Right.
- You're looking at something like this.
So this is what it looked like
back in, I guess, the late 1800s?
Yes.
The ratio of men to
women was about 50 to 1.
And everybody was looking for a good time
when they came in from the mining fields.
So they'd dance with the girls
and maybe they'd get lucky.
Okay, so how were these girls treated?
Well, there some of them down there that
would beat the crap out of the girls.
Is that right?
One person in particular
that I researched
beat the living daylights
out of one of his girls.
He went to court and was fined $5.
Really?
As a matter of a fact, the
closer you got to the badlands,
the worse conditions got for the girls.
Okay, so the guys could act
however the hell they wanted?
Pretty much, as long as
they didn't kill the girl.
That's kind of strange.
What?
They might have had some sex slaves.
I think that they died down
here, a lot of the ladies.
It was cold.
Um...
They would not eat
and they're all naked.
And they put them in here.
Do you know who is putting them here?
Men?
Now, Joey, you mentioned
on the phone there were
two deaths associated
with the Fairmont itself.
- Related to prostitution?
- Yes.
It was in 1907, and, Vinegar Rowan,
a sheep herder from Montana...
Had a girlfriend that he
was very much attached to
who worked as a
prostitute in the Fairmont.
Okay.
And he came in one day to see her.
And when he entered the room, he found
out that she was with another man.
So, he pulls out his gun and
immediately shoots that poor bastard.
Does he kill him?
- Actually, he'll survive.
- Okay.
And then he took a couple of shots at
his girlfriend, and he missed entirely.
So, she leaps out of
bed and grabs him by the
shirt and tries to
force him out the door.
He reaches around with his
gun and is trying to shoot her.
Boom, boom, boom.
And shoots himself in the [Bleep] head.
He's dead.
I've seen a lot of
things in my career but,
this is one of the funniest
stories I've ever heard.
- So, what was the other death, Jerry?
- Maggie Broadwater.
She had been visiting
a boyfriend in Wyoming...
And they had had a bad parting.
And she came back and
started drinking quite a bit.
It wasn't long before she
decided she was going to
jump out of the third floor
window and kill herself.
Here's newspaper clipping.
So, this happened in the
Fairmont, she jumped out...
She jumped out of the Fairmont.
It says here, jumps
three stories and lives.
The ground was so muddy in
the road where she jumped...
She actually stuck in the mud.
And they extracted her from the
mud and took her to the hospital...
Okay.
Where she lingered on for about
36 hours, maybe a little longer.
They thought she was gonna survive.
But it turned out that she
was dying of internal injuries.
Really? All over some guy?
- Yes.
- Okay.
I definitely feel like there was
somebody who killed themselves here.
A female.
And she did it...
Very dramatically.
She was hysterical.
Something bad happened.
She was so sad.
Like she maybe lost someone.
It was really bad.
Very, very sad.
Look, this is Deadwood, South Dakota.
And back in the day,
it was a violent town.
Now, I know there had
to be more murders on my
property that had nothing
to do with prostitution.
So, I reached out to
a local Police Chief.
He looked into it for me,
and he said there's a couple
more homicides that will
definitely help my case.
Chief, I know Deadwood, in my mind,
is the epitome of the wild, Wild West.
How bad was it?
You know, this is an area that was full
of brothels, full of card rooms, saloons.
So, you might have
shooting in the streets.
You might have violence
occurring in the saloons.
So, it was a cop's nightmare.
- Oh, absolutely.
- Okay.
On the phone you said there were a couple
murders on the property I am investigating.
Yeah, actually there
was two tragic deaths.
Back then, the property you're
investigating was known as the Melodeon.
Back in November 16th, 1876...
They had a man by the name of Banjo
Dick Brown who was up on stage playing.
Okay.
A man in the audience stood
up and started to shout.
And in the midst of the shouting
he throws an ax on stage.
And Banjo Dick, without missing a beat,
pulls his gun in a crowded
room and shot him dead.
You're kidding me.
So what was the second
death you were talking about?
In July 23rd, 1949...
Deadwood's Police
Chief, Nestor Erickson...
Shot one of his ex-officers on Main
Street in front of the property.
The ex-officer's name was John Gorham.
He had worked at the Deadwood
Police Department for a few years
before being fired for drinking
while in uniform, and also...
He wrongfully beat
somebody while on the job.
John Gorham was a very tough individual.
He's actually a
middleweight boxing champion.
Okay, so how does the shooting go down?
He had been going on a drunken rampage.
Chief shows up on Main Street and
advised Gorham that he was under arrest.
Gorham approached Chief
Erickson with his fists clenched.
- It was like he was gonna assault him.
- Okay.
Chief Erickson then pulled his
duty weapon, and failing to stop,
the Chief shot him once through
the heart in front of the property.
It is said though, that after
being shot that he did advance
four to five more steps towards Chief
Erickson while flailing his arms.
Some guy is yelling, ha,
ha, ha, you [Bleep] coward.
I feel like I'm staggering.
Like I'm trying to get someone.
I'm feeling pain... pressure here.
I'm staggering.
I'm angry, very angry.
I don't know if it's
a heart attack or what,
but it [Bleep] hurts really [Bleep] bad.
With so many deaths tied to
the property I'm investigating,
I need to see if anything
else went down there.
So, I hit the books
at the local library.
Searching through old records, I came
across an article about Wild Bill Hickok.
Turns out he was murdered right
next door to the Fairmont Hotel.
So, I'm heading over to the cemetery where
Wild Bill is buried to meet a historian.
He is gonna tell me exactly
what happened to him.
Kevin, through my research, I've found
out this Wild Bill Hickok got murdered,
literally, right next door to the
property that I'm investigating.
I know the name, it's famous, but I
really don't know anything about this guy.
- What about him?
- Here's a picture of him.
He died at age 39.
This is where he is buried,
at Mount Moriah Cemetery.
He was famous for being a lawman...
Settling some of the
Wild West communities,
and some shootouts in Missouri, as well.
So he was quick with the gun.
So, why does he come here?
He comes here to prospect and to mine,
but he also loved the
game of cards and gambling.
While he's here, I guess something happens
and he winds up getting murdered, right?
That's right.
Wild Bill comes into the Nuttal & Mann's
Saloon right next door to the Fairmont.
Sits down with his back to the door.
- Okay.
- Unusual for Wild Bill.
And then, a 25-year-old
named Jack McCall
comes in and shoots him
in the back of the head.
Kills him instantly, runs out the door.
Okay.
Here's the one photo that is considered
to be the photo of Jack McCall.
You said he was 25. This guy
looks like he'd be in his 40s.
In my opinion, there is no
known photo of Jack McCall.
- Does he get caught?
- Yeah.
He was taken, tried, convicted and found
guilty of murder, and sentenced to hang.
Four years later, they
moved the cemetery.
And when they moved the
cemetery, they open the casket,
and the noose is still
around Jack McCall's neck.
I'm seeing another guy that was hung.
He admitted that he is not a good man.
And I think it was an improper hanging.
Just from the pain that I've
been experiencing from him,
it was not done well and it
was excruciatingly painful.
- You know when he's from?
- 18...
80s, 1890s.
- Age?
- 24, but he does look older.
It really hurts a lot.
I saw several dead people on my walk.
But, the women being mistreated
in the basement stood out the most.
They were all nude.
How many?
About five.
Super skinny, some of them
looked really sickly and weak.
These women were...
Being abused.
Amy?
Yeah, that's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations...
We're ready to reveal our findings to each
other and our clients for the first time.
Amy, I would like you to meet
Ron. Now, Ron owns this building.
And his dream is to turn this
historic place into a thriving hotel.
Problem is, every time he does some
construction, the activity here goes wild.
He's worried about his
guests and his employees.
Now, Kathleen here is
one of his employees.
She works downstairs at the bar.
She has had some very
frightening experiences.
And she's worried that Ron's not ever
gonna be able to fulfill his dream.
So, with that, I'm gonna ask
Amy to tell us about her walk.
When I first got here,
there were these five men who
came up to me in my opening
and they kind of surrounded me.
They were my escorts
throughout the entire walk.
But all of them had been bad people.
And it went from thievery to murder.
What they are doing...
Here is they are actually
trying to protect people.
This is how they feel they're
going to make up for...
The things that they
did when they were alive.
One of them brought up the fact
that this is the city of the dead.
So, the individual that I worked with
and spoke with the most
was this younger male.
To me he looked like he'd
be in his early to mid 30s,
but he claimed to be much
younger, like in his early 20s.
I had a hard time
believing him about his age.
And he was hanged for whatever he did.
Um... and unfortunately,
his hanging did not go well.
A couple things you mentioned
reminded me of the most
famous murder that actually
took place in this town.
And it took place literally right next
door to the building here, in a saloon.
Wild Bill Hickok, who was a
famous lawman, gunslinger...
Actually, here's a picture of him.
This is Wild Bill Hickok.
He was in the saloon but he wound
up having his back to the door.
A young kid by the name of
Jack McCall, about 25, comes in.
He says, take that, and he puts
one in the back of his head.
Kills him instantly.
He's caught, trial, found
guilty and he's hung.
Now, you mentioned that
there was a bad hanging right?
The cemetery he is buried in, they
decided four years later to move.
So, they took all the bodies
and caskets and they moved them.
When they opened up his casket...
Apparently the hanging must've
went pretty rough and bad...
The noose was still on his neck.
This is a photo of who they
think may be Jack McCall.
The kid is supposed to be 25,
this guy looks much older than 25.
Oh, my God. Oh, he was 25?
Right, but then you said he looked
a lot older than what he was.
Well, yeah he did.
Could he have been
this guy, Jack McCall?
That's what I'm thinking.
So, what else happened on your walk?
When I was standing in
front of the restaurant...
I felt and heard
another violent incident.
One man was yelling, like,
ha, ha, you [Bleep] coward.
And I felt like I was
staggering. And I felt anger.
- Now, you said the guy was staggering?
- Yes.
There actually was a man gunned down in
1949 right in front of the building here.
There was a guy by the
name of Johnny Gorham.
Now, Johnny was a middleweight champion.
- A boxer.
- Oh, my God.
There's a picture of him here.
He was also a Police
Officer in Deadwood.
What?
One night, he got drunk...
Went to a few bars, he
was punching people out.
They call the Police Chief to help
arrest him, who actually fired him.
Oh, he got fired?
He got fired for being drunk
on duty and for beating people.
Police Chief tells him to
stop, draws a service revolver.
Says, stop, don't move.
He starts cursing him,
you're a coward, you're
the one that fired me, you're all rats.
So he had anger towards
this guy, real anger.
Police Chief says, stop, stop, stop.
Boom, plants one right in his chest.
Damn.
Witnesses said that he kept going, because
you kept saying that you were staggering?
Yes.
He staggered right towards
him up until the end then fell.
- And then died.
- Wow.
I came inside.
And there were several
dead people who...
Were commenting, um,
negatively about the decor.
Basically, all of the dead have different
ideas about how this building should look.
It actually gave me
a really bad headache.
The reason we're here is that he can't
get any construction done because every
time they take a hammer and swing
it, there's... activity picks up here.
Yeah. Well, I've been trying to get the
building finished for quite some time.
And every time we seem to
get rolling right along to get
something done, we start
to have increased activity.
And the activity scares
off some of the contractors.
Oh, no.
And the employees, and then we
have to stop and regroup again.
So, what else is going on in
this place? What else you see?
One of the individuals that
was complaining about the
decor in the building was
this elderly woman that I met.
She is really tiny.
She is probably only, like,
five foot. On the heavier side.
She definitely worked a lot here.
I've seen her walking
through the Fairmont Hotel.
And then I've seen her stop
at the edge of the stage.
And just stare at me at the bar.
I've seen her several times.
She startles me if I come
up the back staircase,
because she is always
looking over the railing.
So I got in the habit
of saying, coming up.
Because, really, I don't want
to confront anything here.
Let me ask you a question, is it
possible it is the same woman you saw?
Yes.
Okay, so what else?
When I did a lot of
other walking around,
I finally made it down to the basement
and what I saw was kind of strange.
I saw several women who were...
Down there, and they were nude.
And at first I thought they
were hiding from someone.
But then, I figured out that they were
actually being put down there by someone.
- Really?
- Yes.
And I did hear, at times,
something about sex slavery.
Makes sense, though. This
building was built as a Brothel.
Because of the mining community here,
the ratio of men to women was 50 to 1.
The men that controlled
the prostitutes here did
whatever they wanted to
to keep them under control.
And when they didn't
do what they were told,
a lot of them, from what I
was told, would get beat up.
Well, I did do a sketch of that scene.
- You did?
- Yeah.
Pretty extreme, though.
- Oh, this is what you saw?
- Mm hmm.
That's just a few, though.
There's a terrible vibe in
that area, always has been.
I hate going down there
and getting supplies.
We try to avoid going
down there late at night.
So what is it that you
feel when you're down there?
Extraordinary sadness, pain.
Unpleasantness.
I want to get out as fast as I can.
When I came up to the second floor I...
Encountered a woman that I
think may have, at some point,
been in the basement, simply
because of her appearance.
She talks incessantly.
She probably worked here.
And I did get that she
did sleep with people.
It's very possible that the living...
Might hear some of the commotion
between her and the other dead people.
So, people could possibly
hear her still talking.
Kathleen actually stayed
here for about a week.
Tell her the experience you had.
A woman appeared at the foot of my
bed very briefly and just looked at me.
All of the hair stood up
on the back of my neck.
You seem to have run into
a lot of dead people here.
- Yes.
- Did you run into anybody else?
I was walking by a bedroom
on the third floor...
And I got that someone
had killed themselves.
Um, that it was a female.
She was hysterical.
Very, very sad.
And I felt like she had lost
someone very close to her.
And I got that she killed herself
in a very dramatic fashion.
That's about as accurate of
a hit that I've seen her get.
There was a prostitute back in
1907 named Maggie Broadwater.
Now, I have an article
here that describes
the way she killed
herself and what happened.
She was a prostitute that
worked here and lived here.
Now, the expert I talked to about this said
that she had a relationship that went bad.
And she took it hard
and started drinking,
heavily for about a week straight,
before she killed herself.
Now, you saw a woman when
you lived on the third floor.
Yes, I did.
I saw a woman that fit almost exactly
the same description as she described.
And I woke in the middle
of the night and she
just stood there for
about four or five minutes.
And I never saw her after that.
- You did move out, right?
- I moved out.
I'm uneasy because I don't want
to be involved in the other side.
Okay.
What else did you see?
Then I met a character,
who I called the grumpy man.
He feels like he would like
the third floor to be...
An area just for the
dead people and that no
living people should
be allowed up there.
He does get extremely agitated
and occasionally does lash out.
He does things directed towards the
living that aren't particularly nice.
Like what?
He admitted to having broken
things in the building.
He does want to
physically harm the living.
He does not know how, but he
is trying to teach himself how.
He does get extremely agitated
and occasionally does lash out.
He does things directed towards the
living that aren't particularly nice.
Like what?
He admitted to having broken
things in the building.
He does want to
physically harm the living.
He does not know how, but he
is trying to teach himself how.
That's not very pleasant.
I'm alone here at night.
I'm an older woman. It's alarming.
Does he act in a place other
than the second and third floor?
- Is he downstairs at the bar?
- He is capable to go anywhere.
It bothers me that I hear
that someone might want
to try to harm somebody
or do some mischief here.
Well, you've had investors that have stayed
overnight and physically had their...
Arm moved.
The first time it
happened, I had an investor
of mine who stayed up there to lay down.
And he came down a little bit uh...
Frightened.
And he said when he was
sleeping he was awoken
by somebody moving his
arm off of his chest.
Four or five other people have been in that
room and they all had the same experience.
That would be something that
this person is capable of doing.
Well, you guys have been hit
with a lot of information tonight.
But I think we kind of
know now why you're having
such a hard time getting
this place renovated.
The big question, though, is are you gonna
be able to fulfill your dream and turn this
into the hotel you wanted to, and keep
your staff, your guests, and yourself safe?
For that, I'm gonna turn it over
to Amy to see what she can tell us.
I believe that you can do
what you would like to do,
but it is going to take a bit of work.
So, not only do you have the dead that
people are coming into contact with.
But also all of this residual muck.
Because it's so dense, and
there's so many layers...
This is going to take about a year.
Doing cleansings one
to two times per week.
What kind of a cleansing
are we talking about?
What you need are basic things...
Salt, Sage, and holy water.
The first thing that you're going to do
would be getting some Sage, lighting it.
What this does is it removes the
buildup of the residual energy.
And then, I want you to take
some salt and water, mix it up,
put it into a spray bottle, and
then spray the floors and the walls.
The holy water is going to prevent any
more negative individuals
from coming in.
What it will do is just create a
pure and kind of safe environment.
Once all of this has been done and it's
been about a year, you will see a change.
As far as how people feel, as
far as people's interactions.
The dead that occupy this
location... they'll be gone.
Will he start feeling a
difference sooner than a year?
Yes, but you have to keep doing it.
I feel validated, because
she's brought to light things
that we have seen and it
gives us collective closure.
Now, I'm gonna ask the obvious
question, are you gonna do what she says?
What do you think?
I'll help.
Okay, there's your answer.
It won't be easy removing the layers of
dead people surrounding this location.
But if Ron and Kathleen follow my
advice, the dead will be set free.
And Ron will be able to fulfill his
dream and restore this historic hotel.