This land is bad.
I felt, like, a punch,
like something hit me.
I feel like I'm gonna throw up.
Something is chanting to
me, giving me thoughts.
I think she thinks
she's losing her mind.
I think she kind of is.
I'm surprised you didn't
run the hell out of here.
Where do you go?
I'm hearing, "I'm gonna
eat her for dinner.
I'm gonna eat her. I'm gonna eat her."
There's a dark presence.
My name is Amy Allan.
These things, they're freaking out.
They're from hell.
I see dead people.
They were being hunted.
I speak to dead people.
They were setting people on fire,
burning them alive.
And they speak to me.
Her neck got broken.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I hear a gunshot.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Something's not right here.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
It's not safe here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Are any of them buried on the property?
They're all buried here.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end...
I can't do it no more.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Holy [bleep] look at this.
Or time to get out.
It does not have a happy ending.
Something kills people here.
I'm in Mayfield, Kentucky.
It's a small city in the
southwestern part of the state.
I got a call from a
mother who was hysterical.
She thinks that whatever's in the house
is going after her two kids,
destroying her own health,
and ripping her family apart.
She told me she's tried everything
and that we're her last hope.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the house of
any leading information,
removing family photos
and religious icons.
When I'm finished,
the location will be
ready for tonight's walk.
First thing that I saw was a hill.
There's a hill.
It starts to roll.
There are things inside it.
There's a lot of them.
It makes me feel uncomfortable.
The dead in here are, uh, scared.
They know this land, and
they know that it is bad.
Well, Socorro, when
I talked to you on the phone,
you sounded really upset.
I am.
It's not safe here.
I'm afraid for my kids.
It's been very difficult.
Nobody should have to live like this.
No.
Honestly, I mean, you're our last hope.
Who exactly lives in the house, though?
Well, I have a photo here.
This is my husband, Tim.
This is our oldest daughter, Bianca.
She's 14.
And then, this is McKenzie,
our youngest. She's 8.
What year did you move in?
2006.
Now, if you can, just give me a list
of what's going on in the house.
There's been knocking.
There's been footsteps,
things moving on their
own, shadow figures.
Okay.
And now it seems to be getting violent.
I feel it's picking on the
girls and picking on myself.
McKenzie hasn't slept in her room
in the last 4 or 5 years.
She's been sleeping
with my husband and I.
No 8-year-old's supposed
to go through that.
Well, that can't be
great for the marriage.
It's taken a very big
toll on our marriage.
But at the same time, she's scared.
We're the parents. We're
supposed to protect them.
What about you? How are you holding up?
It's been very hard.
There's days where I just
think I'm going crazy.
I've also had medical
issues with my right leg.
I've been to the doctor's.
I've been to a specialist.
And nobody can seem to tell
me what's wrong with my leg.
Is that the only physical
problem you're having?
Other than my anxiety.
So when these anxiety
attacks happen, is it...
Explain what happens to you.
Almost like I can't
breathe and my chest hurts.
Something doesn't feel right,
almost like I'm crawling
out of my own skin.
It's just not normal.
I know it's not normal.
Well, we're here.
I just
hope you guys can help.
This is a bad room,
very bad.
Yeah. I see a man and a woman fighting.
She has, like, stomach...
bad stomach problems, heart issues.
Real sick. Really, really [bleep] sick.
Panic, anxiety, very depressed.
Ooh.
Oh, this is terrible. This is awful.
My God. This person has,
like, major anxiety issues.
There's this, like, overwhelming feeling
like she can't take it anymore.
Uh...
I think she thinks
she's losing her mind.
I think she kind of is.
Ooh.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Okay. So why'd you
bring me in the kitchen?
In here, we hear a lot
of unexplained noise
that's coming out of
the kitchen area...
doors slamming, things
shuffling in the cabinets.
Now, do you actually see the
drawers opening and closing?
No. We don't.
Do you ever have evidence
that something's been moved?
No. We don't.
Anything else?
In the laundry room area,
I felt, like, a punch,
like something just hit me.
It was whew, right at the rib cage.
It knocked the wind out of me. Really?
And I've seen a shadow
figure at the door.
It's tall, dark, black male figure.
And it's there for a couple
seconds, and it's gone.
You got a lot of lights from cars
going by every once in a while.
What about that?
Could it cast a shadow on
anything you got in there?
No. I don't believe it does. No.
So this shadow figure you saw,
do you feel that this
thing is threatening?
Yes. I was scared.
Being stared at...
It's a stare that makes you
very, very uncomfortable.
I'm surprised you didn't
run the hell out of here.
Where do you go?
The living woman,
she sees the figures from outside,
from inside the earth.
Do you know what these things
would look like to people?
Like shadow people.
They're kind of tall, though.
They're around her a lot.
She's attracting them to her
because of what is happening
or has happened in her life.
Somehow, she knows that
there are these bad things,
so she's, like, inviting this evil in.
How long has McKenzie been
sleeping with you guys?
A little over 4 years.
It's a lot to deal with.
And it has taken a
strain on our marriage.
Okay.
You mentioned that you had
some stuff going on in here.
Yes. Um, I was lying in bed.
Okay.
And I saw a dark shadow figure
standing over my bed.
I closed my eyes
several times and prayed.
And opened my eyes,
and it's still there.
You... you're sure you
weren't dreaming, though?
No. I wasn't dreaming.
Did that ever happen again?
In the bathroom.
As I'm in there taking a shower,
I feel like I'm being stared at.
It's... it's horrible.
There's been another
incident just recently
that I'm laying in bed,
and I felt a tug on the blankets.
And McKenzie usually
tugs at the blankets
and then crawls into bed with us.
So I turned, thinking,
"Well, okay, McKenzie."
Well, McKenzie's not in bed with me.
What about the dogs? Do they ever...
No. They get kenneled at night.
I mean, how are you living like this?
I mean, just listening
to your stories is...
It's been very hard. It's
been very difficult, Steve.
I don't know what's here.
I know that whatever is
here, it's not a good thing.
I feel like I'm gonna throw up.
They're all over.
They're all over in here.
She sees like two to four of them.
I think she thinks
she's losing her mind.
Subconsciously, she invited them in.
They're attracted to negative people.
So if the person is
having a really bad time
or they're depressed, they
see that as an invitation.
You know, it's almost kind of like
she's trying to sell her soul...
like she's trying to make a deal here.
For what?
She's saying she would
give up her eternal soul.
She doesn't really see another way out.
So, Tim, I talked to your
wife about what's going on here,
and things are pretty bad.
Yeah. And it's getting worse.
You got to be concerned
for your wife and daughters,
I would think.
Yeah. I am because my work
takes me out of town a lot.
And it's tough. It's tough leaving.
So, Tim, how is the
relationship with your wife?
It's not like it should be.
I mean, we both snap at each other.
The slightest little thing
just sets... sets us off.
So what about experiences for yourself?
Have you had any?
I went up and was tucking the girls in.
Okay.
And just getting ready
to come down the stairs.
And next thing I know, my
feet are out from under me,
and I'm at the bottom of the stairs.
Did one foot slip? What
happened when you fell?
I don't fall.
I've never fell down stairs before.
You know, I'm...
I'm an iron worker.
Right. So for your
profession alone, you would...
you're not the type
that's just gonna fall.
Right.
Could've broke your neck. Yeah.
There's an old man down
here talking about a barn.
He lived here a long time ago,
a long, long time ago.
He walks through the kitchen wall.
He does pranks...
I think like making
people trip and fall.
I did see somebody tripping,
and he was laughing.
This guy, he's not good.
Uh, he's very, very abusive.
He doesn't give a [bleep]
what I think about him.
So, Bianca, I was
talking to Mom and Dad.
They're telling me
you're going through
some tough times here.
It's kind of hard, you know?
Like, you don't know
if you're sane or not.
You feel crazy. Feels
like you're in a dream.
I was talking to Mom,
and she was telling me
that her mood's changed.
Have you noticed that?
Yeah.
She's mad a lot, short-tempered.
It's... it happens to me.
I'll get extremely mad.
I think it's the thing that's here.
We used to be happy.
What are some of the
experiences you're having?
In the corners or on the wall,
it's this really dark, tall man figure.
But you can't see anything,
no face, no nothing,
just a black mist.
And how often do you see this, honey?
Every other week.
Is anything else going on with you?
I've had thoughts that aren't mine.
Something is chanting to
me, giving me thoughts like,
"I wasn't meant to be here."
Okay.
"I don't belong."
If you already know
it's not your thoughts,
you got this beat.
You know that, right?
Mm-hmm.
Now, is anything else happening?
I hear voices, growls.
Growls?
What kind of growls
are we talking about?
It was like a roar
but a really deep roar
and an animal and, like,
human mixed together.
It's... it
was scary.
How do you stay up here?
Lights. I always sleep with lights on.
Some nights, I don't sleep at all.
Now, do you want to stay
here, or do you want to move?
- I want to move.
- You do?
I do. I don't feel safe here.
Okay.
Ooh. There is a teenage boy.
It's crazy and out of control.
And I think he causes a lot of problems.
He's in here a lot.
He causes noise.
He's very noisy, very loud.
He does, like, growling.
I see an old woman.
And she's done... She's,
like, done good things
to, like, fake this living lady out
to trust her or something
but made her feel like
she's protecting her.
I think these kids are seeing [bleep]
She freaks them out.
Like, she, like, does creepy [bleep]
Maybe looks like a mist, maybe?
She goes to the bed a lot.
I think she's flo...
She's been seen over...
hovering over people.
That's [bleep] creepy.
So, McKenzie,
I was talking to Mom.
I was talking to Dad.
And they were saying
you were having some
tough things going on here
that you were...
things that scared you.
Mm-hmm.
And this is your room, right?
Yeah.
It's beautiful. I wish
I had a room like this.
But you don't sleep up here.
Never.
You're scared to be up here?
You are. Okay.
Are there things that happened
that you can tell me about
that scared you?
Well, one day, whenever I was sleeping
in my mom and dad's room,
I saw a black shadow.
And it was coming across the yard.
And that scared you?
You play up here?
Sometimes.
Okay. Are you alone when you do that?
No. Okay.
How come? Tell me.
Because I always feel like
someone's, like, watching me.
You do?
Okay.
The dead lady, she wants this one bad.
She wants this one very bad.
She didn't want me to come in here.
She just says weird [bleep]
like, "I'm gonna eat her,"
you know, "I'm gonna
eat her for dinner."
She, like, watches constantly this one.
Watches, watches, watches.
Follows everywhere, everywhere, watches.
Bad, bad.
I think she's influencing this person
or will influence this person.
Whoever sleeps in here
the most is in trouble.
Very haunted person.
Very haunted.
Not even a [bleep] chance, man.
Not even a fighting chance.
Socorro and Tim
don't know a lot about
their property's history.
So I got on the phone and
called a bunch of locals.
A historian just got
back to me and told me
that one of the earliest
owners of my client's property
has a story I'm definitely
gonna want to hear about.
You mentioned on the phone
that previous owners
of my client's property
had a pretty tragic time there.
Who are these people?
Well, George and Agnes Wyatt
are the owners of the property.
They bought it in
1919 to farm tobacco on
with their only child, Virgil.
George and Agnes came from
very good farm families.
Here's a picture of
George in his mid-30s.
As you can see, he's a good, strong guy.
And Agnes came from a
very prominent family.
She was one of six children.
Her father was
very well-to-do
and was even elected city assessor.
Okay. So how did it go for them?
You mentioned the tragedy.
What's their story?
Well, in 1937, George
got very, very ill.
He was experiencing intense
pain in his upper-right abdomen,
nausea, vomiting, fever,
even jaundice,
the yellowing of the skin and the eyes.
They took him to the Mayfield hospital,
and he was diagnosed with
a gallbladder inflammation.
Two days after his surgery,
he died in his hospital bed.
It was not a painless way to go at all.
Okay. So as far as Agnes
goes, does she remarry?
What's the story?
She did not remarry.
She remained on the farm
by herself until she died.
Okay. So how soon after
George dies does she die?
Five years.
Five years?
She died in her own
bed on October 20, 1942.
She dies of the same
thing as her husband?
Same symptoms. Same diagnosis.
Okay.
The old woman,
she doesn't want me to
know anything about her.
Terrible. Terrible. Terrible.
This was prop... her
family's property.
Who is this [bleep] person?
A lot of money there.
She had siblings, lots of siblings,
something like five or six.
Okay. So I got to assume
Virgil's the only kid.
He gets the farm.
No. She cuts him out of the will.
When Agnes passed away in 1942,
and here's a copy of the will,
it says in the will that
Virgil doesn't get anything.
Why would she do that?
It would appear as though
she didn't trust him.
It sounds like she's a mean woman.
Yes. It does certainly seem as though
she could be a very spiteful person.
So why didn't she trust him?
He moved off the farm and
trained to become a machinist,
which is a very skilled profession.
Okay.
But he didn't hold
that job for very long.
And he ended up becoming a laborer
for the Kentucky Department of Highways,
which is a very big drop in income.
What do you think happened?
Well, that's the interesting thing.
There are indications
that he may have had
trouble with alcohol.
He ended up dying at the age of 62
from complications...
an enlarged liver and kidney failure,
which is indicative of alcoholism.
Okay.
The old lady doesn't
like the teenage boy.
She says he gets in the way.
She can't abide it.
She's mad.
Some kind of weird dynamic here.
Totally just [bleep]
The old man is laughing.
He's like, "Oh, you met the... upstairs."
He hates her, hates her.
Are you guys related
somehow? I don't know.
They knew her father.
He's saying, like, somebody
should've just, like,
[bleep] like, shot them
all, like, killed them all
because they were all, like, demented.
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity in your home,
go to the "Dead Files"
page at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help Me, Dead
Files!" to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
So far, I've got
a family living in fear
on a property that's
seen at least two deaths.
But I need to see
if there's anything else
that can help my case.
Searching through old records,
I find not one but
four men who were killed
while working on my client's property...
all by a single bolt of lightning.
I'm heading over to meet
with a local archivist
who said those men never had a chance.
Well, Nathan, thanks for
helping me out with my case,
but why out here in
the middle of nowhere?
Well, I wanted to bring you out
here to a working tobacco farm
to kind of give you a glimpse
of what your client's property
looked like at the time.
All right. So what's the
story with this accident?
On September 2, 1939,
seven farmers had been
out cutting tobacco.
And they were taking
it to a barn to hang it
when, all of a sudden,
a huge storm blew up.
It was one of the worst storms
that hit the area in the time.
And you can see here
massive flooding, power lines down.
A number of roofs were
blown off of buildings.
Pretty rough storm.
The lightning strikes
all seven of the men.
They all go down.
That's incredible.
Unfortunately, four of the men die.
Wow.
Did these guys even know it was coming?
I doubt that they had
any idea it was coming.
Okay.
Here's their death certificates here.
You had three women who
became widows that day
and two children who lost their fathers.
Geez. Horrible event.
So this is just bad luck.
Bad luck or something.
I don't know of anyone
that's been hit by lightning
here in Western Kentucky.
I lived here all my life.
These shadow people,
they're all over the place
but mostly stay in the ground.
It's almost like a burial.
There's something with the...
with the outside, with the land.
There's something wrong
here with the earth,
some kind of, like,
entities or something.
Like, I kind of want to
say it's kind of evil.
During my research,
I came across something
that caught my attention.
I traced the property deed
back more than 130 years
and couldn't believe
that the average person
stayed there less than three.
It just doesn't seem right.
I'm heading over to meet
with a local real estate agent
to see if this is as
strange as it sounds.
Now, Fred, when I
pulled the chain of title
on my client's property,
I couldn't believe what I saw.
There was 47 owners in 131 years.
You're a veteran real estate agent.
For that neighborhood,
is frequent turnover on
properties and homes common?
That is a lot of transactions
for any particular area
and this area for certain.
Most people that buy homes there,
they stay there for quite some time.
It's one of the better
and safer neighborhoods
of our whole county.
Now, when you looked
through the records here,
anything stand out?
There were some things
that popped out at me.
For instance, in 1919,
I noticed there were eight
different transactions
just in that one year.
Also, there was a lady that bought it
and only kept it for 10 days.
Wow.
When my chain of title search came in,
I saw all these transactions
when it was a tobacco farm.
But yet the turnovers continued
after my client's
house was built in '89.
They were already the fourth owners.
I just thought that to be odd.
Yeah. Well, no doubt about it.
So the property I'm investigating
has some unusual numbers attached to it.
Very much unusual.
Okay.
I encountered several
entities during my walk,
but the old woman
tormenting the living girl
had me the most concerned.
This old female,
her head was very narrow and long.
And she had long, gray hair.
And she was wrapped around
this young female child,
kind of, "I'm in control of this kid."
Okay. Is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our findings
to each other and our
clients for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to
meet Tim and Socorro.
Now, from the time they
moved into this house in 2006,
things were bad.
But things just kept getting worse.
The biggest worry they have is
their two beautiful daughters.
This is Bianca, who's 14,
and this is McKenzie, who just turned 8.
The kids don't feel
safe in their own home,
and it's killing the parents here.
The activity in the home
is tearing the family apart,
and we're their very last hope.
So now that Amy knows a little bit
about what's going
on in the family here,
I'm gonna ask her to
describe her walk for us.
There's a lot going on here,
and I'm gonna start off by discussing
the conscious dead
that I encountered here.
The first individual that I met
was an elderly male
over in the dining area.
He's in his 60s.
And I heard him talking
a lot about hi... a barn.
I think he lived here a long time ago.
He seemed to be pretty
negative and pretty abusive.
And now, in death,
he's still very ornery.
Something he was telling me
is that when he feels like
somebody says or does something stupid,
he'll try to hit them.
And what he was telling me
was that he actually does hit people.
And one of his favorite
things to do is to trip people.
And if they fall down, he gets a laugh.
Yeah, I was standing
at the top of the stairs
and getting ready to come down.
And I go to take a step.
And the next thing I
know, both my feet are out.
I'm at the bottom of the stairs.
It freaked me out. You know?
Tim's an iron worker.
He's used to being on beams and high up.
- Balance is his life.
- Right.
A guy like this doesn't just trip.
No.
Now, you got punched in the back.
Yes. I was walking in
from the laundry room.
And as I turned and was
walking back into the kitchen,
I felt a punch.
It just knocked the wind out of me.
So this sounds like
something this guy would do?
Yeah. Both of those things
would be right up his alley.
The next person that I encountered
was a teenage male.
He was kind of a wild child.
He's kind of crazy and out of control.
Mostly, I saw him upstairs
in the larger bedroom.
He's very noisy, very loud.
He often makes growling noises as well.
It's driving the dead crazy.
This kid's driving
living people crazy, too.
Mm-hmm.
Explain to Amy how
Bianca hears the growling.
She's come running to me several times.
And Tim and I... And we heard it.
What does it sound like?
A dog. But it's not a dog.
Now, Bianca described it to me
as half animal, half possibly human.
Mm-hmm.
I'll never forget that sound.
The next individual
was an elderly female.
So hates the teenage boy.
Somehow, they're related.
She was also saying that he
gets in the way of everything.
I saw her in each of the
rooms upstairs specifically.
And she's causing trouble.
There's problems there.
I got that she lived here.
She had like six or more siblings
and that she had money.
That's interesting.
Could be a long shot,
but there's a woman who
lived on the property.
Her name was Agnes Wyatt.
Now, Agnes moved here in
1919 with her husband, George,
and their only son, Virgil.
And they came here to farm tobacco.
Now, this is George.
I have a photo of
Virgil I was able to get.
Agnes did come from a wealthy family.
She had six siblings.
There was a couple other
strange things about her.
In 1937, George dies
after gallbladder surgery.
Cholecystitis was what they called it.
Five years later,
Agnes dies of the same exact thing,
which I thought was odd.
Now, Amy, you mentioned
that the woman didn't
like the teenage boy.
Now, when Agnes died, she
cut her only son, Virgil,
out of the will because he was a drunk.
That's a lot of hate.
Yes.
Now, you said the woman
was trouble, though.
Yes. What does she do?
I think that she is possibly
a threat to the living.
When I went upstairs,
I saw her in the lavender bedroom.
And I saw her coming out of the closet,
being like a mist and,
like, hovering over the bed.
So the other thing was that
I saw an unusual relationship
between her and the person,
the female, in that room.
The female there felt like
this was somehow protecting her,
but it was actually making her sick.
That's Bianca's room.
- Bianca's room.
- Okay.
And is Bianca okay up there?
No. She's not.
She doesn't sleep.
She doesn't sleep
because something up there
doesn't let her sleep.
But then, I went into the pink room.
The old lady,
she's very fixated on
the child in that room.
She is always watching her,
tries to be around her
as much as possible,
watches her all the time.
And one of the things that she said
was that she wanted to eat her.
McKenzie will not sleep in her room.
She says that there's something
in her room that bothers her.
She feels like something
is watching her whenever...
Has she ever described
what she's seeing?
McKenzie won't talk
about it. It scares her.
She doesn't like for
us to talk about it.
She'll tell us, "You guys,
stop talking about it."
It just seemed to me like the old lady
had some kind of weird
obsession with McKenzie.
I think that it's her
energy that she's absorbing,
which can be...
have very detrimental
effects on her in her health.
I did a sketch
of what this old woman
is doing to McKenzie.
I'm sorry, guys, to even
show you this, but...
Wow.
It's no wonder she won't sleep up there.
That's scary.
I don't know.
Just so innocent, you know?
No kid should have to go through that.
I'm sorry, guys, to even
show you this, but...
Wow.
It's no wonder she won't sleep up there.
That's scary.
I don't know.
Just so innocent, you know?
No kid should have to go through that.
And that's what she sees
'cause she's told us she
sees something in her room.
I actually got a lot of
information on you guys.
The female of the house
was not in good shape
as far as just mentally and
emotionally and physically.
And I was seeing fights
with a male, a living male.
I got that you were very, very ill,
there were stomach issues, heart issues.
I experienced a lot of
different emotions...
depression, anxiety, and
then feeling panic attacks.
Whoa.
I could feel all of
this pain and misery.
It was excruciating for me,
and I got really dizzy from it
and, like, kind of fell to my knees.
Amy, you hit on just about...
Everything.
Everything that made Socorro call us.
I've had panic attacks, anxiety attacks.
She's woken me up because
she couldn't breathe.
You know, there's days where I feel like
I'm just crawling out of my own skin.
I am angry,
screaming and yelling
and just not myself.
Mm-hmm.
I feel as if I'm going crazy.
I've got medical issues that
can't be explained with my leg.
I've been to doctors and specialists,
and nobody can tell me what's wrong.
Now, you mentioned fighting.
Yes.
It's like I can't do
anything right, you know,
and she probably feels the same way.
And the girls don't
need to be seeing it.
This is it.
You're our last hope.
Just to know, you know, what's going on
and I almost feel like, you know,
to prove to Tim that I'm not crazy.
Oh, no. Yeah.
I'm not crazy.
I... I...
Even though I feel like that a lot.
The last thing I feel very,
very concerned about...
What I saw was a hill,
and the ground was rolling.
And it was making me very nervous.
And I saw, like, through the earth.
And I saw, like, these little things.
They mostly stay in the ground.
And I got, like, some kind of burial
that they were, in fact, human once.
But now, they're, like,
these humanoid shadow creature things.
Mm-hmm.
And when I was in the master bedroom,
I saw that at least two to four of them
had started to surround you
and that you were or
had seen these things
or were and had felt them.
The thing about
these things...
They won't go to someone
unless that person is
in bad shape already.
So, like, if that person
is unhappy or stressed out
or in a negative situation,
they start to come.
You do see shadow people.
I see shadow people all the time.
Does that mean I'm doing it?
Not on purpose.
Well, when I go outside, I
feel like I'm being watched.
Oh, yeah. You're being
watched. Yeah. Mm-hmm.
In my bedroom,
I don't sleep with my back to the wall
because I feel
something's staring at me.
Is this something that can hurt me?
Yes.
They could hurt your body.
So make you sick.
The ones that are around you
now are always around you.
Are they around her right
now, these shadow things?
Yes.
They're over there.
Oh, my gosh.
Now, did you see anything else?
No.
So there's one other thing
I need to tell you about
'cause it's on your property.
Maybe somehow it's
related. I don't know.
Back in 1939, when
this was a tobacco farm,
there were seven guys working
out in the field right here,
trying to get the crops
ready to get stored.
Well, a storm came through.
They tried to outrun the storm.
Lightning hit them.
All seven got struck.
Four of them died.
Their death certificates
here. Four guys.
Three wives became widows,
and two kids lost their father that day.
- Wow.
That's kind of crazy, actually.
Do you think these guys
could be the shadow people
you saw on the hills outside?
No. I think they go
back hundreds of years,
possibly Native Americans.
I don't think that
this land is very good.
Well, Socorro, when I spoke
to you and your family,
I knew things were bad.
But I didn't know it would be this bad.
And I'm sorry for that. I really am.
I know you guys have heard stuff
tonight that's really troubling.
But the big question is,
can you guys raise your
two daughters here in peace?
So for that answer, I'm
gonna turn it over to Amy.
There's a lot of stuff
that you guys need to do.
And the steps you need to take
need to happen relatively quickly.
So it's going to be intense.
First thing you're gonna do is
you're gonna contact a Reiki master.
This person will come in,
and they will remove all
of the negative energy
from the house.
And they will bring in
only positive, balanced,
harmonious energy
into the house.
It's very important in this situation
because the energy in
the house is so negative.
And your bodies are
encountering this negativity.
And when they do that cleansing,
they're going to remove
all negative attachments,
which means those...
- The shadow things.
- Yes.
And with McKenzie,
it'll remove the dead woman from her.
Oh.
So here's the key. You've got 24 hours.
They're gonna want to reattach.
So the next thing that needs
to be done within 24 hours...
I want the same Reiki master
to come back with a medium.
They're going to help move on
the dead that are in the house.
So then they're gone,
and y'all are balanced.
And the house is harmonious.
So after everything's done,
will McKenzie at least
sleep in her own room?
Yes.
- Oh.
- Yes.
When you came to us
to come do this case,
you were done.
I was at my breaking point.
But now, you've got a game plan.
And we've got a plan
and we know what to do.
Are you gonna take her advice?
Yeah. For my family. I'd
do anything for my family.
All right. Good. I'm glad to hear that.
It's gonna be a family thing,
and I think it's gonna
not only bring us closer
but have closure...
Mm-hmm.
And start a new chapter.
I really feel for Socorro,
as the dead tormenting her
family present a serious danger.
But with the help of a
medium and a Reiki master,
they'll be able to rid
their home of the dead
and the negative energy surrounding it.