There's something dangerous here.
And I heard summoning.
It's almost like I was possessed.
It scared me, made me jump.
The injuries make him unrecognizable.
He's getting his face bashed in.
The tray was just thrown out of my hand.
It would be like
cutting out my own heart.
It's really bad.
They're gonna [bleep] kill me.
There's a dark presence.
My name is Amy Allan.
These things, they're freaking out.
They're from hell.
I see dead people.
They were being hunted.
I speak to dead people.
They were setting people on fire,
burning them alive.
And they speak to me.
Her neck got broken.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I hear a gunshot.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Something's not right here.
And I know every person,
every house, has secrets.
It's not safe here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Are any of them buried on the property?
They're all buried here.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end...
I can't do it no more.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Holy [bleep] Look at this.
Or time to get out.
It does not have a happy ending.
Something kills people here.
I'm in Grass Valley, California,
about 60 miles northeast of Sacramento.
I got a call from a guy who
bought an old, historic hotel
and said it was the worst
thing he's ever done.
He says the paranormal
activity there is so bad,
it's attacking his guests,
scaring his employees,
and he even blames it
for causing his divorce.
He says if we can't find a solution,
he's gonna have to shut the place down.
Before Amy arrives, I clear
the area of any leading information.
Photographs and artwork
can influence her findings,
so it's important that I
cover or remove them all.
When I'm finished,
the location will be
ready for tonight's walk.
This town is very active.
Everybody is yelling.
This is a long time ago.
Dirt roads.
There were a lot of tragedies here.
And people were angry about them.
They're pissed. They're [bleep] pissed.
There's lots of chaos here.
Ooh.
Well, Ian, it's good
to finally meet you in person.
When we spoke on the phone,
you sounded like you were at
your wits end with this place.
I still come in
every morning, like,
"What's gonna happen today?"
I've had guests check out
in the middle of the night,
say, "I can't stay
here. It's too scary."
I have employees that are afraid
to go to parts of the building alone.
It's stressful.
I'm tired of it.
Now, you mentioned on the phone,
there was a lot of activity here.
Give me an idea what
you're talking about.
I have people hearing noises.
I have objects moving around.
People are being physically touched.
I've even had people say
that they were being sexually assaulted.
- Guests?
- Guests.
It's not just here and
there. It's consistent.
Ian, you mentioned on the phone
that this place may have
even destroyed your marriage.
I mean, what did you mean by that?
After I took over the hotel,
my marriage really
started falling apart.
It changed my personality.
I've talked to people that
have worked here and managed
and owners in the past,
and they said the exact same thing.
It's like, "It ruined my marriage."
I feel like there's
something in the air here,
something in the energy.
I see people acting
in ways that they normally
wouldn't be acting.
Why are you holding on to this place?
You know, I love it. I
still love the Holbrooke.
It's the centerpiece for Grass Valley.
Have you done anything to try
to figure out what's going on?
I've had three different
paranormal groups come in here
over the last four years.
They had video and audio recording.
What did they tell you?
They say there's a lot of activity,
but no one's ever told me
to do anything about it.
They're more interested in
just trying to see what's here.
I want some answers.
I don't want to walk
away from this place.
I think there's a living person
that is doing something very bad here.
And I heard summoning.
And I do see people doing,
very specifically, EVP stuff.
You mean investigations and stuff?
Yeah. Yeah.
I don't know if they're formal
or just something that
these owners or whoever
are doing on their own time,
but whatever it is,
there's an obsession.
Now I'm hearing obsession.
So, what's going on back here?
My equipment in the
kitchen is always breaking.
We'll buy brand-new equipment.
It will fail within a few weeks.
You sure you don't have an
employee here who's trying
to get even with you for
something and breaking [bleep]
It's possible, but I've seen
equipment installed myself,
and it's failed with
a week for no reason.
Now, is anything else going on?
I've had furniture move around in rooms.
I was staying in room number 9.
Okay.
When I went to bed, I
saw where the chair was.
I got up in the middle of
the night to use the restroom,
the chair had moved to a
completely different spot
in the room, and I tripped on it.
- Now, were you alone?
- I was alone.
- You could have broke your neck.
- Yes.
The chair moving in
your bedroom upstairs
when you were staying
over, I can't explain that.
But the rest of this stuff,
the electrical and all that...
it's an old building. You
think this is all paranormal?
There's no logical explanation
for these events that are happening.
I want people to be safe and happy here.
I'm hoping you can help me.
There's an aggressive male here.
He's very, very hyper.
And I hear "Paul."
I am gonna say that he's mentally ill.
He likes it in here.
It feels more comfortable for him.
He likes little spaces.
He is aggressive,
but it's when he feels
like he's being cornered.
He kind of lashes out.
I do see him touching people.
The things he'll do
is, like, hiding things,
breaking things, stuff like that.
So, how long did you work here?
Approximately two years.
I was a front desk agent.
From my understanding, it
looks like Ian saved this hotel.
How important is that for the city?
It's very important for Grass Valley.
The Holbrooke is basically
the heart of this town.
There's so much history, and
everybody loves this place.
Ian was telling me that he
thinks whatever's going on here
is responsible for his
marriage breaking up.
You think whatever's here has
an effect on relationships?
Yes. I've seen a few relationships
that were really,
really strong break up.
There's something here
that doesn't want you to be happy.
Now, when you worked here,
did you have any experiences?
I've actually seen
a shadow figure...
a very tall shadow figure
...ln the kitchen twice.
Now, describe the shadow
figure. How did it look to you?
Tall and dark.
It was definitely taller
than me, over 6 feet tall.
And dark... You
couldn't see through it.
Okay, is there anything
else you've experienced?
I couldn't count how
many times this happened,
sitting here at the
front desk, and I would...
hear my name
and feel a presence.
And they would, you know, call my name,
and I was, "Can I help... you?
Oh, there's nobody there."
Are you sure it couldn't
have been somebody
that came in from outside?
Absolutely. No one gets
in without me noticing.
- The doors are locked.
- Okay.
There's a woman,
and she is a force to be reckoned with.
She's in charge, you
know, with an iron fist.
She's trying to talk to people.
It bothers them.
She touches them, and it's burning.
It's hot. It's hot. It's so hot.
And then she's got, like, this
whole white mist thing going on.
The living see her kind of
as a full-bodied apparition,
sometimes crying, sometimes yelling,
and sometimes being very forceful.
What is she trying to tell people?
She's in trouble. She needs help.
So, Andrew, I understand
that you actually work here.
Yes, sir. I
used to also live here.
- You lived here?
- Yeah.
- For how long?
- For about seven months.
- Okay, what do you do?
- Now I'm maintenance.
I used to do everything
from front desk, night audit,
fill in for bartending.
So you basically know
the whole building.
In and out.
Okay. Now, you've
experienced some stuff.
Oh, absolutely, yes.
Okay, what can you tell me?
I've seen shadows and shadow figures,
one with a hat that
was down in the kitchen.
It was a dark figure,
and you could tell there
was something there,
and it scared me. Made me jump,
like you or somebody was right
next to me and I didn't know it.
And you were alone in the kitchen.
Mm-hmm.
Okay. Is there anything else going on?
We get a lot of complaints from guests.
Okay, like what?
I've had guests check out
in the middle of the night,
complaints of noise above their roof
when they're on the top floor,
and there's nobody up there,
or the temperatures changing,
or their doorknob keeps rattling.
It's an old building.
I'm sure there's some
quirky things going on,
but that's pretty drastic.
I had a family that checked
in about 3:00 in the afternoon,
and husband and wife
left the son upstairs
in the room to take a nap.
They were eating downstairs, and
he came barging into the saloon,
asked for the car
key, stayed in the car.
He would not come back up to the room.
Did you find out what happened?
We ask him what was going
on. He said he felt something
massaging, like, his legs or his back.
And knowing nobody was in the room,
he just jumped up out of the
room and was not going back.
Wow. That would have scared
the hell out of me, I think.
It's almost like it's...
malicious in a way.
I think that there's
something dangerous here.
And someone's just [bleep] choking bad.
There's a guy
strangling a woman
with his hand.
He's, like, just holding her down.
Real strong.
Living people are experiencing this,
like, little snippets of past
events all over the place.
Some chick's [bleep] crying.
She had a [bleep] fight with some guy.
She's drinking...
morphine.
You know, somebody's who's in this room,
they would hear her crying.
They would hear the pacing, you know?
They would feel like they're
having mental breakdowns.
What's going on?
Whatever is here makes
the living [bleep] insane.
I don't even know how
anyone could stay here.
There are just so many dead.
So, how long you been here?
Over seven years.
Okay, so you were here before
Ian even bought the place?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Any experiences you can't explain?
When I was working graveyard,
I would get up from my
desk and go do something,
and then on my way back,
I would see somebody
sitting in my chair.
So I'd look again, and
they'd be gone, so...
Now, you said you worked
the graveyard shift.
Did you have the doors locked?
Yes. I always locked the
doors for my protection.
What about a guest?
No. It was too fast
for it to be a person.
Okay, so, anything else?
I waitress now,
and a few times, I would be
walking with the empty tray
going to the dining room,
and the tray just, with force,
was just thrown out of my hand.
That's happened three times.
So, where does this usually happen?
Back here in the hallway.
It happened more towards the kitchen.
Did it feel like a hand
came up and smacked it or...
Exactly. It felt like
somebody just went underneath
and just popped it right out of my hand.
Okay. That's interesting.
It scared me.
So, you've had a few
things. Anything else?
Yes, I've taken three very
bad falls in this building
since Ian has taken over.
I fell out here in the lobby once
with a wine glass in
my hand... cut my hand.
Another time, I fell in the kitchen,
and that was a hard fall.
I really hurt my hand.
I had bruises all over the place.
And then another time, I slipped,
and I went and told the cook,
I'm all, "This is dangerous.
It's like ice there," you know?
And he's testing it with his feet,
and he said, "No, it's not.
It's not slippery at all."
That's strange.
These falls, now, is
this uncommon for you?
I've only fallen in here.
I don't usually fall. I'm not clumsy.
I don't know if that's paranormal,
but you've had stuff just
pop out of your hands.
- Right.
- So it's not out of the realm
that somebody may be trying
to make you fall, either.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
Okay.
This hallway is not a good place to be
if you're a living person.
These dead people who have
issues are running amok
doing a lot of, like,
weird physical [bleep] here.
This is not a good hallway to be in.
It's very bad in here.
Ohh.
I feel sick, sick.
Considering Ian's
owned the hotel for five years,
he really doesn't know much about it.
So I've reached out
to a local historian,
who says it's actually a miracle
that the Holbrooke's
still standing today.
So, Hilary, do me a favor.
Will you just start from the
beginning with this place?
When was the hotel built?
It was built in 1851, as
the Golden Gate Saloon.
Did it flourish as a saloon?
Yes, for several years...
until the fire of 1855,
where most of the town was burnt down.
So, what kind of damage are
we talking about in this fire?
- Over 60 acres.
- Wow!
Over 300 buildings were destroyed,
including the Golden Gate Saloon.
Okay, so, obviously, they rebuilt.
Yes. They rebuilt, and then
they added the lot next door,
and they called it the Exchange Hotel.
When did it become the Holbrooke Hotel?
January 1, 1879.
Daniel and his wife, Ellen, Holbrooke
bought the hotel for $12,000.
I have a photo of Daniel Holbrooke.
They renovated it
and reopened it as the Holbrooke.
Nothing's really changed.
No, that's the nice
thing about that hotel.
So, now they have the hotel.
How's it work out for them?
Unfortunately, four years
after they bought it,
Daniel Holbrooke passes
away in the hotel.
In the hotel?
Yes, and here's a copy of his obituary.
And they have his funeral at
the hotel a couple days later.
What happens with the hotel?
Well, Ellen takes it
over, and she runs it
for the next 23 years
until her death in 1906.
And I have a copy of her obituary here.
She also dies in the hotel.
Now, you mentioned on the
phone that it was a miracle
that the Holbrooke was
even standing, still.
What did you mean by that?
Well, after that big fire of 1855,
there were four more major fires
that devastated Grass Valley...
one in 1860, 1862,
1873, and 1896.
But, somehow, the
Holbrooke was left standing.
How close of a call
was it for the hotel?
Well, in 1860 and 1873,
everything within 100 feet
of the Holbrooke burned down.
So, for some miraculous
reason, this survives.
- Right.
- Okay.
There were a lot of tragedies here,
but then good stuff.
Good things coming in waves.
So, it's like good, good, good,
and then [bleep] decimation.
You know, I'm seeing, like, buildings...
I don't know, burning.
The ground goes under, buckling.
It's [bleep] chaos.
Frankly, I don't know
how there's still, like,
a [bleep] town here.
So, you've got a hotel and bar
operating for over 150 years.
I got to think there's
some violence there.
I called the Grass Valley police chief,
and he said some cases come to mind
that will definitely
help my investigation.
So, what were
you able to find out?
Well, the first mysterious
death was a suicide.
And that occurred April 17, 1927.
And the gentleman's name
was John Henry Martin.
He was a wealthy miner and a gambler.
Okay.
Martin was found here dead in
his hotel room at the Holbrooke.
Do we know how this guy killed himself?
Yes, he slashed his own throat.
That's unusual.
Yes. Here's a death certificate.
I've been in the business for 34 years,
and I've never experienced
anyone cutting their own throat.
- I've seen it once.
- Yeah.
Did we have any idea why he did it?
No. But I do have a
suicide note that he left.
In the note, he says he was
being shadowed and followed.
That's strange. So,
it sounds like this guy
might have been
hallucinating about something.
That's what it appears.
Okay. What else you come up with?
The second one was 1909, and it involved
a former bus driver of the
hotel named Cyrus McMath.
- Okay.
- He was downstairs in the bar,
drinking one night and very intoxicated,
and he got into some kind
of beef with the owner.
Frank DeMaine was his name.
He was 76 years old. Here's his picture.
Okay, so this guy's the owner
of the Holbrooke at the time.
Correct.
McMath starts beating DeMaine.
And his son, Louis, is upstairs,
hears about this, comes down,
and tries to protect his father,
and gets in a fight with McMath.
Well, McMath loses,
and he gets pummeled.
Really?
Witnesses report they can't
even identify who McMath is
because the injuries
make him unrecognizable.
Okay, so what happens next?
He's still conscious,
and he's taken home,
but he dies shortly thereafter at home.
I'm seeing, like, another guy.
He's getting his face bashed in.
I'm literally seeing men's boots,
the bottom of their shoes,
coming down on my face.
And that hurts.
And then these two guys picked me up,
and they're dragging me,
'cause I can't even walk.
This is [bleep] up.
This was creepy.
I'm thinking, "Oh [bleep]
They're gonna [bleep] kill me."
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity in your home,
go to the "Dead Files"
page at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help me, Dead
Files" to submit you story,
and we'll help if we can.
So far, I've uncovered
several deaths inside
my client's property
and multiple fires
that devastated the
city of Grass Valley.
But I need to see if
there's anything else.
Searching through old records,
I find an article about an
exotic dancer named Lola Montez.
Turns out she brutally
beat a local newspaper man
inside the hotel.
I'm on my way to meet
with a local author
who said Lola Montez traveled the world,
and wherever she went,
violence followed her.
So, Chris, you mentioned on the phone
this Lola Montez was quite a character.
But let me ask you a question.
Was she from Grass Valley?
She was not.
She was born in Ireland
between 1818 and 1821,
and she was raised in India.
She was quite beautiful
from a very young age.
She becomes this great dancer by
the time she's 17, 18 years old,
and starts to develop what we
know as the spider dance today.
Okay, so, what the
hell is a spider dance?
Part ballet, part interpretive dance,
pretending as though she
was caught in a spider web.
And as she's spun around,
the opportunity to be
able to see some thigh
or maybe the dress coming up a
little bit higher than the thigh
was something that was very real
and the audience thought was risque.
And, certainly, men
would come to see this.
Lola Montez's dance is so titillating
that she gains the attention
of King Ludwig of Bavaria.
He takes her as his mistress.
She takes over pretty much politically
and kind of masterminds
what he should be doing
within the government.
And she's a young kid at this time.
Right. Got a photo here of her.
I mean, she was a stunning lady.
So, how does she end up in Grass Valley?
Well, after a relationship with
the king of Bavaria went bad,
she left Europe and came to America
and traveled around quite extensively,
and ends up in the gold country,
because there's a lot of gold
and a lot of money to be made here.
All right, Chris. So, how does
she wind up at the Holbrooke
giving this guy a beating?
She performs at the Holbrooke.
And Henry Shipley,
who is a newspaperman
here in the gold country...
Okay.
And he has been reprinting articles
that are very bad about Lola Montez.
And so she trots on
down to the Holbrooke
and takes a bull whip out
and gives him four
lashes across the face.
Wow. Okay.
The beating made national news.
All right, so, what
happens to this guy Shipley?
He never does get over being
humiliated by Lola Montez.
He ends up in Sacramento.
He drinks himself to death, literally,
because he downs a whole
bottle of strychnine.
- Okay, so, he commits suicide.
- He does.
So, what happened with Lola?
Lola dies in 1861 in
New York in her late 30s,
and she's impoverished.
I'm seeing the woman who
rules with the iron fist again.
Out there,
she was very overwhelming
in her energy...
like bigger-than-life
kind of person.
It seems she's crying.
Somebody says she was
tormenting herself.
She's a mess.
Obviously, something happened.
There's a male.
Oh, had to put her in her place.
Too big for her britches.
It was because she really
was, like, too powerful.
People really, like, listened to her,
and people respected her.
There's something with
the right of her head.
Man...
Right side...
Yeah, I think these guys
really [bleep] with her, man.
I saw dozens of dead
people during my walk.
But the group harassing
the living in the hallway
had me the most concerned.
There was a man on the left
who was, like, climbing up the wall.
And then there was
some crazy-looking woman
standing in front of the door.
Another guy was charging towards me.
Amy, is this what you saw?
Yes, this is what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our findings
to each other and our
clients for the first time.
Well, Amy, this is a very
special investigation.
This hotel is the heart of the city,
but because of the activity here,
it's in danger of
shutting down for good.
Now, for the past five years,
Ian has owned and run the hotel,
but he can't go on like this.
Terri has worked here for seven years.
She's had a lot of experiences.
The same with Kelly. She's a
local who used to work here,
but she considers the
Holbrooke a home away from home.
So, now that I told Amy
just a little bit about
what's going on with you guys,
I'm gonna ask her to
describe her walk for us.
When I got here,
I was seeing the town
being decimated over
and over and over again,
almost like it came in waves.
And I saw people coming,
and that was good.
Like, people were
excited. They're happy.
It would be built up,
and then it would just
be, like, decimated.
And then there was fire.
The ground was, like,
sinking or something.
Well, it's probably a good time
to give you a little
history about Grass Valley.
In the mid-1800s, this town
was the heart of the gold rush,
and people were coming
from all over the world
looking for fortune.
Now, in 1851,
this place was opened up
as the Golden Gate Saloon.
Now, just four years later,
a huge fire ripped through this town.
The building was burned to the ground.
But when it was rebuilt,
it was rebuilt as the hotel.
Now, in 1860, 1862, 1873,
huge fires leveled this town again...
destroying just about everything.
Okay.
Amazingly, though,
the hotel survived each
of those other times.
1879, a couple named Holbrooke
brought the hotel and
named it after themselves.
Now, I got a picture of it back then.
1896, there was another fire,
and the Holbrooke was
one of the only buildings
- left standing again.
- Hmm.
I didn't know about
all the fire history.
It sounds like this hotel is a survivor,
but there's something here.
When I walked
in, I was overwhelmed.
Obviously, there's a lot of dead here.
Now, I'm on the main floor,
and I went into the long peach hallway.
That was probably not a good place
for living people to be in...
because there are a lot of
dead people in that hallway.
Some of the other dead
have put these different
dead people in there.
The reason why they're
put in that hallway
is because they're mentally unstable.
So, let me get this straight.
The normal dead people
are putting the nutty
dead people in a corner.
- Yes.
- Wow.
Because they're mentally unstable,
the living might have
some experiences there,
like seeing, perhaps,
like, dark shadows,
feeling movement,
possibly feeling touched.
When I was walking through the
hallway, I usually carry a tray.
And the tray was knocked out of my hand.
I had it up like this,
and I felt as if somebody
just pushed it up,
and it just toppled out of my hand.
And that's happened to
me three times, so...
Okay.
And it's always been right
there in that hallway, so...
You know where that hallway leads?
That leads to my office.
There's something
about the feeling there.
When I first took the hotel over,
within 48 hours,
the ceiling collapsed in that office.
That's kind of weird.
And then now I'm wondering
if there's something more going on.
I did a sketch of what I saw.
I mean, it looks like
a scene from a mental ward.
Oh, my!
I can't believe I have
to walk through that
20 times a day.
I can't believe that they
were here when I worked here.
There's times when I feel anxious,
like energy is being sucked out of me.
That makes sense,
because the other thing that I
got was a sense of extreme panic
and feeling overwhelmed with anxiety.
I've been being treated
for anxiety and depression.
Mm.
That's something that can
happen from being here.
I have a huge investment
here, inside of me.
It's a huge investment.
Mm-hmm,
mm-hmm.
That's tough, yeah.
Anything else?
There was some other
weird guy, a dead guy.
His name is Paul.
And one of the places he likes a lot
is the storage area in the kitchen.
I think he might have had
some mental illness, as well.
He'll lash out and touch people.
He'll take things. He'll hide things.
He would like to burn things
and/or has burned things.
And from what you were telling me,
now I'm kind of concerned that
he's a little bit more dangerous
than what I initially
assessed about him.
His main goal is to
get rid of the living.
I mean, the guy she's describing
doesn't match up with anybody
I found in my research,
but a lot of what you're saying
matches up with what
they're experiencing.
At first, I thought it was
just I was kind of losing it.
I mean, honestly, it
doesn't make any sense.
Stuff will go missing all the time.
Now, you said
this guy can get physical.
Terri, tell Amy about
the falls you've taken.
Once was out here in the lobby,
but in the kitchen both other times.
Yeah, I was pretty bruised up.
I still have pain from that fall.
The next thing
that I saw was a female.
And she was in charge here,
and she ran this with,
like, an iron fist.
In life, people listened to her,
and she was very influential.
And men here did not like this.
They wanted to put her in her place.
There were a couple of
men, very specific men,
one Hank and one Gerald,
that really had big issues with her.
There was a lot of pain in her head.
I think that occasionally,
she might look like a fawn apparition.
And she tries to talk to people,
and when she's trying to talk to them,
they'll feel heat, and
they'll get very hot.
So, Kelly, didn't you have
voices trying to talk to you?
At the front desk.
I've heard my name called,
just walking through the
hall, and I hear my name.
And I ask everybody who called
my name, but nobody knows.
- That happens to you, too?
- Quite often.
It may be a shot in the dark,
but a woman did come across
in my research that could
possibly fit the bill,
a woman by the name of Lola Montez.
Now, she was probably one of
the most fascinating characters
I've ever come across in my research.
She was born in Ireland
between 1818 and maybe 1821.
Nobody's really sure.
By the time she was 16,
she was a famous dancer.
She became very famous throughout Europe
and had tons of
high-profile men after her.
She wound up coming here to America
and ended up dancing
here at the Holbrooke.
Now, you mention a guy named Hank.
Well, a guy named Henry
Shipley wrote articles about her
in the local newspaper
that weren't very nice.
She didn't take this too well.
She came right here in
this saloon and whipped him.
- Oh, goodness!
- I got an article here about it.
Now, she caught him four times
across the face with this whip.
Holy
This guy was so embarrassed
by what happened to him
that he eventually committed suicide.
That's how embarrassed he was by it.
Oh, wow! What...
Wow.
I've got a photo of her.
Is it possible that might
be who you might have seen?
Actually, yeah.
I feel very connected to this person.
I don't know.
Maybe that's why this place
is my home away from home.
So, what else?
When I was upstairs,
I encountered a lot
of residual information
and a lot of different dead people.
I went into one room, and I saw a male
trying to strangle a
woman with his bare hands.
And then I saw, unfortunately,
another woman in a room
drinking some morphine.
You know, finally, I just
kind of had to just stop,
because it was just too much.
Living people would go through,
possibly seeing some of the dead
walking through their rooms at night.
Also, people might feel really dizzy.
I was getting that consistently
through the building.
And some people, obviously,
might have physical experiences.
So, Amy, obviously,
we're getting to the
heart of why we're here,
and the problem with the hotel.
The upstairs is obviously
where the guests stay.
Yeah, one gentleman
was in room number 3, laying in his bed,
and he said just, suddenly,
there's a whirlwind...
with all the windows
closed, doors closed.
He came down here. He
was white as a ghost.
He said, "I'm leaving. This
place has got problems."
I spoke to one of the employees
who saw a kid run out of here.
It turned out the kid felt
like he was being massaged
by something on the bed,
which was kind of freaky.
Wow.
This place is pretty damn active.
How would being around all
these dead people in this place
affect somebody like Ian and Terri
that are here all the time?
That exposure over a long period of time
would cause some...
emotional and mental
disorders to develop.
Employees could suffer breakdowns,
and then some physically
could be harmed.
Not good.
You told me you thought this
place destroyed your marriage.
I think it had a big, big hand...
Hmm.
In my breakup of my marriage.
It's changed my personality.
It came down to a point where
I was very short-tempered.
I had a relationship with
someone who worked here,
and...
he changed.
The relationship went to crap.
Does what they're
saying make sense to you?
Yeah.
I've done a lot of hotels.
Maybe 5% are as active as this.
I don't want you to lose your sanity,
and I don't want to lose mine,
but I think that if we
give up on the Holbrooke,
then we'll be giving
up on the entire town.
So, Ian, now we know
why your employees have been
so scared to be here alone.
We know why your guests
have been checking out
in the middle of the night
and why your relationships
are falling apart.
But we still don't know
if you can safely keep
the Holbrooke's doors open.
So, for that answer, I'm
gonna turn it over to Amy.
Sometimes, there are places
that are just
so extremely active
that, literally, it would take
a town of various practitioners
and many years
to completely cleanse
and remove the dead
and the residual energy.
This is one of those places.
And I know it's not really
what y'all want to hear.
It sounds like you're saying
they can't get rid of the dead here.
Frankly, it would take, really, years.
That's not at all what I expected,
to be honest with you.
No. Not at all what I expected to hear.
Here's the thing.
Typically, what ends up happening
to these kinds of places
is that, kind of, the
dead win in the end.
Most of the locations
that have been like this
either end up getting torn down,
or they sit vacant.
They're, like, literally
run out of business.
Yeah, I mean, that's just not an option.
I got to come up with something.
I got to keep this place open.
It actually is kind
of breaking my heart.
She's like another one of my kids.
I have never felt as strong
about a place in my life.
That's horrible.
I mean, I've got to come
up with an option here
to make this place
successful for the town.
If this were my
place, I would leave,
because there's nothing you
can do to make it totally safe.
But if you're really determined to stay,
there are things that you can do
to protect yourselves.
Here's a bag of black salt.
Take some of this,
sprinkle it in approximately
the four corners of the building.
And what that's gonna do is just kind of
build an energetic wall of purity
to keep the dead out.
The other thing is is to utilize stones.
Okay, we have black tourmaline,
and we have selenite.
It protects you
specifically from the dead.
You would carry those stones all day.
Here's the problem.
None of them are long-lasting,
so this would be a daily type of ritual.
So, what are you gonna do?
Well, I'm gonna take
precautions, to start with.
I'm not gonna give up.
My concern is for the living here
who are consistently here
and your mental well-being,
because I've seen people,
you know, undertake tasks like this
and kind of self-destruct.
Instead of the building being torn down,
you might be torn down.
This place being boarded
up would be a travesty.
I'm gonna give it a
good, good try, anyway,
- the old college try.
- Yeah. Good.
I wish I had better news for Ian.
The dead inside this hotel would
literally take years to remove.
But with the precautions I gave him,
Ian will at least have
a fighting chance
of keeping the doors
of his hotel open.