He's agitated.
He's not happy that I'm here.
It gives me crazy vibes
up and down my spine.
He's making the living sick.
To think that whatever's here
is actually picking on you
pisses me off.
I have horrible nightmares.
He is...
an evil lunatic.
This is bad, bad stuff all around.
There's a dark presence.
My name is Amy Allan.
These things, they're freaking out.
They're from hell.
I see dead people.
They were being hunted.
I speak to dead people.
They were setting people on fire,
burning them alive.
And they speak to me.
Her neck got broken.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I hear a gunshot.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Something's not right here.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
It's not safe here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Are any of them buried on the property?
They're all buried here.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end...
I can't do it no more.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Holy [bleep] Look at this.
Or time to get out.
It does not have a happy ending.
Something kills people here.
I'm in Wausau, Wisconsin,
about an hour and a half from Green Bay.
I didn't think long
about taking on this case.
I received a call from a mother of four
who just moved into a new townhouse
and says the entire
family's under attack.
Now, to make things worse,
she has a degenerative eye disease
and now is legally blind.
Her story really touched my heart,
and I hope we can bring
this woman some peace.
Before Amy arrives...
I clear the area of
any leading information...
covering personal items
and removing family photos
that may influence her findings.
When I'm done,
the location will be
ready for tonight's walk.
There's a lot going on around here.
There's a lady...
she's got a really bad vibe to her.
She's claiming to be either Death
or associated with Death.
Ahh, this is a disaster.
There's a jerk,
and he's not happy that I'm here.
He said something about
trying to stab me in the eye
with, like, needles.
So, Beth, when I
spoke to you on the phone,
it was obvious that your problems here
are pretty intense.
Before we even get to that,
I want to talk about
your medical condition.
You're going blind.
Yes, just been slowly going
blind since I was like five.
Can you explain to me what
you're seeing right now?
Do you see me?
The clothes you're wearing are dark,
and I can't see detail.
Okay, and how much
time do you have left?
- Maybe a couple months.
- Wow.
I mean, it breaks my heart.
It's one of the main
reasons I took this case.
How long have you guys been here?
We've only been here
for like four months.
The last two places we
were at got really intense.
It's happened pretty much
everywhere we've lived.
- But now you bought this place?
- Yes.
We can't just up and leave
like we did the last two houses.
Who exactly lives here
in the house with you?
It's me, my fiancé,
Klay, our 4 kids...
- Jeanette, she's 16, Mitchell, he's 14.
- Okay.
Kayleigh's seven, and
then Klayton is six.
Okay, so, why don't you take
me through what's going on?
You can hear stomping,
you'll hear walking
up and down the stairs,
see a lot of dark shadows,
and you'll hear voices.
You feel like you're being watched 24/7,
everywhere you are.
And it's started getting physical now.
And I got to assume this
is frightening the kids.
We all sleep in here.
This is where we all come.
We move the table, and we
make a bed on the floor.
- All you guys?
- Yeah.
Nobody wants to be in their room.
I'm scared to death of my bedroom.
When you guys are all
sleeping down here,
does that make things
better for you guys?
No, not really.
I've started getting
a little bit drained,
feeling more tired than usual.
The kids complain about
stomachaches and headaches.
As the activity intensifies,
so does, like, the health issues.
To think that whatever's here
is actually picking on you
pisses me off...
I mean, to the point where
I want to strangle somebody.
I don't know how you're
as composed as you are.
I just...
learned to keep my
composure very well.
I have to.
I just don't really have a choice.
- I have to do it for the kids.
- Right.
'Cause they're my first concern.
You okay?
I know, honey. I'm sorry.
I know.
You know, you're allowed to
break down once in awhile.
I just don't want my kids to
have to rely on everybody else.
I should be the one
that is able to take care of them
and protect them and...
Yeah, but you can't
do it all by yourself.
"Dire."
"Dire, dire."
Ah, somebody keeps yelling that.
Okay, okay.
Somebody here is affected
by the energy here,
which is making them...
like, disoriented.
They can't...
function properly.
I think that it's making
them feel sick, drained.
Mm.
Very... bad.
You know, Beth, looking around,
you guys obviously haven't
really moved in yet.
We don't use this room, really.
'Cause you guys are downstairs.
Yeah.
Okay, so, what's happening up here
that's scaring you guys off?
You can hear walking around up here
when everyone's sleeping.
Well, you got six people
living in the house.
- Kids sleepwalk or anything like that?
- No.
How often are you hearing that?
Daily. Okay.
Anything else up here?
Shadows, lots of shadows.
I'm not trying to be mean,
but you have this eye problem.
You're seeing shadows
because of your eyes?
No, I don't think so.
Everyone else has seen them.
Death Lady is...
happy.
She seems...
excited and enthusiastic.
She wants me to go upstairs.
Mm.
She tells me that she has a
lot of business in this area.
I'm gonna assume that that means
that a lot of people die
around here very often.
Most people imagine Death
looking like the Grim Reaper,
but it can project
itself any way it wants.
And for some reason,
it's showing itself to me
as a short woman with a wide hat.
Ugh. Geez.
It's hard to breathe.
There's a lot of crying...
hyperventilating.
- The living, you're talking about?
- Yeah, oh, yeah.
Like, freaking out.
This is bad, bad stuff all around.
So, Jeanette,
I was talking to Mom.
She says she relies on you a lot.
I'm the oldest. I'm
like her second eyes.
- How old are you?
- I'm 16.
That's a lot for a
16-year-old to have to take on.
Yeah.
So, what kind of things
are happening to you?
What's going on?
I'm seeing a tall black
figure that looks like a human,
but just black shadow.
And would you say it
was a male or a female?
Male.
Anything face...
could you see any face,
or it was all black?
All black.
You blink, and then it's gone.
Okay, now, where are you seeing it?
I always see it upstairs.
It just happened yesterday.
I was going to sleep,
and I got this feeling of being watched.
And I turned around,
and there's that black figure
standing in front of my door.
So, what happens?
I screamed,
and I ran straight downstairs.
Okay, interesting.
Do you have anything else going on?
Yes, there are times when
I wake up in the morning,
and I'll have these bruises.
They're usually always on my legs.
In fact, I woke up
with one this morning.
Well, that could almost
anything, sweetie.
You might have a deficiency
in a vitamin or something.
- But you don't know how you've done it?
- Yeah.
I don't remember hitting
myself on anything.
Okay, so you're just
waking up like that.
Yes.
How do you even sleep at night?
It's hard to sleep.
And whenever I do fall asleep,
I have horrible nightmares.
Mnh-mnh.
Death Lady a lot in here.
Well, she does come through
the door in the closet.
A creepy guy comes
in here, too...
the one who threatened me outside.
Do you have any idea
if anybody's seen him?
He's pretty [bleep] strong,
so I would assume it's a possibility.
There is a girl...
a teenager, getting choked.
I think maybe he's the
one who's choking her.
And he's influencing this girl,
making bad thoughts in her head
to do things to herself
that are not good.
Death cannot intervene.
It can only watch, wait.
Why is he doing this?
Because he is an evil lunatic.
I understand that you guys
only lived here a few months
and some things have been going on.
Okay. So, Kayleigh, how old are you?
- Seven.
- And, Klayton, how old are you, buddy?
- Six.
Why don't you, Kayleigh,
tell me one thing that's happened
that you can remember?
Upstairs in my bedroom,
someone was looking through the window.
I think it was a man.
Do you know if he was a man like me?
Was he an older man, white man?
He was all black.
How about you, buddy?
Did you ever see anything like that?
I know I saw that down
here in the window.
Which window?
In here.
In the kitchen here?
Can you tell me what he looked like?
Black in color.
Okay, did he frighten you?
He did.
- So, anything else happen to you?
- Mm...
I remember when I was asleep,
and then I was getting poked.
Show me how you got poked.
Let me feel it.
Like that?
Okay, did it wake you up?
You guys like living here?
- Mnh-mnh.
- Not that much.
We only sleep downstairs
'cause we're scared a lot.
Oh, God.
You all right?
I think I might have to leave soon.
What's going on?
The guy...
What is he doing to you?
He keeps, like, touching me and...
making me feel sick.
Is this something he
does to the living, also?
I think that's possible.
Yeah.
I was talking to Beth
about what's going on,
and I tell you, she breaks my heart.
- Strong woman, though.
- Very, very.
You got to be worried
about her, I would think.
I worry about everyone.
I mean, I look at
her, and I want to cry.
Okay. You know, we
bought it, and we want...
I want this to be our home.
Like, this is our final
resting spot for Beth 'cause...
or I say it's gonna be gone.
I mean, I'm worried more
about somebody getting hurt.
Right.
It gives me crazy vibes
up and down my spine.
What about you? Have
you experienced anything?
Yeah.
Sitting down, just
chilling, watching TV,
and I'm just sitting in my chair,
and something just came right past me.
You know, it was tall...
well, probably at least six foot...
kind of, like,
dark-in-the-middle figure
with a light glow around it.
So I got up out of my chair,
and I walked in the
kitchen, and nobody there.
I went into the garage.
And I looked, and nothing.
That was whacked.
It was shortly after my brother died.
And my mother passed,
and then my brother died.
I lost like seven,
eight, nine family members
in like a matter of two years.
I asked the good Lord...
try to stay strong.
When you saw the shadow,
you thought maybe it was
somebody from the family.
The energy down here
is almost like you can grab it.
It's so thick.
The creepy guy from upstairs
likes it down here, too.
And he's being bad.
He's influencing living people here.
He's really good
at making physical connections
with living people.
Yeah, he's not doing good stuff.
He's making the living sick.
He's hurting them.
Mm. Interesting.
He's...
He's very strong.
Very, actually... very, very
[bleep] very [bleep] strong.
You got a problem with people
getting physically touched here,
you know, and keeping
you guys up at night.
You know, it's not good.
There's definitely something.
I'd really like to stay.
I love her to death,
and I'm here for her.
I worry more about them than myself,
'cause they're the ones
that are suffering more.
You know, that's what I'm here for.
We'll do the best we can.
Appreciate it.
Ah, no worries.
You're so welcome.
You'll be all right, trust me.
I started making some calls
and found something surprising.
Beth and Klay's property
used to be part of a large factory.
Apparently, they used to
make fly swatters there.
I'm heading over to
meet with a local author
who said there was nothing funny
about what happened to
the owner of that business.
So, Shawn, you
mentioned on the phone
that factory sitting
on my client's property
at one time made fly swatters.
- Is that right?
- Correct.
What's the story with that?
Well, Arthur Hurd and George Wilson
purchased your client's
property around 1908,
and by 1910, they had
a factory built there.
I have a map here that kind
of shows where the factory was.
It sat right where your
client's house is right now.
This is actually what
the factory looked like.
You said things went bad for these guys.
What happened?
By 1911, Wilson left the company
and left Mr. Hurd by himself
to try to run the place.
All right, so, how's it
go for Hurd at this point?
Well, it was a struggle for him.
He didn't have the expertise
that his partner had,
but he continued to work forward,
and he put his heart
and soul into running it.
And I think it became
pretty stressful on him,
and February 3rd of 1925,
he actually suffered a heart attack
at the site.
In the factory?
Correct.
Here's actually his death certificate.
And he was pretty influential
in the town because,
right on the front page,
they put in his obituary that day.
I saw a very different
structure than this one.
The structure seemed large.
I think it had bricks.
There's a guy...
he's agitated.
He's very high-strung,
and this is his territory,
and he had to, I guess,
fight really hard for it.
This guy is not dealing
with his death very well.
I'm gonna say he died from, like,
a stroke or a heart attack.
After finding out that a factory
used to sit right on
my client's property
and that the owner basically
worked himself to death,
I hit the local library
to see if there was anything else
that could help my investigation.
Turns out, a massive
insane asylum and poor farm
operated for nearly 80 years
right next to Beth
and Klayton's property.
You know, from doing
these investigations,
I know a lot of these poor
farms and mental asylums
mistreated their patients.
So I reached out to a
local newspaper reporter.
He said this place was filled
with neglect, abuse, and death.
So, Keith, the asylum seemed
like it was really close
to my client's original property line.
- Is that right?
- That's right.
And as a matter of fact, you can see it.
It's right over there across the river.
Were you able to find out
when this place was built?
Yeah, it was built in 1893.
It was in operation for about 78 years.
How many people did this house?
It was big. It would've
housed up to about 300 people.
What kind of people would
actually be treated at this place?
There'd been schizophrenics.
There would've been manic-depressives.
There would've been the elderly.
Now, you mentioned on the phone
how bad the conditions were.
What are we talking about?
In the 1950s, the superintendents
came under investigation
by the Marathon County D.A.
for overcrowded conditions,
limited staffing.
There were hundreds of people there.
They only had four bathtubs.
So, when I first contacted you,
I asked you to find out if
there was any unusual deaths
that might help my case.
Were you able to come up with anything?
Yeah, I found five interesting deaths.
The first one was in 1895,
when an inmate hung himself.
In 1899, three men were asphyxiated
while working in a silo on the farm.
In 1903, a 37-year-old inmate
was stabbed to death by
an 85-year-old inmate.
What was it over?
I guess it was over living quarters.
Couple more.
In 1920, a man named
John Kyough told nurses
that he was gonna go
fishing down on the river.
He had a wooden leg.
He removed it, tied
an anchor to his waist,
threw himself in the river.
You said there was
five. What was the fifth?
Yeah, there was one more inmate suicide.
This one happened in 1933.
He laid down on a stick of dynamite
and blew himself up.
That's a lot of death.
These are the ones we know about.
There certainly would've had
to been a lot more deaths.
Nurses reported that they didn't
even bother keeping records,
'cause once people were brought in,
they just expected them to be
there forever till they died.
Okay.
I hear a male, and he said,
"We are lost and need help out of here."
And he said,
"We can't see to find our way out."
There's about 11 of them.
They can't even see each other.
I asked how did he die?
He said, "A death camp."
One other thing got my
attention during my research.
There was a brutal murder about
1,200 feet from Beth's house.
The victim was a young woman
heading home from church.
Now, look, it may be a long shot,
but I'm heading over to
meet with a Wausau detective
who said it was one of
the most notorious crimes
in the city's history.
So, Greg, I came across this homicide
that happened pretty close
to my client's property.
What do you know about it?
Murder happened on April 18, 1966.
This is our victim...
Mary Holzem, 26 years old.
This is the guy
that killed her...
Eugene Schopf, 29 years old.
All right, so, how's
the homicide go down?
Mary, she was walking home from church.
Eugene Schopf here, he
picks her up in a vehicle.
They go down to a bar, and
they have a couple of drinks,
and then they leave
together in a vehicle.
And that's the last anybody sees of her.
So, what happens after that?
He was somewhat infatuated
with her and came on to her.
She resisted, and he
stabbed her three times.
She screamed...
and then he cut her throat.
Oof.
This is a copy of Mary
Holzem's death certificate.
"Male subject apparently seduced victim
to a secluded spot for his act."
So, Greg, the actual
location of the homicide,
how far is that from
my client's location?
That was about a quarter of a mile.
Okay, so, now, from the article,
I understand he was caught.
How'd they wind up getting him?
Police received a call
at about 10:45 that night
that there was screaming
coming from an area
just two blocks down from that bar.
Police officers go over to the bar,
talk to the bartender.
Bartender tells them,
"Yep, Mary was in here,
and she was with a guy by
the name of Gene Schopf.
So they knew the guy.
They knew the guy.
They go down to his house.
They look at the vehicle,
they find blood in the trunk,
they find bloody
clothes in the back seat.
Gene confesses to killing her.
That's his booking photo from the 19th,
- the day after she was killed.
- Okay.
He was charged with
first-degree murder.
Wow.
Ah, there's a man and a woman,
and the man is the creepy guy.
They're both dead, and...
It's bad. It's so bad. It's so bad.
They knew each other
when they were alive.
And she's always...
trying to get away from him...
still.
Mm. Mnh-mnh.
Her heart's racing,
'cause she's got to get away.
And she's...
very stressed-out.
I think that the woman died here.
I saw knives...
somebody messing with knives.
Okay, so, what happens at the trial?
He goes to court and pleads "not
guilty by reason of insanity."
It's a pretty brutal crime.
Is there any indication
he's done this before?
It came out that, in 1954,
he had asked military doctors for help
because he had thoughts
of slicing the throats of animals
and he thought he might hurt a woman.
- He asked for help.
- He did.
Obviously, he didn't get it,
'cause this guy's got the
markings of a serial killer...
especially with the animals.
Yeah.
In July of 1966,
he was found "not guilty
by reason of insanity."
He was committed to a
state mental institution
in Waupun, Wisconsin.
In the early '70s, he was released.
That son of a [bleep]
Can't believe they let this guy out.
What happened after he was released?
Last information we have
is he moves to Alabama
and dies in 2002 at age 65.
This creepy guy,
he didn't die a long time ago.
I don't think he's that old,
maybe in his early 50s,
and he does not like animals.
And children are pests.
Woman are pests... bad,
evil, evil creatures.
They're evil creatures.
He is very mentally ill.
Mm.
I see 5 and a 4, 54,
so...
something like that.
He is evil,
and he wants
nothing good for anybody.
I saw several dead
people during my walk,
but two stood out the most...
first, the creepy man
choking a living teenager
in the house.
He has, like, a huge rope...
and he's strangling the kid with it.
Over on the side, in
front of this big closet,
is this woman who is really Death,
and she's watching this
situation happening.
Next, I describe how
Death showed herself to me.
She had a... hat on,
and it was black.
She had very large eyes,
and she was wearing,
like, a fur-collar thing,
and it was black.
Is this who you saw?
Yes, that's who I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients for the first time.
So, Amy, when I decided that
we should take on this case,
I knew it was gonna be emotional,
but I didn't realize how emotional.
This is Beth.
She's one of the strongest
women I've ever met.
And this is her very
supportive fiancé, Klay.
Now, on top of dealing with a
really bad paranormal problem
that they have here,
Beth has a disease that's
gonna leave her blind
within the next three to four months.
She called us in
because she's desperate to make sure
that their four kids are okay
before she goes completely blind.
So, now that Amy knows a little
bit about your background,
I'm gonna ask her to
describe her walk for us.
Honestly, I was not looking forward
to walking through the door,
but I did, and as
soon as I came in here,
I was hearing somebody yelling,
"Dire, dire, dire!"
Somebody here
is affected by the energy here,
which is making them...
like, disoriented.
Then...
I went upstairs,
and I was so sick up there.
I felt so drained and horrible.
I get a lot of headaches.
I'm just tired.
I don't want to do anything.
I just have, like, absolutely no
"get up and go."
Klay, don't the kids
have stomachaches a lot?
Oh, yeah, they get stomach, headache,
and you can tell they're not themselves.
Now, one thing you
should know about Beth
is that she felt this
way in her last place.
Yeah, the last place...
actually, the last two places.
It started out little things,
and then it just intensifies
to the point where it gets...
like, physical.
I just wish there was
something I could do to stop it.
You okay, honey?
- Sorry.
- No.
I don't give a [bleep]
about the cameras, okay?
If you need to take
a break, you tell me.
I just have a hard time
talking about those places.
It's okay. That's why we're here.
In those houses, there
was lots of shadows,
and I would see them
reach out for the kids.
I just feel like I'm
going nuts or something.
It's crazy.
And had that kind of stuff
happened throughout your life?
Yeah.
I've had issues as
long as I can remember.
There are two main entities
that are in this house,
and they're the ones
that I'm most concerned about.
The first was the female.
She explained to me that she is Death.
The other interesting thing
is that she interacts
directly with the living.
She was very excited
for me to go upstairs
and see what was going on up there.
She was actually waiting
at the top of the staircase,
like, smiling.
And I think she causes
a lot of the living stress.
People may see her as a silhouette.
She wears a hat,
and people may see that.
But she did say,
"I can project myself
any which way I want."
We see shadows, and, like,
I've referred to them
as silhouettes before.
You saw a shadow in the kitchen, right?
Oh, yeah. Right here, as we sit.
It just gave me the heebie-jeebies.
I'm like, "Wow, that was whacked."
You know, Klay, I
hate to bring it up...
I know you're in a
bad spot right now...
but when you mentioned Death,
you lost how many people
in the last year or so?
Brother.
Mother.
Aunt.
Uncle.
Cousin.
Sorry.
No, don't be.
He's had a lot of loss
in a very short time.
Now, do you have any idea
what the woman looked like?
I had a sketch of her done.
Here, take a look at this.
Not what I'd expect her to look like,
but her eyes look like Death.
I don't like her eyes.
Yeah, I do. I didn't
want to bring it up.
When I first saw the sketch,
it did remind me of
his mom a little bit.
Wow.
This is a picture of his mom.
Wow. Ohh.
I do not think that it was
done in a malicious manner.
I think that this is Death
acknowledging what's happened
by taking on a familiar... guise.
So you didn't run into his mom.
No.
So this is Death projecting
itself as Klay's mom.
Yeah.
I then encountered a male,
and this guy is no good.
He was a very bad
person when he was alive.
He's still a very bad person.
My opinion of this guy
is that he's an evil lunatic.
I ran into him initially in the kitchen.
He was chasing a female.
This carried over from
when they were alive.
She experienced her death
in the heart or chest area.
I was shown knives.
He was very mentally
ill when he was alive.
He's still extremely mentally ill.
The only clear thing that I got from him
was that he hates animals
and that women are evil creatures.
And then I did get two
numbers... five and four.
They were extremely
important...
possibly 54.
Now, a lot of things you just said
make me think of a
murder that took place
nearly 50 years ago, right
here in the neighborhood.
On April 18, 1966,
there was a girl
walking home from church.
Her name was Mary Holzem.
She was 26 years old.
Now, it's raining.
This guy Eugene Schopf
pulls up and says,
"Let me give you a ride."
I have his booking photo right here.
He made an advance on her.
She rejects it.
He flips out,
stabs her several times in
the chest and the stomach,
slits her throat from ear to ear...
and then winds up taking her body,
sticking it in the trunk,
and driving her to a remote
area about seven miles from here.
I got the death certificate here.
This will give you an
idea of the damages on her.
You mention you picked up
on a 5 and 4, or maybe a 54,
which kind of blew me away a little bit.
In 1954, when he was in the army,
he asked for psychiatric help.
He told them that he had
slashed the throats of animals
and that he thought
he wanted to do that to a woman one day.
Instead of serving prison time,
this sick bastard wound up
going to a mental hospital
for 10 years.
He gets released.
2002, he dies in
Alabama at the age of 65.
Is it possible this is your guy?
I mean, a lot of things
match, for sure, for sure.
Is it possible that he's
following Beth by any chance,
since she's having these
problems wherever she goes?
I mean, it could be that
he's, you know, attracted here
because you have abilities.
If he was alive today, I'd kick
him right in his friggin' [bleep]
How is this [bleep] affecting
everybody in the house?
I do think that he can
physically attack the living.
I think that people could see him.
He's just pure evil,
and he just wants to torment people.
My oldest daughter, Jeanette,
she'll wake up with brand-new bruises.
She woke up one morning with...
it looked almost like a burn
above her eye.
So, I had a sketch done
of what I saw
a living female experiencing.
What a piece of [bleep]
Mother Mary of God.
Here, baby, I can brighten it up.
That's crazy.
Well, it ain't funny.
- I'm sorry.
- No, don't be.
Mnh-mnh.
Amy, what do you think
may be going on here?
What I understand is going on
is that this crazy, evil man
is focused on your daughter.
He is trying to influence her, as well,
her thoughts,
and influencing her
to do possibly bad things to herself.
I'm concerned because...
Death is there
and is watching and waiting.
I mean, I think that his intentions
are the same intentions
he had when he was alive.
Do bodily harm.
Yes.
He likes to torture, you know?
And obviously, he likes to kill people.
Well, Beth, Klay, at least now we know
what's causing all the
problems in your family.
And I know you two guys are fighters,
but we need to find out
how to kick this
[bleep] out of the house
so you can live here
with your kids peacefully,
the way you guys deserve.
I'll turn it over to Amy,
and she'll have an idea of
what we can do about this.
What I would like
is to get a really big,
bad, scary male medium
to come in
and basically kick his ass out
and to then set up
a very firm barrier around your property
to keep the dead out of here.
Let's just block those suckers out.
So, I think I already know
the answer to this question,
but why such a big, burly, tough medium?
This crazy lunatic tries
to prey on the weak,
and he is an abuser,
and I think that he's
quite afraid of men.
It'll be very intimidating
and frightening for him.
Good.
So, now, what happens with Death?
My perception is that,
once that guy's out of here...
Death probably won't
be hanging around anymore.
That's the first time
I've seen you two smile
the entire night.
Hmm.
I mean, this is good news, I think.
I'm hoping.
How you feeling, Beth?
Still a little in shock,
but what Amy found...
hopeful that,
by doing what she's suggesting,
that things will get better.
You guys got a lot of
love going on here...
so that helps.
Thank you guys very much.
So much.