Something happened. Bam, bam, bam.
I felt hands push on my back.
And I just kept
flippin' down the stairs.
I think he's [bleep] with
people's heads really bad.
It was a deep, animalistic
growl, like...
It's just gonna happen
again and again and again.
I don't know if we are just crazy.
He's like, "You think you can stop me?
Because you can't."
He is bent on revenge.
There's a dark presence.
My name is Amy Allan.
These things, they're freaking out.
They're from hell.
I see dead people.
They were being hunted.
I speak to dead people.
They were setting people on fire,
burning them alive.
And they speak to me.
Her neck got broken.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I hear a gunshot.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Something's not right here.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
It's not safe here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Are any of them buried on the property?
They're all buried here.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end...
I can't do it no more.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Holy [bleep] Look at this.
Or time to get out.
It does not have a happy ending.
Something kills people here.
I'm in the small town of
Sicily Island, Louisiana.
It's about two hours
north of Baton Rouge.
I got a call from a woman
who sounded real bad,
and I mean terrible.
She says whatever's in her house
is goin' after her
children and her grandchild.
She told me, if we can't help her,
someone's gonna get hurt.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area of
any leading information,
covering anything that
might reveal to Amy
who lives in the house.
When I'm done,
the location will be
ready for tonight's walk.
There's a lot of men.
They're, like forming a big circle.
But they're, like,
very active over there.
I don't like it.
There are a lot of these men.
How many would you say?
I would say like 100.
They go all the way
around in the circle,
all the way around.
They're surrounding the place.
Well, when I
talked to you on the phone,
you sounded really upset.
I'm at wits' end.
We bought this place
a couple of years ago.
This is goin' to be our retirement home,
the dream home I always wanted.
Two or three months in, you know,
then, things started changing.
The family is at each other's throats.
My husband and I have
been together since 1987.
We've never argued, never had a fight.
We were always known
as the happy family.
Now I've had fantasies
that I want everybody gone.
It's gotten to the point where
we're on the verge of divorce
because we don't even
like to look at each other
without feeling some kind of resentment,
and we don't know why.
All right.
So who exactly lives
in the house with you?
We have my husband, Johnny, myself.
Then, we have Chelsea, who is 22.
Okay.
And then Jonathan, who is 26,
and then my youngest daughter, Brittany,
who's 19, and then the grandbaby,
who just turned a year old in February.
Give me a list of what
everybody's going through.
Footsteps, shadows,
apparitions, things moving.
It's starting to get violent.
Pat, it gets me concerned
when you say "violent."
What are we talkin' about?
I've had a daughter
pushed down the stairs.
I've had one pinned up against her wall.
Oh, geez.
What are you hoping we can do
for you now that we're here?
We trust you guys, and we're
really hoping and praying
that you can give us some answers,
help us find out what
we're dealing with.
But they definitely see them,
and they do see them like shadow people.
They can be physical and very direct.
They can completely
interact with the living,
and they can absolutely affect them.
This place is all about revenge.
Mm.
Different people want revenge.
What do they want to do?
They would like to
murder and torture people.
Okay. So what's going on in here?
It's a lot of activity
that goes on in here.
So I haven't slept in a year and a half.
Okay, so what are we talkin' about?
What kind of activity?
- I've heard some growling.
- What did it sound like?
It was a deep, throaty,
animalistic growl, like...
What about animals, stray animals,
do a growling noise like that?
No, no. There is no stray
animals that run around.
And then, I've seen shadow people
in the corner of the room.
Okay. Describe 'em to me.
It's a group of five or six,
I would say, just standing there.
I mean, you got a big window here.
Could it possibly be
people from outside?
I don't see how.
Not at night.
Oh, I just saw this huge [bleep] thing.
He, like, bent down,
and then, he stood up.
And he was, like, enormous.
How tall would you say?
As tall as the ceiling.
Is he related to the ones outside?
Yes. He just He comes in.
Then, he's just stare...
you know, standing there.
Do you think people have seen him?
Yes.
It was a vision from
the person in the bed.
I was talking to your wife, Pat,
and she's pretty upset.
She thinks that
whatever's happening here
is tearing the family apart.
I believe so, yeah.
She said to me, you know,
she fantasizes about
being alone in the house.
Right.
I mean, does that sound like Pat to you?
Ordinarily, no. Since
we've been here, yes.
I get the feeling that she
would be okay with me leavin'.
So you think she's allowing the house
to come between you guys?
Yep. She's obsessed with it.
To me, there's nothin'
more important than family.
I mean, I could care
less about this house.
Now, what about yourself?
Have you ever experienced
anything in the house?
Yeah.
I've seen the silhouette of a man
at the top of the stairs.
It was, uh, a dark figure.
And it looked like he had a beard.
Okay. Anything else?
I've heard things
fall, uh, or...
or being thrown,
like maybe somebody
dropped a book on carpet.
How often are you hearing these sounds?
I've just heard 'em a few times,
but everyone else tells me
they hear 'em all the time.
What do you think's in this house?
I haven't got an idea, but if it's evil,
then it's got to be some
kind of demonic figure.
If it's somethin' bad,
I'm... I'm not gonna stay.
I just saw another shadow
person in the hallway.
It was right here.
And then, it crawled up
the back of the stairs.
And then, it popped through this stair.
But it makes a lot of
noise, a lot of ruckus.
It would be, like, a lot
of crashing and banging.
And I think they might hear, like,
the grunting and the growling.
It was angry that we
came into its space.
When I was talkin' to
your mom, she mentioned that
her and your dad were
talking about divorce.
That started about a month or two
after we moved into this house.
Honestly, I don't like it.
I feel like the house is
just tearing us all apart.
All right, now, she's
concerned about your son.
Think she has a reason to be concerned?
I do.
And why do you say that?
Um, I was about six to
seven months pregnant,
and I was comin' out of the bathroom.
And I felt hands push on my back.
And I just kept
flippin' down the stairs.
I mean, that's some
friggin' fall you took.
So how bad you get hurt?
Scrapes and bruises.
They did suspect
that I was going into premature labor.
But they were able to slow it down.
Okay.
- You got lucky on that one.
- Oh, yeah.
Seen people fall less than that
and break their neck and died.
I feel like something was
intentionally trying
to make me lose my son.
I'm seeing this... old man.
He's pissed.
There's a lot of anger here,
a lot of tension...
'Cause he is bent on revenge.
So a woman died up here.
Way in her death state.
She's puking.
She's really sick.
Now I'm feeling pain.
Ugh.
It literally feels like
I'm being stabbed to death.
The old man's like, "Oh. Ha-ha.
You think you can stop me?
Because you can't."
He's like, "And it's
just gonna happen again
and again and again and again."
What is?
Women gettin' killed.
Seems like everybody in the
house is having experiences.
What about you?
I would wake up sometimes
to feel like someone's
hand was on my neck.
Kind of just woke me up
like I was gasping for air.
How many times has this happened to you?
It has happened at least a dozen times.
Okay. So has anything else happened?
Three times, on separate occasions
since I've lived here in the
two years, I would wake up,
and there'd be open razor blades
sitting where I was sleeping.
I mean, are you [bleep] with me?
Or are you tellin' me
the truth about this?
I'm tellin' you the truth.
So basically, what you're tellin' me is
every night you go
to bed, you don't know
if you're gonna get choked,
woken up by razor blades?
Do you have any idea
how [bleep] this sounds?
Yeah.
I don't know if it's the house
or if we are just crazy.
I don't really
like it in here, either.
This dead guy is the
main [bleep] problem.
I think he can cause hallucinations.
I think he can [bleep]
people's heads really bad.
He can cause physical
pain, um, to the living.
He's very creepy.
He can cause, like, stabbing pain,
cutting pain, burning
pain, um, choking pain,
um, things like that.
I was talkin' to mom
about some of the bizarre
stuff goin' on here.
Now, she thinks that whatever's here
is tearing the family apart.
Do you agree with that?
We used to be a pretty
close, tight-knit family.
We just kind of barely can
stand the sight of each other.
As far as your experiences,
you've had some, I understand.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
Why don't you tell me about one of 'em?
I woke up one night, um,
in a really odd position.
I was, uh, up my wall.
And my feet were kind of dangling.
So you're basically
pinned on the ceiling?
Mm-hmm.
That's something out of a movie.
You sure you didn't dream that?
I'm positive.
I fell down onto the bed.
All right. What else has happened?
I was actually having, um,
a pretty strange nightmare,
which is what woke me up.
I was being pinned down by a woman.
Um, and she had her hands
over my mouth and my nose.
So, Chelsea, if you saw this woman again
in a sketch or a photo
or somethin' like that,
would you recognize her?
Actually, a year after I had the dream
that my mom was doin'
some research on the house
and came across a photo
of Nettie Fairbanks.
Okay.
And, um...
it was the woman from my nightmares.
- This person lived here?
- Yes.
A lot of the old man's anger, like,
just fills every nook
and cranny in here.
He just comes in, and it's
like just all this rage.
I think that there's a living person.
Um, he's, like, stomping her down.
Like, he's stomping her down.
And because of the
hallucinations and stuff,
I don't think there's a
lot of sleep to be had.
He gets in there, and he's,
like, pullin' stuff out,
like, nasty [bleep].
And, like, making these weird
hallucinations around it.
He does not want them here.
And I think that he
is trying to figure out how exactly
to get rid of them.
He's a mean [bleep].
Chelsea thinks that some woman
named Nettie Fairbanks
is haunting her house.
Now, when clients do their own research,
I take it with a grain of salt,
but I reached out to a
state historian who says
that woman really did live in the house
and that her time there was
filled with nothing but tragedy.
So, Charlotte,
it's true that Nettie Fairbanks lived in
my clients' property and in the house.
Yes, that's true.
Okay. So what do we know about her?
Well, in 1892,
Henry Fairbanks actually
bought the property.
He fell in love with Henrietta Blackman,
who he called Nettie.
And I have a photo of her for you.
Okay, so this is good news
because my client said
she saw this woman.
Now, did she and Henry have any kids?
Yes. They have three children.
Two boys, Russell and Thomas,
and a little girl named Henrietta.
Now, Charlotte, you
mentioned on the phone
that this woman in the
family had a life of tragedy.
What'd you mean?
Well, in 1899, the night
that Henrietta was born,
Henry had a terrible accident.
- Okay.
- He was out celebrating.
And he decided to
ride home on his horse.
He was stinking, fall-down drunk.
And he fell in a water-filled ditch.
This would seem harmless,
but he actually caught pneumonia
from the dirty water he fell into,
and he died three days later.
Oh, you're kiddin' me.
The following year, in 1900,
her baby boy, Thomas, dies.
He was three years old at the time.
Okay. Do we know how Thomas died?
There are no details how he died.
Okay, so, now her husband's
dead, her kid's dead.
Does she stay on the property?
She did stay after that.
In 1901, she actually marries again.
This time, she marries
a traveling dentist,
Dr. Henry Joseph Disch.
And that is his photo.
I mean, do things go well?
She live happily ever after?
What happens?
Actually, no. As it turns out,
Nettie's daughter was
born with epilepsy.
Here's a photo of Henrietta.
She suffered from severe seizures.
She became difficult to handle.
So when she was 22 years
old, she was sent away
to the Louisiana State
Hospital for the Insane.
In 1922, at the age of 23,
Henrietta dies in the hospital.
According to her death
record, she died of epilepsy.
Okay.
Nettie remains on the
property another 10 years.
Okay.
She becomes weak and
suffers from an illness
that eventually leads
to a cerebral hemorrhage.
Here's her death certificate.
Okay.
She dies in 1932 at the age of 58.
Does she die on the property?
She actually dies at her son's home.
But according to descendants,
her body was brought back
to her home for the wake.
Okay. That's interesting.
Some of these... Like, there
was a lot of death here.
There were, like, three or four deaths.
Something happened. Bam, bam, bam.
But they had, like,
some kind of private,
like, uh, ceremonies here or something.
It's all in embarrassment.
They're talking about
this sister in particular.
And everybody's, like,
talking like this.
"Uh, we have to do something
because it's just awful.
It's just too embarrassing."
Yeah. I don't even know
who's dead because, honestly,
it's like, they're just, like,
literally shoved in a corner.
So you can't see the actual body?
No.
I want to say it's a male and a female.
I think the male is the old man
causing all the problems here.
Ah.
All right.
So who's on the property at this point?
After Nettie, her
son, Russell Fairbanks,
moved onto the property.
This is a photo of Russell.
Okay. What's his story?
Well, actually, he was a
well-known, prominent man
in the community.
He had followed in his
stepfather's footsteps
and become a dentist.
Well, in 1971, Russell
suffers his own tragic death.
He decides to take a fishing trip
one mile from his
home, on Lake Lovelace.
Okay. So what happens at the lake?
Well, no one knows why,
but for some reason, he fell overboard.
He drowned.
Here's a newspaper article.
He was 75 at the time.
He was a rugged man's man.
And there's really no indication
of why he fell overboard.
It's a mystery.
That's interesting.
This guy
causing all the problems,
do you know how old he was when he died?
Late 60s, early 70s.
He lived here then, you think?
I believe he did.
Like, I think he died with
his shirt off or something.
Like, he walks around without a shirt.
He had a lot of money.
And I think people
really [bleep] respected
the [bleep] out of him.
He's just, like, raving.
Like, he's like a [bleep]
lunatic about this woman.
"[Bleep] hate her,
and she's gonna eat it.
She's gonna [bleep] eat it."
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity in your home,
go to the "Dead Files"
page at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help Me, Dead
Files!" to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
So far, I've got
a family being torn apart
by unexplained activity on a property
that's seen one tragic
death after another.
But I want to see if
there's anything else
that might help my investigation.
Searching through old records,
I find a man named William Ditto.
Turns out he used to run a plantation
right on my clients' property.
So I've asked a local
genealogist to meet me here.
He says William Ditto got destroyed
defending the Confederate cause.
In the 1860s,
William Lego Ditto owned
your clients' property.
He was a lawyer and a slave owner.
This guy was pretty
wealthy, I would assume.
He was a very, very wealthy man.
He was worth $120,000 at that time,
which was a lot of money.
How many slaves did Ditto have?
According to the 1860
census, he had 72 slaves.
Okay. So that's a lot, right?
That's a lot of slaves, yes.
Slaves had very few rights.
It was illegal to teach your
slaves to read and write.
A slave owner could beat 'em.
Ohh.
That's pretty brutal.
Even for a homicide detective,
this makes me squeamish
just lookin' at this.
Would I assume correctly that slaves
would have been buried on the property?
Yes, 'cause in this country
We're so warm and all...
you had to bury a person quickly.
Okay. Now, this guy, Ditto,
you mentioned that he
was a staunch Confederate.
Yes, he helped form a cavalry unit.
He went and fought, I
believe it was in Kentucky.
- Okay.
- And he was captured.
He was prisoner of war for
about a year and a half.
He was released from that the same day
that Lee signed the treaty
for the end of the war.
Okay. So this guy was a POW.
- Right.
- What happens?
He comes home. All the slaves are gone.
If he had Confederate
money, it was worth nothing.
All he had was the value of the land.
So this guy basically went
off to fight in the war,
came home, he lost everything.
He lost everything.
He ended up
having to sell your
clients' property in 1868.
Okay.
And he moves to Florida.
Not surprised to find that
there was slaves on the property,
but my clients had no idea.
Those slaves were not the
only slaves in Sicily Island.
The Native Americans there
had slaves and were slaves.
And you might want to look into that.
Okay. Interesting.
I'm trying to understand
who these shadow men are.
I think they were human before.
Do you have any idea when this was?
I get, like, a 1798
and then an 1843.
Okay.
I'm definitely hearing
about bad, bad deaths.
I think they're all buried nearby.
And they're just bent on revenge.
Do you have any idea what
they want revenge for?
How they were treated, like animals.
They had to walk a lot.
Their feet were bloody.
And I do see chains.
They don't want to go anywhere
because they want their revenge.
You know, I
placed a couple calls,
and Dave's lead checked out.
The Native Americans in Sicily Island
were sold off into slavery.
I'm heading over to
meet with a local author
who wants to show me the exact spot
where the Natchez tribe was wiped out.
We're really close to the
spot where the Natchez Indians
made their last stand against the French
in early 1731.
So I know we're only a couple of
miles from my clients' property,
so this is important then.
So what can you tell me about the tribe?
To give you an idea of
what they looked like,
this is a modern representation.
So I know you mentioned
that they were wiped out.
How'd that all happen?
In January of 1731,
the French brought in
cannons, brought in mortars.
And after pounding the place
with things like...
this...
the vast majority of them are
taken prisoner by the French.
They're taken down the
Mississippi to New Orleans
and shipped off to Santo Domingo
and probably end up
being worked to death in
sugar cane fields there.
So that's it.
There's no more...
There's no Natchez Nation after that.
Okay.
I saw dozens of dead
people during my walk.
But two have me the most concerned.
First, the leader of the shadow men.
I was in a bedroom. There
was a person in the bed.
And there was this huge figure
coming in from the other room.
Next, I describe the old
man terrorizing the living.
He's white.
He had jowls, kind of wrinkled.
And he had deep-set eyes,
like, kind of grumpy-looking.
Is this who you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients for the first time.
So, Amy, I'd like you to meet Pat.
And this is her husband, Johnny.
Now, they bought this
fixer-upper about two years ago.
They hoped to turn it into
their dream retirement home,
and it's been anything but.
Chelsea is one of their three
grown children that live here.
I got a photo of the other kids.
This is Jonathan, and this is
Brittany, who also has a baby.
Now, everyone here agrees
there's something weird
going on, and I mean weird.
But Pat doesn't want to leave.
On the other hand,
if Johnny doesn't like
what he hears tonight,
he's ready to pack up and leave.
So now that Amy knows a little
bit about what's goin' on,
I'm gonna ask her to
describe her walk for us.
One of the most disturbing
things that I encountered
was actually outside.
I saw about 100 shadow men.
They were surrounding the house.
Wow.
These shadow people
are extremely solid, and I felt like
they could affect and
influence people in the area.
And I do feel like
they're capable of physical
contact with the living.
Well, pretty much
everybody in the house
has seen shadow figures.
- Yeah.
I've seen it twice.
In the corner of my bedroom,
they were all standing
shoulder to shoulder,
some in the backs, tall,
short, varying heights.
I call them watchers.
That's what they
were doing...
just standing there,
observing and watching.
Well, when I was in the master bedroom,
I was seeing a situation
that took place,
but I was seeing it through the eyes
of the person who was laying in the bed.
He, like, bent down,
and then, he stood up,
and he was, like, enormous.
How tall would you say?
As tall as the ceiling.
I did do a sketch.
Oh, geez.
Take a look at that.
This is what I see.
It's definitely unnerving.
I don't need anybody watchin' me sleep.
These shadow
things, what are they?
Were they ever alive? What's the story?
Yes, they were all
alive at one point in time.
What I believe is that these people
are from several different time periods.
I did see men being beaten,
being treated like animals.
A group of them had
walked a long distance.
And their feet were bleeding.
I saw some that were
chained and starving.
I saw some dying.
The one consistent element
with all of these men,
mainly, um, is revenge.
They want revenge for how they all died.
Wow.
I think a large percentage
of them are buried nearby.
Hmm.
And I got two
specific dates...
1798 and 1843.
Now, we're in the Deep
South, so it's no surprise
that this place used to be
a plantation at one time.
Now, back in 1860,
your property was owned by a
guy named William Lego Ditto.
Actually got a photo of him.
Oh.
That reminds me of the
silhouette that I saw.
Couldn't make out any
real detail like this.
But now that I see the picture
with the beard, the shape,
it's a lot like what I was seein'.
Interesting.
He owned 72 slaves who worked the land.
Now, we all know
the conditions of slaves
and how inhumane it was.
This is a picture.
- Oh, my God.
This is as it healed.
The expert I talked to
said, more than likely,
you have a lot of buried slaves here
in unmarked graves.
Now, this guy, Ditto,
was a staunch Confederate.
And he actually formed
his own regiment right here
and went off to fight the war.
Now, he wound up becomin' a POW.
Came back here to nothing.
Slaves were gone. Place was in ruins.
Not only did he lose the
war, he lost everything.
Now, here's the other surprising thing
that I came up with during the research.
There's another group of people
that lived on the land also
that became slaves.
This area was once occupied,
in the 1700s, by the Native Americans.
They're called the Natchez tribe.
I got an artist's rendition of
what they might've looked like.
In 1731, they got
wiped out by the French.
Now, most of the tribe's
people were killed.
- But 200 were taken prisoner.
- Mm.
They were put in chains
and walked to New Orleans.
Oh, my gosh.
Where they were basically
sold into slavery.
And they were sent to
the Dominican Republic,
where they worked in sugar canes.
The tribe was annihilated.
You think these shadow people may be
the slaves and the
Indians gettin' together?
Yeah. Totally makes sense.
- Inhumane.
- It is.
No excuse.
And I don't blame 'em
for wanting revenge.
We're desecrating their resting place.
So what else did you see?
I went to the back
room behind the stairs.
And I heard someone say
there was a lot of death here.
And then, I got bam, bam, bam.
And I heard three to four deaths.
And then, I was seeing wakes
or funerals taking place.
I heard people talking in hushed tones.
I actually did overhear someone
talking about how embarrassing,
uh, about the sister
and that she was kind of
messed up or something.
And I was seeing two
bodies in the corner.
One was male, and one was female.
The male was elderly.
And then, when I walked up the stairs,
I ran into a woman who
was in her death state.
And it was an extremely painful death.
She wasn't able to catch her breath.
And I suddenly felt like I
was being stabbed to death
all through my stomach area.
You okay, honey?
Just started a few days ago
where I couldn't catch my breath.
And there was this... this
sharp pain in my chest.
And I've had that stabbing pain
in my side and my
stomach for months now.
I'm assuming that's what
she's feeling, Amy, or...
More than likely, yeah.
This is what we know for sure.
There was a woman whose wake
was held here in the house.
She did die a very painful death.
Her name was Nettie Fairbanks.
And she moved into the house in 1894,
when it was first built.
I actually have a photograph of her.
This is Nettie.
Her time here was pretty miserable.
In 1899, her husband got drunk,
fell off his horse into some water,
and wound up gettin' pneumonia
and died three days later.
Mm.
In 1900, her
three-year-old son died.
We don't know what the causes are.
She gets remarried to
this traveling dentist.
Now, I tracked down a family portrait.
This is her daughter, Henrietta.
You mentioned somethin' about
an embarrassment or something like that.
Whoa, yeah.
Okay. Now, Henrietta had epilepsy.
Her family couldn't handle it.
So she was sent to an insane asylum.
Oh, wow.
Henrietta spent less than
a year in that insane asylum
before she died at the age of 23.
Nettie's second husband
died a couple years later...
- Geez.
- 1924.
Now, Nettie stayed in the
house for about 10 years
before getting very sick.
In 1932, she died of
a cerebral hemorrhage.
And her wake was actually
held right here, in the house.
Wow.
Chelsea, you think
she's haunting the house.
Yeah.
I've seen her this
clearly in nightmares.
She pins me down and puts her
hands over my mouth and my nose.
Interesting.
So the person
that I'm most concerned about
is a nasty old man that I encountered.
He's very manipulative, very bad.
And he was laughing
at me, and he was like,
"You think you can stop me?
No way. "You're not gonna."
He really likes the room
upstairs to the left.
That's Chelsea's room, just so you know.
Oh.
This guy, comin' into that
room, he was stompin'...
boom, boom, boom... and
just pushing the rage.
I mean, it's overwhelming.
I saw that he was, like,
stomping down on a living woman,
um, like, trying to repress her.
And I got that she
wasn't getting any sleep.
Also making people
paranoid of one another
and causing fights.
What he does is he'll
reach into people's minds,
and he'll dig out the nastiest stuff,
like, the worst issues,
and pop those up.
He can cause serious physical harm.
I feel that he is capable of that.
Sensations that I was getting
was stabbing, cutting,
burning, and choking pains.
Well, pretty much listed
every single thing these
guys are experiencing.
I was having a nightmare,
actually of... about Nettie.
And she was pinning me down.
And I woke up to this
pressure on my chest.
And I was all the way up my wall.
My head was touching the
rafters of my ceiling.
Now, your sister,
when she was six months pregnant,
got pushed down the steps.
Yeah.
That could be him.
Now, her brother sleeps upstairs, too,
and he has a lot of trouble
feeling like he's being choked.
Mm-hmm. The smothering.
- Yep.
- Yeah.
Now, Jonathan, when I interviewed him,
told me a story that
I still don't believe,
to be honest with you.
He'd wake up with
razor blades in his bed.
And I thought he was messin' with me.
But maybe it's this guy
making him hallucinate.
Now, you also said this
guy can make people fight.
Whoa, yeah.
The anger is just at...
just can just tip over
at any slight, little
thing, and we explode.
We never acted like this before.
It's got to be in this house.
This house is gonna tear us apart.
You got any idea who this
[bleep] was when he was alive?
I got that he lived here,
that he had a lot of money and power,
that people really respected
him when he was alive.
He was white, in his late
60s or early 70s when he died.
What I saw when he
was crawling towards me
was that he had his shirt off.
And I think that's how he died.
All right, so this is
a... It may be a long shot,
but Nettie had a son named Russell.
Now, after Nettie died in 1932,
he took over this house
with his wife and six kids.
Now, this guy was a prominent guy.
He was a World War I
vet. He was a dentist.
He was involved in politics.
- Okay.
- What really caught my attention
is when you said he
died with his shirt off.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Now, in 1971, Russell drowned
in Lake Lovelace, which is
less than a mile from here.
Oh.
He was 75 years old according
to this article here.
So I was able to get
a photo of this guy.
The only thing is it
was when he was young.
So, you had seen him as an older man.
I don't know if...
This is what he looked like
when he was in his younger days.
Now, is it possible this
could be the guy you saw?
I had a sketch done of him.
Tell me what you think.
Take a look at who's
terrorizing your family.
This one was the one
I feel like I've seen.
They have a lot of similarities.
So you guys are thinking
you might have ran into this guy, Ditto.
No beard, though.
Yeah. I think it's him.
- What do you think of these?
- You know what?
The more I look at the photo,
if you put a beard on him...
They look a lot...
- ...it's really close.
- Very, very close.
He was a lawyer, well-respected.
So, Chelsea, now you
know who's in your room.
I'm terrified, actually.
All right. So those
shadow people outside,
you think they're his former slaves?
Yeah, I'm thinkin'.
I also think some of
those people out there
are the Native Americans.
Is this guy responsible
for all their infighting,
their animosity towards each other?
- Oh, yeah. Yeah.
- Okay.
I think he's the master manipulator.
He's the one causing hallucinations,
causing people to fight.
I think he's the major problem.
There's got to be some
way I can reach into his...
his world and take care of him.
Well, guys, there's
some good news here.
All the fighting, talk
of divorce, it's not you.
Chelsea, all the stuff
you been going through
upstairs in your bedroom,
you're not goin' nuts.
Now it's time to answer the
question you brought us in for.
Can you live here safely, happily
with your family like
you always intended to do?
Well, for that answer, I'm
gonna turn it over to Amy.
The first order of business
is to remove this guy.
What I would like to see happen is
a black, male medium
needs to come in and remove him.
And this will be by force.
This isn't gonna be
a pleasant experience,
probably for either one, really.
This would then be followed by
that same medium working with
the dead slaves to move them on.
I think that once he's
gotten rid of this jerk,
most, if not all, of the
dead that are still here
will move on themselves.
Then, once all of that's done,
a Native American
medicine man needs to come.
And what needs to be done
then is all of you guys
need to do a peace offering ritual.
This is to let the Native Americans know
that you mean them no harm.
Once that's done, they're
going to back off of you.
Okay, so if they do everything you say,
and one year from now,
we walk back in here,
you think they'll be better?
- Yeah. It'll be great.
- Good. Good. Yeah.
Well, I'm relieved that I don't
have to leave my dream home.
You saved more than a house.
You saved a family.
Yeah.
I'm ready to start fightin' it.
Yeah. He's not gonna win.
There's no way, no way. Unh-unh.
Removing the old,
dead man from this property
won't be easy.