It's like this family was cursed.
I go outside, found
him in the truck, dead.
What he gets off on is being seen.
Every night, I see a shadow
coming down the hallway.
I do hear pounding.
There were some lynchings or murders.
What is he trying to do?
Kill them.
They want to wreak havoc and chaos.
There's a dark presence.
My name is Amy Allan.
These things, they're freaking out.
They're from hell.
I see dead people.
They were being hunted.
I speak to dead people.
They were setting people on fire,
burning them alive.
And they speak to me.
Her neck got broken.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I hear a gunshot.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Something's not right here.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
It's not safe here.
It's my job to reveal them.
Are any of them buried on the property?
They're all buried here.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end...
I can't do it no more.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Holy [bleep] Look at this.
Or time to get out.
It does not have a happy ending.
Something kills people here.
I'm in Patricksburg, Indiana.
It's a tiny, little town 70
miles southwest of Indianapolis.
I got a call from a woman named Sonya.
Now, she'd been in an
abusive relationship
and finally got the courage
to grab her two daughters
and get the hell out.
Now here's where
the problem is...
She moved back into the
house that she grew up in,
and the abuse didn't stop.
But this time, she's
being attacked by something
she can't even see.
Things are so bad, she's
living in an RV on the property
just to avoid the house.
This poor girl's been through a lot,
and I really hope Amy
and I can help her out.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the house of
any leading information,
removing family photos and
covering personal items.
When I'm finished,
the location will be
ready for tonight's walk.
Oh, boy.
Uh, this isn't good.
This probably isn't a good
place to build anything.
It's like the earth literally
sucks the structures into it.
It's almost like the earth devours them.
There's a lot of mental illness there,
and there's a lot of pain
inflicted upon others.
Well, Sonya, I'm glad I'm here
'cause you sounded
really bad on the phone.
So let me get this
straight. You're living here?
Yes.
I'd rather live here in
the RV in the front yard
than I would in their house, any day.
I'm scared of that house.
Now, where's your parents' house
in relation to where we are now?
Up the hill, basically.
Who's living where?
This is all of us.
This is my youngest daughter, Cassie.
She's 13.
This is myself.
We live here.
This is my mother,
Pam, and my father, Ted.
And they live in the house.
And my oldest daughter, Ashlyn,
refused to even be on the property.
What are you hoping we can do for you?
My parents are planning on
finding a place down in Florida,
and they've offered
me the house, which...
I would love to have Cassie there,
but I won't because I don't want
her childhood to be like mine.
Okay. So let me get this straight.
- You grew up in this house?
- Yes.
Was the house haunted then?
Yes.
I swore I'd never come back here.
But you had to come back to
escape an abusive relationship.
Yes.
It definitely took a
lot to get away from.
This was my only option.
So this was like a safe haven for you.
So I thought.
If you can, just give me a rundown
of what everybody's
experiencing in the house.
Voices, growling,
things moving, the
fear of being watched.
And there have been shadow people.
There's been attacks,
people being touched.
I can only imagine
how tough this must be
for you to talk about.
It's been a whirlwind of
emotions and, you know,
I worry about my daughters.
You know, I've lived with this
for... Well, I'm 35 years old.
And since I was young,
it's haunted me, you know.
Why? Why me?
Why?
I'm seeing this man, and
he's dressed in black.
He is kind of wearing a cowboy outfit.
He looks fairly young,
I would say in his 30s.
He's pretty tough.
And he's quiet, and
he's just standing there.
He likes to be seen.
He also likes this area a great deal.
He is trying to experiment
with moving things
and actually really hardcore
interact with the living.
So, this is your backyard?
Am I seeing what I think I'm seeing?
Yes.
This is a privately owned cemetery.
As a child looking
out my bedroom window,
this is what I saw.
How do you feel
now, being in here?
- I'm on edge being in here.
- Okay.
So, what's going on?
Well, we have a shadow
that you actually see it every
night go down this hallway.
Okay. So describe what it looks like.
- Just a black mist, really.
- How big is it?
How tall is it?
I'd say about right
here, about five feet.
The guy in black...
people would see him as a
shadow person, without a doubt.
He looks a lot shorter
when he's in that form
than what he really is 'cause
he's probably about 5'10".
But in the shadow-person form,
he looks more, maybe,
about five foot and wider.
He wants a lot of attention.
What he gets off on is being seen.
Okay. So, anything else going on?
Uncontrollable crying.
Cannot figure out why.
From the time I woke up
to the time I went to bed,
if I was in this house, I was sobbing.
The whole day?
Oh, the whole day,
until I went to the RV.
And then, it just stopped.
I'm not a psychologist,
but you have bad
memories here growing up.
Yes.
But it's not that kind
of emotion, you know?
It's not the feeling of losing someone.
Okay. So, you've had
that kind of heartbreak?
Yeah.
A couple years ago, my
uncle had taken his own life.
His name was Jeff.
Actually... he's right here.
He had lived here for a while.
We were very, very close.
Where did this happen?
Not in this house.
But he did spend a lot of time here.
- We were real tight.
- Yeah.
How old was he when he passed?
He would've been 45,
I think, when he died.
Oh. So he was a young man.
What kind of guy was he?
He just brought a smile
to everybody's face.
If somebody was in a bad mood,
he'd be the one to get you out of it.
Never, ever, ever thought he
would do it, especially now,
after he knew what we went through
with my first husband
that took his own life,
as well.
He spent a lot of time here.
And we got married and left
and moved in with his mother.
And then, next thing I know,
I go outside and couldn't find him
and found him in the truck, dead.
That's Raymond.
How did he do it, if
you don't mind me asking?
He shot himself in the head also.
He died in '99.
I hold a lot of guilt for both of them.
Listen. Listen to me.
Listen to me good. Okay?
I learned one thing in life.
If somebody wants to do
what your husband did,
if they want to do that, nothing
you do is gonna change it.
These are tortured souls
you're talking about here.
I know. And I do know that.
I do. I just can't tell my heart that.
The cowboy guy... I do
see him with a handgun.
He was pretty intimidating
when he was alive.
He likes this space the most.
There's a familiarity here with him.
I don't trust this guy,
and I think he's doing
very bad things in here.
So, what's going on in here?
I woke up one night to somebody
pushing at the end of the bed.
I looked up, and in
between the wall and the bed
was two hooded figures
that had no face, no eyes.
And there was one at the end of my bed
and one on the other side of my bed.
And I woke up screaming bloody murder.
And that was when my mom got
up out of bed, came in here.
And I told her what had happened.
And she immediately went
into my brother's room
and was like, "Okay, Chad.
It's time to tell her."
I'm like, "Tell me what?"
You know, and that's when
they began to tell me that,
you know, they had had
similar experiences.
With the same type of sighting?
Yes.
Anything else?
I had a dream one night.
It was almost like the shadow people
that we saw going down the hallway,
but it was leaning over
me, scratching my forehead.
And the next morning, I got up,
and I had a scratch on my head.
Now, couldn't you have
just scratched yourself?
I don't believe so because
of the way, you know,
when I looked in the mirror,
it was exactly how, in my dream,
the shadow would have did it.
In this room, I just see,
like, this younger girl.
There's something off about her.
Somebody's summoned her up from
her grave and, like, dug her up.
And, like, she didn't come back right.
I see her standing
at the end of the bed,
and she's just staring.
And it's really [bleep] creepy
because standing behind
her is this dark thing
that has attached itself to this kid.
The thing ultimately
controls her and has, like,
a connection to her.
Do you have any idea what this
thing that's controlling her is?
I would say it's some
kind of demonic force.
Can you see it? What does it look like?
This thing is very tall.
Its hands are super
weird-looking...
long, really super little
hands but long fingers.
And do you have any idea
what it's trying to do?
I think that it's trying
to attach itself to
somebody in this room.
What demons want... they
want to wreak havoc and chaos.
Would you say that this
person is in danger?
Yes, I would.
So Sonya said she had a hell
of a time growing up here.
I did not know that it marked
her for life like it has.
Now, Sonya's at the point where
she won't even stay in the house.
She's staying in the RV.
Yeah. It broke my heart.
She's got a bedroom in
there that's still her room.
I mean, we still call it her room.
It's still decorated, like, for her.
Have you experienced anything?
The very first night we
ever stayed in this house,
I woke up with a girl
standing beside my bed,
I mean, just, like, right here.
Like, she's just
looking down at my face.
Have you seen anything else like that?
Just... every night,
I see a shadow coming down the hallway.
And it looks like it
goes out the front door.
Your daughter explained
the same thing to me.
And we both have seen
it at the same time.
So, it's not been easy
here for you, either?
No.
It's that back hallway.
If anything in this house
spooks me, it's the back hallway.
And why does that spook you?
Well, number one, that's
where I heard the voice.
What voice?
I was in the bathroom one day,
and just this most evil, growly
voice was like, "Stop it."
Just as low.
And I was petrified that day.
There's also another male here.
And I see, like, an older male.
He's a big problem.
He yells a lot, very threatening.
I do hear pounding on the walls,
especially in, like, in this area.
He's related to somebody
in the household.
And he's somebody's grandfather
or great-grandfather.
There's something in the
family that's really bad.
Two people, at some point,
in this family, got married.
They shouldn't have. It
was bad, very wrong and bad.
And from that point
on, it's like this...
this line, this family,
was cursed by their own.
I don't think I've
ever... seen this before.
I don't think he wants to show me
who he's related to
because that's the person
he's trying to destroy.
So, Chad, I was talking to Sonya.
Now, she told me about the experiences
and how this house really
scarred her for life.
Now, she had mentioned
you'd moved out of here
pretty quick when you were young.
Oh, as soon as I was 18, I was gone.
Why, though?
Most of it was because of the
things that had happened here.
Okay. So tell me about some of them.
One particular night, when I
was probably 8 or 9 years old,
standing around my bed, I
counted six hooded figures.
I had three on one side of my bed,
three on the other side.
So, you saw the same exact thing
that Sonya was telling me about?
Yeah.
I'm 37 now, and I close my
eyes and I can still see them.
- Okay. Anything else?
- Yeah.
Around the same time that I seen that,
I was laying in bed and woke up
to feeling pressure on my chest.
And it felt like they
were underneath my bed
and were pulling the
sheet tight down so...
pinning me to my bed where
I could not move at all.
I went to scream out,
and I couldn't get
any words to come out.
It took all the air out of my chest.
I just told myself that I
shouldn't look underneath there.
I may not like what I see.
I see that the grandfather guy
is attacking somebody in this room
and is pushing down on their heart.
It might feel more like their
throat or chest pressure,
but he's actually inside their chest.
He's trying to figure out
how to make the heart stop.
He can't... grab it.
He can put pressure on it,
but he can't squeeze it.
And what is he trying to do?
Kill them.
First thing I do
when I get to a location
is pull the property deed.
Turns out one of the original owners
was on the land for 65 years.
I had a local historian check them out,
and she just called back
saying these people have a story
I'm definitely gonna want to know about.
So, Glenda, what
were you able to find out
about the original owners
of my client's property?
Stephen Macgerlein came
from Germany to Owen County
in the later 1830s.
He married,
and he and his wife had,
over the years, 12 children.
Okay.
They bought the property in
1864 and used it as a coal mine.
Did he mine coal right
on my client's property?
That's my understanding.
Okay. That's interesting.
You mentioned on the phone
that this family had a story I'm
gonna want to hear for my case.
What was that?
Well, they had a number of deaths
in the course of the time that
they lived in Patricksburg.
In 1872, a 2-year-old son
died in an accident at the mill
less than a 1/2 a mile down the road.
- His name was Frederick.
- Okay.
In 1888, his
13-year-old daughter,
Hermione, died of typhoid fever.
I'm afraid to even ask what else.
In 1901, his
35-year-old daughter,
Molly, died of consumption.
The next year, in 1902,
his wife died at the
age of 61 of peritonitis,
intestinal problems, also.
- Pretty tragic.
- Mm-hmm.
So, what happened to him, Stephen?
He died in 1915 at home of dropsy.
- That's a heart condition.
- Okay.
I brought you an obituary I
thought you'd like to see...
"The Death of a Prominent Man."
So he's 81 when he dies.
- Mm-hmm.
- He died on the property.
Yes. And, Glenda, let
me ask you a question.
There's a couple cemeteries literally
right next door to the property.
- Right.
- Is he buried there?
- Yes.
- Okay.
The whole family is
buried in that cemetery.
Hmm.
There's something about
two children that died.
There's two children graves.
I think one of them belongs to
the girl I saw in the bedroom.
How old?
Like 11 to 14 years of age, maybe.
I'm not sure about the other one.
I think it was a littler kid...
which I think is a boy.
The girl... I see
her with blond hair.
And I feel like she was sick,
that she died from an illness.
More than likely, she
died here, on this land,
and that's what makes her close by.
There's something weird
with her... her soul.
And that's why she's out of her grave.
Very strange.
When Glenda
mentioned the Macgerleins
operated a coal mine on the property,
my ears perked up.
Every time I've looked into one,
I found some terrible accident.
I'm on my way back to the house
to meet a coal-mining expert
who says two people
died horrible deaths
right on Pam's property.
I understand that there
was coal mining done
right here on this property.
That's correct. That was very common.
People would have small mines
that they would operate
on their own property.
Do you have any idea where
they would have did the mining
- on the property here?
- Right here.
They opened this up,
dug down to the coal.
And they just left it open,
and it filled up with rainwater.
Oh. See, I...
Just looking at it,
I would have never
known this was a mine.
It totally changed the landscape
of this part of the country.
I know it was a dangerous job.
It was very hazardous,
particularly the underground mines.
We have a picture right here. Wow.
These look like terrible
working conditions.
There were numerous people killed
and seriously injured
literally every day.
You mentioned two people died on
the property here in the mines.
What happened with that? The
first one happened in 1894.
The victim's name was Aaron Wark,
and he was taking a
break in the coal mine,
and the roof caved in on him.
He lingered for two
days from his injuries
and then finally passed away.
He was 32 years old,
and he left a wife and
three small children.
Okay. So, what was the second death?
Ralph Wright.
He was killed in 1934.
He just got careless.
He was pushing a cart
along and made a mistake
and fell 90 feet down an open shaft,
broke his neck, fractured
his skull, very tragic.
I know what that looks
like. I've seen it.
It's not a pretty sight.
It's quite a big circle of land
that surrounds this particular location,
and it has something to do
with what's going on here.
And it did seem like the
earth was bad for a long time,
like things couldn't grow.
It's like the earth literally
sucks the structures into it
and somehow destroys them.
And I really think that
there's this subtle poisoning
going on.
Nothing should be built here
because they do eventually take it down.
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity in your home,
go to the "Dead Files"
page at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help Me, Dead
Files!" to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
So far, I've got clients
being physically assaulted
on a property that's seen more
than a half a dozen deaths.
But I need to see if
there's anything else
that could help my case.
Searching through city
records, I find a crime
involving a vigilante
group called the White Caps.
Turns out, they nearly
beat a man to death
right next to my client's property.
I'm on my way to meet
with a local researcher
who says this gang
terrorized the entire region.
This article I came
across showed that a guy
got beaten up on or right
near my client's property
by a group of guys called White Cappers.
I've never even heard of
them. What the hell is that?
White Caps existed as secret societies
in mainly Southern Indiana
in local, rural areas
that passed out vigilante justice
from around 1850
through the early 1900s.
Were these guys like the KKK?
They weren't racially motivated,
but there were similarities.
The articles indicated
they wore robes...
sometimes white, sometimes dark.
Okay.
But they felt that they had the right
to enforce the moral
code of their community.
What kind of people would they target?
Drunks, adulterers, prostitutes,
unwed mothers, petty thievery,
or not attending church.
There are, like, a group of men,
and they're all linked arm in arm.
There is maybe 10 of them.
These things are pretty
powerful, very aggressive.
As far as them directly
interacting with the living,
I think that they would feel a sense
of absolutely being
watched and feeling stalked
and feeling extreme fear,
like you're being hunted.
And they want that to be their message.
Okay.
So now that I know
who White Cappers are,
what do you know about the beating
that this guy got near
my client's property?
One evening...
February 14, 1890...
there was a man by the
name of Fleming Bremmer
who was coming home,
going through Patricksburg.
A group of men in
dark robes grabbed him,
took him through an
orchard, tied him to a tree,
and pulled the branches off the trees
and whipped him till
he was a bloody mess...
- Okay...
- and left him there unconscious.
And he didn't wake up till morning.
Well, it's lucky this guy
didn't freeze to death,
let alone from the beating.
Do we know what the White
Cappers went after him?
He had been warned that he
had been abusive to his mother.
And so that was what
led to this incident.
Okay. So, was anybody charged?
No.
Today, they would
never get away with it.
In the hills of Southern
Indiana during the late 1800s...
Right.
There wasn't always the sheriffs
and the police and the courts.
I don't think they want anybody here.
And there's also no denying
the feeling that they invoke,
which is that you're being hunted.
They've gone to where
this is a sport for them.
This is, like, wicked bad.
During my walk, I saw
several dead people,
but two stood out the most.
First, the cowboy.
He was probably in his
mid-to late-30s, very thin.
He had a black cowboy hat on,
and he had a very thick mustache.
Okay.
Next, I described a demon
who was using a dead little
girl to torment a living person.
She was dressed like a doll.
Behind her, which was
this tall, dark thing,
and it had its hands on her shoulders
and its fingers went like
halfway down her body.
So it's, like, controlling her.
Is this what you saw?
Yes. That's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our findings
to each other and our
clients for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to meet Sonya.
She grew up in the house right
across from the barn here,
and she was tortured by
the activity growing up.
Now, a few months ago,
she was able to get out of a
very bad, abusive relationship
and had to move back here
with one of her daughters.
Now, here's how it's
working out for her.
She's so afraid of the house
that she's living in this
RV that's in the front lawn.
So that's why we're
doing the reveal here
'cause she doesn't want
to be in that house.
This is Pam. This is Sonya's mom.
And this is Chad, her brother.
Here's where the twist comes in.
Pam is getting ready
to retire and move out
and wants to give the house to the kids,
but they don't think it's safe.
So with that, I'm gonna have
Amy tell us about her walk
and how things went.
When I first got
here, I saw a group of men.
There were about 10 of them.
And they roam around
the entire property.
The living would experience
them in various ways.
These guys make you feel
like you're being watched
and, specifically, hunted.
It's like that's what
I kept feeling like.
I was being hunted like an animal.
I felt like being watched real bad...
Yeah... just, like, with pure hate,
and just so bad that you had to move.
You couldn't just stand
there. You had to go.
I'll be sitting in the
living room, watching TV,
and it's just like I
know they're watching me.
The creepy thing about them is
that they do not want anybody
on this land.
All right. The only
thing I can think of...
It's a long shot, but
there was something
I came across in my research
that I thought was interesting.
Apparently, back in the late 1800s,
there was a gang of moral
vigilantes called White Cappers.
Now, they performed
violence against anybody
that they thought
were acting amorally...
unwed mothers, hobos, drunks.
They beat women. They beat men.
Didn't matter who it was.
They'd only attack at night,
and when they would do attacks,
they'd wear robes and wear...
Oh, no.
Either white or black hoods.
Oh.
One of the victims was
beaten right on the property.
Oh, my God.
His name was Fleming Bremmer.
He was a white male
who was 51 years old.
Apparently, he was
abusive to his mother.
Now, you guys had a big reaction
when I mentioned the robes.
Tell Amy why.
When I was probably
about 8 years old or so,
and I had six...
three up against the wall,
three on the side of the bed.
They had no faces,
had their arms folded.
I woke up the next morning
and told my mom what had happened,
and that's when she
sat me down that morning
and told me that she had had
that same thing happen to her.
I woke up in the middle of the night,
and there was four hooded
figures around my bed.
And I screamed until
Mom got up and came in.
Okay. Well, that makes a lot of sense.
What else did you see?
When I walked into the house,
I came across a couple of
dead people that concerned me.
One of them is an older male.
He's extremely active in the house,
and he's a big problem here.
He affects the living in a lot of ways.
He does yell a lot,
so people might hear a voice,
humming, or buzzing sound.
He pounds on the walls.
I got very concerned, though,
when I walked into the
first bedroom down the hall.
That's Chad's room.
His sights were set on
whoever was in there.
I saw him on the bed,
sitting over this person,
literally reaching into their chest,
touching their heart and
trying to squeeze the heart,
trying to give the
person a heart attack.
That would be me.
I felt like someone
was underneath my bed,
pulling the sheet
down tight around me...
Mm-hmm... compressing my chest
to the point where I
I could not move.
I couldn't breathe.
I think there's a family connection
between him and the living here.
I got that he was somebody's grandfather
or great-grandfather.
Somewhere, a very long time ago,
there was a marriage that
occurred in the family
that was not deemed appropriate.
And ever since that marriage took place,
there's, like, a family curse.
Whoever shows the dominant
traits of the individual
that was deemed inappropriate
for the marriage,
they are the ones who are targeted.
I wouldn't be surprised,
if you take a look back
at your mother's line,
and see how they met
their demise, some of them.
There might be some
unusual issues there.
- There are.
- Yes.
You're gonna have to tell them.
Wow.
I mean, my mom was very promiscuous.
She was married seven times.
She was shot.
She was with a guy
that got his head blown off
by her soon-to-be ex-husband.
I mean, we were raised going
to maybe five different schools
- in a year...
- Oh, my goodness.
Watching her being beat all the time.
And I worry about her
because she... takes after
her in a lot of those ways.
Interesting.
Now, Amy, you mentioned unusual
deaths within the family.
This is Pam's brother Jeff,
who passed away a few years
ago by committing suicide.
He spent a lot of time here,
too, as a matter of fact.
We were more like brothers.
It was definitely over a woman.
I don't know much about curses,
but it's a doozy of a curse.
Yes.
So then I met another dead
guy, and he's very active here.
One of the things that
he does to get attention
is he does, like,
show himself as a, like, a
five-foot-tall shadow person.
But he's about 5'10 ", 5'11".
He can go all over
the property...
inside, outside, everywhere.
He likes the living room,
and he likes the back bedroom the best.
He wants a lot of attention,
so he does act out.
He's dressed all in black.
I got a very cowboy vibe from him.
I thought he was in his 30s.
I saw him holding a gun.
I...would say that would be Raymond.
We're talking about Sonya's ex-husband,
who also committed suicide.
You okay, honey?
Mm-hmm. I don't know.
I guess I just didn't really
figure him to stick around here.
Well, I did have a sketch done,
so you can tell me what you think.
Oh, yeah. Are you kidding me?
I think it looks a lot like him.
- I think it could be.
- I really do.
The Adam's apple is so prominent.
So, what do you think?
After hearing what
they're saying about him...
Yeah. I think it's him.
Why would he stay here?
Why would he not go where I go?
There's something about your mother
that he's attached to,
and he feels comfortable.
You've been through hell, kid.
Yeah. I was young.
Got a lot of guilt with both of them.
This is where, to me,
things got really weird.
Uh-oh. The little girl...
This girl looked really sweet,
and to me, she was just pure innocence.
I can tell that you
like the little girl,
and this is not gonna be good news.
I saw two graves of children.
One was a female,
like 9 to 12 or something in there.
The other was a little boy.
I do believe that the girl got
sick and died from an illness.
And I believe she died
somewhere on this land.
And I would place the young
girl in, like, the 1900s,
by her little outfit.
There are two kids that
you described who did live
and died right on the property.
The land was owned by a guy
named Stephen Macgerlein.
He lived here from 1864 to 1915.
In 1872, his 2-year-old
son, Frederick,
died in a horrible accident
in the family's gristmill.
Now, in 1888, Macgerlein's
daughter Hermione
died from typhoid fever.
Now, the kicker is, both
those kids are buried
in one of the cemeteries
right next door to you.
Oh, wow.
So, what's the little girl do here?
She was in the middle bedroom.
That's your old room.
Yes.
She was standing at the edge of the bed
and just staring straight
ahead at the person in the bed.
It was very creepy.
I realized that the dead
girl was pretty much gone.
And behind her,
I see this dark thing
standing and controlling her.
He was very tall and creepy
and had extremely long fingers.
Now, I've seen a creature,
is what I described it as...
four feet tall, humanoid
with long, white hair.
But it had fingers that
were probably this long.
So I had a sketch done of
what I saw in the bedroom.
That's it.
Oh, my God.
So I had a sketch done
of what I saw in the bedroom.
That's it.
Oh, my God.
Do you think they were
gonna cause me harm?
There is a demon or
a demonic presence...
that is utilizing a deceased girl.
The intention there is
to possess the individual
that was in this bed.
All right.
So, are you saying that
this thing that you had drawn
is a demon and is
trying to get to Sonya?
Yes.
And it's also projecting those
hooded figures you've all seen.
That's what I thought.
That's how I felt because
it was such hate and malice
that you felt.
And I always wondered
in the back of my mind
if it was demonic.
When I was a child, I
had a dream of, like,
these nails over me and being
scratched on my forehead.
And as I... when I
woke up that morning,
there was that scratch on my forehead.
I really think that this goes
back to this initial curse.
Whoever placed this curse
was very well-versed in how to do it...
And brought in this
kind of demonic presence.
I think that it's through your line.
Never in my wildest imagination
did I think there was this much.
So now, Sonya, after hearing
what Amy has told us tonight,
it's pretty clear
you haven't had a day of
peace in your entire life.
I'm really hoping tonight's
a turning point for you,
as well as everybody else at the table.
And it starts by answering
one big question...
Can you kick out whatever
the hell's in the house
so that you and your
daughter can move in
and start your lives over, basically?
So for that answer, I'm
gonna turn it over to Amy.
There is a lot that needs to be done,
and the first thing is
to find a group of shamen
because there is some
type of demonic force
that's been following the
family as part of this curse.
What they will do is a curse unraveling,
a cord cutting, a removal
of all the negative energies,
and then they will also do protections
to lock down the land and the house.
What the cord cutting will do
is it will remove any and
all invisible attachments
that you've made to any
dead people or entities.
So once all of that's done,
then Raymond must be moved on.
I would like an older female,
gentle medium go into your room
and have a session with
him and help him to move on.
It's just hard to...
I mean, I want him to move on.
And I always...
I guess I always was hoping
that he was watching over his daughter
and not stuck here.
Oh, it's just
That's hard.
Well, now you have a chance.
You know exactly where he is,
and you can help him to go.
So, Sonya, you're gonna
listen to Amy's advice on this?
- Definitely.
- Mom?
Oh, absolutely.
I think we can put them
on their heels pretty
- pretty quick.
- So once this gets done,
you think you're gonna move
up here with your daughter?
I wouldn't mind it.
I just don't want Cassie to go through
the same thing I went
through as a child.
Removing the demon needs
to happen immediately for Sonya
and her family to protect their souls.
In doing so, they'll free
the dead and break the curse
that's been plaguing their
family for generations.