Oh, boy.
I feel like there's a man down here.
He came and he bumped me.
Like, you know, I felt it.
Punching, slapping,
kicking. He's a bully.
So, it's still an open case?
Yes. It's an unsolved murder.
I'm gonna [bleep] kill you.
I've been through a lot in this house.
He's kinda freaked out.
They're everywhere.
He's disgusting and nasty.
There's a dark presence.
My name is Amy Allan.
These things, they're freaking out.
They're from hell.
I see dead people.
They were being hunted.
I speak to dead people...
They were setting people
on fire, burning them alive.
...and they speak to me.
Her neck got broken.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
And I hear a gunshot.
- I rely on my partner.
- I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Somethin's not right here.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
- It's not safe here.
- It's my job to reveal them.
Are any of them buried on the property?
They're all buried here.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation...
- ...until the very end.
- I can't do it no more.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Holy [Bleep]. Look at this.
Or time to get out.
It does not have a happy ending.
Something kills people here.
I'm in the small town
of Canton, Illinois.
It's between Chicago and St. Louis.
Now, I got a call from a woman
who said she's at her breaking point.
Her 7-year-old
is so traumatized,
he won't go anywhere alone in the house.
She's says it's gotten physical,
and she's afraid he's gonna get hurt.
She's beggin' us for help.
Before Amy arrives,
I look for anything that
could influence her findings.
This home is covered with family photos
and spiritual items
that I need to remove.
When I'm done, the location
will be ready for tonight's walk.
In... in my opening, I saw
two of these big trees...
...and five shadow
men hanging from them.
There's something that's, like,
right outside here that is so bad.
Like, there is this dark wall
of energy around this place
because of whatever happened
to these five people,
and they're creating this,
like, cloud of sadness.
And they're creepy.
When you and
I spoke the phone, uh,
you sounded like a young
mom at her wit's end.
Let's start. What the hell's goin' on?
Um, I'm really worried about
my 7-year-old son, Layne.
Things have been happening
in the house with him.
Where he can't even sleep in
his room without, you know,
four night-lights.
I can tell, like, most of the time,
Layne don't wanna be home
'cause he's terrified.
Is everybody in the
house having experiences?
- Yes.
- Okay, like what?
There's banging going
on, um, things moving.
Uh, we have seen
apparitions, shadow figures,
and it has been physical.
So, who exactly is living in the house?
- Um, my husband, Mike...
- Okay.
My son, Layne, and my
daughter, Hannelore.
Layne is 7, and Hannelore
is about a year-and-a-half.
I'm worried that Hannelore is starting
to experience the same things
that Layne is experiencing.
She'll point that the
window and say, "Uh-oh,"
and... and kinda make a...
like, a whining noise like she's scared.
Now, you had mentioned that Layne
is gettin' the worst of it.
Yes. He gets upset.
He hyperventilates when he sees things.
Here's, um, a picture that he drew,
and he said it was the devil
that he's seen in his room.
He's got more pictures right here.
This poor kid.
He sees things that normal
7- year-olds don't see.
One of the reasons I did take this case
was because a child
was getting affected.
Why do you think Layne's
being affected so much?
I feel like they like him.
They gravitate towards him.
I mean, he says, "What do
they want? I want them gone."
And then I'm... I don't
know what to tell him.
I just want all of us
to be free and happy
and not scared to be here.
I don't know how much more I can take.
Okay.
I'm thinking that there
is a dead person here
who is capable or wants to
inflict physical pain on people,
or illness, uh, on living people.
It's, like, in this room
that I'm gettin' the big pull from him.
This is where he retreated to,
which kinda makes me nervous
'cause it seems like
it's a child's room,
so that's kind of unnerving.
I'm getting, like,
this 20-year-old male.
This dead guy, he
looks big. He's a bully.
He can bully, um, you know,
weak people, vulnerable people.
He's angry. He's very, very, very angry,
and that does not bode well
for whoever might be in here.
So what's goin' on in here?
Um, I've seen shadow figures,
um, when I'm laying on the bed.
Um, I have one that was in my face.
I can feel them, on me, in my face.
Like, watching me.
You just said "them."
- Yeah.
- Is there more than one?
I did see another one
at a different time,
and it was at the end of the bed.
- Okay.
- And it was tall,
and it was, like, just
standing there, watching me.
Okay. Anything else?
In the bathroom, it was late.
I got in the shower, and I felt
like something was watching me.
And it was, um, it made me feel,
like, violated, like, disgusted.
I was disgusted.
I opened the curtain,
and I was like, "Get out!"
I knew it was there, and
as soon as I said that,
I felt, like, "Okay, now I
can at least take a shower."
So, you felt like a
Peepin' Tom or something?
- Yes, definitely.
- Okay.
I see, like, a woman with long hair.
And this is a living person.
And then, like, that guy.
This guy is dead,
and he's making moves on a living woman.
This person, it's
like she's not herself.
She's anxious and restless.
She's, like, pacing.
She's having, like, these,
like, weird, intrusive thoughts.
Like, she wants to run away.
She wants to leave this life.
I- I mean, I think it might be this male
who's, like, influencing her,
but she's fighting
it, like, all the time.
And that's, like, the
restlessness and the pacing
and the can't sleep
and, like, the, you know,
trying to, like, relax and, like, focus.
He's, like, freaking out now
that I'm talking about it.
He doesn't like it. He's
getting really anxious
and really upset and he's just, like...
Ow.
My neck and my head.
I hate being down here.
It definitely creeps me out to be here.
Okay. Why?
When I have to come
down here and do laundry,
I always feel like
somebody is watching me.
I feel like it's a man.
Is it the same feeling
you get in the bathroom?
Yes. Exact same feeling.
Every time I come down here,
I have the exact same feeling.
Do you feel it right this second
while you're in front of me?
Yes.
- Now, where are you feelin' it?
- Right there.
Okay.
Recently he, um, came
and he bumped me to get my attention.
Like, he definitely
wanted me to feel him.
- Do it to me.
- So it was like... that.
Okay, so it was pretty significant.
So it was, like... It,
like, you know, I felt it.
I know you're a mom.
You gotta do laundry.
But how the hell do you
come down here every day?
I mean, I hate coming down here.
I feel like I'm a
prisoner in my own home.
I feel like
there's a man down here.
Very, uh, aggressive male down here.
Mm.
He was an older male, uh,
probably, like, 50s, maybe?
And he's a big guy.
Like, he's kinda chubby.
I don't know how they would see him,
but I think they could see something.
He can be very aggressive
towards the living,
'cause this is very
much his [bleep] space.
What does he do to them?
He likes to trip people a lot.
Like, he'll kneel down and
wait and then grab them.
He, like, rushes them.
I think they'll see something,
like, barreling towards them,
right up on them.
He's just disgusting and nasty.
I don't like him.
So, Mike, it looks like you're
doing renovations, obviously.
Yeah. Okay, so how long you...
this been going on?
Almost 5 years.
- Five years?
- Yes.
It takes so long 'cause
I'm uncomfortable up here.
It really bothers me.
What about your
experiences? What's goin' on?
In the basement, we have
an old coal room down there,
and when I was putting
together the pool table,
I looked over and seen
an old man starin' at me
through a plate glass window.
Inside the coal room?
Inside the coal room, you
know, just looking out.
I probably sat there for 5...
5 minutes, just lookin' back.
You know, your wife felt
something watching her
from that window, too.
So describe what the
old man looked like.
All I seen was his
shoulders and his face,
and he just looked old and
his face was just wrinkly.
It freaked me out so
much that the next day,
I went down with a can of spray paint,
and I spray painted that window black.
Okay. Anything else?
Whenever I'm up here workin',
overwhelming feeling
somebody's standin' right there
in the doorway watchin' me.
I cannot stop lookin' over my shoulder
to see what's there, but
there's never anything there.
You gettin' that feeling right now?
Yeah. You do?
And is it...
I've got a feeling
that somebody's standing
right there, watching me.
Okay.
Oh, boy.
I don't like in there though.
It's terrible. It's terrible energy.
Okay, so there's this old woman.
She's, like, talking about, uh,
somethin' up here, somebody.
She does not like him.
Would the living be
affected by this in any way?
I would think yeah,
maybe feeling oppression.
Maybe, like, an oppressive anxiety?
And they feel her watching them.
I don't like it in here.
She would make the living feel sick.
They would have, like,
intestinal issues.
I don't like her. I don't
really want to talk to her.
She is [bleep] so mean.
She's like, "I'm gonna
[bleep] kill you!"
How old are you now, Layne?
- 7.
- Okay.
I was talkin' to Mommy, and she
was telling was telling me that,
uh, some of the things that
are happening in the house
- make you afraid.
- Yes.
Tell me about some of
the stuff you've seen.
I hear children laughing,
a boy and a girl.
And there was a guy right there.
He was a black mass.
There was an angel there.
I saw floating dolls.
They had stitch-up eyes
and it was really creepy.
You know, I can believe
what I'm hearing.
This kid is firing off
experience after experience
to the point where I can barely keep up.
I saw a black figure in the bathroom.
It was, like, crunched down like this,
and it was pretty creepy.
Either Layne has an
overactive imagination
or he's seen way too
much, way too young.
I saw the devil.
Okay, where'd you see the devil?
Right here.
Okay. Tell me about that.
He had horns.
What about his face?
Red. Red.
And he had black hair.
He was, like, smiling so freaky at me.
Okay. Is that the one you drew
the picture for, for Mommy?
- Yes.
- How do you know it's the devil?
I know it's the devil.
I don't know why, but I know it's evil.
How do you know all this?
You seem pretty smart.
Thank you. 'Cause I'm just kind of open.
Okay, so what do you think
these things your seeing want?
They probably want to go to the light
so they can go to heaven.
So, do you think that when
people are bad in life,
they go down?
- Yes.
- Okay.
And when you're a good
guy or a good girl you up?
- Up.
- Yep.
Okay. You're a good guy.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- You are, too.
- Thank you.
Appreciate that. All right.
So it sounds like this stuff
is scaring you in the house.
You don't want to be
here alone, I understand?
Yeah, I've been through
a lot in this house.
They're everywhere.
I'm seeing the
younger dead guy again.
This 20-year-old,
he's squatting down in the closet.
So I think, like, he might
be afraid of me a little bit.
He feels like he can't hurt me,
so he's, like, kind of freaked out.
And he takes his
finger and he's, like...
...doing this kind of stuff.
And he's, like, laughing
'cause he knows it's disturbing.
- So, the people hear that?
- Yes.
It's like a spooky, creepy elf.
And he's got, like,
sharp teeth, you know,
um, and long nails.
What does he do?
He wants to physically harm...
punching, slapping,
kicking, or make them sick.
He can hurt vulnerable people.
This is pretty... pretty serious.
Mike and Angie didn't
know much about the history
of their property,
so I'm at the local library
to see what I can dig up.
Searching through old records,
I find a brutal rape and
murder of an 8-year-old girl.
Turns out this sick, twisted crime
happened less than a mile
from my client's house.
I'm on my way to meet with
a criminal defense attorney
who says the case remains
a mystery to this day.
The 8-year-old girl
that was murdered
right near my client's property,
what'd you find out about it?
It was November 1955.
Janice May went missing from her house.
Her two brothers went lookin' for her.
Uh, the family dog led
them to the rail road tracks,
and next to the rail road tracks there
was some abandoned mining cars.
There, the brothers found
their sister shoved underneath
one of the cars. Oh, you're kiddin' me.
She had a terrible skull fracture
on the right side of her face.
- Okay.
- There was a concrete block
sitting next to her with blood on it.
She was half-nude.
It was determined she
was sexually assaulted.
Did the police make an arrest?
The police interviewed
about 30 different suspects.
Ultimately, they
focused on Lloyd Miller,
a local taxi cab driver.
It turned out that
right after this crime,
he quickly fled town.
They found Lloyd Miller in
a town 150 miles from Canton.
He was at a bus station,
trying to get a bus
ticket to go to Detroit.
They brought him in for questioning.
Miller denied involvement
but after several days of interrogation,
he ultimately confessed.
What do we know about this guy?
At this time, he was 29 years old.
Miller completed the first
two years of high school,
but then he was drafted in the military.
He served in Italy durin' World War II.
After he was discharged,
he came back to the States.
And his dream was to become
an auto mechanic in Detroit.
But he hopped around job to job.
He ultimately joined the
Coast Guard, also the Army.
But he went AWOL three separate times.
He was sent to the stockade each time.
Wow.
He also got in trouble in California.
For what? Uh, he and
a friend stole a car.
He ended up spending 7
months in a prison farm.
So this guy's all over the map.
He was somewhat
unpredictable and impulsive.
He got married four times,
and a couple of these marriages
to women he had only met
for the past few days.
Who the hell does that?
Sounds like a bit of a whack job.
This 20-year-old,
he doesn't like to think about
his life 'cause it was not good.
It was very bad.
He was a real tough guy.
He was a bully when he was alive.
He got... I think he
got thrown out of school.
He was in and out of prison.
And he hated his [bleep] mother.
Wow. Like, real, like, [bleep] hate.
I'm seeing like a garage...
...and, like, wrenches and, um, oil.
I wanna say he worked on
cars or something like this.
He's freakin' out.
All right, so how'd the trial go?
The jury convicted him,
and a judge sentenced him to
death by the electric chair.
He had seven different execution dates.
So, Dale, I noticed it
went to the Supreme Court.
Do we know why?
The defense team, throughout
these 10 years of appeals,
started dismantling the state's case.
The so-called confession
that Miller signed,
he never wrote it.
It was written by the police officers.
In February 1967,
the United States Supreme
Court overturned the conviction.
And in March 20th, 1967,
Miller walked out of
death row a free man.
Do we know what happens to him?
He moved to Mexico.
He got remarried, again.
Uh, he ended up writing a
book about his ordeals here.
Um, he ultimately became a minister.
Do we know if this
guy's still alive today?
No, he's not. He died in 2013
in Reading, Pennsylvania,
at the age of 86.
Did cops back then ever
look into this case again
and look at anybody else,
question anybody else about it?
Not that we could tell.
So it's still an open case?
Yes, it's an unsolved murder.
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity in your home,
go to the "Dead Files"
page at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help Me, Dead
Files!" to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
During my research, I
came across several families
who used to own my client's land.
Now one family, the Barrys, stood out.
Three of them died
right on the property.
I'm on my way to meet with a genealogist
who says this family
suffered from illness,
depression, and madness.
So, Julie, thanks for
helpin' me out with my case.
The Barry family... what
can you tell me about them?
Bernard and his wife, Mary, um,
were both Irish immigrants
who came over to the U.S. in the 1850s
- during the potato famine.
- Okay.
Bernard and his wife, Mary,
purchased the property in 1890.
Who moved there with them?
A daughter, Maryann, who was 30.
And then their youngest
daughter, Francis, who was 15.
Now I know there was deaths
associated with family
on the property.
What'd you find out?
Well, the first one occurred in 1915,
and that was Mary, the wife.
Okay. Have her obituary here.
She became ill and
suffered for nearly a year
until she contracted pneumonia
and lived with that
painfully for 5 days, uh,
before she finally passed.
I have a copy of her
death certificate here
which lists pneumonia
as the 'cause of death.
- Oh, she was 82?
- Yeah.
And you know, my mother
suffered same age from emphysema
and wound up dyin' from pneumonia.
- And that's a miserable...
- Yes.
...way of life.
I'm seeing that angry older woman again.
She kinda looks like
an older Irish lady.
I hear, like, "Mabel."
I think she was, like, 70 when she died.
I think she's got, like,
cancer or something.
This is what she dies from.
And this is, like, a long time ago.
I would say this is, like, '20s, '30s?
And the guy's, like, big.
Her husband's, like, a big guy.
They didn't have a good marriage.
And it was the woman,
this little woman who would... you know,
I think she beat the [bleep]
out of her husband all the time.
Like, pretty bad.
This is strange.
Mary's death certificate
lists her son, Bernard Jr.,
as the informant.
Yes, we know that Bernard Sr., uh,
was suffering from
dementia when he died.
So it's quite possible
that his son was the informant
on the death certificate
because he might've started
to show signs of dementia at this point.
Okay, so now that Mary's dead,
who's taking care of Bernard?
Their daughter, Maryann,
she's the primary
caregiver for her father,
who's probably continuing
on in his dementia.
At some point, she
gets extremely depressed
and she starves herself,
um, and dies as a result.
- She starved herself to death?
- Yes.
We have a copy of her
death certificate here.
She was 56.
And you'll notice that they
do list a contributing factor
of melancholia.
So what happens to the dad?
By 1926, his suffering finally ends.
- Okay, he...
- He passes away on the property.
Okay, so what's the official
cause of death for him?
Well, his death certificate
lists heart failure
with a contributing factor of senility.
Another thing caught my eye in research.
It was a deadly factory
explosion down the block
from Michael and Angie's house.
I reached out to a
historian who said it was
one of the biggest tragedies
in the town's history.
So I gotta assume this
is where the factory was?
That's right. This was, uh, the location
of the Parlin Orendorff
manufacturing company.
Okay. What did they manufacture?
Well, mostly farm products
and especially the steel plow,
which was so important to
the evolution of farming
in the Midwest.
This is a picture of
how the plant looked
at its very best.
Okay, so the day of the
explosion, what happened?
It was December 18, 1882.
7:00 in the morning, the first shift
had just gone on the job.
7:10, this tremendous explosion occurs.
Debris is shot up into
the air all over town.
It falls in peoples' yards.
Many people thought there
had been an earthquake.
Uh, buildings shook, windows rattled,
people ran out of their houses
to try to find out what was going on.
What had happened was
that three of the boilers,
which were used to generate steam
which powered the equipment
in the plant, had exploded.
The building came down on the
workers, fell down on them,
and a fire was started.
Some of the employees who
had escaped the explosion
tried to go in and see if
they could save some people.
Right.
Well, they got in and
found six people dead
- right at their workstation.
- Ah.
And the interesting thing about
that was they died in a position
which suggests they had no idea
that an explosion was about to happen.
They did find four people
who were still living
and they carried them out.
Three of those died.
So the number of people
killed in the explosion
- was nine people killed.
- Nine people killed.
- Yeah.
- And six right at their stations?
That's right. Six never moved.
Yeah. Right.
People must've been like,
"What the hell was that?"
Oh, absolutely.
People from all over town
were... they were just so
startled by this, that it...
they were running to the plant
to find out about what's...
And it so dominated the...
the economy, the area.
Right.
Everybody was concerned about it, yeah.
I feel, like, disoriented.
I am seeing people coming this way
towards the house from...
the dirt driveway from this direction.
Any idea when this was?
Like, the '20s or '30s.
I do here, like, a lot
of yelling and stuff.
There's a lot of commotion,
uh, going on. Like, angry.
Everybody's just
agitated and pissed off.
It's all crazy.
I saw several dead
people during my walk,
but the 20-year-old bully
concerned me the most.
He's white.
His face shape was more squared.
And he had a weird-kinda look.
Next, I described how
he torments the living.
He's in the closet
and he's, like, scratching his
finger down the closet door.
And it's just, like, a black hole.
In the room, there's a
kid being freaked out.
Amy, is this what you saw?
Yes, that's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to
meet Mike and Angie.
They're a great,
down-to-Earth couple, uh,
who are going through a
hell of a time in this house.
But this is the reason I took this case.
This is their son, Layne.
Now Layne is 7,
and he's basically scared
to death in his own house.
The activity here is
ruining his childhood.
And they're worried now
that even their daughter,
Hannelore, is startin'
to have these experiences.
Mike and Angie don't know
how to protect their kids,
and they're desperate for help.
So now that Amy knows a little
bit about your family dynamics,
I'll have her describe her walk for us.
There's several conscious entities
who are very active here.
The first one was an elderly woman
who has major anger control issues.
And I encountered her upstairs.
Her energy is really horrendous.
The living would feel
her stress and her fear
and this oppressive anxiety.
And she's always watching.
Uh, that's her big thing. You
know, Amy, you might've noticed
the upstairs is under construction.
Mike's been tryin' to turn
it into a master bedroom.
Why don't you explain to
Amy why it's not finished?
That is almost a
5- year-long project.
When I'm up there, I
have so much bad feelings,
I just can't get any work done up there.
It's like somebody's just sittin' there,
starin' right at me.
It freaks the hell outta me.
So this old, cranky woman...
any idea who she might've been?
She lived here with her husband.
They had a terrible marriage.
And interestingly, she beat him.
Oh, my.
Yeah. And he was, like, a big guy,
and she was really short.
She was, like, 5 feet tall.
I think she was from Ireland.
I got the name Mabel.
She was in her 70s when she died,
and I think it was cancer.
It's a long shot,
but one of the original
owners on the property
was an Irish woman.
Her name wasn't Mabel, but it was Mary.
Mary Barry was her name.
She and her husband, Bernard,
moved onto the property in 1890.
They were older when they moved here.
They were both in their 50s.
But the husband, Bernard,
started to lose his mind.
He started havin' dementia.
Mary may have had a hard
time takin' care of him.
In 1915, Mary came down
with terrible illness.
The official cause
of death is pneumonia.
Now the woman you saw, you
said might've died in her 70s.
Uh, Mary Barry was 82 when she died.
Okay.
Now she had a daughter
who died a horrible death
on the property as
well, only 3 years later.
Mm. Her name was Maryann.
She was takin' care of her dad,
and she got extremely depressed
and she starved herself to death.
Now Bernard stayed on the property
and he sank deeper and
deeper into this illness.
And he died about 10 years later.
Now, could Mary be the woman you saw?
'Cause you said she was
a housewife and Irish.
- I believe so, yes.
- Okay.
I do. Could she be the reason
Mike's so uncomfortable
on the second floor?
Yeah.
The other thing is, you're
kinda the same, like,
build and height as her husband.
So I wonder if she's...
Confusing me with him?
Yeah.
What else did you see on the walk?
So then I came down here.
I did not like it.
I felt, like, very dizzy.
And then I saw this
little man down here.
He was chubby. He was in his 50s.
And his favorite area is
over in the corner over there.
He likes that.
He can get very
aggressive with the living
when they come down here.
You'll actually kinda feel him, like,
barreling towards you,
invading your space.
And he also does shove and push.
Tell her the story about
the old man you saw.
I was down here putting
together the pool table,
and I just happened to look up.
All I could see was his
shoulders and his face
in that window.
And I sat here, petrified,
for about 5 minutes, just,
"Am I seein' what I'm seein'?"
And the reason that window's black
is 'cause I painted it black.
- Oh,.
- Yeah.
I feel like he's, like,
right here, creeping on me.
Tell her about
when you got bumped.
I was down her doin'
laundry, I was folding it.
Um, all of a sudden from the back,
he, like, bumped into me.
- Mm.
- Like, you can feel it.
I'm thinkin' you're seein' her husband.
- The husband with dementia?
- Yeah.
I wonder if this guy's watchin' you now.
Without a doubt.
He's always there.
We're not gonna provoke him.
So what else did you see?
Uh, went into the yellow room...
Which is Layne's room.
And, uh, I saw a
dead 20-year-old.
He's a bully,
and he likes to prey on
the weak and the vulnerable.
The thing about him, he
can take different forms.
So, like, I saw him
acting like a creepy elf.
He has, like, the pointed
ears, sharp teeth, long nails.
And his eyes can get really, you know,
he'll make 'em dark and evil-looking.
He can cause illness,
but what he would prefer to
do is punch or kick or slap.
He wants to be physical
with this person.
Well, that's why we're here.
Layne and I spoke for a long time,
and he had too many
experiences to go through.
When you mentioned
this elf-like creature,
Angie, tell Amy how Layne
describes how he sees the devil.
He hyperventilated.
Like, he couldn't even
talk about what he'd seen.
He'd explain it like he's
holding onto his toy chest
and, like... like smiling, like,
"Yeah, I'm gonna getcha."
Like, to scare him.
It breaks my heart to look at this,
but this is what he says he sees.
Wow.
And he said to me, it's the devil.
I had a sketch done of what
I saw goin' on in the room.
Oh, this poor kid.
Oh, my God.
Sorry.
It's just not fair,
you know?
That it scares him,
and I can't protect him.
Now Layne told me that
he thinks he's open.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Really?
He talks like he's 40.
And it scares kids away.
I got a message from a
parent saying that they just
don't want their child
to hang out with Layne.
Him sounding
like a 40-year-old
is pretty common with
sensitives 'cause basically,
they've really been
surrounded by subject matter
that is way beyond their years.
The dead come and they show and tell you
their entire life story...
Whoa.
...before they can move on.
So we think Layne's a medium.
Yeah.
I then followed the dead
guy into the master bedroom.
I saw him with a living woman
and I saw the dead man being
sexually inappropriate with her,
maybe putting sexual
thoughts into her mind.
In the bathroom, uh, if I
take showers late at night,
there's definitely a male in there,
to the point where it was after midnight
and I yelled, "Get out!"
I also felt this guy
would make this living woman
feel restless and anxious,
and I saw her pacing around.
And she's having weird,
intrusive thoughts,
like she wants to run
away and leave this life.
I do have, um, restless
nights, lots of restless nights.
Okay.
Do you have any idea who this
guy might have been in life?
I know he had a very bad
life, very rough life.
I got that he was from
the '30s and the '40s.
Uh, a bully in life,
just like he is in death,
and he either dropped out
of school or was kicked out.
I wasn't sure I got
the whole story on that.
Um, he was in and out of prisons.
And I saw him with oil and
wrenches and in a garage,
so I think he worked on cars as well.
That was like,
his... his thing.
Uh, and I'm not sure
when or how he died.
You said the guy was
in and out of prison,
high school dropout, worked on cars.
So I do have one guy in my
research that fits that bill.
In 1955, there was an
8- year-old girl named Janice May
who was found beaten
and sexually assaulted
4,000 feet from your property.
I got a photo of her here.
She was unconscious but
alive, taken to the hospital,
and died an hour later.
They ended up arresting
a 29-year-old male
by the name of Lloyd Miller,
who was a taxi driver in town.
I got a picture of this guy right here.
Oh,.
Now, this guy sounds a lot like
the guy you met in Layne's room.
He was a high school dropout,
he was in the Coast Guard
and the Army, but went
AWOL three separate times.
In his early 20s, he
stole a car in California
and spent 7 months in a prison farm.
His dream was to work as
an auto mechanic in Detroit,
but he drifted from job to
job, mostly as a laborer.
After the murder, they
found him 150 miles away
on his way to Detroit,
and they arrested him.
After 2 days of interrogation,
he confessed to the murder.
Now later on, he recanted
and said he was coerced
into this confession,
but he was convicted
and sentenced to the electric chair.
Now eventually, it was found
that the prosecution
fudged some of the evidence.
In 1967, the Supreme Court
overturned his conviction.
He was a free man.
He wind out moving to
Mexico, got married,
and became a minister.
- Are you freaking kidding me?
- No.
He came back to the States
and he died in Reading,
Pennsylvania, in 2013
at the age of 86.
Oh, my gosh.
Wow.
All right, now do you
think this guy could be Miller?
I had a sketch done of him, so...
All right.
Well, he's 29 in this photo.
Wow.
Take a look at this.
Oh.
Whoa.
Like... to me, it's identical.
Like, the nose, the lips...
The... the
nose and the lips is...
The eyebrows.
So this son of a [bleep]
Is the one acting like
a devil to a 7-year-old?
Yes.
This guy totally did this.
I want to grab the son of a
By his throat right now.
I'm really pissed off.
It's on.
So this son of a
Is the one acting like
a devil to a 7-year-old?
Yes.
This guy totally did this.
I want to grab the son of a
By his throat right now.
I'm really pissed off.
It's on.
So why is this dirt bag here?
When he died, he came right back
to his favorite memory
and his happiest moment,
which would be killing that child.
And then you guys moved in.
And he's drawn to Layne
because of his abilities.
And then the sexual thing
is coming out, unfortunately,
in... in your direction.
So, Mike and Angie, when we spoke,
you guys told me family comes first
and you'd do anything
to protect your kids.
Now I'm gonna find out
exactly what that's gonna take,
and for that, I'm gonna
turn it over to Amy.
The main person I want involved
is to be a male who's a medium.
And I want this male to
be a pretty tough cookie.
I want him to then deal
with the elderly female.
This is going to be a process,
and it's probably not gonna
be a pleasant one for him
because he does need to
be aggressive with her.
Once she goes, her husband'll go.
Then I want him to come
back with a demonologist
to get rid of him.
And I don't think he has
any intentions of moving on
because he is perfectly
happy where he is.
That's when the demonologist
is going to take over,
and that person will perform
an exorcism of the location.
And they will remove him
and send him on his way.
So once all that's taken care
of, I want you to buy a lock
and put it on Layne's closet door.
Putting it on will give
him a sense of empowerment,
where he's taking
control of the situation
and he's locking them in
there and away from him
so they can't invade his space.
The other thing is,
is I'll be sending you
some guided meditations.
And these guided
mediations are very simple
and they are for balancing,
grounding, and protection.
They're so basic, but
they're so important.
He needs to integrate
these into... into his life.
Will he ever have a normal childhood,
or is this gonna be something
he's gonna have to deal with?
Well, yeah, he's gonna
have to deal with it, like,
his whole life.
Now Hannelore,
you consider her somebody
that's gonna have abilities,
or is she just open because of her age?
Right now, it's just because of her age.
When might they find out when
If she's gonna be like Layne?
Between 5 and 8.
At least we'll know how
to handle it, you know,
with her, doing it with him.
Sounds like a little bit
of work, but I'm on it.
And this solution is
gonna help them both.
Are you gonna take Amy's advice?
- Oh, yeah.
- Absolutely.
- No doubts.
- Okay.
Mm-hmm.
I really hope Mike and Angie
follow my advice and contact
a male medium and demonologist
to remove the dead
terrorizing their family.
Once they're gone,
Layne can learn to manage his abilities,
and this family will find the peace
they've been searching for.