There's all kinds of
[bleep] going on out here.
I'm terrified to be in my own home.
There is a man with a
double-barreled shotgun,
lots of violence.
Why were you
willing to talk to me?
You were a suspect.
I think she was murdered.
This property was soaked with blood.
I just hear death.
Yeah. We're not supposed to be here.
There's a dark presence.
My name is Amy Allan.
These things, they're freaking out.
They're from hell.
I see dead people.
They were being hunted.
I speak to dead people.
They were setting people
on fire, burning them alive.
And they speak to me.
Her neck got broken.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I hear a gunshot.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Something's not right here.
And I know every person,
every house, has secrets.
- It's not safe here.
- It's my job to reveal them.
Are any of them buried on the property?
They're all buried here.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
- Until the very end...
- I can't do it no more.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Holy [bleep]. Look at this.
Or time to get out.
It does not have a happy ending.
Something kills people here.
I'm out here in the small
town of Concrete, Washington.
It's about 2 hours north of Seattle.
I got a call from a lady
who sounded hysterical.
She was crying on the phone,
saying whatever's in the house
is destroying her health,
ruining her marriage
and making her feel like
she's losing her mind.
She doesn't know where to turn,
and we're her very last hope.
Before Amy arrives, I clear the area
of anything that could
influence her findings.
This home is filled with family photos,
so it's important that I
cover or remove them all.
When I'm done, the location
will be ready for tonight's walk.
There's definitely
something strange
down the street.
What the [bleep]?
There's, like, a, um,
energy field or something.
I think somebody put this
up, put this barrier up.
I don't know how [bleep]
big this thing is.
You know, there was,
like, a lot of violence,
lots of violence, lots of violence.
There's all kinds of
[bleep] going on out here.
Now, Melissa, when
we spoke on the phone,
you were almost in hysterics.
I'm terrified to be in my own home.
It's like living in a nightmare.
Do me a favor and just
start from the beginning.
- When'd you get here?
- Um, we came in 2006.
My husband was transferred
up here with the military.
- Okay.
- We found the land,
and we had the home built.
- All right. So the house is new.
- Yes.
Okay. Do you know anything
about the history of the land
that the house sits on?
I know there was a woman next door.
I know she had her throat slit.
Wow. So I'll look into that.
That's pretty interesting.
This is a big house.
Who exactly lives here with you?
This is a picture of, uh, my family.
This is my husband,
Brandon, and my son, Taylor.
He's 20.
Up until about 2 months
ago, he lived here.
So what exactly is
happening? What's going on?
Sounds, uh, banging,
shadow figures,
apparitions, being touched.
It's getting worse and worse and worse.
Did you hear that?
No.
It went right by my ear,
like "Shh," telling me to be quiet.
Well, you're not gonna be quiet.
So whatever's here can go to hell.
All right? All right?
I'm here with you now.
Nothing's gonna happen.
Take a deep breath
'cause you're shaking.
Come on, with me. Ready?
- Okay.
- I trust you.
Okay. Good.
Nothing in this house is gonna
stop me from doing my job.
See? You feel like you're going crazy
'cause other people don't hear it.
And then, they go,
"Oh, she's just nuts."
I'm not saying that, am I?
- Okay?
- Okay.
Hmm?
All right.
There's, like, a
lot of people talking.
I heard voices in the dark.
And they're yelling and
screaming about this wave
of illness.
There are so many people.
I don't know who these damn people
are in the [bleep] darkness.
They seem to be in this
area of containment.
I'm wondering if they
hear people around.
You know, if they hear
people around their house,
they've gotta be hearing people talking.
They've gotta be hearing conversations.
It's pretty [bleep] bad.
Too much going on.
You said that you
think whatever's going on here
is affecting the marriage.
We used to be really strong.
It seems whatever force is
here is trying to divide us.
My health, um, is rapidly declining.
I have bad osteoporosis.
I see a specialist for my throat.
They say I have vocal cord dysfunction.
But actually, I feel like I've
been choked by what's ever here.
Did you have any of these
symptoms prior to moving here?
No.
I was healthy.
I think it's trying to kill me.
Okay.
These dead people in
the dark, they're so sick.
The living are feeling some
of these physical symptoms.
Oh, I don't feel good.
Really bad, really bad.
This is fear.
This is fear, like,
uh, you're so afraid. You're so afraid.
You're so afraid that you,
like, you know, you get sick.
You're [bleep] sick.
Terrified. [Bleep] terrified.
Terrified.
Okay. What's going on?
Hearing voices, multiple.
Is it male, female?
Two females arguing, really mad.
What about the TV being
on? Anything like that?
No. Everything was shut off.
All right. So you're hearing voices.
What else is going on?
Had a woman sit on the
bed and try to touch me.
Okay. Can you describe her for me?
She had long hair. It
was like a skeleton face.
Okay. So this is something
that was meant to scare you.
Yeah. She sat down on the bed,
and she reached out for me.
She said, "You're gonna die."
Relax. Just hold my hand. Relax.
I'm hearing a woman outside.
I think she was murdered.
There's a man, uh, with a, uh,
double-barrel shotgun.
And then, there's these two guys.
They're like... They're bullies.
And they don't wanna talk
about the... the lady at all.
I don't know what's going on here.
This dead woman, who crawls all around,
I see her crawling into bed.
She does, uh, wrap herself around,
uh, this living, uh, woman, I believe.
And it's not good for a living person.
Why?
The living person is taking
on that dead person's energy.
So they can start acting
like the dead person.
They'll take on
mannerisms, speech patterns.
And then, that makes the
living person [bleep] sick.
Has anything else happened?
I was taking a bath 2 nights ago.
Got out of the bathtub,
felt burning on my leg.
- Okay.
- I looked down.
And I had scratches.
They were deep.
It hurt.
Wow.
I gotta say, this is probably
one of the more severe
cases we've worked on.
Just make it go away and
make it stop hurting me.
I will. We're gonna take care of it.
- Okay.
- It's okay.
I know.
The two bullies,
I think that they are around
when the chick strays.
They have to get her back
because she belongs to them.
But the living go through something
when they [bleep] retrieve her.
What happens to them?
I think the living person
would feel potentially like,
you know, they're being
grabbed or touched.
They feel the anger.
They feel the pressure.
They feel like all of this
is happening around them.
Okay. So I
understand you're a vet.
I am. I spent, uh, all of 2004
in Fallujah, Iraq, with the Marines.
I was talking to your wife.
And, uh, she got real upset.
She thinks that whatever's
here is trying to kill her.
I can't say it's not.
'Kay. So what about yourself?
- Any experiences in the house?
- Yeah.
Okay. So tell me about them.
I would get this neck pain.
It felt like someone had me,
but with a rope around my neck,
was pulling me up in the air.
I couldn't breathe, and I
could start tasting blood,
undeniable taste of blood.
And I've tasted blood in my
mouth a lot over my lifetime.
How long did it last?
That experience can last
anywhere from 5 to 10 minutes.
It's happened multiple
times, Steve, multiple times.
Yeah.
- So anything else?
- Yeah.
Uh, I was sitting there, watching TV,
and felt something weird.
Just looked up and
looked out the window.
And when I looked out the window,
at that second pane up on
that window right there,
was a child's face looking in at me.
Now, when you saw the face,
did you think it mighta been
some kid in the neighborhood
and go out and check.
Um, we don't have any neighborhood kids.
You think you're losing your mind.
You do. You think you're
absolutely going crazy.
Okay. I'm afraid to even ask
what other experiences you've had.
- But, uh...
- My wife and son had gone out,
and I was sitting here on the couch.
And everything was fine.
When I looked up, there
was a black...
There was a black shadow
thing standing right here
in front of the TV, clear as
you are right now in front of me.
I looked right at this thing,
and I couldn't see through it.
And it scared me so
bad that I... I gasped,
and I leaned back in the chair,
and I looked down.
When I looked back up, it was gone.
You all right?
Sounds crazy, dunnit?
Your job to protect... How
do you protect something
you can't protect against?
I'm seeing this other guy.
He's a weirdo.
And when I first saw him,
he looked like a shadow crawling
up the wall, onto the ceiling.
And then he shows me his face.
He just says he's the manager.
I oversee the operations.
He likes the ceilings.
He's all about the ceilings.
They could see him as,
like, a translucent male
or if they see, like,
just a little shadow that
moves on the ceilings.
He likes to feel like
he's on top of people.
He's always watching everybody.
He's gotta know everything
at all [bleep] times.
So, Tamee, I understand that
you used to live next door here.
- Yes.
- All right.
Lived 140 yards from here.
Okay. When did you move?
- Two years ago.
- Okay. Why?
I had a lot of experiences in the house
- that I couldn't explain.
- Okay.
Can you tell me some
experiences you had?
Um, one of the things that,
um, really made me
fearful for my life, um,
and my children...
I would get so sick.
So what kind of illnesses
are we talking about?
I would get horrendous
stomach pains often.
- Okay.
- I couldn't stop throwing up.
I hardly could breathe.
And since I've moved,
I have not had any stomach problems.
Listened to Melissa today
and what she had to say
about her health issues.
A lot of it sounds similar
to some of the stuff
she's going through.
Everybody's health is failing
around here, everybody.
Interesting.
Did anything else happen?
It seemed our moods and
attitudes were affected.
We were very, very angry.
And we're not angry people.
Did you ever bring any,
uh, priest or preachers
into the house to bless
it or anything like that?
I did talk to the local tribes.
I was told that this used
to be Native American land
before white people settled here,
that it was soaked with blood and people
shouldn't live on this property.
Well, I don't like it out here.
Hm-mm.
I just hear death.
I think that,
if you come here, you're tainted.
How would being here affect the living?
It would seem like it could
potentially drive people insane.
I don't think it's a good
place for anything alive.
And I'm kind of freaked out.
What I'm getting is that, if
you enter this space, you're...
you're kind of, like, doomed.
Melissa mentioned someone got murdered
on the original property line.
So I made some calls,
and the story checks out.
Only thing is, the cops won't
talk to me about it 'cause
it's still an open case.
So I'm heading over to
meet with a local historian
who's looking through the original case
files for me to tell me
exactly what happened.
What do we know about the victim?
- The victim was Vicki Silves.
- Okay.
Vicki was an accountant
at a local company.
She was actually married to a gentleman
by the name of John Silves.
And here's actually a couple
of their wedding photos.
Do we have any idea
when they got married?
1993.
They moved to Concrete in 1996.
And shortly after
coming to Concrete, uh,
their marriage starts to fall apart.
And then, John ended
up moving back to, uh,
Port Angeles, where
he worked as a trucker.
How's the murder take
place? What happened?
The morning of December 8, 1997,
she had been known to
be very prompt to work,
and she didn't show up.
So the manager for the
company became very concerned
and sent a, uh, coworker
over to check on her,
where he found her dead in
her gravel driveway and...
and then covered her with a blanket.
- Uh, the first attempt...
- Whoa, whoa.
The coworker covered her with a blanket?
- Correct.
- All right.
So he contaminated the
crime scene right away.
He did.
I have her, uh, death certificate here
that describes her cause of
death of acute exsanguination.
So she's stabbed in the
neck. She bleeds out.
Yes. I was able to
get the first 40 pages
of the police report on the murder.
What it described was, there
was no sign of forcible entry.
The door was opened about 6 to 8 inches.
- All right.
- All the lights were on.
The interesting thing was
that she was laying there
with a large pool of blood,
but her shoes were 20 feet away.
All right. So, Eric,
there's a lot of stuff here.
But do you know when the
last time she was seen alive?
Yes. Vicki was seen alive at a party.
There were 4 people that were
at that party besides Vicki.
Uh, two actually would
become important to this case.
We have Ray Valeton and a Richard Brink.
Vicki had gotten fairly drunk,
and Mr. Brink says that
he would take her home.
According to him, when they get there,
they did a little more drinking.
And according to him,
they'd be kissing one minute,
and then she'd be
cursing at him the next.
He apparently got uncomfortable
with this and left the house
about 1:15 in the morning.
He's putting himself at the crime scene.
So what happens next?
So the other guy in
the party, Ray Valeton,
he is the alibi for... for Mr. Brink.
He says he just happens to know
that Mr. Brink came home
at 1:30 in the morning.
All right. That's not much of an alibi.
I would have to say
that you're not mistaken.
Okay. Now, what about the ex-husband?
So the ex-husband,
John, uh, actually did
have a really good alibi.
He had been in Port
Angeles when this happened.
Plus, he took a
polygraph test and passed.
Okay. So was anybody arrested
and brought to the
grand jury on this case?
Nobody was ever
arrested for this murder.
Wow. And this is still
an open case today?
It's an unsolved case today, still open.
As far as I know, there
is nobody working the case.
That's a shame.
Try to get more on the bed lady.
She's so [bleep] confused
about how she died.
Do you have any idea when this was?
It doesn't feel like that long ago.
Even the guys, like,
they don't feel that old.
And she died horribly.
The assault is outside, raining, dark.
She was [bleep] blindsided.
Up until, really, the end,
she was just like, "What the?"
There's pain, mm,
to the left eye, uh, very sharp...
and then to the head and neck area.
I can't breathe. What's happening?
Like, it's like she's
not registering anything.
So I actually managed to track down
the victim's estranged husband.
And I've gotta be honest,
I was surprised that he
was not only willing but excited
to talk to me about the case.
So I'm meeting him
back at the crime scene,
where he wants to tell me what
he thinks happened the night
his wife was murdered.
So, John, thanks for taking
the time to meet with me.
I know this is a pretty touchy subject.
Your wife was murdered right here,
- in this building back here.
- Yes.
Why were you willing to talk to me?
You were a suspect.
This is 18 years ago.
And this is a cold
case. And nobody's on it.
Nobody's doing anything about it.
And maybe somebody knows something.
So let's get on it. Let's
keep this case going.
Okay. Now, what kind of woman was she?
She was really outgoing.
But Vicki had a jealousy issue.
She accused me of
stuff that I never did.
I said, "That's it."
I said, "Baby," I says,
"I'm outta here." I says, "I'm gone."
Okay. She gets murdered.
How do you get notified?
I was in bed.
And, um, there was people
beating on the side of my house.
And I got up, went to
the door and opened it,
and here's a guy standing there with
a Skagit County Sheriff's
Department jacket on.
Before the night was over,
he had told me how much easier
it would be if I just confessed.
I said, "Confess to something I
never had anything to do with?"
So, John, exactly what was your alibi?
They found a receipt showing
that I was 150 miles away
the night of the murder.
Okay.
So, John, you mentioned on
the phone that you had a theory
about what might have
happened to your wife.
- Yeah, I do.
- 'Kay. What was it?
Well, I got this letter.
It was an anonymous letter.
The person who wrote it kind of
explains what... what happened.
- Vicki was an accountant.
- Okay.
And she evidently uncovered
a stealing operation
that had been going on for years.
And it involved a lot of money.
I believe she told the wrong person,
- and they took her out.
- All right.
This is pretty far-fetched stuff here.
But you think this mighta had
something to do with her murder?
I think so, yeah.
The two guys are all
in black, all in shadow.
The other guy, like, with
the shotgun, you know,
he's got, like, some hat on.
He's got, like, a long jacket on.
You know, he strikes me
as the type of guy who,
in life, obviously
held a power position,
somewhere like a con artist.
Do you know if these two guys
had anything to do
with killing the girl?
I am going to say she
knew these men, uh,
and was possibly friends with them.
So they have some sort of
relationship with the guy
that actually killed her?
Yes.
This poor chick,
whatever happened was
completely unexpected.
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity in your home,
go to the "Dead Files"
page at travelchannel.com.
Click on "Help Me, Dead
Files" to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
So far, I've got
a couple living in fear
on a property connected
to an unsolved murder.
But I need to see if there's
anything else that could
help my investigation.
Searching through old records,
I find dozens of people
who died of illnesses
on my clients' land.
But what really catches
my attention is the murder
of a Native American
less than 300 feet
from Melissa's property.
I called my old friend,
author Jeff Davis,
to look into it for me.
He says this murder was pretty brutal,
and it remains unsolved to this day.
So, Jeff, before we get to the murder,
who were the Native Americans
that inhabited this area?
Those people were the
Upper Skagit Indian tribe.
And I've got a photo of some.
Now, this was taken, uh,
probably in the early 1900s.
So obviously, the Native Americans
were displaced by the white
settlers at some point.
How did they do that?
There were a whole series of battles
throughout the Northwest from 1855.
All the way up to the 1900s,
- there were still tensions.
- Okay.
So at some point, obviously,
they were wiped out.
Exactly.
There is Native Americans here.
Boy, they don't wanna have anything
to do with this place.
Like, they're... It's, like,
repulsed, repulsed, very angry.
Anger is a understatement.
There's a lot of them.
But I think Native Americans
here put this barrier up.
What I'm getting from them is
that this is contaminated land,
and that no living
organism should exist here.
All right.
So tensions were high up into
the beginning of the 1900s.
Now, I know the homicide
happened in 1905.
Now, what do you know
about the homicide itself?
One of the Native Americans...
his name was Wapato Joe...
- went missing.
- Okay.
At this time, he was about 75 years old.
And he seemed to be liked by everybody.
About 2 weeks passed,
and then they finally
found his body, uh,
on the bank of the river.
How far from my
clients' property was it?
Uh, it was about 300
feet from the property.
How was he murdered? 'Cause
the article's kind of vague.
He had been shot through the throat.
It was at close range
because there were powder burns...
- Okay.
- Around that.
And the... the weirdest thing
was that somebody had cut off his hands.
That's a real cold-blooded
killing for a...
to a 75-year-old guy that...
You know, not bothering anybody.
Did they ever make an
arrest on this case?
No. No, nobody was ever arrested.
And from what I can tell,
they didn't seem to look very
hard for... for the killer.
This barrier, it promotes
violence and violent acts.
It seems to trap, uh, people
who died on this land here.
And I don't know if it
pulls people back here
who have died elsewhere.
The Native Americans,
they would throw crazy people in there.
And then they, like, go mad.
And they're, like, screaming
and yelling and hollering.
And they're, like,
jumping around all crazy.
And they're just acting like animals.
I saw several dead
people during my walk,
but the murdered woman
stood out the most.
She was probably about my height.
- She had very thin brows.
- Mm-hmm.
It was raining or had
been raining 'cause
she was completely wet.
Then, I described her wrapping
herself around a living woman
in the house.
The dead lady is really thin.
She is naked. And she's gray.
She's covered in mud.
She is kind of
coming up behind the living woman
and embracing her.
Is this what you saw?
Yes, that's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our findings
to each other and our
clients for the first time.
When I sat down with Melissa here,
the first words out of her mouth
were, "I'm terrified
to be in my own home."
She believes that whatever's
here is destroying her marriage,
her health, and she
thinks she's going insane.
This is her husband, Brandon.
Uh, he served with the Navy,
and he was with the
Marine Corps in Iraq.
He's been to hell and back, basically,
but never expected to come home
to a war zone in his own house.
They can't afford to leave,
but they're not sure
they'll survive if they stay.
So now that Amy knows who
you guys are, a little bit
about what's going on, she's
gonna describe her walk for us.
When I first approached the property,
I realized your house seems
to be located inside some kind
of energy barrier.
It seemed very negative
and very, very powerful.
There's a lot of dead
that are just on the land,
who are trapped.
And I was thinking that
it would be possible
that you guys would hear
them talking or hear voices.
I felt nauseous and this illness.
And the people
were saying that a lot of
them had died from this.
What I kept hearing out there
was that we were not
supposed to be here.
We've heard children.
Uh, I've heard a man, heard women.
I was sitting
on the couch, looked up,
and I saw what looked
like a child's face.
It almost looked like
a hologram projection,
a blue and white face looking
in the... in the glass.
- Okay.
- You mentioned sicknesses, right?
- Oh, yeah.
- One of the main reasons
we're here is because her
health has deteriorated.
A couple months ago,
I had an iron infusion.
My blood won't produce iron.
Vocal cord dysfunction,
now, all of a sudden, nausea,
vomiting.
I was pretty healthy
before we moved here.
Wow.
Now, the barrier thing, do
you know who put this thing up?
Native Americans put up the barrier.
And the reason why was, over
a very long period of time,
they noticed a pattern.
Some of the men from the
tribe would come out here.
And after exposure to this area,
they would basically go insane.
So they decided the best thing to do
was to block off this land
because they felt like it causes
mental illness, violent acts.
And what really freaked me
out was, any living person
who steps onto this land is tainted.
And what they were kind
of saying was, "Doomed."
Yeah, I feel like I'm going crazy.
I spoke to one of Melissa's neighbors.
They used to live here.
Her name was Tamee.
Her and her husband fought a lot here,
and she had mysterious stomach pains
that she couldn't figure out.
She moved away 2 years ago.
When she moved, she was fine.
Interesting. Interesting.
Now, when Tamee was living here,
she said she went to a local
Native American tribe for help.
And they told her, "Too
much bloodshed on the land.
We can't help you."
Really?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Now, let me tell you
a little bit of history
about what we're sitting on.
This was the Upper Skagit Tribe area.
They were around for
about 7,000 to 8,000 years,
- apparently, on this land.
- Holy.
Yeah.
I got a photo of them
from the early 1900s.
Now, 1840 is when the
white settlers came in.
This is when they started
to push these guys out.
After 50 years of fighting, eventually,
the white settlers wiped
out nearly the entire tribe.
We really have had a run of
bad luck since we moved here.
We used to joke and say, "Did
we move on Indian burial ground?"
Well, it's not a burial ground.
It's kind of their dumping ground.
So what else did you see on the walk?
When I got here,
I encountered a deceased
woman who was murdered.
There were these two men
that were constantly with her.
And they were preventing
her from speaking to me.
They didn't want me to
find out who had killed her.
I felt like she knew these two men.
They were around at
the time of her murder,
but they didn't directly do it.
And the only thing that I
got on the man who killed her
was that he did something
about, like, stealing money.
I got that it was relatively recent.
Uh, she died a horrible, horrible death.
And I felt extremely sharp
pains in the neck and the head.
I mean, it was awful, what he did.
I'm sorry, guys. I'm having a neck pain.
Yeah. It's bad here.
This happens a lot to me.
It just comes on out of nowhere.
I taste blood in my mouth.
I feel like I can't breathe.
- I feel like I'm choking.
- You okay?
- I'm okay.
- Are you sure?
Mm-hmm.
So you guys mentioned there
might have been a murder.
Literally, you can throw a
rock at where it happened.
So I looked into it,
and there was a murder of a woman.
Her name was Vicki Silves.
She and her husband, John,
moved next door in 1996.
When they did move here,
their marriage quickly went downhill.
And John moved out within a few months.
On December 8, 1997, Vicki
failed to show up for work.
So her boss sent a coworker to the house
to see if she was around.
When he came here,
he found her in the driveway
in a pool of her own blood.
Now, you felt neck pain.
She'd been stabbed in
the neck multiple times.
I got a hold of the
death certificate here.
Now, it's still an open case.
And I was only able to get 40 pages
out of a 160-page case folder.
She had been at a party that night,
and she was invited there
by a guy named Richard Brink.
Apparently, she got drunk.
And this guy, Richard Brink,
walks her back to the house.
He admits to the cops that,
when he gets there,
they start making out.
She was very flirtatious all night.
And then, she'd get violent with him.
And then, she'd be okay again.
Brink told the detectives that
he got fed up with her behavior,
and he decided to leave.
But he said, he left her, she was alive.
He was never arrested.
I tried tracking him down.
I figured, let me talk to him myself.
Uh, he's dead.
He died in 2003 at the age
of 47 of a heart attack.
But the other suspect was the husband,
who she was estranged from.
I spoke to him, and he had
a really rock-solid alibi.
He was at least 3 hours away
the night she was murdered.
He couldn't have been here
when the murder went down.
I don't understand why the cops
didn't take a closer look at Brink.
But what I found interesting
was that, about 18 months
after Vicki was murdered,
John's mother got an anonymous letter.
Basically said that she was
working at a local company,
and she found out that
people were stealing money.
And she told the wrong person.
And then, they had her killed.
It's still an open case.
This theory is interesting to me,
just because of all the different people
that this dead female
was showing me were
involved in her death.
I know her killer is
dead because he's here.
You think this is the same
person you came across,
or you think it's somebody else?
I had a sketch done of her.
Take a look at that.
Yeah. It could be her.
They look similar.
You okay?
What do you think
when you see that face?
Do you know her?
I don't know.
Have you felt her in
your room, in your bed?
I can't breathe.
What I was seeing, that
she'll get into the bed,
and she'll wrap herself around you.
And the reason why she does that
is because she feels
safe from the two men.
The problem is... is that
being in close proximity
consistently with a dead person
can not only make you extremely sick.
It can also cause you to take
on the dead's personality,
mannerisms, speech patterns.
Melissa has changed a lot.
I told her just the other night,
I said she's not the
same woman I married.
She's a completely different person.
Sometimes, it's like
living with a stranger.
This woman sat
on the end of the bed.
She had, like, a skeleton face.
She said, "You're gonna
die," or "Do you wanna die?"
I couldn't... I couldn't figure it out.
I was too scared.
Okay.
I did have a sketch done of what I saw.
Oh.
Yeah. I know... I know that.
I have a... a lotta nightmares.
And I feel a lotta pressure on me.
It's like a snake.
She's been complaining
of a lot of chest pain lately.
She says it feels like a rubber
band's wrapped around her.
She's killing you.
When I sit down at the table at reveals,
I will, like, tap the
people and scan them.
What I saw around you was death.
When I sit down at the table at reveals,
I will, like, tap the
people and scan them.
What I saw around you was death.
You have a choice to make here.
I know the choice.
My god.
I can't breathe.
Sweetie, you're a fighter.
Listen, I know you two got more
than you bargained for tonight.
Um, the only good news is
that you know you're not crazy.
Uh, but to see if there's
a way out of this mess,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
This is, like, when my job really sucks.
Sometimes, there are
those places and locations
that just never should
have been inhabited.
And this is one of those places.
So, in this situation,
for your very survival,
you should leave.
And you should leave
as soon as possible.
So there's no way of putting up
a barrier or anything like that?
I mean, the Native Americans
knew that this place was...
was not livable.
And they put their garbage here.
Okay. So, if she leaves,
death would go away.
If you make this choice, yes.
If, for some reason, we can't go...
I know.
So if she moves away from here,
could she be like her friend
Tamee, happy and healthy again?
Yeah.
Melissa's gotta make
the choice to be healthy.
I'd have to send her,
and I'd have to stay.
I can't move. I brought my mother here.
I came back from the war, and
my mom wasn't doing too well.
She's kind of wasting away.
She wouldn't be able to leave.
- You know I won't leave you.
- Thank you.
I won't leave, I'll never leave you.
Been with you 22 years, won't leave.
I know it's a lot, but just
promise me you'll at least
think about...
- Oh, yeah.
- The advice.
Promise you.
- Okay.
- I understand.
I think Melissa understands, as well,
the... the gravity of the situation.
We've gone through hell
since we've moved here.
But I was hoping there
was gonna be a way out.
The only way Melissa
and Brandon can be safe
is to move as far away
from this land as possible.
If they do that, they'll free themselves
of the evil surrounding them
and lead a healthy and peaceful life.