There's a lot of people running
around in here, like, mad.
We've had people run
out of here screaming.
I think they might feel trapped
and like they can't breathe.
I've seen an apparition
of a little girl.
All these dead people, they're
feeding off of living energy.
This whole area is a battlefield.
What's going on?
I felt like he was
gonna choke me to death.
This guy, he's not good.
There's a dark presence.
My name is Amy Allan.
These things, they're freaking out.
They're from hell.
I see dead people.
They were being hunted.
I speak to dead people.
They were setting people
on fire, burning them alive.
And they speak to me.
Her neck got broken.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
I hear a gunshot.
- I rely on my partner.
- I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
Something's not right here.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
It's not safe here. It's
my job to reveal them.
Are any of them buried on the property?
They're all buried here.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end...
I can't do it no more.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Holy [bleep] Look at this.
Or time to get out.
It does not have a happy ending.
Something kills people here.
I'm in Waipahu, Hawaii,
just northwest of Honolulu.
I got a call from a guy named Jeff,
who says he's got trouble in paradise.
Now, he runs a museum on
an old sugar plantation.
But business was so slow,
he agreed to open up a
haunted house attraction.
Since then, all hell's broken loose.
He says, if we can't find a solution,
he's gonna have to shut the place down
before somebody gets seriously hurt.
This is a museum with
more than a dozen buildings.
I've got to clear all of them
of any artwork, photographs
or religious symbols
so Amy is not influenced
by anything she sees.
When I'm done, the location
will be ready for tonight's walk.
I'm feeling a lot of stress here.
It feels like these dead
people are very stressed out.
I'm seeing, like, a
tall, glass enclosure.
And all these dead people were in it.
It said, "Do not let them
out. They are my pets."
Then, I hear,
"The earth here is as
alive as a human, more so.
Listen to its heartbeat."
And then, I hear, "The earth
has been asleep for 1,000 years,
and it's waking up."
Hey, Jeff. This place is amazing.
This is like a small city out here.
How many buildings
altogether do you have?
Do you know?
- Uh, about 22.
- 22?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
We've never done an
investigation like this.
I can tell you that.
Tell me, what's the
story? What's going on?
We've had numerous
incidents with my volunteers,
with my staff, with the general public.
And we're starting to
get a reputation for being
really a hotbed of paranormal activity.
Now, Jeff, you mentioned on the phone
you allowed a haunted
attraction to come in.
That's correct.
I partnered with one of my friends, Noa.
So why would you do that?
Well, because we wanted
to get younger people here,
get them interested
in their own history.
So obviously, we're here.
So something backfired.
We've had a lot more activity.
We have school children here.
We have seniors.
It's becoming a real problem.
Okay, so tell me about
some of the experiences
people are having.
People have been seeing apparitions.
They've been seeing spirits.
Some people have been touched.
We've had workers who have
volunteered for a night
and never come back.
People run out of here screaming.
I feel very, very bad about it.
I feel like perhaps it's been my fault
partnering with Noa.
I'm ultimately responsible for that.
So what if Amy turned around
and said you need to
shut down this attraction?
Honestly, if we had to
shut down the whole thing,
I'm not sure that we would survive that.
Okay.
Oh, boy.
There are two types
of dead here...
the ones who stay inside and
the ones who stay outside.
The outside ones are the problem.
Yeah. They're mad.
And they've got issues.
They don't want us here.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
They are mostly out here, these people.
They stay pretty much
outside all the...
Pretty much all the time.
I don't think they like the people.
So they stay outside.
One of the things that they
do to the living here is,
obviously, they take their energy.
It's got to be difficult, I think,
for many people to be here
because I think you would
feel immediately drained.
So, now, what about
your own experiences?
Well, I have had an experience
right in this house, right here.
I was speaking to a tour
group in front of the kitchen.
And a couple of pots banged together.
Okay.
Were the windows open,
wind going through there?
No.
All right. Anything else?
Yeah. One night, I
was here with a friend.
And we were walking along the sidewalk.
And I looked down, and I noticed
that there were three
shadows instead of two.
And I knew which shadow was his
'cause he was wearing a baseball hat.
So I started to move to figure
out which shadow was mine.
And in between us,
there was another shadow.
A man, woman? Do you have any idea?
You know, in that
area, we've...
we've had other shadow activity.
And people always seem
to think it's a male.
Now, you said other people
have seen this shadow.
Is that common?
Yes, other people have
seen the shadow running
and felt somebody brush past them.
Let me ask you a question as far as
what you're hoping to get
out of this investigation.
I've been running this
thing for nine years.
But now, we're at a point
where we've had so many problems
that I don't know what to do.
I want to be sure that the public,
that my volunteers,
that my staff is safe.
Okay.
There's a man. And he
doesn't want us here.
I'm definitely feeling,
like, a push, like, "Ahhhh."
He's, like, this drunk guy, wasted.
I think that people
would have, possibly,
experiences with this man.
He's very solid.
I think they might feel trapped
and like they can't breathe.
The wasted guy's in the tunnel.
And what he's doing is just
bouncing back and forth,
all along in there.
I think that people would
probably see him like a shadow,
but in human form.
So, Noa, I was talking to Jeff.
And he was explaining to me
about how bad the
activity's gotten here.
And he seems to think that it started
when you guys started doing
the Halloween-type tours.
You agree with that?
I'm starting to believe
there's something.
A few actors working for me
actually quit because of...
- What's happened?
- Something, yeah.
Have you had any experiences
at all that you can't explain?
Yeah. I've had a few.
Okay. Tell me about them.
I would see the curtain go up and down.
It looked like the curtain actually,
like, was lifted up
and dropped, you know?
And you're positive nobody
was in the house at the time?
No. Nobody's in the house.
The doors are locked usually.
That's why.
Okay. Anything else?
I've seen an apparition
of a little girl,
maybe, like, around 4 or 5 years old.
Did you get a color hair description?
No, no. Maybe, like, black.
- It was a darker color?
- Yeah.
My partner says, when people
do these kind of attractions,
they're antagonizing the spirits
and the dead that are here.
Yeah. I thought about that.
But, you know, pretty much
the whole state of Oahu is,
like, a believer in this
kind of superstition.
What if she turned around and said
you guys need to shut this down,
or people are gonna get hurt?
Wouldn't really care. I
wouldn't listen to her.
I mean, we'd still be doing it.
I would still continue.
Yeah. I don't think these, you know,
many of these dead people
really want to be here.
There's an indication that,
somehow, they were
trapped here by someone.
People would have a really hard time
with the dead out here.
They're very [bleep]
present and pretty powerful.
And then, the ones outside,
they hate everybody
else, like, passionately.
And they would really like
to kick the other
deads' asses out of here.
They want to get rid of the living.
They were here first.
They want this back.
So, Moira,
talking to Jeff, he seems
to feel guilty about what he started
with this ghost tour thing,
that it was a bad idea.
Do you agree with that at all?
I agree. I didn't think
they should have done it,
energize more spirits
in different houses
and got them to be really active.
Can I assume you've
had experiences or not?
Yes.
We seen a shadow by the Portuguese House
of a man, and you could fully see him.
And he just, poof, vanished.
Okay. Anything else?
So, we walked over to the Social Club,
and we were standing
outside after a tour ended.
And a door was
latched open, and it...
Someone unlatched it,
and it just slammed shut.
And some people started running.
Okay. What was the weather like?
Still, no wind.
- Like it is now?
- Yes.
Okay. Is there anything else?
There's a doll case that's in here.
And every morning,
they would come back in
to make sure everything's clean,
presentable for the next
tours during the day.
The doll would be out on the ground.
This case is enclosed.
So it got to the point where
you'd come in every morning,
and the thing would be
open, the doll would be out?
Yes.
Now, are you sure nobody
was playing a prank?
Yes.
How do we know that?
'Cause they always
close the windows and
lock everything up.
One day, someone thought
they saw a little girl
that was in here.
So we think that she's
been playing with the doll.
Okay, so you think the
spirit of a young child
might have been taking the
doll out to play with it
- when everybody went home?
- Yes.
That's kind of sad, actually,
when you think about it.
Yes, it is.
Moira, with all the stuff
that's going on here,
I've got to ask you, why are you
so interested in working here?
It's kind of important
to my side of the family.
My grandmother, she
worked on the plantation.
- This plantation?
- Yes.
Okay. So you're telling family history.
Yes.
Okay.
There's a lot of people here
who didn't get along
when they were alive.
And now, it's even worse
because they're dead.
All these dead people, they're
feeding off of living energy.
And all this combined energy
is creating poltergeist-type
of phenomenon,
things ending up in places
where they weren't left,
things flying across the room,
doors opening and closing,
and objects moving.
They're prepping for something.
Something's gonna happen...
something really bad.
All right, so now, it seems like
everybody's having experiences here.
But what about yourself?
I've had some experiences here, too.
Okay. Explain some of them to me.
Um, I'm pretty exhausted
when I leave here,
nauseated, dizzy.
Why do you think it's paranormal?
I'm really healthy.
So are you the only one having
these physical experiences here?
Oh, there's other actors, too,
that have either injuries or illnesses.
Okay. Anything else?
There were a few times
when I came home with bruises
on my body, unexplained.
Looks like a hand print,
like little fingerprints.
Having bruising could be
a million-and-one things.
But you're saying it
was the shape of a hand?
Mm-hmm.
Did you feel it?
No. Oh, no.
That's why I was
surprised when I got home
and I had that bruise.
Anything else?
Yeah, there was an experience
that sticks in my mind.
I got home from work,
and I had a choking
sensation out of nowhere.
And it was pretty scary.
And I started to pray.
And what happened?
It eventually went
away, after my prayers.
Oh, geez.
You okay?
What's going on? Um, I got attacked.
I'm, like, freaked out.
There's a guy, um,
and he doesn't want me here.
He's, like, really aggressive.
Like, first, I didn't know...
I didn't understand what was happening.
But he got really mad.
And so he was like,
grabbing me like this...
...really hard.
And I got scared
because I felt like he was
gonna choke me to death.
I think that he can
physically harm people,
choke them out or scare
the [bleep] out of me.
Like, I'm still scared.
Jeffrey's property is
on an old sugar plantation.
And you know what?
It doesn't take a homicide detective
to figure out where to
start this investigation.
I'm on my way back to the property
to meet a local historian,
who said the conditions
there were absolutely brutal.
What do you know about
the history of this place?
It was built in 1897,
and it stayed open for almost 100 years.
Wow.
It was about 10,000 acres,
extended all the way
down to Pearl Harbor,
which is that way.
There are close to 1,000
people that worked here.
All right. So do me a favor.
Paint the picture. What's
their work day like?
So, you leave before sunrise.
You spend the entire day
working on the plantation.
Back-breaking work.
Now, the people who worked here,
did they live here, as well?
Lived and died.
What were living conditions like?
Well, can you imagine
coming home to a house
that has a corrugated tin
roof and your floor is dirt?
The health conditions are
just unbelievably just filthy.
You were lucky if your
baby lived to see a year.
Geez.
Are these native Hawaiians
that are in this picture?
Native Hawaiians were
decimated by sicknesses.
And so plantation bosses,
the chief laborers,
had to go elsewhere to find
other people to bring here
to work the plantation,
like the Japanese, the
Chinese, the Filipinos,
the Puerto Ricans, Portuguese
and even the Koreans.
Okay, so now, with all these different
cultures and ethnicities here,
did they all live together?
What was the story?
According to this map, everybody
was separated by ethnicity.
Now, is that by the people
that worked here's choice
or by the people that owned the place?
People that owned the place.
They wanted to make sure that
these different ethnicities
didn't get together
and unionize and demand
better living conditions and better pay.
So they thought it was a better thing
to keep them segregated,
even to the point where
they began to pay people
a different rate
according to the ethnicity.
So, what was the purpose of
paying people differently?
To make sure that they
resented each other
and they didn't get along.
Okay.
These dead people
who are lined up outside,
they were, like, neglected
or mistreated or something
when they were alive.
I think that they were kind
of starving at some point.
They don't seem like they
had good clothing, either.
Doesn't seem like they
had good shelter, either.
They were outside a lot.
They're pretty old. I
don't know from when.
There's a lot of people here
who didn't get along
when they were alive.
And now, it's even worse
because they're dead
and they're all [bleep]
jumbled together.
Yeah. They're really mad.
Look, when you got that
many people packed together
under bad conditions,
there's definitely gonna be violence.
I had a retired detective
look into it for me.
Says she found at least 10 homicides
right on the plantation.
Chris, I don't think I've
ever handled an investigation
where I had at least 10
homicides in one location.
Here's some of them.
Okay.
Did any of these stand out to you?
Yes. April 5th of 1905.
A captain in the police department,
a lieutenant and four officers
are asked to assist a sheriff
in raiding a gambling
game on the plantation.
They arrested 11 Chinese laborers.
Okay.
All of a sudden, all hell breaks loose.
Police and the prisoners get surrounded
by the rest of the laborers
that are at the gambling game.
Okay.
Now they are being attacked
with clubs and sticks.
Shots are fired.
In the chaos, a laborer
named Chong Chi Fat
was shot six times and was killed.
Do we know who shoots him?
There was never a determination
of who actually shot the man.
Okay.
I'm just hearing people
yelling numbers or something,
some numbers.
But it's, like, you know, "Eight, nine,
two, zero, four, five, six! Ah!
Three, nine, eight!"
You know, like, somebody's
[bleep] yelling all this...
These numbers.
I'm hearing, um, a man
screaming and crying.
It feels like his back is broken.
Like, he is, like, on his forearms.
He's looking at the ground.
And there's something
on his back and his neck.
He's just [bleep] screaming.
Okay, so what was the other
homicide you were talking about?
Well, in May 1985,
we have a man that was
killed at a cock fight,
which was across from
the plantation housing.
And his name is Henry Cuba.
All right, so what's this guy
get killed for? What happened?
Mr. Cuba had gotten into
altercations with the guy
that was running the chicken fight.
And he also got into another altercation
and was acting belligerent
and out of control
with Jaime Fernandez.
Who's this Fernandez guy?
Just someone watching the fights?
Yes.
By the way you're
telling the story to me,
it sounds like this
guy showed up already
a little bit inebriated.
So what's the circumstances
of this guy getting killed?
Well, Fernandez went back
to his house, got his gun,
came back to the chicken fight
and shot him four times in the chest.
Okay. Is he D.O.A. right there?
And he died right there on the scene.
Okay.
That drunk dude is, like, wasted.
And he's, like,
running around, like,
just acting like a fool.
Hmm. He's a big guy.
He's not that old.
I'd say, like, you know,
between 30 and 40 years of age.
And he died...
This was fairly recently,
I would say within the last 20 years.
But he's yelling about the animals.
Like, all the animals died?
There's a lot of confusion.
Like, if you try to ask
him certain questions,
he gets very confused.
I really don't think that, right now,
he doesn't understand that he's dead.
If you need us to investigate
unexplained activity in your home,
go to the "Dead Files"
page at travelchannel.com.
Click on, "Help me, Dead
Files," to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
So far, I know a deadly
riot and at least 10 homicides
took place on my client's property.
But I need to see if
there's anything else.
Searching through old records,
I find the plantation shared
a border with Pearl Harbor
and that two people on Jeff's property
were actually killed during the attack.
I'm heading over to the
Naval base to meet with
one of the world's foremost
authorities on Pearl Harbor.
And he says Jeffrey's plantation
played an important role
in that dark day in American history.
Right here, this
is where it all started.
So, during the attack,
what am I seeing from
my client's property?
You are seeing aircraft
buzzing about you like bees.
You are seeing, in the distance,
the Pacific fleet being destroyed.
This whole area's a battlefield.
So where your clients were
was part of the battlefield.
There's indication that Japanese
aircrafts strafed that camp.
And probably from a Japanese
pilot's point of view,
it looked like a military camp.
The two killed on my property
during the day of the attack,
Is that from the Japanese fire?
It's not.
The indication is, it was friendly fire
that was raining down all
over the island of Oahu
from the anti-aircraft guns
firing at the Japanese planes.
Now, what can you tell
me about the victims?
There's a report that I have here.
It indicates a Hawaiian
girl, 3 years of age,
was hit by shrapnel.
She died within 10 minutes of
being admitted to the hospital.
And then, a 19-year-old
man, Tomaso Kimura,
suffered a shrapnel wound
that penetrated his brain.
He lost his life at
about 5:00 that afternoon,
December 7, 1941.
Oh, geez.
I'm, like, hearing
yelling, [bleep] screaming.
There's dirt and debris hitting my eyes,
blinding so many people,
like, so many people having this happen.
Like, this dirt and all this
[bleep] is hitting their face.
I can't breathe.
Awful breathing problems, asphyxiation,
incredibly dizzy and nauseous.
And I feel, like, lots
of sticks piercing my body
on my right jaw, my neck,
my left eye, my right side.
So, Daniel, I'm aware
that Japanese immigrants,
as well as Japanese Americans,
worked on the plantation.
Were they ever put in internment camps?
Yes.
After the attack,
there was a suspicion that
the local Japanese population
was somehow involved with it.
There was arrests made,
and they were interned.
The camp was established
on your property
that you're investigating.
It was known as Honouliuli.
And this is what it looked like.
It was over 160 acres,
barbed-wire fences
nearly eight feet tall,
eight guard towers.
It almost looks like a base.
What was the population like this place?
Well, there was two populations.
Initially, 322 Japanese Americans
were interned.
Later on, as the months
progressed into the war,
there'll be a population
of Italian Americans
and German Americans,
Koreans, were brought here
because they were considered
possibilities of disloyalty.
And here's some of their dossiers.
So, what were the conditions
like for these people?
Let's put it this way. They
called it Hell's Canyon.
They lived in tents. They
had latrines they went to.
It was hot, dusty, uncomfortable.
It would be over 90 to 100 degrees
in that canyon.
So, it starts out as a plantation...
And then a battlefield,
and then an internment
and prisoner-of-war camp.
Something about a camp.
I don't know. A bunch of people
talking all at the same time.
I can't understand any of it.
Somebody's freaking out about the camp.
Camp... Stop the
camp? I don't know.
Something like this.
You're just overhearing random snippets?
Yeah. They're having,
like, meetings, like,
"Should we talk about
these things or not?"
Oh.
I feel a lot of anxiousness,
stress, illness immediately.
It's like a [bleep] tidal wave of it.
There's a lot of people
running around in here
like mad, like mad,
prepping for something.
Something's gonna
happen. They need to talk.
They need to take care
of the situation promptly.
Something big, big, big is happening,
and they're freaking
the [bleep] out about it.
Whoo, so [bleep] stressful.
Holy [bleep]
My god, it's like whoosh.
Like, crazy, crazy, crazy.
I encountered many dead
people during my walk.
But the angry group outside
had me the most concerned.
I saw these people.
They were all lined up, side by side.
They were very upset.
Basically, they want to
destroy the living here.
They don't want anything to live here.
Is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients for the first time.
So, Amy, I'm sure this walk
must have been a little
disorienting for you
because the property here is so big.
Mm-hmm.
I don't want to give away too much,
but this place used to be
a major sugar plantation.
And now, it's a museum.
Now, this is Jeff.
He's been running the
place for almost 10 years.
This is Laura and Moira.
They both work here.
Activity is bad and getting worse.
And Jeff is concerned
that, if they can't stop it,
this important part of Hawaii's history
may not survive.
So with that,
Amy knows a little
bit about the location.
I'll ask her to
describe her walk for us.
When I first arrived, I
got a lot of information.
I was feeling the
emotions from the dead.
And they seemed very stressed out.
Then, I was seeing this
kind of glass dome structure.
And inside of it was all of the dead.
And I heard someone say,
"Don't let them out. These are my pets."
Well, might as well get right into this.
When Jeff took over the
museum, business was slow.
So a friend of his came with
an idea to turn this museum
into a haunted attraction for 10 nights
during the month of October.
And that's when activity went nuts.
Okay.
So that's why they called us in.
Now, tell Amy why you
thought you had to do this.
Young people aren't exactly
that interested in history sometimes.
So we thought a haunted attraction would
appeal to a younger demographic.
Moira, when we spoke originally,
you said you weren't
crazy about the idea
of this haunted attraction.
My parents and my grandparents
would tell me that there's
strange things that happen here.
My mom would tell me,
you know, "Be careful,"
that the spirits that was here
would probably attack a person.
Now, I talked to the guy
that runs the attraction.
His name's Noa.
I was thinking about
bringing him to the reveal,
but, honestly, it was a waste of time.
He told me he didn't really
care what you would have to say,
and nothing would convince
him that what he's doing
is a bad thing.
Jeff, on the other hand,
thinks he's opened a door.
And he thinks that they can't close it.
I'm really concerned about
the increase in activity.
And it's more confrontational now.
It's kind of in-your-face
and very direct.
Yeah, there's a lot of different
things going on as far as
how the dead are interpreting
what you're doing.
So some are irritated
and some are frightened
and some are confused.
I looked in the tunnel,
and I saw this man.
He was kind of a mess.
He had a special
attachment to this property.
He used to be here a lot.
I got that he was
probably in his 30s or 40s.
And he died fairly recently,
within the last 20 years.
And he was drunk when he died.
And what I got that the
living might encounter there
is hearing him bang into the
walls and things like that.
And I believe that they would see him
as a very, very dark, large shadow.
Tell Amy that story.
One day, I was walking with a friend.
And we were just walking down the path.
And then, I looked down,
and I noticed there's
only the two of us,
but there's three shadows on the ground.
And I just kept looking at
that as we walked down the path.
I was so surprised.
What I found shocking about the property
during my investigation
is the amount of homicides
and strange deaths
that occurred on the property.
One of the most recent deaths
may be of interest to you.
Now, back in '85, a group
of plantation employees
used to hold illegal cock
fights on the land here.
Now, there was a guy named Henry Cuba
who used to come here all the time.
May of 1985, he came here,
but he got into a fight
with the guy running the cock fight
and a couple of the patrons.
It sounded like he was pretty
belligerent, and he was drunk.
He gets into a fight with
this guy, Jaime Fernandez.
This guy gets mad.
He goes back to his house,
grabs a gun, comes back
and plants four in this guy's chest.
Wow.
And he kills him right here.
Now, you said the man
was between 30 and 40.
Cuba was 40 when he got gunned down.
I actually managed to track
down a photo from the family.
This is him, here.
This guy look familiar to you?
Yeah, totally. Yeah.
All right. So that's interesting.
At least you know who
the shadow might be.
Okay. So what else?
I was standing on the
porch, and I got attacked.
This person came up from
behind and to my side
and grabbed my neck.
Like, I was being choked
and was squeezing so hard.
And it was excruciating pain.
Then, he was standing in the doorway,
and he was, like, a dark,
tall, you know, shadow figure.
And I got that he, obviously,
doesn't want me here,
doesn't want anybody here.
He's aggressive.
I think that the living would
have experiences with him
and could possibly get physically hurt.
One night that I went home
after doing the attraction,
I had a choking sensation.
I just started praying, and I just said,
"Rebuke Satan in the name of Jesus."
- And it just went away.
- Mm-hmm.
And then, I also, another
night, had a bruise on my arms,
like somebody was grabbing me.
Now, does that sound like
something that this guy might do?
Yeah. And he is not good.
Anything else?
There's a lot of issues
here between the dead people.
The dead who stay outside,
they spent a lot of time
outside when they were alive.
And they still like to be outside
even though they're deceased.
They were telling me
that they were mistreated
when they were alive.
They didn't have good clothing.
They didn't have a lot of food.
And their shelter was not so great.
They didn't get along
that well with each other
when they were alive.
They're very unsettled.
They're very mad.
They're very angry.
And I heard, "The camp,
the camp. Stop the camp."
Okay, well, the history of
this place is pretty incredible.
There's two possibilities of
what you might have been seeing.
As I mentioned before,
the museum sits on the land
that used to be the
Oahu Sugar Plantation.
Right.
Now, the plantation ran
for almost 100 years,
from 1897 to 1995.
In the beginning, there
weren't enough local workers.
So the plantation
owners brought people in
from around the world.
Now, the conditions
these workers lived in
was horrible.
They lived in tin-roofed
houses with this heat
and, basically, dirt floors.
Now, you mentioned that
the different groups
didn't like each other.
Well, the plantation owners
were worried they may unionize.
So they made segregated camps.
And they would pay each
ethnic group a different wage
so that they would resent each other.
Now, there is one other possibility.
When this place was a plantation,
it actually touched the
shores of Pearl Harbor.
Now, when Pearl Harbor
was bombed in '41,
the Americans fired
at the Japanese planes.
And you had two fatalities
right on the property
from friendly fire.
The day after the attack,
martial law is imposed,
and the military rounded
up Japanese immigrants
and Japanese Americans,
and they placed them
in an internment camp
right on this property.
Oh.
And I got photos of that.
The conditions were so bad at this camp,
they called it Hell's Canyon.
As the war waged on,
not only did they bring
Japanese P.O.W.s here.
They brought in German, Italian,
and kept them separated
in the same camp.
So based on the
information that I provided,
who do you think you
might have ran into?
I think that they're
probably from both camps.
And I think they're from
different time periods.
Now, Moira, your grandparents
worked on this plantation.
Yes.
How's that make you
feel, hearing all this?
It's, like, sad.
We didn't even realize
how many of them were here.
It's sad to see them, you
know, get caught in here.
I wouldn't want to be caught here.
So now, the dead people on the outside,
do they interact with
the living in any way?
They feed off the energy of the living.
So I think that, when
people would leave here,
they would feel excessively drained.
Like, also, people would
feel stressed and anxious
because they are so angry.
The other thing that I got
is that they've become able to
interact with their environment.
And so they can make
doors open and close.
They're able to move objects
from one location to another
and also move objects,
like, in front of you.
Well, now you're hitting
on pretty much everything
these guys are experiencing.
Moira, tell Amy about the doll.
We have a doll. It's in a Japanese case.
How they built it was with
glass on both sides of the wood.
Every morning, when we came to
make sure everything was clean,
nothing was messed, the
doll would be outside.
Tell her about the
story right in this room.
We were standing outside on the porch.
So the door's really
heavy, and it was latched.
And all of a sudden, the
door just slammed really hard.
Everybody else jumped.
We saw some people run the other way.
Laura, tell Amy about
co-workers getting sick.
Getting dizzy, nauseated,
kind of a streak of the flu.
I'm pretty exhausted when I leave here.
So does that make sense?
Yes.
I did do a sketch
of some of the outside
people that I encountered
and how they are draining the living.
Take a look at this.
Oh, God.
Oh, my gosh.
Uh-huh.
That explains why I feel
the way I do sometimes.
What do these people want?
The majority of them feel
that they were here first
and this was their land.
So their common goal, the
people who live outside,
is to drive out everyone here.
They want the dead gone, and
they want the living gone.
Wow. Oh, my God.
How's that make you
feel, hearing all this?
Just really freaks me out.
I'm just stunned.
I can understand why
all this is happening,
to know how many spirits are here.
It's like they have no rest.
I don't know if I'd feel comfortable
coming back here to work.
One thing I've learned
this week is that Hawaiians
have a very different
attitude about the paranormal.
You believe in spirits,
and you believe in respecting the dead.
So I know you want to make
sure this place is safe
for both the living and the dead.
To find out how you can do that,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
I think that, if you do a few things,
it'll help a great deal.
The first thing that
I would have you do,
because you have such
an eclectic group here,
is to find various religious leaders.
And then, those
individuals would proceed
to do funeral rites from their faith.
This would assist the dead that are here
from that particular religion
to go ahead and move on.
Then, what I would have you do
is bring in maybe three
or four different mediums
to do a walk and see if
they find any dead people
that couldn't move on
because they don't have
a particular faith that they follow.
The mediums will help
those dead move on.
Okay, so, what about the
guy that's choking people?
I think that he probably
would prefer to move on.
But if you have any more incidents,
then you're going to need
to bring in an exorcist.
Now, as far as the haunted tours go,
maybe toning it down just a smidge.
How can we tone it down?
You know, maybe only having,
like, one or two of the locations open.
Yeah, that would be nice.
I mean, it wasn't as bad
when you first started.
The years pass on,
and it got more spooky.
It really got worse.
How's your boy, Noa, gonna
take this toning down stuff?
Well, I think we can work it out.
What are you shaking your head for?
I mean, I don't want to disappoint,
but I don't think he's gonna like it.
You gonna talk to him, or
you just gonna, you know?
Of course I'm gonna talk to him.
I mean, he needs us, you know?
Now, Laura, if Jeff
follows Amy's advice,
will you come back?
Yeah.
It's encouraging to
know that we can help
the dead that are here.
And that's, I think, what
our hope was to begin with.
It's been a real education.
I'll ask you first. You
gonna take Amy's advice?
Yeah, definitely.
I mean, to do nothing
would just make it worse.
Whatever will make this place better.
I'm gonna make sure he's gonna
do what he's supposed to do.
It's very important.
I really hope Jeff follows my advice,
or the dead will continue
to put all those who visit
in harm's way.
But I believe, if he
performs funeral rites,
brings in mediums and
tones down the haunted tour,
the dead will move on,
and this important
piece of Hawaii's history
can stay open for years to come.