I'm getting violence.
It could harm the living,
physically.
I feel like this house
killed my husband.
This female feels suicidal.
He was the love
of my life.
I blame myself
for him.
I could feel
a rope around my neck.
It felt like something
went through me.
I don't want anything
to happen to my daughter.
"This can't be happening.
No way."
This is not
a good situation.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's death here.
Don't want to
go down there.
I see dead people.
They hide in the walls
and they watch.
I speak to dead people.
She's definitely
a serial killer.
And they speak to me.
She's going
to torture them.
But there's only one way
to know if my findings are real.
They were all murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
So, is this the only time
you've been physically attacked?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
There's no question
in my mind
that he was talking
about Satan.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who do you think
possessed you?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end...
Well, you're not gonna
want to see this.
...when we uncover
if it's safe for you to stay...
Hell no!
...or time to get out.
Everyone is in jeopardy.
I'm back in Waxahachie, Texas.
It's a small town about
a half-hour south of Dallas.
I got a call
from a woman named Kim.
She sounds real broken up,
says whatever's in the house
killed her husband.
Now, her daughter is about
to move back in,
and she's terrified
it's gonna go after her, too.
She's desperate for
help and says we are
her very last hope.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area
of any leading information.
This home is filled
with family photographs,
so it's important that I cover
or remove them all.
When I'm done, the location will
be ready for tonight's walk.
Boy.
Somebody doesn't
want me over there.
Literally, I'm feeling like
I'm having to push
through energy to get there.
I'm feeling like
I'm being pushed away.
This is not a good situation.
I'm getting violence, violence.
Well, Kim,
I got to tell you,
this is an absolutely
beautiful home.
It sounds like
you're going through
a tough time here.
Why were you so desperate
for us to come?
As crazy as it sounds,
I feel like this house
killed my husband.
What did he pass from?
He died of
a malignant brain tumor
that was inoperable.
He eventually
became bedridden,
and he passed away
in the house.
And how old was he
when he passed?
45 years old.
Why do you think the
house had anything to
do with his tumor?
He was
a perfectly healthy man,
strong as an ox.
And then you just...
you die.
It's not fair.
No, it's not.
This is a picture
of my husband, Angel.
Had he been
diagnosed already?
No, that was within the year
before he was diagnosed.
Okay.
When did you guys
start having experiences?
From the very first moment
we stepped foot in the house.
While your husband
was alive, did you
guys do anything
to try to figure out
what was going on here?
We actually had a team come
and do a blessing.
When you say "a team,"
what do you mean?
Like a paranormal...
A paranormal team.
Okay,
so how did that go?
The atmosphere
felt lighter,
but it didn't last long.
Now, Kim, do you know
any history about the house?
I know that it was built
in 1915,
and that one of
the original owners,
T.W. Burleson...
Okay.
...was actually struck
by an automobile
across the street,
and he was killed.
Why did you want
this house so bad?
I saw the house
and fell in love with it.
Angel said that my dream
would be his
and he would learn
to love it.
But it wasn't something
that he was crazy about.
And he says,
"If it's your dream,
it will become mine."
I feel like I'm responsible
for his death
because if I hadn't
have been insistent
about moving
into this house,
maybe he would
still be alive.
He was the love
of my life.
I don't want you
to feel guilty.
Here, hang on.
Take this.
I do.
If it was just his time,
because things happen,
I can totally accept that.
But if there was something
attached to him,
in this house...
Yeah.
...that hurt him...
...I can't help
but blame myself.
And now you have your daughter
moving back in, right?
I can't risk
her coming back home
and something
happening to her.
I'd never forgive myself,
because I don't --
I blame myself for him.
I can't have anything
happen to my daughter.
Okay.
I need whatever it is,
if there's something here,
to be gone.
I think a living woman here
is suffering from depression.
I got a great loss.
Something happened
to somebody that they know,
and now this female
feels suicidal.
Somebody died in this area.
I'm not exactly sure where.
I'm hearing,
"Man, this is wrong.
This is so wrong.
No way, no way.
This is wrong."
Like, this can't be
happening, no way.
You spend a lot of time
up here?
Yes.
It was Angel's room.
Occasionally,
I come up here
to remember him
and feel close to him.
In fact,
those are his ashes.
- Right there?
- Yes.
Okay, so what's
going on up here?
We've heard
disembodied voices.
Okay, what kind?
The sound
of a little girl,
and we've heard
a woman screaming.
Now, the scream --
what did it sound like?
It sounded like
a woman was being hurt.
We even called the police
and had them come out.
They showed up,
searched the grounds,
and found no evidence
of a woman.
Anything else?
Yes, I've been pushed
down the stairs.
Okay,
tell me what happened.
I was actually walking
down the stairs
and felt two hands
on my back and shoved me,
and I went tumbling down
to the end.
How bad
did you get hurt?
I was bruised
and battered,
but not seriously hurt.
I mean, you're very lucky.
You could've broke your neck.
I saw a crazy old man,
like late 60s, early 70s.
He acts like an animal
with him crawling
on the ceiling,
crawling on the walls.
Well, he jumped down,
and he was, like, kind of like
doing an all-fours
kind of thing.
And he then went back up
on the ceiling,
and then he was
grabbing my hair.
So, I felt like that's something
the living here
might experience,
is having their hair
pulled or tugged.
I'm hearing children up here.
Little, little kids.
Somebody's screaming.
Piercing scream, female.
Okay, is this where
Angel passed?
Yes.
Do you
still sleep here?
Yes.
What about experiences
that you've had?
Several times,
I've actually seen
a shadow figure.
Describe it for me.
It's a tall, slim
shadow figure.
So, how are you so sure
it's not an actual person?
Because when it's a person,
there are distinct features,
and this was just
total blackness.
Anything else?
I was actually scratched
on my hand.
We were actually
having a discussion,
and I looked down,
and there were three
scratches on my hand.
And it actually felt
like my hand was on fire.
Okay, now,
what about Angel?
Did he have experiences
in here?
Yes, oftentimes
he would wake up
with bruises
and bite marks.
Here's a photo.
Geez.
Now, could this bruising
have come from the
medication he was on?
No, because that happened
well before he was diagnosed.
All right, did anything else
happen with Angel?
Yes, one night I awakened
to him standing over me,
and he looked or appeared
as if he was possessed.
Okay, so what
makes you say that?
It wasn't my husband.
One of the things
I called him was "Papi"...
Okay.
...and he loved that.
This person looked at me
and said, essentially,
"If you call me
'Papi' one more time,
I'll smack
the hell out of you."
The next morning,
he remembered
absolutely nothing.
Yeah, but was he drinking
that night?
No.
Did he take any drugs
or anything?
No.
Do you think
he's here?
I do.
You do.
I'm sorry.
I know. I know.
This room has issues.
There are a lot of dead
in here,
and they're walking
through that mirror.
I think some go in the mirror,
and I think some go out.
So would the living
in this room
be in any kind of danger
from all this traffic?
Yes. This place
is extremely active.
I feel really bad.
You haven't lived here
in a while,
but when you were here,
did you have experiences?
Yes, I did.
Okay, let's talk
about them.
One night,
while I was in bed,
I felt something bad.
In what way?
Whatever it was,
it wasn't friendly,
and I felt that
it wanted to hurt me.
It was terrifying.
You sure you weren't
dreaming this?
Yes.
It was one of
the worst experiences
I've ever had
in this house.
So, you said it was
one of the worst experiences.
What was the worst?
I was standing
in front of the toilet,
and something pushed me
over the counter.
When you got pushed,
did it feel like
a human being
was pushing you?
No, it felt like
something went through me.
Did you get hurt
at all?
No, I managed
to catch myself.
You're lucky because
that could have been
really serious.
Something happened here, man.
I'm seeing a male
with a shotgun on his hip.
He's kind of dressed
like a farmer.
He's in here with this thing.
It's a black mass.
This black mass and this farmer
have the capability
of interacting
with its surroundings.
That could mean that it could
harm the living, physically.
Do you know
what they want?
I'm hearing the farmer say,
"I want my house back."
So, Vernon, I understand
you're Kim's brother?
Yes, sir.
What's it like
when you come here?
I'm scared. I won't even go
to the restroom by myself.
Me and my wife
go together.
So, I'm assuming
you've had experiences, then?
Yeah, with the swing
on the front porch.
I come outside,
it was just swinging.
The trees won't
be swaying or nothing.
It be swinging like
somebody's sitting in it.
And you didn't see no
kids going by, maybe
jerking around with it?
None of that.
Okay, anything else?
Yeah, I saw a man,
a dog, and a tree
just disappear.
Okay,
that's a new one on me.
Tell me what happened.
About 2:00
in the morning,
and I looked
out the window,
and I saw it.
I looked again,
and it was gone,
just like that.
That's pretty interesting stuff
you've experienced here.
Yeah.
So, are you worried
about your sister
being in this house
all alone?
I mean, this house is huge.
Yes, sir.
Would you stay
in this house alone,
or you and your wife together
stay here alone?
I ain't gonna
be able to do it.
Okay.
For real, I ain't gonna
be able to do it.
There's a lot
of residual energy here.
It's kind of overwhelming.
How would the living
be affected by all this?
I think that they would
see things on occasion.
I think they would hear
a lot of things.
It's making me sick.
Okay, so, Tony, Sarah,
I understand that you guys
are part of
the paranormal team
that came in
to investigate the house.
Kim called you guys,
right?
- We are.
- That's right.
All right, so, Tony,
you used this equipment
on your investigation?
Yes.
Okay, now tell me
about what you got in there.
This right here
would be a digital recorder,
which would record EVPs,
or, you know,
electronic voice phenomena.
Okay.
This would be
a Mel Meter,
and this right here
actually detects
ambient temperature,
as well as
electromagnetic fields.
A ghost box
is a tool used.
It gives spirits
a way to communicate --
a white noise,
if you will.
After your investigation,
in your
professional opinion,
what did you find
that was here?
You felt like something
was watching you all the time,
like the air
might bite you.
Kim believes that
whatever's in this house
is what made Angel sick
and eventually pass away.
Do you agree with that?
- I do.
- Yes.
We're pretty certain that
that's what happened to Angel.
At some point, spiritualism
was practiced here.
Like 1901 to 1920s?
Possibly, these people
did something bad,
accidentally,
you know?
I'm seeing paranormal
investigators doing EVPs, maybe?
And he's taking pictures
and video.
The female is saying,
"Don't go into the darkness."
I'm seeing
a paranormal investigator here,
and then, downstairs,
seeing these spiritualists
practiced here.
To me, that's scary
because you don't know
what they're doing,
so they could be
agitating dead people.
And if you agitate them,
they could be hurting
living people.
Kim said a previous
homeowner died
after getting hit by a car
in front of the house,
so I called my old friend,
historian Sylvia Smith,
and she says it's true.
But she says this guy
also led a colorful life
I'm definitely going
to want to know about.
Well, Sylvia,
it's good to see you again.
Before we get to the accident,
you said on the phone
that this guy had
an interesting life.
What can you
tell me about him?
The gentleman
you're speaking of
is T.W. Burleson.
He was a farmer,
and he came here in 1902
and bought this property
that you're investigating.
Was he married
at this point?
Yes, he was.
He was married to a lady
named May Ward.
Soon after they came,
he turned his property
into a honey business.
Okay.
And I have this photo here
of the backyard
just filled
with bee hives.
So, now, did they
live on the property
with the bees?
I'm not sure where
they lived up until 1915,
when they built the house
that's on the property today.
So, business
had to be good
because that house
is big.
They did very well
until 1925,
when the factory
that was on the
property burned.
Okay, so how much damage
we talking about?
Well, they had
$30,000 worth of damage.
And, in today's market,
it would probably be
$400,000.
They shut down for
like three months
while they rebuilt.
Okay.
I'm seeing the farmer guy again,
and I think he owned this land.
But I hear a,
"Don't go in the barn,"
and I'm getting a fire.
I feel like
there's a couple of structures
that aren't here anymore
that belonged to him,
and he's, like,
just pacing over here.
I'm getting panicked and,
like, completely freaked out.
He's in a rage.
Somebody pissed him off...
bad.
Do you have
any idea why?
Bad dealings, business,
money lost.
He's got nothing else to lose.
Okay, so let's
get to the accident.
I know Burleson
was hit by a car
in front of
my client's property.
Yes, the accident
was in 1944,
and he was
severely injured.
In fact, he remained
in the hospital for two weeks
before he passed away.
He had a fractured skull,
and he died
from swelling of the brain.
Here's
his death certificate,
right here,
that states that.
He was only 67 years old
when he passed away.
So he was
a young man still.
Well, I know
what you meant now
when you said that
he had an interesting life.
I mean, he started out with
nothing, worked his way...
All the way to the top,
you might say.
Right, and then
he tragically gets
hit by a car...
That's true.
...and dies.
I think something bad happened
to this farmer guy.
I hear 1940s,
and I feel my neck break.
He's trying to make me sick.
Because his energy is so bad,
I don't think
the living would enjoy
a large portion,
even, of the land.
Their heart
would start hurting.
They would feel
extremely nauseous, shaky,
nervous, scared.
I just, like,
totally want to cry here.
So far, I've got
a grieving widow
who believes her house
killed her husband
on a property
where a previous owner died
in a tragic car accident.
But I want to see
if there's anything else.
Searching through old records,
I come across a teenager
named Kenneth Doty
who worked
in the bee factory.
Turns out he hung himself
in 1968,
right on Kim's property.
So I called a bunch
of Kimberly's neighbors.
Most of them didn't know
anything about the hanging.
But then I found one old guy,
and it turns out he worked
side by side with Kenny.
Not only that,
he remembers the day he died.
Now, I understand
this kid Doty
actually worked
on the property.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Did you get
to know him at all?
Yeah, just through
working with him.
What was he like?
Well,
he was a good kid.
You know,
he was a hard worker.
He played football,
number 63.
He didn't talk
a whole lot.
You asked him
to do something, he did it,
and he did a good job.
And he was
how old at the time?
I think 18.
Now, Sonny, I know
this happened on
October 19th in 1968.
What happened that day?
I guess he just
got depressed
and hung himself.
Now, where
did he do that?
Right here.
He took
a piece of strapping,
similar to this stuff.
Let me see that.
Okay.
So it looks like,
almost like a rope.
He ties it
on the ladder,
climbs up the ladder,
puts it
around his neck,
and jumps
over that rafter.
And he was hanging
about where I'm standing.
Now, who found him?
My wife.
- Your wife did?
- Yes.
I come in
later that evening
and find out about it.
There wasn't anything left
but that piece of rope
tied to the ladder.
So, now,
were they pretty sure
it was officially
a suicide?
That's what his
death certificate says...
Let me see.
...and I don't have
any reason to believe it
would be anything else.
Any indication why the hell
he might have did this?
He had broken up
with his girlfriend,
and he was depressed.
18 years old, he
had his whole life
in front of him,
and, you know, he threw it
all away for a girl.
Yeah.
I just got a young male,
not that long ago --
'40s, '50s --
I would say between
the age of 15 and 20.
I was in his body,
and I could feel
a rope around my neck.
Somebody had the other side
of the rope,
so it's looped over something,
and they're tugging
on that rope,
so I kept going up and down
by my neck.
I don't know specifically
how many people there were,
but I heard them laughing,
so I know a man
was doing the tugging on me.
Eventually,
it did break the neck.
He's reliving,
over and over again,
what happened to him.
It's really bad!
Another thing got my attention
in research --
during the Civil War,
there was a deadly explosion
at a gunpowder mill
right near Kim's house.
I'm heading over
to meet a local professor
who says it was a massive blast
that rocked the entire area.
Robin, I appreciate
you meeting with me.
Thank you.
Okay, this explosion
that happened,
before we even get to that,
I'm curious --
what was Waxahachie like
during the Civil War?
Waxahachie and pretty
much all of the small
towns in Texas --
there were
a number of people
who were opposed
to secession
and a number of people who
wanted secession to happen,
and Waxahachie
was the same way.
So there was
a lot of tension.
This was a period of time
that was called
the "Texas Troubles."
Okay, so what happened
with the explosion?
On April 29th, 1863,
a gunpowder mill exploded
less than a mile away
from the property
you're investigating.
It's less than a mile
from my client's property.
I got to assume they must
have heard it and felt it.
Most definitely.
I would describe it
as "seismic,"
meaning that it probably
shook the walls and so forth.
Now, how much gunpowder
do we think exploded?
There was about 800 pounds
that exploded.
Wow. Okay,
so what about casualties?
There were two
men who perished
in the explosion.
Okay, so now
we have two dead?
Yes.
So, was there an
investigation or
any arrests done?
There were no arrests
then, no.
Okay. All right, so
what's the theories
on what happened?
Well, there were
a number of people
that thought
it was sabotage.
David Natz, who survived
the explosion,
he mentioned that
there was a possible
Northern sympathizer
or a stranger that
was lurking around the mill
before the explosion.
But they never
found this guy?
No. No, they never
found this guy.
He magically disappeared.
So, Robin, what do
you think happened?
David Natz,
he was in charge of the mill
at the explosion,
at the time,
and he was just
a 20-year-old kid --
inexperienced
and kind of green.
It was most likely
an accident,
is what I believe.
Right.
Well,
it's a tragic story,
but pretty lucky that
only two people died
in this explosion.
I agree.
I'm getting
a sharp pain here.
This is a male.
I'm hearing military.
He's white, crew cut.
I think he's in his 20s.
I'm seeing people drinking,
having a good time,
and then I see
the room turns like
this weird,
pinkish-orange color,
and I hear people
yelling and screaming.
There's maybe, in this room,
four or five people,
and literally
everything goes dark,
and all you see
is this weird color.
I heard the word "fire."
Any idea
when this was?
It's old.
They're showing me
bodies laid out.
I'm hearing someone say,
"It came to a bad end."
During my walk,
I saw several disturbing things,
but the angry farmer
concerned me the most.
I'd probably put him
in his late 60s.
He was wearing a hat,
and he had massive,
like, dark circles
and deep sun lines.
Amy,
is this who you saw?
Yes,
that's who I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our client
for the first time.
Now, Amy, when I sat down
the other day
to talk with Kim,
her story
was so heartbreaking
I had a tough time
keeping it together.
For now, I'm gonna hold off
on telling you too much,
but she lives here alone,
and the main reason
she called us in
is because of her daughter,
Gabrielle.
She's supposed to
move back in,
and Kim doesn't think
it's safe.
So now that I told Amy
a little bit about you, Kim,
I'm gonna ask her
to describe her walk.
When I first
got to your house,
I ran into a dead male
between 15 and 20 years old.
I got that he is
a conscious entity,
but, unfortunately,
he's stuck
in the loop
of his death.
I was in his body,
so I'm not sure
what he looked like,
but I could feel that there
was a rope around my neck.
Rope, I know,
was looped over something.
He was hanged.
I believe
it was a murder,
and I believe
it was fairly recent --
as far as
the '40s or the '50s.
That's pretty amazing.
Well, back in the day,
the property used to be
a family-run
honey factory.
It's a family-run business,
but they hired a few
local teenagers to help out.
Now, one of these kids
was an 18-year-old
named Kenny Doty.
He was a quiet,
hardworking kid
who mostly
kept to himself,
but, on October 19th, 1968,
they found his dead body
hanging from a rafter
in the shed.
What?
Now, I talked to
this nice older guy
who ran
the family business.
He told me
he got to know Kenny.
Apparently, he was really upset
about a breakup with a girl.
Now, I got his
death certificate here.
Now, the cops ruled it
a suicide.
I got a photo. You didn't see
the kid, though, right?
No, I was in his body.
Okay,
this is the kid here.
My daughter has
seen a teenage boy
on the property
with dark hair.
Is it possible
she's seen this kid
on the property?
Yeah,
it's a huge possibility.
What else?
When I was upstairs,
in the bedroom
to the far right...
That sounds like
Gabrielle's room.
Yes.
...now, I encountered
two entities up there
that did concern me.
One was in the form
of a black mass.
Black mass could be
physically violent.
Anybody who would stay
in that room
would potentially have
negative experiences.
This is interesting
'cause when I spoke
to Gabrielle,
she told me
that she was lying in bed
and she felt
that something really bad
was lying
right next to her.
She thought
if she turned around,
she was gonna
get attacked.
The second experience
happened
in the bathroom upstairs
next to her room.
She told me she was pushed,
and she was pushed hard.
Did you know about that?
She didn't tell you?
No.
Here.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
I thought you knew.
No, I didn't know that
she was being attacked.
And I certainly didn't know
about the thing
hovering over her.
Well, that's why
we're here --
to find out what the hell
is going on, right?
Now, you also got attacked
outside Gabrielle's bedroom.
Tell Amy what happened.
I was actually walking
down the stairs,
and I actually felt the presence
of something on my back,
and I actually felt two hands
just shove me.
And I went tumbling
down the stairs.
Wow!
Now, you said there was
another entity you saw.
Yes, and the second entity
is a dead male.
I got that
he was a farmer.
He is probably in his 60s,
and, on his hip,
he has a double-barrel shotgun.
Outside, he was going off
about a fire.
He was angry, stomping around
all over back there.
I felt that this dude
lost his money.
He was saying, "I don't have
anything else left to lose."
And I heard something
about 1940s,
and I got that he was
connected to the property,
that he may have owned it.
I said,
"Well, what do you want?"
And he goes,
"I just want my house back."
I'm pissed.
He wants his home back?
He can't have it.
This reminds me
of one of the previous owners
that I came across
in my research.
Now, his name
was T.W. Burleson,
and he built your house,
this house, in 1915.
Now, he ran
that honey business
that I was talking
about earlier.
Right.
This is pretty interesting.
Here's a picture of all
these damn bee hives
he had in the backyard.
You said something
about fire.
Well, in 1925,
there was a major fire,
and it burned
the factory down.
Now, you said something
about the 1940s.
In 1944,
T.W. was crossing the street
right in front of the house
when he was hit by a car.
They rushed him
to the hospital.
Two weeks later,
he dies from a brain swelling.
You said this guy
was in his 60s.
Burleson was 67
at the time of his death.
Now, I managed to track
down a photo of him,
but this was probably closer to
when, I think, he passed away.
Is it possible
this is who you saw?
I mean, I had a sketch
done of him.
You kidding?
Tell me what you think.
They resemble.
You can see the nose,
the cheekbones, the mouth.
I mean, it clearly looks
like the same person to me.
I've seen 1,000, 2,000
sketches done
from witnesses on crimes.
This is pretty damn close.
Yeah.
What else?
I was in
the dining room,
and I saw people
practicing spiritualism.
So I would put this back
between 1901 and 1920.
And then I was upstairs.
I'm sitting there,
and I see a male
coming into the room,
and he has an EMF meter,
and he's taking pictures.
And this seemed to be
pretty dang recent.
Now, I don't know anything
about spiritualists,
but Kim did bring in
a paranormal team
to do an investigation.
Okay.
Now, I spoke with them...
...and they did use EMFs.
Obviously,
they took photos.
Okay.
Now, do you think these guys
might have stirred things up?
I don't think so.
But the spiritualists may...
have done something
in the past
that agitated the dead
so much
they may now try
to physically harm people.
The other thing I got
was a massive amount
of depression and loss.
I felt that this was due
to a living person.
This person is female.
Something happened
to a person that they love.
They can't recover
from this grief.
I got that they're not eating,
and that they feel suicidal.
You okay?
Amy, you remember
when I told you
that Kim was breaking
my heart?
That's because
her husband died
a couple years ago
at a very young age.
I actually have a photo of him
right here with Kim.
He was
the love of my life.
And we were
supposed to spend
the rest of our lives
in that house.
It wasn't particularly
one he cared for,
but he said
if it's my dream,
it will become
his dream, too.
She feels guilty.
I feel like something
in the house
could have killed him.
Kim, tell her
what he passed from.
He passed away
of a malignant brain tumor
that was inoperable.
None of us
were prepared for that.
If it was his time,
I can accept that.
But if it was me...
convincing him to
buy that house,
and something in it
that was dark hurt him,
I couldn't
forgive myself.
She's worried about
Gabrielle coming back
to live at the house,
and maybe something in the house
could do something to her.
I don't want anything
to happen to my daughter,
and I certainly don't
want her to move back
home if something --
I didn't even know about
the dark mass over her bed.
She never told me that.
I'm tired.
Yeah.
I know you are.
So what else
was going on?
At the foot of the stairs,
what I felt was a male
in his death state.
It was not a good death.
It took a while.
I felt
overwhelming sadness.
I kept hearing,
"Man. This is wrong.
No way, no way.
This can't be happening.
No way."
I felt he was scared.
Angel passed away
downstairs, right?
In the master bedroom.
So not that far away.
Okay, I'm hoping Amy
wasn't feeling Angel's death,
but the other things that she
described about him being scared
and saying,
"This can't happen,"
does that sound like
what Angel was going through?
All of the stages
you go through
when you find out
that you have cancer,
he experienced them all.
We all did.
I got to ask you, Amy --
do you think that's
Angel that you felt?
I'm sorry.
I wish I knew for sure.
But I could not see him.
Obviously, it's not
a definitive answer for you.
What's your gut tell you?
That he's at peace
where he is...
and I'm the one struggling
with being not at peace.
Anything else?
So, here's the thing.
There is random dead
who are constantly
coming through your house.
So these dead can come and go
through the mirrors.
I've encountered this before
on walks,
and basically some mirrors,
for whatever reason,
which I think
it's more about the location,
are openings for the dead
to come and go through.
What bothered me about that
bed location, the master bed,
is that they're
literally walking back,
like, through that bed,
constant, constant.
You're consistently exposed.
That is something
that can make you sick.
After Angel passed away,
I always wake up
with aches in my side,
said I felt like I'm actually
being punched in my sleep.
Yeah, that would be them
probably walking through you.
So if she doesn't call us in
and Gabrielle moved in,
what could have happened?
I think that you would've
eventually developed
some kind of long-term
and possibly terminal illness
by continuing
to sleep here.
You know, you're talking
about all these dead
people walking through.
You had an incident with Angel
when he was alive
that you thought
it wasn't him.
I believe
he was possessed.
He didn't look the same.
His voice
was not the same.
And I actually remember
stepping back
because I was fearful
because when I looked at him,
he wasn't my husband.
Now, could this be
from people walking through?
I think so.
It makes complete sense to me
that he would be possessed.
Yeah, you got to get
the...out of there, like...
And now I'm...
worried.
So the big question is,
did the house make Angel sick?
No. I don't think so.
So you didn't cause this.
You understand that?
Okay.
At least he got a chance
to love me before he...
before he died.
So even though it
was for a short time,
it was worth it.
Everybody's gonna grieve.
But the guilt part
you got to let go.
- Okay.
- Okay?
I made her cry.
I'm sorry.
So, Kim, if you only get
one thing out of tonight,
I hope you now know
you had nothing to do
with Angel's death.
As far as whether it's safe
for you to stay in the house
or to have Gabrielle
move back in,
I'm going to turn it over
to Amy.
Before I get to that,
I am going to go into
what you need to do to heal
and take care of yourself.
The first thing is to
see a psychotherapist
who specializes in grief
for intensive therapy.
And also, I want you
in a grief-counseling group
because the pain
is stuck.
I need to do that.
I didn't actually realize
that I was...so stuck
emotionally...
in the grieving...state.
As for the hauntings,
the first thing is
you have to move your bedroom.
That has to happen.
I'm sorry.
But this is your health,
so that needs
to be done ASAP.
Next, you need
to remove both mirrors,
specifically downstairs.
They're contaminated.
You need to get rid
of those mirrors.
The next thing is
a medium needs to come in
to remove...
most of the dead.
They'll be able to get
rid of the black mass
and this guy here.
Okay.
What about your daughter?
You going to have her move in
after you get this done?
I don't think
I'll have her move in.
Feels like
I could cause harm to her.
I hate to see you
in this house by yourself.
When the time comes,
when I feel comfortable,
she can move back.
How do you feel about the whole
investigation, how it went?
I have the answers
I wanted
and that I needed
because you have a gift.
And you help
a lot of people,
whether you realize it
or not,
so thank you.
I really hope Kim seeks the help
of a therapist and support group
to deal with the guilt she feels
over her husband's death.
If she does that and contacts
a medium to remove the dead,
she can begin to heal
and maybe even live here
in peace with her daughter.