I'm seeing blood.
He doesn't have a face anymore.
It kills me to think
that he's going
to have to grow up
like I did.
You're around
this person enough,
and you literally become insane.
He left a lot of bodies
in his wake.
He might have killed her.
All I want for my family
is to be safe.
I'm extremely worried.
This guy wants death.
This is not a good situation.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's death here.
Don't want to go down there.
I see dead people.
They hide in the walls,
and they watch.
I speak to dead people.
She's definitely
a serial killer.
And they speak to me.
She's going to torture them.
But there's only one way
to know if my findings are real.
They were all murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
So, is this the only time
you've been physically attacked?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
There's no question
in my mind
that he was talking
about Satan.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who do you think
possessed you?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end...
Well, you're not gonna
want to see this.
...when we uncover
if it's safe for you to stay...
Hell no!
...or time to get out.
Everyone is in jeopardy.
I'm in El Cajon, California.
It's a blue-collar suburb
just outside of San Diego.
I got a call from a woman
named Melissa.
Now, she sounded really bad.
She told me she was forced
to move back into the house
that destroyed her childhood,
and now she's convinced
whatever's there
is going after
her 6-year-old son.
She really needs our help bad,
and I'm hoping
we can help her out.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the house
of any leading information.
Photographs, artwork,
and religious statues
can influence her findings,
so it's important that I cover
or remove them all.
When I'm finished,
the location will be ready
for tonight's walk.
A man is showing me
this, like,
6- to 7-foot skeleton,
half-burnt mess,
and he's, like, oozing,
dripping...stuff,
like, blood.
And he says,
"I am the great deceiver."
He goes, "Living are being
driven insane
by the madness
that surrounds them."
And he goes, "You think this
is crazy, you ain't seen..."
So, Melissa, when we spoke
on the phone,
you sounded pretty upset.
Yeah.
Especially about
your youngest son.
What's going on?
Charlie says he hears noises
and sees things
that kids --
You can't just
fake stuff like that.
How long has this been
going on with him?
He's lived in this house
his whole life,
and he started
talking to us about it
when he was like 3 or 4.
All right.
So who else lives in the house?
My grandfather. He's 85.
- Okay.
- Myself.
My husband, Corey.
Charlie, he is 6,
and Nathan, who is 16.
- I understand you grew up here.
- Yeah, I did.
And it was pretty bad
for you as a kid.
Yeah.
I always had experiences,
and they never stopped
until I left.
It kills me to think
that he's going
to have to grow up
like I did.
I don't want that.
I just don't. I want him
to have a normal childhood.
Why would you come back?
My grandmother passed away,
and my grandfather wasn't
doing so well on his own.
The only reason
why I came back.
Okay.
This is actually a picture
of her with a young Nathan.
What did she die of?
She had a routine back surgery
that went wrong.
She came home,
and two days later,
she went rushed back to
the hospital, and she was dead.
Any other history
I should know about?
I had an uncle who passed away
here as a child.
- As a child?
- As a child.
And this is your
grandfather's son?
- Yeah.
- You think your grandfather
would be willing
to talk to me?
We've never really
discussed it much before.
- Okay.
- You can try.
So, Melissa, I know you guys
are going through hell here,
but give me an idea
or a list of what's happening.
Things move on their own.
We have fluctuating moods,
horrible nightmares,
and, like, physical attacks.
You mentioned mood swings.
What did you mean by that?
I can just get super angry
or super sad, super depressed.
It's just -- on a dime.
And I've never been
a depressed person.
Why don't you just
leave here, honey,
and take your
grandfather with you?
He doesn't want to go.
He's asked to die in this house.
That's his wishes.
I want to respect his wishes.
- Um...
- Okay.
He helped raise me.
He did so much for me,
and I want him to live
the rest of his life happy.
There's another man here,
and he's very sad.
I think he's suffering
from severe depression.
You know, all he does
is sit in a ball
and...cry all the...time.
So he is definitely
filling the location
with this despair and heaviness.
The living here
would feel depressed,
thoughts of suicide and stress,
so we got to get him out.
Okay.
So, what's going on in here?
In here, I've seen a full
apparition of my grandmother.
So, where exactly did you
see your grandmother?
Actually right where
I'm standing.
She used to be
in the kitchen a lot.
What else is going on?
We hear really loud noises
going up and down the stairway.
It actually sounds like
a herd of buffalo.
- It's very loud.
- All right.
You got two kids here.
How do you know it's not them?
Charlie sleeps with us.
Nathan sleeps heavy.
Okay.
So what else is going on?
Things get thrown,
like, violently thrown.
Like what, for instance?
My hairbrush
has gotten thrown
completely across the room
with force.
Okay.
Has anybody been hit by it?
No, but it went
about this far away
from the person's face.
So far, you guys have been
kind of lucky.
I mean, what if that caught
somebody in the eye?
I figure
it's a matter of time.
I mean, with all the stuff
going on, you got to feel like
- you're going out of your mind.
- I feel insane.
I'm seeing another guy.
He's crazy.
I think he's been in and out
of mental institutions.
He's usually confused and lost,
and he's, like, running through
the walls, throwing a fit.
I think that the living
can hear him,
and he's, like,
right up in their faces.
He's over them.
He's staring at them.
I think they would
feel that, too,
like, that kind of,
like, smothering.
They'd wake up and be like,
"What the..."
They know
somebody's right there.
He's very sick.
You're around
this person enough,
and you literally become insane.
Okay. Master bedroom.
This is where you sleep
- with your husband...
- Yeah.
- ...and Charlie.
- And Charlie.
Okay.
So what's going on?
Having really
bad nightmares.
Okay. Now, what kind
of nightmares are you having?
I feel like
I can't get home,
like there's
something very urgent,
and someone keeps preventing me
from coming home.
Anybody else having
dreams like that?
Charlie does.
He's woken up with bruises.
I have a picture
of when we woke him up.
That's not just a bruise.
I mean --
What about you? Are you
getting anything like this?
Yeah. I wake up with bruises,
scratches,
like burning scratches.
I have a picture.
It actually puffs up.
I mean, we are out in the middle
of the mountains here.
Any chance it could be
some kind of a rodent
that came in and did this to you
or anything like --
- No.
- Okay. What else?
I feel like someone
is watching me,
but not just watching me,
like, looming over
my face and bed.
- Do you see something?
- No.
It's just a feeling I get.
Okay.
Anything else going on in here?
I was laying in bed,
and I felt a hand
grab my ankle,
and it was a forceful grab.
It was so unnerving
and so scary.
I just --
I couldn't believe
it was --
that was actually happening.
It's a nightmare.
It's like
an actual nightmare.
I mean, does
your grandfather know
the sacrifice you're
making for him?
No.
I don't want him to know.
I don't want him to worry.
He's 85.
He should be
enjoying his life.
You know, I don't want
to see him upset.
I mean, he's 85.
He lived his life.
- Something's got to give here.
- Yeah, I agree.
Well, hopefully we can get
some help for you that you need.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm seeing blood.
All right. So, skeleton dude,
the one I saw outside
when I first got here,
is with me,
and he's like,
"The writing's on the wall."
I'm so nervous.
Why are you here?
He says he was asked to be here.
The...would ask that?
Okay. I'm going to assume
that someone at some point here
...around with...
and somehow
pulled this dead guy here.
He gets physical down here --
slapping,
pulling, pushing,
tugging them
by the ankles down the bed.
He's like, "I'll show you.
I'll show you how...bad I am."
He's like,
"I have killed people."
So, Charlie,
let me ask you something.
- How old are you?
-6.
So, this looks like a fun room
to hang out in.
I mean, do you like it
in here?
It's scary for me.
It's scary?
You seen some bad things here?
Can you tell me
about some of them?
So, I've heard a noise
in the kitchen.
What kind of sound was it?
It was like a bang sound.
Okay.
How many times?
Three bangs.
- Three bangs.
- From one right here,
one in the kitchen,
and then one right next to me.
What else
are you experiencing?
I'm seeing stuff in my room.
Okay.
What are you seeing?
Black figures.
How often do you see that?
I only see it at night.
All right.
So, what else are you seeing?
I was, like,
just watching TV,
and I looked over
at a bottle,
and it when I was
looking at it, it moved.
- Where'd this happen?
- In my room.
Okay. So, Charlie, I know
this place is scary for you,
but if we could fix this,
would you like to stay here?
I want you to get rid of it
so I can sleep
in my room again.
Okay. That's what
we're here for.
We're going to try
to do that. Okay?
Skeleton man, he's, like,
showing me the person sleeping,
and he's, like,
covering their mouth
and pinching their nose.
He does that until
they, like, pass out,
and then he, like, lets go.
So a lot of walking up,
crying, being scared,
seeing him,
seeing him, screaming.
So, Corey, I was talking
to your wife, Melissa,
and she's really
worried about Charlie.
- How about you?
- I mean, what do you do
when your 6-year-old son
comes to you,
and he's so worried
about everything,
and there's nothing
I can do?
What I want most for him
is to be able
to, you know, have
a normal childhood.
She was telling me
about her grandfather.
Is he that stubborn
where he won't leave here?
There's no talking him
out of here.
He'll die in this house.
So, what experiences
have you had?
I see shadow figures
all over the house.
The one I saw was upstairs,
had white eyes,
and when I noticed it,
it was kind of sinking
into the floor.
Now, how often are you
seeing these things?
Probably at least
twice a week.
All right. So you're seeing
shadow figures. What else?
Everywhere we go
in the house,
it's a constant feeling
of being watched.
It's much heavier upstairs.
Is it a peeping tom thing
or somebody stalking you?
It's more, like, just a presence
right at your back
just looming over you,
watching you.
Anything else?
I was actually attacked
in the kitchen.
How?
I was standing
next to the stove.
There was a Tupperware
container on top of the fridge,
and it flew
across the counter
and hit me in the side
of the head with force.
- Were you alone?
- No. Nathan was with me.
Are you sure he didn't
do it by accident?
Yeah, he was actually
on the opposite side of me.
Could have been a glass jar,
God forbid.
Right.
It had very malicious intent.
With all the activity
you guys are experiencing,
it's got to be taking
a toll on you and Melissa.
Over the last few years,
seeing, like,
a total breakdown
in her mentally.
Sometimes she'll wake me up
in the middle of the night,
and she'll just be sobbing.
It just breaks my heart
to see her that way.
And it's just totally taking
a toll on her mental state,
and it's really hard
to see her go through that.
So, Corey, when I was
talking to your wife,
she mentioned
that the house, she feels,
is changing people's
personalities.
I definitely would agree
with her on that.
We go through bouts of anger,
bouts of depression,
and we'll kind of
start bickering
amongst each other
as a family.
When the anger comes on,
does it come on real fast,
- or does it build?
- You just go from zero to pissed
in 0.2 seconds
out of nowhere.
Okay.
This skeleton guy,
I think that he can
jump someone here,
and I think it's a male.
So when he is that way,
he is possessed.
There's, like, a change,
literally a physical --
There's some kind
of physical change
when he's inside of this person.
The skeleton guy goes in,
like, literally walk
into the guy's body...
...and take that energy
and utilize that anger.
He wants to get the dude
possessed to kill other people.
Melissa told me
her uncle died in the house
when he was just 4 years old.
She also told me her grandfather
never talked about it.
So I was a little surprised
this morning when he asked me
to come over
to discuss what happened.
Gene, I appreciate you
taking the time to talk with me.
I know this is
a hard subject.
But what can you tell me
about your little boy, Jerry?
He loved playing with the kids
in the neighborhood,
and he loved going to baseball
games with his brothers,
just a normal 4-year-old boy.
My God.
He was such a cute kid.
Yeah, he was a cute kid.
So, Gene, that day,
what exactly happened?
On a hot day
back in August of '67,
went off to work.
Jerry and a neighborhood
friend of his
were looking
for a place to play.
And I had my old refrigerator
in the garage.
And when the boys got in it,
I assume to cool off
or hide,
playing hide and seek,
the door automatically caught
when they closed the door.
It was an accident.
Okay.
So they ran out of oxygen.
Yeah.
They suffocated.
Okay.
How'd you and your wife
handle this?
As you can imagine,
she was pretty well torn up.
- Gene, how old are you now?
- I'm 85.
And this still sticks
with you today?
Yeah. Yeah.
That and my wife's
death, also.
So, Gene, how do you feel
as far as,
you know, your wife
and your son?
- You think they're here?
- I don't know about the son,
but my wife,
I feel she's --
She's been
looking after me,
keeping me on
the straight and narrow.
I think she said
she was going to haunt me.
- But in a good way.
- In a good way, yeah.
I see a woman.
She's in her late 40s,
early 50s.
I see she has long brown hair.
It's kind of clipped up.
She's wearing big glasses.
I think she's white,
and she is crying.
She was here at some point
and very stressed out
and hysterical.
I don't know what happened.
She's depressed,
thoughts of suicide
and stress.
She's screaming,
crying, pleading,
"No, no, no, not my baby."
So far, I've got a family being
tormented by paranormal activity
on a property where two
young children suffocated.
But I want to see
if there's anything else.
Searching through old records,
I come across a serial killer
named Clyde Carl Wilkerson.
Turns out, he terrorized
the El Cajon area for years.
So I reached out to a local
true crime writer
who's on her way
over to meet me.
She says to this day,
no one knows exactly
how many people this guy killed.
Cathy, thanks for meeting
with me. I appreciate that.
So, let's start
from the beginning.
What do we know
about this Wilkerson guy?
Clyde Carl Wilkerson was born
in Northern California.
And from day one,
he was trouble.
He was almost a blueprint
for becoming a serial killer.
At age 6, he committed arson,
was arrested for it.
And at age 8, he was given
psychiatric treatment.
I mean, that's the youngest
I've ever heard.
He was in and out
of mental institutions
most of his childhood.
I'm seeing the crazy guy again.
I'm in his body, and I'm looking
down a hospital corridor.
No, it's not a hospital.
It's like a psych ward.
I'm seeing only a few
other patients,
and I would say
this is the 1940s or '50s.
He's strapped on a...
weird table.
The table looks like
those tables
that they do
lethal injections on.
I know that he was at least
in some kind of institution
on two occasions
for his mental state.
All right. So, Cathy, what's
the body count with this guy?
Well, he was convicted
of three,
but he was suspected
of many more.
Okay. So we know he did three.
What about the first one?
On June 6, 1965,
just 3 miles
from your client's home,
Cheryl Burnett got home
at 3:00 a.m. in the morning
from bowling with friends.
She was 19 years old.
Her toddler was sleeping
in the bedroom.
And Wilkerson broke in
through a window
and ended up raping her
and then strangling her
- with a drapery cord.
- All right.
Does he get arrested
then for that murder?
Not then for that murder,
but he was always
in trouble with the law.
Okay.
What about the second one?
This one was just a mile
from your client's home.
About two
or three weeks later,
a couple were getting
ready for bed.
Wilkerson goes into
the apartment building
and starts beating on the couple
with a crescent wrench.
He beat them so badly
that he killed the husband.
Does he kill the wife,
as well?
He raped the wife and left her
for dead, but she survived.
Okay.
Was she able to identify him?
She was unable to.
Okay. So now we got two murders
a couple weeks apart.
When's the third one happen?
Third one doesn't happen
until 1975.
Okay.
So it's 1975. What happened?
Wilkerson ends up going
to Tulsa, Oklahoma,
breaks into an apartment,
and rapes and murders
28-year-old college student
Geraldine Martin.
All right. So we got three
homicides we know he did.
How did they catch him?
Three letters -- DNA.
The El Cajon Police Department,
they grabbed him in 2002.
I can only imagine there's got
to be a lot more.
I think he left a lot
of bodies in his wake.
Okay.
So is this guy still alive?
No. He died in 2016
at age 77 of an illness.
He died in prison.
So, there's this woman,
and it's a beautiful day out,
and it's 1978.
The crazy guy,
he's watching her.
And they're at the beach.
And so I was like,
"Did he do something to her?"
He might have killed her.
He says he's very lost
and confused.
He's very sick.
Do you know how he died?
I don't know.
Dementia, maybe a stroke.
He said they
scrambled his brain.
And he says, "I ruined
everything, everything."
And then I know he's dead, too.
For more information
about the show,
and if you need us
to investigate
unexplained activity
in your home...
Please visit
travelchannel.com/thedeadfiles.
Click on "Help me, Dead Files!"
to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
You know, another thing
caught my eye in research.
The day after the attacks
on Pearl Harbor,
the military took over
a bunch of land in the area,
including Melissa
and Corey's property.
I'm heading over to meet
with a military expert,
who says there was
a deadly accident on the site
I definitely want to know about.
Well, Sergeant Major,
thanks for meeting with me.
You mentioned on the phone
that the military
basically just took over
my client's property
right after
the Pearl Harbor attack.
Now, was that common?
It was very common
on the West Coast.
The Army came in.
The federal government
seized the property.
All right. So I know my client's
house wasn't built yet,
but who owned
the property back then?
This was a farm owned by
a gentleman named Ed Fletcher.
So what'd they wind up
doing with the property?
The property became an army camp
known as Camp La Mesa,
and by the way,
I have some pictures here
of what the camp looked like
at the early part of the war
and then later when
they actually built buildings.
Had a pretty big setup,
didn't they?
It was an infantry
regiment of 1,400 men.
So, you mentioned on the phone,
there was a pretty bad accident
I'm going to want
to know about.
Yeah, on April 24, 1942,
there was mortar training.
That's what the weapon
looks like.
Okay.
I'm familiar with this.
And one of the rounds
exploded in the tube.
Ooh. Now, how bad
was this explosion?
It killed five men instantly.
One died in hospital.
-16 were wounded.
- Okay.
So were there any other deaths
that I should know about?
Not that I'm aware of,
but here at Gillespie Field,
which bordered
Ed Fletcher's property,
there's been 24 people killed
in 13 separate accidents.
Okay.
So that's a lot deaths.
I don't want to go through all
of them, but did any stand out?
Yeah, two of them
really stood out.
In January of 1981,
a 15-year-old
by the name of Grant Thompson
talked his mother,
his stepfather,
and two of their friends
into flying to Las Vegas.
Never mind that he had
never flown a plane before.
So these four adults got
on a plane with a 15-year-old,
- and this kid never flew.
- That's correct.
Okay.
What the hell happened?
The plane never got
off the ground. It crashed.
All were killed aboard.
Okay. That was
a pretty bad accident.
What about the second one?
The second one was
a Navy F-14 Tomcat
flying out of Naval Air
Station Miramar in San Diego.
It encountered
mechanical problems,
and the air crew
had to eject.
Upon ejection, one of
the air crew broke his neck.
All right. So do we know
how he broke his neck?
The plane
was out of control.
It was upside down
when they ejected,
and he broke his neck
somewhere in that process.
- Okay.
- Now, the plane did travel on
and crashed here
on the airfield.
It injured three people.
It destroyed $6 to $9 million
worth of airport property.
Have you ever seen this much
death on one airfield before?
Not that I'm aware of.
- It's, like, bad luck over here.
- It's quite bizarre.
I'm seeing
the skeleton dude in here.
Do you know how he died?
I see blood, and I feel
like he had a bad death.
He's, like,
dripping and melting.
I know his neck got broken.
I mean, he looks a little burnt.
I saw several dead people
during my walk,
but the skeleton man
tormenting a child
had me the most concerned.
There's this dead guy
who doesn't really
have any clothes on.
There were definitely
a lot of areas
on his body and face
that were burned.
And there was a child in a bed,
and he has his hands
on the kid's face,
over the mouth
and pinching the nose.
Amy, is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients
for the first time.
So, Amy, this is Melissa
and her husband, Corey.
Now, Melissa grew up
in this house
and had a miserable time here.
But she has a huge heart.
She moved her entire family
back here
to take care of her 85-year-old
grandfather, Gene.
This is her 16-year-old son,
Nathan,
and this is Charlie, who's 6.
Now, he's the reason we're here.
Kid's having a rough time,
and Melissa is scared
his childhood's going to be
ruined just like hers was.
So now that Amy knows
a little bit about you guys,
I'll ask her describe
her walk for us.
The first thing that I got
was a deceased female.
She's white, and I got
that she was in her late 40s,
early 50s.
I also got
that she was living here
around 1980s or early 1990s.
She spent most of her time
in the kitchen
and dining area,
which is where she is still.
I saw her in a very bad state.
She was hysterically crying.
She was extremely depressed.
She's very stressed out.
She was screaming,
"No, no, no, not my baby."
Now, Melissa lost her
grandmother about 10 years ago?
Yeah. Well, you just
described her, basically.
You told me you saw your
grandmother's apparition
- in the kitchen.
- Yeah.
And I could tell you
exactly what she was wearing.
And we just looked
at each other.
It scared me.
So, why are you
afraid of her?
She was a strict woman.
She tried to teach me
how to be a lady.
And, you know,
she had a lot of kids.
And she lost her
youngest child here.
Okay.
You should know about
Melissa's uncle, Jerry.
He died in the garage
when he was 4 years old.
On August 30, 1967, Jerry
was playing with another kid
in the neighborhood
who was 3 years old,
and they walked into a fridge
that was in the garage.
The door locked on them,
and they suffocated.
I got a photo of Jerry.
He was a really cute kid, too.
Now, I actually have a picture
of Melissa's grandmother.
Is it possible
this is who you saw?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Do you think she ever
got over Jerry passing?
No.
It's kind of hard to think that,
you know, she hasn't moved past.
That's what's hard for me
right now to accept.
Okay.
So what else?
So there's two other dead people
who are very present,
and I'm concerned about them.
The first individual has mental
disorders, mental illness.
He's definitely nuts.
I do think that he would
affect the living.
I thought maybe some of you
would hear him,
because he does get
a little worked up,
and so he'll start banging
things, throwing things.
I was attacked
in the kitchen.
There was a Tupperware
on top of the fridge,
and it flew
across the counter
and hit me with force
in the side of the head.
- Wow.
- When I spoke to Charlie,
he told me that he hears
a lot of things banging,
scratching noises.
He doesn't sleep downstairs.
- Okay.
- He hasn't for over a year.
He sleeps with us.
Okay.
The other thing that unnerved me
was that he does watch,
and he stares,
and he'll get right in your face
and do this.
Being subjected to him
consistently
can make you feel
like you're going insane.
Actually, that's part of the
reason why I called you guys.
Sometimes I can't go to sleep
because I feel like somebody's
pacing on my side of the bed,
back and forth,
and that he leans over
and is right in my face.
I've spent whole nights
just crying
because it feels
so intrusive.
Any idea who this guy might
have been when he was alive?
What I was able to get from him
was that he had been
in and out
of mental institutions,
and I was getting the 1940s,
1950s with him,
and he was showing me
that he's on a beach.
He's looking out.
There's a young,
attractive woman.
It was 1978.
I believe he killed her.
Wow. It's interesting, 'cause
the stuff you're talking about
reminds me of a serial killer
that terrorized the city.
Now, the guy's name
is Clyde Carl Wilkerson.
This kid was bad news
from the start.
Wilkerson was arrested
for arson at the age of 6.
Then he was in and out
of mental hospitals
starting at the age of 8.
Holy...
Now, you mentioned
mental institutions
in the '40s and '50s.
Now, Wilkerson was born in '38,
so the time frame matches.
Unfortunately, in the '60s,
he started killing.
In 1965, he beat, strangled,
and raped a 19-year-old girl
a couple of miles from here
while her 2-year-old son
slept in the other room.
A few weeks later,
this sick bastard
breaks into
an older couple's house
less than a mile from here.
He beats the man to death.
Then he raped and badly beat
his wife, leaving her for dead.
She survived. Barely, though.
She was never right again
and couldn't identify him.
Now, in 1975, he struck again.
Now, this time, his victim
was a 28-year-old student
named Geraldine Martin.
He wound up raping
and murdering her, too.
This guy may have killed more,
but that's all they got him on.
Now, he wasn't
arrested until 2002.
Holy...
I got a great mug shot
array of him
from when he was younger
to when he was older.
Now, what do you think?
Is this who you might have seen?
Yes.
This just blows
my -- my mind.
And when did he die?
Last year.
Everything started happening
about a year ago here,
like, real bad.
That makes me
totally disgusted.
I don't want this guy
around my kid.
I agree.
The next guy that I encountered,
I felt, was the bigger threat.
The way he showed himself
was extremely disturbing.
He looked like a skeleton,
and it looked like
he had burns all over his body.
And this skeleton guy
was not a good person in life.
He said that he did kill people.
Because of how he looked,
I believe he had
a really gruesome death,
and I think the thing
that killed him
- was actually a broken neck.
- I have history that I really
don't think has anything to do
with who she's talking about,
but I think it's something
you guys should know about.
Now, the day after
the attacks on Pearl Harbor,
the military came in
and enforced eminent domain
and took over all the property,
and then they created
two military bases here.
One camp was La Mesa.
The other one was right next
to your old property line,
and that's called
Gillespie Field now.
According to the expert
I talked to,
there have been
13 separate accidents there
that killed 24 people.
One stood to me was this one.
It was an F-14 in 1988
that malfunctioned
and began spinning
out of control.
When the two pilots
ejected from the airplane,
one of them broke
his neck upon impact.
Any chance one of these deaths
could have been
the skeleton guy you saw?
No. Mnh-mnh.
Okay. So now we have an idea
who it's not.
So why is this skeleton guy
such a big threat?
When I first got here,
he told me
that he causes pain and death.
He did get physical with me
a couple of times,
and I do believe
that he's very capable
of becoming physical
with living people.
One of the things that I saw
and felt this skeleton guy does
is, like, slapping and pushing
and hitting people.
The other thing I saw
was he was wrapping his hands
around the bottom
of the feet and the ankles
and pulling them out of bed.
Tell Amy what happened.
I was laying there,
and I got a grab on my ankle,
a real tight grab.
- Really?
- And it scared me to death.
Well, you even wake up
with scratches and bruises.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Lookit. Here's one of the
scratches she took pictures of.
Wow.
That's, like, nothing.
And matter of fact,
Charlie wakes up
with bruises on him.
Yeah, I know.
Okay. So, the other thing
that I saw him doing
was possessing
a living male here.
He can enter the body
and take over
and completely change
his personality,
and that would be becoming
angry and violent.
I go from zero to angry
in 0.5 seconds.
Do you notice, when he does
that, any physical changes?
Yes. If we're fighting,
he has this specific face
where he looks at me,
almost like a disgust,
the way he squints his eyes.
The other thing
that I saw him doing was,
we went into the little room,
- the little blue room.
- Yep, yep.
And that blue room's
Charlie's room, right?
It's the one
he won't sleep in.
And what I saw
was very disturbing.
I did have a sketch done of what
I saw happening in there.
Jesus.
I don't even want
to show it to them.
My gosh.
I want to say that it's
a surprising picture,
but the way he thrashes
around at night.
He's always saying,
"No. Stop. Get away."
So what's he doing
in this picture?
He was trying to smother him.
He was covering his mouth,
pinching his nose.
Obviously, he's trying
to kill your child.
I did get that sometimes
the kid would wake up
and would actually
see him in his room,
and he was crying,
and it scares him.
That's just...disgusting.
That pisses me off to no end.
I can't -- I mean --
Yeah.
I don't even have any words.
I'm extremely,
extremely worried,
because this guy wants death,
and he wants to be able
to jump the living male here
and have basically, you know,
a murder-suicide
kind of situation.
He showed me
where he enters you.
He said it's on your
right side right here.
I get rib pain on that side
all the time.
I don't even know
what to say to you guys.
This is bad.
This is -- It is. Bad.
Would I be able to just,
like, have just maybe
- a minute or two?
- Yeah.
Now, Melissa, you called us in
because you wanted us
to save your son.
But as it turns out,
your entire family is in danger.
And I know taking care
of your grandfather
means everything to you,
but I don't know how
you're going to be able
to do that here safely.
For that answer, I'm going
to turn it over to Amy.
So, I'm very worried.
My suggestion is that you leave
as soon as possible.
You guys need to put
a lot of distance
between here and where you go.
But before entering
a new place of residence,
you need to have a male
who is a psychic
and a reiki master,
because this skeleton guy,
he showed me that he has entered
you on several occasions.
There could be cords there.
And the psychic reiki master
will be doing a cord removal
and cutting.
This can be painful,
but you'll feel so much better
after it's done.
Now, what about Charlie?
Other than obviously
removing him from this location,
he is clear right now.
Now, what about Melissa? Does
she have to do anything, or --
No. Mnh-mnh.
What are the chances
Gene's going to come with you,
your grandfather?
I don't think
they're very high.
I'll try to get him
to come with us, but...
I don't know that
he's going to want to go.
You said something to me
the other day
that I thought about
for a long time.
He's 85, and he has
lived his life,
and my son hasn't, so...
So, the main thing is,
you called us in for Charlie.
So my question to you is,
if they move
and they do everything
you tell them to do,
this kid should have
a normal life, Charlie?
Yes,
as long as y'all do
everything I'm telling you
to do.
I had already
made up my mind
if it was going to be something
like this
- that we were going to leave.
- Absolutely. We're gone.
The kids come first,
and they got to have
a normal childhood.
The only way this family
can remain safe
is to move as far away
as possible.
They also need to contact
a psychic reiki master
to break Corey's
negative attachments.
If they do that, they can leave
the skeleton man behind
and begin a peaceful life
somewhere else.