Over here is really bad.
It breeds psychopaths.
I've been jumped.
He is breaking her neck.
I had to get out of the building
as quickly as I possibly could.
The dead can't rest.
I'm convinced it was
a homicide.
He likes killing people.
This is not a good situation.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's death here.
Don't wanna go down there.
I see dead people.
They hide in the walls
and they watch.
I speak to dead people...
She's definitely
a serial killer.
...and they speak to me.
She's going to torture them.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
They were all murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
So is this the only time
you've been physically attacked?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
There's no question in my mind
that he was talking about Satan.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who do you think
possessed you?
But Steve and I
never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
Well, you're not gonna want
to see this.
When we uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
Hell, no.
Or time to get out.
Everyone is in jeopardy.
I'm out here
in Sauk Centre, Minnesota.
It's about 100 miles northwest
of Minneapolis.
I got called in
by a woman named Kelley.
Now she thought she was
doing a good thing for her town
by buying and restoring
an historic hotel.
But no good deed
goes unpunished.
Activity in the building
is out of control,
but she says she's not leaving
no matter what,
so it's up to me and Amy
to find a solution.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area
of any leading information.
This is a large space,
and there are a lot of
historical photos and antiques.
I need to cover or remove each
and every one of them.
When I'm done, the location will
be ready for tonight's walk.
There's, like,
a dead guy here.
He's, like, being a stalker.
All you see is a skeleton
with, like, sharp teeth,
and he has a woman,
and he's holding her
by the back
of her head and neck.
He indicated that he murdered
her along with others.
He is a killer.
So, Kelley, when we spoke
on the phone,
you sounded really upset
about the things that are
happening here.
I'm really glad you're here.
The Palmer house is
so incredibly important to me.
I want it to be here
for generations to come,
and with the type of activity
that's going on,
it's become a real concern,
and now I begin to wonder
if it's even safe.
What are some of
the experiences
people are having?
There's been a lot of things
that are going on,
hearing footsteps,
objects being moved,
shadow figures,
and, in some cases,
people are being
touched and pushed.
I got to think, with all
the activity that's going on,
it's got to be bad
for business.
I definitely think
it is.
I've had guests that
have left.
It's frequent enough that
I actually created these binders
for guests to be able
to write their experiences down
themselves if they would like.
I got to tell you, this is
pretty interesting stuff.
What about employees?
Are they being affected?
I've had employees
that have quit
and mood shifts happen.
- Okay.
They can become
very quarrelsome,
very argumentative
with one another.
And you think that has something
to do with what's going on here?
I definitely think
it is.
Is it affecting you at all?
Sometimes,
I feel a little anxious
and really angry
and short-tempered,
but I can't imagine my life
anywhere but here.
It has my heart.
I love it with every fiber
of my being.
I want to make it work,
but I need it to be safe.
I walk in here
and my stomach drops,
and I hear a woman
crying and screaming.
This living woman,
she's just losing her...
The killer,
the skeleton face dude,
he's making me feel
extremely stressed out.
Also, the living people here
will feel,
sudden, extreme nausea
and projectile vomiting.
Okay, Kelley.
So what's going gonna in here?
There's just sometimes
that I end up
getting really sick
with no explanation.
Okay. What kind of sick?
What are we talking about?
Extreme nausea and terrible,
terrible headaches.
When you're away from here,
does the symptoms go away?
Yes, they do.
Okay. Anything else?
There's many times
I'm hearing voices.
Okay.
So what kind of voices?
Male, female.
Sometimes, it's even children
laughing and playing.
Kelley, in the building here,
I can hear people outside.
I can hear people in the back,
here in the kitchen.
How do you know
it's not that?
There's many occasions
when it's happened,
and we're already closed
for the night.
Is there anything else
going on in here?
One time, actually,
when I was just passing
through the kitchen,
this bowl on the end here
flew 10 feet across the kitchen.
Well, this can't really
fall off of here.
You're damn lucky that
it's that and not a knife.
My feelings exactly.
I'm seeing this living woman
being pushed out of here.
But I'm hearing, "Thrown,"
and I see that the dead woman,
that the skeleton-face guy
killed,
is the one who's doing it.
I don't think she likes
women very much.
She's very tough.
She's able to physically
interact with the living.
And, yeah,
she doesn't like women.
Okay, Kelley.
What's going on down here?
There's a very,
very large black shadow
that I've seen down here
on multiple occasions.
Can you describe
what it looks like?
Extremely tall,
very broad-shouldered.
Because of the sheer size,
I tend to say man,
but I don't know.
You ever see him anyplace else
in the building?
Sometimes upstairs.
Okay.
Anything else going on?
Well, the reason
I called you in for help
was because I've been
jumped.
What do you mean?
Like a spirit jumped you?
- Yes.
- So what was the feeling like?
It was absolutely like
somebody had complete control
over my body.
Did you get a sense of who
or what it might be?
It felt like a man.
I don't think that he
particularly cared for me.
That was as intense
as it comes.
So what do you think
this thing wants?
You have any idea?
I sometimes wonder if
it just wants me to leave.
I'm not going anywhere.
You're going to fight this.
Every step of the way
for as long as I have to.
This guy with
the skeleton-like face,
I don't feel to comfortable here
because I feel like
I'm constantly having
to push him away from me
because he can jump people.
So are you saying
he's trying to jump you now?
Yes, he's been trying to jump me
the whole time, the whole night.
Do you have any idea
what he wants from the living?
He indicated that
now he's death,
and he's enjoying that.
He likes killing people,
and he would like
to continue doing that.
So, Wyatt, I understand
you live at the hotel.
- How long has that been?
- Been here around 7 months.
Do you think this place
is dangerous?
I wouldn't like to say
it was dangerous,
but there has definitely
been times
where I've been
a little worried.
Okay.
So if you're uncomfortable,
could I assume
you've had experiences?
A few of them, yeah.
Absolutely.
I hear these banging sounds.
It's almost like a 30-pound
weight is being dropped.
All right. So how do you know
it's not guests?
Steve, I've been in this
building when I absolutely know
there has been nobody else
in the building with me.
Okay. Anything else?
I was sleeping one night.
All of a sudden, I felt like
somebody had laid in my bed
and put their arm around me.
- All right.
So can you actually feel
this person net to you?
Yeah, and I could feel
the fingertips
run across my chest,
and as it's touching me,
I feel almost like
being shocked
by an electric fence.
What'd you do?
I actually had thought about
climbing out of my window.
I couldn't move, so I just
kind of laid there,
and I just
kind of closed my eyes
and just hoped that
it would go away.
All right.
So anything else?
So I went into the basement.
As quick as snapping my fingers,
something had entered me.
The insides of me, it was almost
like they had changed.
My emotional state had changed.
I felt like a sickness had just
kind of embedded inside of me.
I had to get out of the building
as quickly as I possibly could.
I know Kelley mentioned
about an experience she had
where she felt she actually got
physically jumped by a spirit,
and it sounds a lot like
what you're talking about.
You think that's what
happened to you?
- Yeah. Yeah, I do.
- Okay.
So you're hearing noises
when people shouldn't be here.
You're getting something
crawling into bed with you.
You're getting...sounds like
jumped by a spirit
in the basement,
but yet you don't think
it's dangerous here.
Yeah, I can see why you'd think
that that would be a problem,
and, I, you know, sometimes,
it does worry me.
Are you not taking it
as serious as you should?
That's possible.
The skeleton-face dude, he is
very protective of this area,
so I think that he would
probably get physical
with the living down here
because he doesn't
want them down here.
Over here is really bad.
People would be pushed, hit,
slapped, punched.
I don't know how many people
he's actually had
to physically assault
to get them out of here.
It seems like he does more
of the killing upstairs.
Kelley is here all the time, and
you don't get here that often.
You know, with some of
the stuff she talked about,
it's pretty dangerous.
- Yeah. That's true.
You know, the amount of time
she spends here, that scares me.
I'm concerned about something,
you know, jumping on.
I'm concerned about her
bringing something home.
- Have you had any experiences?
- Yeah.
We were downstairs with a group
of people and just really,
all of a sudden,
it just turned black,
couldn't really even see
the hand in front of your face.
It startled me.
Now you say you were
down there with a group.
- What are you talking about?
- There was an investigation.
All right, so you had
a paranormal investigative group
in the building.
- Yes.
Is that something
you regularly do here?
Yeah.
I gotta warn you,
Amy's not gonna like that.
All right.
So any other experiences?
Well, in this room,
I was here one evening,
and there was this sound
of glasses clanking together,
and a bottle on this back bar
just burst on its own.
I mean, is it possible that
bottle already had a crack in it
and just finally gave way?
- I suppose it's possible.
To me, was hard to explain.
I've learned one thing
from my partner is that
when things get physical
like they are here,
it's only gonna get worse.
Wow. Okay.
There's a lot of residual here.
A lot of residual.
Now this is going back,
and so I'm seeing,
like, people drinking,
partying, having a good time,
and this looks like
a long time ago.
So how might all this
residual affect living people?
Wouldn't be surprised
if the living are
hearing the partying
from way back in the day --
glasses clinging,
chairs being moved,
like, stuff like that.
Or they'll hear bits
of conversation.
Residual energy is funny because
it can cause health problems.
Like?
Having flu symptoms
or cold symptoms.
Like, getting sick often.
I talked to a bunch of people
who spend time
at the Palmer House...
One time I was here,
I heard a loud explosion,
like a bomb went off.
...and all of them
had strange things happen
that they couldn't explain.
I stayed overnight,
third-floor room upstairs,
and I had a big wicker chair
move on its own.
As a cop, I always look for
witnesses whose stories match.
And just about everyone here
talked about seeing
shadow figures.
I can tell you about my most
emotional, scary experience.
One time, in the basement,
I was shoved by
a big black shadow figure.
Can you describe
what it looked like?
An outline, a silhouette
of a man in a suit
with very broad shoulders,
and his head went all the way up
to the top of the doorway.
Okay.
There's just a lot
of people.
Kind of looked like
shadow people, but they're not.
I don't know
what they're doing here.
I don't know why.
I would say, like, five or six.
It seems that they're men.
They seem confused,
and they seem a little crazy.
How would the living
be affected by them?
I think being exposed to them
would make a living person angry
and kind of nuts.
Look, this is a small town,
and the Palmer House
is probably the most important
local landmark.
So all the historian types
know all about it.
But one woman
just called me back and says
the man who owned the property
before it became this hotel
has a story I'm definitely
gonna wanna know about.
So, Jill, thanks
for reaching out to me.
I appreciate that.
Who was this guy?
Yeah, that would have been
Cassius Sprigg.
He was one of
the early pioneers in town.
Okay. So what was so interesting
about this guy?
He was a soldier in one of
the bloodiest battles
between settlers
and Native Americans.
Okay. So now tell me about
this battle.
He was just, like, 15 years old
when he fought in the battle
that become known
as the Battle of Ridgely.
It's about 90 miles south
of here.
- And this kid was only 15?
- Yes, he was.
That was not uncommon
for that time.
Okay. So how does this
bloody battle end?
Well, on December 26, 1862,
38 Native Americans
were hung.
To this day, it's the largest
mass execution in history.
Jeez.
I'm seeing a woman,
and she is hanging herself.
The skeleton-face guy,
he is breaking her neck.
He's directly involved.
He's killing people,
actually killing them.
This land is very, very bad.
It draws the dead in.
The dead can't rest,
so it's like a gathering place.
It breeds psychopaths.
Okay.
So now the war's over.
When does Cassius get ahold
of my client's property?
He would have bought it
in 1898.
- Okay.
- It was a hotel
called the Sauk Centre House
at the time.
It was not
a great investment.
- Why?
- On June 27, 1900,
it burned completely
to the ground.
All right.
This poor guy had the property
2 years and lost everything.
Yes. Now, there have been
several fires
on that property
over the years.
You might want
to look into that.
That's interesting.
Okay. I will.
Okay. Any idea what started
this fire?
It started in the kitchen,
they believe.
- Anybody die?
- No.
There were 30 guests
in the hotel at the time.
There were no fatalities.
Okay, but it's destroyed
totally.
- Completely.
- What happens next?
He collected
the insurance money
and then sold it
to the family, the Palmers.
Who built the hotel
that's there today.
Correct.
Okay. So what happens to him
after he sells the property
to the Palmers?
Well, his fortune seemed
to change after that.
He went into banking.
By the end of his life,
he owned 12 banks.
Okay.
So he it turns out this fire
might have been
a good thing for him.
You can look at it that way.
I'm trying to figure out
who this skeleton-face guy was
when he was alive.
He had a lot of money,
something with a bank.
I'm seeing a bank had
a direct connection here.
Do you know when this was?
Around 1890.
He's protecting something.
I know that this is part
of his secret.
He admits to killing people
when he was alive.
He let that slip out.
He's pissed.
Jill said there were
other fires on the property,
and it turns out she's right.
I'm headed over to meet with
the city's former fire chief,
who dug through
the records for me
and found four major fires
on the land.
Now, John, you mentioned
on the phone
that there were
four major fires
at the property
I'm investigating.
Now I know one happened
in 1900.
I know there's three more.
Let's start with the first one.
Okay. It was back
in September of 1873.
The fire was in the barn.
They believe it had
caught on fire
from a cigar discarded
into a bale of hay.
All right.
Was anybody injured or killed?
No injured or nobody killed.
All right, John.
So what about the second fire?
February of 1885,
there was a large fire.
I'm not sure where or how
it started.
One oddity to it is that
the current owner of
that building at that time
was the Sauk Centre
Fire Chief.
Jeez. Okay.
So now we got three fires
on my client's property.
What about the fourth one?
July 31, 1905. It happened
at the Palmer House.
And as you can see, it looks
pretty much as it does today.
And it was quite big news
at the time.
According to this, boarders
jumped from the windows?
There was eight employees,
I believe, on the second floor
that were trapped which had
to jump out of the building,
onto a canopy.
- Wow.
Yeah, desperate times,
desperate measures.
You know, over a 30-year-period,
you got four major fires,
two really bad ones.
- Yes.
And I'm just shocked that
nobody got injured or killed.
It's amazing.
Getting, like, a lot of smoke.
Yeah, there's a lot of smoke
up here.
I'm seeing a woman,
and she can't get out.
I don't know what this is.
She is panicked.
She feels very dizzy,
lightheaded.
She can't breathe.
I- I don't feel good.
This is bad.
For more information
about the show
and if you need us
to investigate
unexplained activity
in your home...
Please visit
travelchannel.com/thedeadfiles.
Click on "Help me, Dead Files!"
to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
So far, I've got
employees and guests
being tormented
by bizarre activity
on a property devastated
by four mysterious fires.
But I wanna see
if there's anything else.
Searching through old records,
I find a local police officer
named Jason Rosenburger.
Turns out, Jason was found dead
right down the street
from the Palmer House.
So I have a local reporter
looking into
this cop's death for me.
He did some digging and said
not only did he figure out
what happened to this guy,
but he found another death
associated with the Palmer House
that may help me out.
Mark, this article I came across
where the cop wound up dead,
what were you able
to find out?
On April 17, 1929,
Jason Rosenburger was
a policeman,
also night patrol,
was found dead at City Hall.
How far is this
from the Palmer House?
Approximately 500 feet.
In fact, the last person
to see him alive
was the night clerk
at the Palmer House.
I know this guy got shot,
so do we know
where the bullet entered?
Next to his nose,
just right underneath the eye.
So I'm assuming
this is a homicide.
Not necessarily.
The coroner's jury came back
and said it was accidental
discharge of the firearm.
All right.
So if it's accidental,
I guess a round
from his firearm was missing,
and that's what
he shot himself with.
Well, that's where it gets
interesting, because the round
that they found
did not match his gun.
Plus, his gun was
still fully loaded.
So how the hell is this
an accidental shooting?
That, I don't know.
To me, it's a homicide.
I mean, it sounds almost like
there's something being
covered up.
Somebody lost their left eye.
It's a male.
This male is getting shot,
definitely a shooting.
The guy in there
got shot in the eye.
I'm not being able
to see out of it.
He could absolutely be
in denial.
So, Mark, you mentioned
on the phone
there was another death
that might help my case.
Yes.
Back in 1870, there was
a freed slave named Mose
that lived and worked
at the property
you're investigating.
It was called the Barnum Hotel
at that time.
So do we know anything
about this guy Mose?
Well, it was known that
he was terrified of ghosts.
And also, he had experienced
some paranormal activity
at the Barnum Hotel.
Well, this is something
new I've never come across.
So back in 1870, somebody
was having experiences
on the property
I'm investigating now.
- Correct.
- How did he die?
A couple of local boys
wanted to pull a prank on him,
dress up as ghosts.
They hid in the hotel,
and everywhere he turned,
he'd run into a ghost,
and he got so scared
he just ran off into
the woods,
and he ended up spending
the night out there.
It was a cold and rainy night.
Right. So did this guy
die out in the woods?
No. They found him
the next morning,
and he was horribly sick,
brought him back to the hotel,
where he later died
on your client's property.
I saw several disturbing
things during my walk,
but two stood out.
First, the shadows figures
who hang out upstairs.
There was one crawling
on the ceiling.
There was one
crawling up the wall,
and then others that were
just really fragmented.
One looked like he was dripping,
like, chunks of tar.
Next, I described
the skeleton-face man
attacking the living.
There was this dead guy,
and he was pretty tall,
really thin,
and he was punching
a living person.
Amy, is this what
you saw?
Yes, that's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients
for the first time.
Well, Amy, I want you
to meet Kelley.
She owns the hotel and called us
in because activity is bad
and it's getting worse.
I got to be up front
with something.
No matter what you say tonight,
she ain't leaving.
Wyatt's been living here
for about 7 months,
and he's already been through
a hell of a lot,
and I don't think
it's going to take a lot
to convince him to move.
But they're hoping
you can figure out a way
to make this place safe.
So now that
Amy has met you guys,
I'm going to ask her
to describe her walk for us.
I got that this was
a gathering spot
for the dead,
and it has been for
a very, very long time,
and because of that,
there is
this huge collection
of residual information.
I think that living would
maybe hear partying going on.
You'd hear, like, glasses
clinking, chairs moving,
people walking around.
If you're consistently exposed
to this kind of energy,
it can make somebody sick.
Well, it's funny.
You hit on some of
the experiences they're having.
Now, Wyatt,
you mentioned it sounded like
somebody dropped a...
30-pound weight above me,
and it's during a time
when I know
there's nobody in the hotel.
- Kelley, you've heard footsteps.
- That's very common.
I've had other guests
talk about that as well.
Now, Kelley, and you as well,
Wyatt, told me about being sick.
There are some days that
it's just unexplainable fatigue,
the headache, nausea...
...feeling a little off-balance
or dizzy.
I get the exact same
kind of feeling.
Sick to my stomach,
a little woozy.
Amy, you said you got a lot
of residual information.
Well, this building we're
sitting in was built in 1901.
I have a photo right around
when it was built.
There's been a hotel on this
property since at least 1867.
You can imagine, there's been
a lot of people over the years
that have come through here.
That totally makes sense
with all the residual energy
that's here.
Okay, so what else?
So I'm on the third floor.
I'm literally tasting smoke
in my mouth and coughing.
Then I'm feeling this woman,
but she was all alone
and she was freaking out,
so she was panicking, too,
which was making it worse
because she was
breathing more in.
There's something
you should know about, Amy,
about this place.
There were
four major fires here.
Holy...
First fire happened in 1873
when this hotel was known
as the Sauk Centre House.
Here's a photo of
the original hotel.
Then in February of 1885,
the Sauk Centre Hotel
partially burned down.
Records are kind of thin
on that fire,
so we don't know what happened,
but nobody was hurt.
The next fire was in 1900,
and this one started
in the kitchen.
Once again, no casualties,
but the building was destroyed.
After that fire,
this hotel was built.
Now, the final fire happened
in July of 1905
at about 2:45 a.m.,
and that was the scariest one.
They had 45 employees and guests
in the hotel at the time.
They were forced to evacuate,
but eight of those people
were trapped upstairs
on the second floor.
They had to jump out
of the window...
...onto the old canvas tarps
to escape.
I actually have an article
on that fire.
Now, the building
was badly damaged.
But amazingly enough, again,
there was no casualties.
- That's a lot of fires.
- I did not know that.
So I'm in the dining room,
and now I'm getting this guy.
And he's shot
in one of his eyes,
'cause I couldn't see
out of the eye.
He is a dead person,
but he's in denial.
I did come across one individual
that was shot in the eye,
and his name was
Jason Rosenburger.
Yeah, he was a Sauk Centre
policeman and a night watchman.
Wow.
April 17, 1929, his body
was found in the old City Hall,
less than 500 feet from here.
In fact, the Palmer House Hotel
was on Rosenburger's beat,
and the night that he died,
this was the last location
he was seen alive.
He had been shot in the face,
and the bullet entered
just underneath his eye.
Now the coroner's jury decided
it was an accidental death.
I don't buy it.
The bullet on the scene didn't
match the bullets in his gun.
Not only that, no round
was discharged from his firearm.
I'm convinced it was a homicide.
I...Yeah.
- You agree?
- Absolutely.
Whatever happened,
happened so quick.
He had no knowledge because he's
in complete denial of his death.
I- I didn't know any of this,
and everything is
so much more real.
So another thing that I saw --
now we're going back up
to the third floor,
and I see about
four to six shadow beings,
and I knew
pretty damn quickly
that they were
actually dead men,
and the thing is,
is that these are
severely mentally ill people.
I think the biggest problem
with this for the living
is that, when you're exposed
to that kind of energy,
you're going to start having
behavioral changes yourself --
anger, acting kind of off
would begin to happen.
I've noticed that myself.
In yourself?
Even in myself.
What kind of thoughts
or emotions were you having?
A lot of anxiety, panicky,
a lot of nervousness
that came out of nowhere.
There's days where
all of the employees,
there can just be
very erratic,
unreasonable behavior,
actually.
- Really?
- You got a hotel here.
Why don't you
just sell it, right?
But I want you to tell Amy
how important this is.
I have come to take it
very personal and very seriously
that this is my purpose,
and my life is to be
the steward for it now.
And this is why, I told you
at the beginning,
she's not giving up.
She's not moving.
The crazy people
that look like shadows,
now would the living see that?
Or is that something
only you saw?
I do think that the living would
occasionally see shadow figures,
and I had a sketch done
of specifically what I saw.
Here you go, guys.
I gotta say that that's exactly
kind of how it feels.
It just feels like
I'm falling apart.
Just about everyone I talked
to here has seen shadow figures.
Other guests have shared
with me...
Right.
...lots of
different things...
Yeah.
...that are fairly extreme.
What did you consider
extreme?
On the ceiling, for example.
- Yeah.
- Up the wall.
That would be terrifying.
Yeah.
I would think so, yeah.
Kelley here has seen
specific shadow figures
down here in this basement.
He is so big.
His mass is so wide
and he's so tall.
- Is that what she's seeing?
- No. Mnh-mnh, no.
- That's somebody else.
- Ooh.
- That's not good news.
- Yeah.
So one of the dead people
that I encountered
was a dead woman
who was murdered.
She was murdered by the guy
that she was with,
and he's here,
and he's very active here,
but I'll get to him
in a second.
The woman is most active
in the kitchen.
She can get physical
with the living,
and I did see her pushing
a female
out one of the doors
out there.
Like, just pushing her out.
Now, Kelley,
you weren't pushed,
but you had something
thrown at you.
There was a mixing bowl.
It flew off of the shelf
it was on,
about 10 feet
through the air.
So she's throwing...
Now how about the guy
that killed her?
Yes. I'm gonna refer to him
as "skeleton face."
This is the male
who killed this female.
He is definitely
the biggest threat.
He's very, very powerful,
very dangerous,
and very secretive.
There are a few things that
I was able to get out of him.
He was white, lots of money.
I got that the 1890s were
very important to him,
absolute connection
to this location.
He made it very clear to me
that he did a lot of bad things
when he was alive,
and that included
killing several people.
You know, it's not a lot
to go on, but some of the stuff
you were talking about
reminds me
of one of the past owners
of this place.
His name was Cassius Sprigg.
You mentioned the 1890s
were important to him.
Now, he bought
this property in 1898.
Now, the guy you saw killed
people when he was alive.
Well, Cassius fought
in the Dakota-Indian Wars.
Now, we have no idea
how many people Cassius killed,
but we do know
that the war ended
with the execution
of 38 people,
and he was part of all this.
To this day, it's the largest
mass execution
in American history.
Now, Sprigg only owned
this hotel for a few years.
After he got out of
the hotel business, though,
he got into banking
and made a small fortune.
I've got a photo of him.
Any chances this is who you saw?
- Any idea?
- I don't think so
'cause he made it seem
like the killings
he did were not, like,
public knowledge.
Now you said you were concerned
about the skeleton-face guy.
Why is that?
This guy is capable
of mimicking voices,
mimicking people.
So like,
a friend, coworker,
when you think
they're saying something
and there's nobody there.
That's a common occurrence
for myself and other employees,
and you keep trying
to go find it, thinking,
"Maybe somebody came back
into the building,"
and then that's
eventually realized
that you're
in the building alone.
And what's probably the most
frightening for living people
is that he does know
how to jump people.
He was trying to do it to me
throughout my walk,
and he was
extremely aggressive
when I got down into
the basement.
My god.
These are two people that feel
like they've been jumped.
I don't have a lot of memory
when it happened to me,
I just knew it wasn't me.
Couldn't collect my thoughts.
Like, I felt like this outer
shell of me was doing something,
and the inside was
looking around going,
"What is going on?"
Something similar
happened to Wyatt.
I was down here in the basement
and was just, like,
a snap of my fingers,
and I felt overcome
and overwhelmed.
He will do anything he can
to instill fear
and get the living
out of here,
and that can become
physical or be physical --
slapping, pushing, punching.
I saw him punching a male
in the back,
and I did have a sketch done.
This should be interesting.
Ooh.
That's some picture, ain't it?
I don't know even know
what to say to that.
My god.
What's this speck behind it?
What's this going on?
This is a friend of his,
and they're killing
this guy here.
He didn't want me
to see that.
He's gotta go.
What the hell does this guy
want from these guys?
Basically, he wants
to kill living people.
Kelley, you made it
very clear
that leaving here
is not an option for you.
But after what
we've heard tonight,
it's crystal clear that
it's not safe here for you,
your employees or the guests.
Now we're going to find out if
there's any way to change that.
For that answer, I'm going to
turn it over to Amy.
I have something to say
really quickly.
A few days after my walk,
I see that you're doing
an event here --
a ghost tour.
- Yeah.
How long have you been
doing that?
Probably for about
4 or 5 years now.
You've noticed an increase
in activity?
I would say that's fair.
When you're stirring up
this kind of activity,
...gonna go wrong.
I gotta ask you.
When we talked,
you never really mentioned
about this whole
ghost-hunting thing.
I never thought of that as
being a contributing factor.
A big reason of why
I do what I do is the dead.
These were people,
and they still are people.
It's easy, I think,
for the living, um,
to have a disassociation
with that concept.
My question is,
what do you want to do?
And do you want
the dead here or not?
If they need moving on,
I'm in complete support of that.
All right. So how do they
get rid of 'em?
You do have to find
a male medium
who is also
a chaos magician.
He is going to basically
collect
the dead skeleton guy
and remove him
from the location altogether.
The other thing that does
is that it literally
will clear the basement
of not only him but also
all the residual information
and energy down here.
So, like, this basement?
Nothing. Nothing going on.
So she won't see the shadows
down here, won't get jumped.
Yeah, that's right.
On another day, the same medium
could come back and remove
all of the shadow people
and the pissy lady.
Unfortunately, the cop, nothing,
at this point, can be done.
Now, if you want to keep
doing ghost tours,
you can keep the residual,
and there is
a plethora of it.
So, Kelley,
when we first talked,
you were just about ready
to break down.
Now it looks like you get to
not only keep your place
but find out a way
to make it safe
and still have it
as an attraction for people
that are into the ghost hunting.
That would absolutely
be ideal.
Now the ultimate question --
Are you gonna do what she says?
Yes, I absolutely will.
So, Wyatt, what about you?
Would you be willing
to help out?
Yeah, I'm here for her.
I am so immensely pleased
and relieved and grateful.
I feel very optimistic
about everything.
It won't be easy
removing the dangerous dead
inside this hotel.
But if Kelley contacts
the medium, who is also
a chaos magician,
to banish the dead,
her guests and employees
will be safe,
and she can keep running
the hotel she loves so much.