There's a lot of chaos.
He's like, "Get out of here.
I own this."
You just grab
your head in agony.
It literally felt like fire.
You okay?
I'm just hearing "knife."
He died instantly.
There's so much commotion here,
it's ridiculous.
This is not a good situation.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's death here.
Don't wanna go down there.
I see dead people.
They hide in the walls
and they watch.
I speak to dead people...
She's definitely
a serial killer.
...and they speak to me.
She's going to torture them.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
They were all murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
So is this the only time
you've been physically attacked?
I know every person,
every house has secrets.
There's no question in my mind
that he was talking about Satan.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who do you think
possessed you?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
Well, you're not gonna want
to see this.
When we uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
Hell, no.
Or time to get out.
Everyone is in jeopardy.
I'm in Sahuarita, Arizona, about
a half-hour south of Tucson.
I got a call
from a woman named Karen
who just recently
moved into a new house.
Now she says
all hell has broken loose
and it's ripping
her marriage apart.
But this is what has got
her most worried --
Her daughter is
supposed to move in
with her two grandkids soon,
and she's worried
they're going to be stepping
into a paranormal war zone.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the house
of any leading information --
photographs, personal items.
Even medical equipment
can influence her findings,
so it's important I cover
or remove them all.
When I'm done, the location will
be ready for tonight's walk.
This place is really,
really bad.
There's quite a lot going on.
There's a lot of chaos,
a lot of chaos.
It's never quiet.
I can understand why
nobody would sleep here.
There's so much commotion here,
it's ridiculous.
So, Karen, when we spoke on
the phone, you sounded upset.
What's going on?
We bought this house
about a year and a half ago.
This is our retirement home.
It was supposed to be
the forever home...
But it's not.
So your retirement home
is basically a war zone.
It is right now.
You also mentioned
on the phone
that you were concerned
about your husband.
Yeah. His name is Don.
Okay.
And about 6 years ago,
he had a stroke.
His moods changes
are getting worse.
Little tiny things
will just make him blow up.
I call him a human volcano.
So it's just you and Don
that live here.
Right now, yeah.
In about 5 weeks,
my youngest daughter
and two of my grandchildren
are moving in.
And how old are her kids?
4 and almost 9.
So, Karen, you've got
to be concerned about
a 4 and an 8-year-old
moving in here.
Very concerned.
I'll do whatever you guys say.
What exactly are you guys
experiencing here?
There's everything
from noises and shadows
to physical touching,
scratching.
It's also affecting
my health.
Okay. So what's going on?
Headaches.
It feels like hot prod
to the point
where you just
grab your head in agony.
I don't sleep.
I'm up all night.
You know, what are you hoping
we can do for you guys?
I'm hoping that we can get
a happy home
for my daughter
and granddaughters,
and I'm concerned with Don
being here all the time,
so I want it to be
a good home.
You're not asking for a lot.
I don't think I could deal
with it if anything happened
to the girls
or the grandchildren.
I couldn't handle it.
I do feel sick.
I'm just getting, like,
horrible nausea,
so somebody is dealing
with that, a living person.
Headaches,
you know,
with the insomnia.
There is this guy here
who is dressed like a priest,
but I think he's lying
about being a priest.
I think he's lying about
what he looks like.
He could be a demon.
The nausea, the headaches,
the not sleeping
is a way that this thing
breaks people down
so that it can get them.
So what's going on
in this room?
I was sitting
in my recliner.
My leg started burning,
and I looked down,
and I had scratches.
How bad of a scratch
was it?
- It raised the skin.
- Okay.
And the worst part was
the burn.
Now you told me you have cats.
Could it have been the cats?
No, 'cause they were
in their bedroom.
Okay, so there was
no animals in here?
No.
Okay, have you ever been
physically touched
like that anyplace else
or before?
Yes.
- Right in the hallway...
- Okay.
...I was sweeping,
and I had my arm grabbed.
Okay, describe to me
how it felt.
Okay. Like that.
- That hard?
- That hard.
Now have you had
muscle spasms before?
No.
All right,
is there anything else?
Yeah. Shadows.
I see a lot of shadows,
and there's this almost
constant parade at times.
All right, so do these shadows
have any shape, like a human?
I don't really see them
as a shape.
It's more of a mist
or a mass.
Now how often
are you seeing them?
Almost daily.
People see a lot of...
outside here.
There is a path,
and then I got a line of, like,
shadow people lining up.
Yeah, they're all in line,
one behind the other,
single file.
But they're not shadow people.
They're dead people.
Is there any connection
between this priest guy
and these people that are
lined up and walking?
I don't really know, but I think
these dead people,
the living see them.
I think they just, like,
see them, like,
corner of their eye.
They're somewhere in the house.
It's very stressful.
Stress. Stress.
Stress.
All right, so what's
going on down here?
As I get into bed
and I'm just settling in,
I felt somebody
crawl over the top of me.
I'm in full prayer mode,
and it just went away.
Any of the animals stay in bed
with you guys?
No. No.
The dogs have kennels...
Okay.
...that are over on
the far side of the room.
Okay.
All right.
so anything else?
Well, yes.
A couple nights ago,
when I laid down,
I could feel something
sit next to me,
pulling the blankets tight
around my legs.
Okay, can you show me
how hard the pressure was?
It was just like this.
Okay, so as if a normal person
was sitting down on the bed.
Right.
I'm trying to figure out
what else it could be.
I'm at a loss right now.
I don't know why
they're grabbing me.
And why would
they crawl over me?
I just know
that I want them gone.
Yeah.
I'm seeing, like, vomiting,
crying, punching.
And, I mean, I think
this is happening now
with a living person here.
They're vulnerable
to, priest man.
The priest comes
and becomes
as thin as the blanket,
and then it's melding
into the person's body.
So what is this thing doing to
this person when it does this?
It goes inside of their body.
Like, all the way in,
into all of the bones
and the muscles and the tissues.
I see it, like, affecting
the physiology of the person.
What does it want
from this person?
Death.
So, Don, I was talking
to your wife Karen,
and she's concerned about
her daughter coming to live
with the kids.
Yeah. I'm concerned, too.
I mean, I don't want them
in here
if it's not safe for them.
Now as far as
your own experiences,
can you tell me about any?
Yeah. I see shadow figures
all the time.
Karen mentioned
the same thing to me.
Okay, so how often are you
seeing these shadows?
Daily basis.
All right, Don,
anything else?
Yeah, in the downstairs
bathroom,
I would get pushed
almost every time
I took a shower.
I know you had a stroke.
Could it be a side effect
from some of the medications
you're taking?
No.
I'm down to only
blood pressure medications now.
All right, Don,
anything else?
I was downstairs,
and I heard Karen crying
uncontrollably upstairs,
so I'm running upstairs
to see what was wrong.
And when I got there,
she was just fine
and said that she hadn't been
crying, that she was quiet.
All right. What about a TV
or a radio being on?
No. It wasn't on.
Okay, mow did you ever
hear that again?
Yeah. It actually happened
the other way around after that.
- She heard you?
- Yes.
Karen said that
she heard me screaming
like something
was really wrong,
that I was pissed off
about something.
Okay. You sure you weren't
going crazy and having a fit?
No. I was folding laundry.
All right, this is...
That's a little strange.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
The priest, who now
is claiming to be a demon,
I think he can jump people.
Like, the word,
the possession word,
is being thrown around a lot.
Living people see, like,
this pretty thick, black mist,
and it's pretty tall.
That's how he melds with people.
Like, that's why
he's in that form,
so he can meld easily
with people's bodies.
The way that,
that would affect the living,
I'm seeing, you know,
them acting crazy.
And they wouldn't remember.
Say they're eating,
and then all of a sudden,
somebody jumps up
from the kitchen table
and is like, "I'm gonna...
kill everyone!"
That's this thing, like,
jumping them.
It speaks through the living.
So, Don, talking to Karen,
she also mentioned to me
that you're having
mood swings.
Your attitude has changed.
What's the story there?
I will, all of a sudden,
get really frustrated
or get really mad,
and I don't know why
I feel like that.
It just hits me,
and I just...
I'll get really mad
and frustrated out of the blue.
Are you afraid
you might get physical?
I'm just afraid that, yeah,
I'm gonna yell or scream
or say something that's really
going to hurt somebody,
and I don't mean it.
Okay.
I mean, do you think Karen's
afraid of you when this happens?
Well, she will tell me
sometimes, "You're yelling."
And it's, "I'm not
trying to yell.
I'm just trying to talk
to you."
I want to do whatever it takes
to protect our family.
- Okay.
- You know, this is something
that I just can't fight
on my own.
Okay.
This priest-demon thing...
...will go after the weak
and vulnerable.
I think he's trying to do that
with somebody at this location.
There's something about this
place that attracts bad things.
Karen told me
her daughter Valerie plans
on moving into the house
with her kids.
Now she's not in state,
so I'm reaching out to her
on video chat to see
if she's had any experiences.
So, Val, I got to tell you, I've
been talking to your parents,
and I'm not sure
it's such a good idea
for you to move in here
with the kids.
I mean, how you feel
about that?
It is very concerning.
My mom is allowing us
to come in and get back
on our feet
after a divorce and try
to reestablish ourselves.
But if things can't
get figured out,
I may have to find
a different living situation.
So have you visited
the house here in Arizona?
Yes, actually. I have
been there multiple times.
When you were here,
did you have any experiences?
Yeah. I've experienced
a shadow a couple of times.
Okay. It seems everybody's
seen shadows here.
How did you experience it?
I was sitting on the love seat
in the living room,
and off to my right-hand side,
there was a shadow
that would walk in front of it
and block the reflection.
All right. Anything else?
I've had feelings
of being watched.
Now was that in anyplace
specific in the house?
Mainly downstairs.
It just felt like somebody
was in the room watching me.
I would feel like I was going
to have a panic attack.
You got to be concerned
about yourself
and the kids at this point,
if they do come here.
I'm afraid that, with
the children being so young,
that they may be vulnerable
to attacks on themself.
My feeling, at this point,
about the priest/demon thing
is that it was a human.
And this person was religious.
And I don't think they look like
how they presented themselves
to me at any time.
This priest-demon guy
is going nuts.
He's like, "Get out of here.
I own this."
Like, "Get the...out of here,
or I'm gonna, like,
kill everybody."
So I made my usual calls
when I got into town,
and a local journalist
just called back
and said he's got something
that's going to help me out.
Apparently, a hotel owner got
lost wandering in the desert
and ended up dying right on
Karen and Don's property.
So, David, do me a favor.
Set the scene for me.
When this guy wandered
onto my clients' property,
when was this,
and who owned the property?
Well, your clients' property
was part of a ranch owned
by a man named
James Kilroy Brown.
Brown had purchased
the property in 1877
and named it
the Sahuarito Ranch.
All right.
Over time, the ranch grew
to about 4,000 acres.
All right, so now this guy
has got 4,000 acres.
But what's he do with it?
Well, Brown fully utilized
his 4,000 acres
as a cattle ranch as well
as, also, a stage stop.
All right. So what can you tell
me about the guy that got lost?
Well, the gentleman that got
lost, his name was James Dixon.
He was a hotel owner
in Tucson.
He invested in mines
in southern Arizona.
On May 1, 1887, he decided to
take a wagon and a horse
and head down towards his mines
to see how they were doing.
And on the way down there,
he stops at the Sahuarito Ranch,
just to water his horse
for a little bit,
and then decides
to continue on going south.
At that point,
he ends up getting lost.
And if you look out here,
this is not a place
you want to get lost
in the middle of summer.
It's deadly.
Well, eventually,
Brown gets wind of this
and gathered together
a bunch of the ranchers
in the area,
and they formed a search party.
It actually made
the local paper.
Brown basically did
the right thing.
He didn't have to look
for this guy.
And they searched for days
and days, and eventually,
they find Dixon lying
under a tree, half-naked.
Now why would he do that?
I think he went plumb crazy
wandering the desert.
What did they do with him?
Well, Brown takes him
back to the ranch,
and Dixon dies on your clients'
property that night.
Here's an article about that.
Sadly, Dixon was
only 47 years old,
and he had a wife and two
daughters he left behind.
- That's a shame.
- Yeah.
I'm seeing a church.
I think it belongs
to the priest-demon guy.
In the pews were
all of these dead people.
They're freaked out,
and they're trapped
in this space by the priest.
But he ain't no priest.
He ain't no Catholic.
He is a fake, false prophet.
He'll kill 'em off
and put 'em
into one of the pews.
So far, I've got a couple
being tormented on a property
where a lost traveler died,
but I want to see
if there's anything else.
Searching through old records,
I come across an article
about a homeless Mexican man
who was brutally murdered
back in 1893.
It turns out
the homicide took place
right next to
Karen and Don's property.
I asked a local sergeant to look
into this murder for me,
and he stumbled
onto a second homicide.
It's a small town, so I'm
actually kind of surprised,
but hopefully, one of these
will help my case.
So, Mike, thanks
for meeting with me.
The homicide I found,
what were you able
to find out
about the victim?
We don't know a lot.
We know that he's homeless
and his name is Pancho Mendozo.
How's he wind up
getting murdered?
On October 13, 1893,
he was passing by
the James Kilroy Brown Ranch,
which is now
your clients' property,
and I guess he got tired
and he got hot, and he decided
he was going to lay down
underneath a mesquite tree
and take a nap.
While he's doing that, he's not
aware that he's being followed,
but what happens is,
is that the murderer came up
and caught him
while he was asleep
and stabbed him
once in the throat
and once in the right side
of the abdomen.
He had died instantly.
They ever make an arrest?
The sheriff did make
an arrest.
Did he get indicted,
convicted?
No, there was no indictment.
They weren't convicted.
There was -- The grand jury
could not agree on the charges.
All right, so it's 1893.
You got a homeless Mexican guy.
What did they do with
the body?
At that time,
he didn't have any money,
and he had no family,
nobody to claim the body,
so they buried him very close
to exactly where he was killed,
right near
your clients' property.
- You're kidding me.
- No.
That's just the way
they did it back then.
There's this older drunk guy
who looks like he was,
back in the day, from Mexico.
I feel sick.
And I'm feeling, like...pain,
lots of pain all through here.
I'm hearing all these noises.
I was outside, and then "knife."
I'm just hearing "knife."
I don't know what that is.
And I hear, "Back away."
All right, so, Mike,
you mentioned on the phone
there was a second homicide
you found.
Correct.
Okay, so what can you tell me
about the victim?
The victim's name
is Glendell Soape.
He's 25 years old.
He's married
and has three kids,
and he's from
Scottsdale, Arizona.
All right, so I assume
he's down here on business.
Well, actually,
on May 23, 1963,
he went down
to a predominantly black bar
looking for a prostitute,
and goes up
to a perfect stranger,
whose name is Leo Davis,
and asked him if he can
hook him up with a black girl.
- And does he get hooked up?
- He did so.
He went
and found one for him,
and they went and had sex
outside of the bar.
- Does the pros set him up?
- No, not at all.
After they were done having sex,
he decides, all of a sudden,
that he wants to go to Mexico
and get cheap liquor.
So he jumps in the car
with his new friend, Leo Davis,
and another guy
and the prostitute,
and they all head
down the road for Mexico.
Well, about a mile from
your clients' property,
they pull off
the side of the road.
So Davis slugs Mr. Soape
in the head,
and then
they both grabbed him,
pulled him out of the car,
killed him,
and take his watch
and $600.
And I have his certificate
of death right here.
Cause of death was
listed as a broken neck.
So did this guy Davis
or anybody else
get arrested for this?
Yes. They did.
A couple months later,
the prostitute gave up both men.
Here's the article.
They were convicted,
and both of them
were sentenced
to life in prison.
When I walked out here,
I was seeing, like,
a guy,
and I was seeing, like,
him feeling
like he was burning.
Like, it literally felt
like fire, like, on the inside.
All of a sudden,
he's like, "...!"
Like, somebody's, like,
kicking him in the shins,
and then he's feeling hit
in the back here.
You know what I mean?
And then he's on the ground.
Very scary.
Look, it's Arizona,
so obviously,
there's gonna be a lot
of Native American history.
But I just got off the phone
with local historian
who says a tribe that lived
where Don and Karen's house sits
was involved
in a horrific massacre.
I'm driving over now to
find out exactly what happened.
So, Bridgette, before we get
to the massacre
you told me about
on the phone,
what can you tell me
about the tribe that lived
on my clients' property?
The tribe was called
the Tohono O'odham,
and they've been in this area
for hundreds of years.
Here's a picture
that we have of them.
And they actually are
still around.
They have a large reservation
just west of here.
So this big massacre,
who was involved?
The massacre was between
the Tohono O'odham
and the Apache.
Okay. So now
what was the beef?
Well, the Apache would come to
the Tohono O'odham settlements,
and they would raid
and they would steal,
and they would often kill a lot
of the Tohono O'odham people.
Now did any of these attacks
by the Apache happen
on my clients' property?
We don't have any record
of them actually happening
on your clients' property,
but we're sure
they happened nearby.
So, Bridgette, tell me
about the massacre.
It started in
the spring of 1871.
The Apaches surrendered
to the American government
at Camp Grant,
and these are some pictures
of Camp Grant.
It's about 60 miles north
from your clients' property.
Okay, so it's north up here.
Okay. So what happened?
The Tohono O'odham saw
an opportunity to attack,
so they traveled 2 days.
- Okay.
And they go up to
Camp Grant.
On April 30, 1871, at dawn,
they attacked.
144 people died,
and 136 of those
were women and children.
All right. So all these people
dead. Did anybody survive?
They take any prisoners?
There were 30 children
that did survive,
and they were sold
into slavery,
and they were marched down
into Sonora, Mexico.
There's a road
that actually went
right by
your clients' property.
And a couple of them did
manage to escape.
This is one that we know
for sure made it back,
and as far as we know,
the rest of them
died in slavery
down in Mexico.
All right. So did anybody pay
for this massacre at all?
The territory governor
arrested over 100 people,
and when the verdict
went to the jury,
they were all acquitted.
Nobody got convicted
of anything?
No.
The people of Pima County were
very supportive of the massacre,
so the Apache
never saw justice.
The Native Americans
cursed this land.
That stems from way, way, way,
way, way, way, way, way back,
from the murder and mayhem
that was committed.
This was specific to this area.
They were tying Native Americans
that they had captured.
These Native Americans
were slaves.
I don't know exactly
what they were forced to do,
but I just saw
the word "slaves."
Is the priest
trapping them in the church
with the other dead people?
I think so. Yeah.
Some of them were
pretty much skeletons
with just, like, little bits
of flesh hanging off.
So I'm estimating that there
were about 80 of these people.
The ones who were
almost skeletons, I think,
died at the same time,
so they're in a lot of pain.
During my walk, I saw a whole
bunch of disturbing things,
but two stood out.
First,
the group of shadow figures
marching through the house.
What I saw in this hallway was,
in single file,
shadow people,
and different heights.
Next, I described
the priest-demon
tormenting the living.
You can see that he was
looking like a human
and it stands by the bed
and it becomes a thin mist
and it covers the person
and then it meshes into them.
Amy, is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients
for the first time.
Well, Amy, I want you to meet
Karen and Don.
They bought this house
about a year and a half ago,
and they were hoping to make it
a dream retirement home.
Obviously, that hasn't
worked out that way.
But the main reason we're here
is Karen's daughter, Valerie.
Now she's in a tough spot
and is supposed to move in here
with her two daughters.
Next month?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
The problem is, these guys
don't think it's safe,
so I'll ask Amy to describe
her walk for us.
When I first arrived,
and I saw murder and mayhem
that happened here
a long, long time ago.
It involved Native Americans
who had ties to the land.
They were being utilized
as slaves.
The other thing is that there
was a curse placed on this land
a very long time ago.
I got something with slaves
when I did the research.
It was an Indian tribe
called the Tohono O'odham...
Okay.
...who lived
in and around your property
for hundreds of years.
Now I actually have a photo
of what they had looked like
back in the 1850s.
But there was bad blood
between them and the Apaches.
They took abuse
from the Apaches for years.
Now in 1871, the Tohono O'odham
got their revenge.
The Apaches surrendered
to the U.S. government
at Camp Grant,
which is about 60 miles north
of here.
Here's a picture of Camp Grant.
On April 28, 1871,
the local tribe headed north
and surrounded the camp,
and it turned into a bloodbath.
By the end of it,
144 people were killed.
136 of them
were women and children.
Wow.
Now about 30 of these Apache
kids survived the massacre,
but they marched them
down past here into Mexico...
...to sell them off
into slavery.
And I actually have a picture
of one of the Native Americans
that we know escaped.
My god. I've seen her.
I've seen her.
When I close my eyes
at night, I-I see...
- Here, sweetie. Take that.
- ...I see people.
I just hope
she's okay somewhere.
I'll just put this picture here.
It seems to be upsetting you.
You think this could have
something to do
with the curse on the land?
Yes.
Essentially, the curse
is that anyone who's white
will not live
a peaceful life here.
So what else happened
on the walk?
So I came inside,
and I was pulled immediately
to the downstairs hallway.
And I was then
in a male's body,
and he was in a lot of pain,
and I started to hear
all of these noises around him.
So we're outside,
and I felt like I was being
stabbed in my side.
And I, of course, felt very ill,
and I didn't really understand
what the hell was happening,
and then I heard
the word "knife."
So, Amy, that's not much
to go on,
but it does sound
like a homicide
I did come across
in my research.
Now the victim's name
was Pancho Mendozo.
We didn't know much about this
guy other than he was homeless,
and he was about 55 to 60.
On October 13, 1893,
Mendozo was traveling
from Tucson to Mexico,
passing right through
your property.
So he was tired and decided to
take a little nap nearby a tree.
It turns out he was
being followed.
While Mendozo was sleeping,
someone came up to him
and attacked him.
He was stabbed twice, once in
the throat and in the torso.
And he basically bled out
and died on the scene.
To this day, the case
is still unsolved.
Wow.
This is the real kicker
of the whole thing --
Mendozo had no family or money,
and he was buried
right under the tree
where they found him.
Interesting.
So what else happened
on the walk?
When I was outside,
I saw a lot of dead people
walking in single file,
and they're on
a specific pathway,
and it goes right through
your house.
Here I'm seeing four,
and here I'm seeing eight.
At the same time, living people
would see them as shadow people.
But they're not.
They're just dead people.
- I refer to it as a parade...
- Yeah. Okay.
...going through the house
this way.-
And I'll see, like,
two, four, six.
Crazy.
It's like it's a constant,
daily...
- Now you see them too, Don.
- Yeah.
Interesting. Okay.
When I spoke to Valerie
on a video conference,
she described the same thing.
I did have a sketch done
of what I was kind of seeing.
Take a look at that.
My god.
And that's how it looks
to you, Karen?
Yeah. Yeah.
It's like wave after
wave after wave.
Now you know you're not nuts.
Thank you.
All right,
so interesting walk so far.
What else?
So then I ran into
an entity here that, to me,
represents
the biggest problem.
He's dressed like
a Catholic priest,
but he's not really
a priest at all,
but I couldn't figure out
if he was a demon
or if, in fact,
he had once been human.
So what was he?
A dead person.
And he started, like,
swearing and cursing at me,
being very threatening
and saying
that he was going
to kill all of us.
When I met him,
he's in a church,
and in his church,
he has a lot of dead people.
So his thing is he is
collecting all of these people
and brings them into this church
that he's created,
and he's trapping them there.
So does this priest thing...
Would it interact
with these guys?
I think that it does have
the ability
to go after you physically.
I had an experience
last night
where he was messing
with my throat,
so I got these four lines,
and it was burning
like a...
- Yeah.
- That's you.
That's me.
I came home from work,
and within just a couple minutes
of walking in the door,
my leg starting burning
like a chemical burn.
I looked down,
and I had three scratches
right up the calf.
He likes to go after
the weak and sick
din this house specifically.
That's easy prey for him.
I did feel that there was
a living individual
in this house
that had become
a target for him
and that this thing
is making this person sicker.
I had a stroke 6 years ago,
and I've had, you know,
ongoing blood-pressure issues.
I got specific illness traits
of terrible headaches,
nausea, and insomnia,
and essentially, what he's doing
is torturing the person.
I've been put on
a sleeping pill.
Tell her about the headaches,
the way you described them
to me.
I get these intense...
It's almost like a fire prod
being put in your head.
Now is he targeting
both of them?
Well, I think that
it's mainly you,
but it's not just
one person.
The guy is into torture.
- Yeah.
- You know?
And the worst thing is that
he can jump people.
He can make himself appear
like a black mist,
and then he'll meld
into the person's body.
This can cause mood swings,
and when he does that,
he literally speaks through
the living in this house.
And so I saw people
yelling out strange things.
You know, you're
sitting at the table.
You're eating, and then,
all of a sudden,
somebody jumps up
and is like,
"I'm gonna...kill everybody!"
just out of nowhere,
and then has no recollection
that they did that.
Yeah.
I was downstairs one day,
and I heard Karen up here
crying uncontrollably,
so I come running upstairs.
She was sitting in the chair
and just said, "I was fine."
And then, about a week
or two later, she goes,
"I heard you
downstairs yelling and..."
- Throwing a full tantrum.
- I said, "No."
- Wow.
- I was fine.
And you've got the mood swings
you were talking.
Yeah. All of a sudden,
I'll get extremely frustrated
to the point where, you know,
I almost start to vibrate,
but then I just get pissed off
and I don't know why.
His whole
speech mannerism changes.
And it's like,
"Don, knock it off."
Yeah.
Yeah. You okay? Yeah.
It's tough to hear.
I know.
- Yeah.
- You okay?
It's okay.
That's why
we're doing this.
- Right?
- It's not you, Don.
- Right.
- It's okay, man.
It's okay.
We can get this fixed.
You can be happy.
Now this thing do anything else
besides torture these people?
- Um...
- It's doing a good job of that.
I was in the downstairs
basement,
and I saw him standing
at the end of the bed.
God.
And then he became
that mist again,
and he will sink
into the person's body.
Obviously, this affects
the living person's
body horribly.
Gosh.
Um...
I had just gone to bed,
and I felt something
from the foot of the bed,
hand, knee, crawl
right over my body.
You also had another experience
where it felt like somebody
sat on the bed.
Yes.
I'll be laying in bed,
and you can feel somebody sit.
The blankets tighten,
and from my knees
to my feet got ice cold.
I did have a sketch done
of that situation that I saw.
Jeez.
You guys have been through
a lot tonight. All right.
My god.
Valerie's bringing
her small kids here.
Would they be in danger, too?
Yes. Absolutely,
the children, yeah.
That scares the hell
out of me.
What the hell does this priest
thing want from these guys?
His goal is to kill you guys,
and it's definitely got you
in mind for his church.
Well, Karen, you called us in
because you were worried
about Valerie moving in
with the grandkids.
Turns out bringing us in may
have saved you and Don's life.
Now we're gonna answer
the big question.
Can you kick this
priest-demon thing out,
and what's it going to take?
For that answer, I'm going
to turn it over to Amy.
There are things you can do,
but the thing you do need
to be aware of
is that you will deal
with issues on a daily basis
because of the area
and the curse that's here.
So basically,
you'll never have peace
like you've known prior
to moving to this place.
So the first thing is
to bring a medium in
and simply have them
help the stabbing victim
and the group
of dead people move on.
What I would like for you to do
in dealing with
this priest dead guy
is a true Catholic priest
needs to come in
and do a blessing
at the property line.
Then, using rosaries that have
been blessed by the same priest,
so five rosaries,
bury them at approximately
the four corners
of your property
and then place the fifth one
in the approximate center
of the house.
Now once they do all this,
will this priest-demon
get the hell out of here?
Correct.
It won't be easy.
But we need to do it,
and we're going to do it.
You're worth it.
The grandkids are worth it.
So now if they do everything
you told them they need to do,
is Don going to feel better?
I think you will.
What about Karen?
She'll be able to go to sleep,
no more of those big headaches?
That'll be done.
Maybe we can actually unpack,
and you don't turn into
evil grandpa.
Well, that's good.
I'm glad to see smiles on your
faces at the end of all this.
We can do it.
We've been through a lot
of other worse stuff.
There's a light at the end
of the tunnel.
Karen and Don have a lot
of work ahead of them,
but if they contact a medium
to remove the shadow people
and the murder victim,
and a priest
to set up a boundary
banishing the priest-demon,
they can free themselves of evil
and lead a peaceful life.