This man is insane.
He's a predator.
He should have gone to hell.
- It really freaked me out.
- I just want it gone.
I see a war.
What a horrible way to go.
You're my last hope.
He likes them young.
He needs to get the hell
out of my house.
They're absorbing
way too much dead energy.
This is not a good situation.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's death here.
Don't wanna go down there.
I see dead people.
They hide in the walls
and they watch.
I speak to dead people...
She's definitely
a serial killer.
...and they speak to me.
She's going to torture them.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
They were all murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
So is this the only time
you've been physically attacked?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
There's no question in my mind
that he was talking about Satan.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who do you think
possessed you?
But Steve and I
never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
Well, you're not gonna want
to see this.
When we uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
Hell, no.
Or time to get out.
Everyone is in jeopardy.
I'm in the small town
of Briceville, Tennessee.
It's about a half-hour north
of Knoxville.
I got a call from
a single mom named Leonora.
Now, this poor woman
scrimped and saved to buy
a dream house
for her three kids.
Now here's the problem --
they're all being pushed,
scratched,
and basically scared to death.
She says if we can't help,
someone is going to
wind up badly hurt.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area
of any leading information.
This home has a lot
of photographs
and religious symbols,
so it's important that I cover
or remove them all.
When I'm done, the location will
be ready for tonight's walk.
Boy.
I'm just hearing, like,
"Don't come down here."
It's an older male.
He doesn't want living
or dead out here.
He's saying, "Mine. Mine.
Mine. Mine. It's all mine."
How would he affect
the living?
I think, with him, it would be
impressing upon them emotions
of fear and urgency to get out.
This man is completely,
utterly insane.
So, Leonora, you sounded
terrified on the phone.
What are you guys
going through?
I feel like something
is evil here.
It's attacking my family.
It's targeting my kids.
I don't know what to do
to protect them.
How long have you guys
been living here?
I've been here
a little over a year.
Do you know anything
about the history
of the house
or the property?
I was told by a neighbor
that the previous owners
had passed away.
- In the house?
- Yes.
That's something
I'll look into.
Who exactly
lives in the house?
I have a photo.
This is my 14-year-old son,
William.
This is me, my 20-year-old
daughter, Amber.
This is my 4-year-old son,
Easton.
I adopted him to make sure
he had a safe place to go,
and I do not feel like
he has a safe place here.
Easton is being targeted.
He sees things that
we can't explain.
It's getting
very physical with him.
That's got to be hard
on you as a mom.
It's a little
heartbreaking for me.
Do me a favor.
Give me a list of what's
going on as far as activity.
We have everything.
There's been footsteps,
feeling watched, items moving,
shadow figures,
constant nausea,
and physical attacks.
I've got to ask you
a question.
Why don't you just
pick up and leave?
Moving is not an option.
I've poured every bit
of life savings in this home.
What are you hoping to get
out of this investigation?
My family to be safe and go back
to the way it used to be
before we were being
assaulted.
The kids are afraid,
so that breaks my heart.
What do you think is in
this house? What's it want?
I believe it wants to tear
our family apart,
and I believe that it wants us
out of the house.
There's something wrong.
The old dead guy,
he particularly
likes to bother children.
He does call them rug rats,
and he says they are like rats.
They're pests.
And he's very grumpy.
He's very angry.
He will get into...rages.
When he's in a...mood,
he stomps, like...
The whole house will shake.
The living, with him,
would definitely hear
stomping all throughout
the house.
Okay, Leonora, what's going on
in this hallway?
Footsteps coming up and down
the hallway almost nightly.
All right.
So when you hear these steps,
what's it sound like?
I would say it sounds
like a heavier man
stomping down the hallway.
You sure it's nobody that got up
in the middle of the night?
No, because I've got up and
checked, and nothing is there.
Okay. What else?
When I'm laying in
my bedroom at night,
I see a very tall
dark figure of a man
moving up
and down the hallway.
What makes you say
it's a man?
Just the way it's built.
It's really tall.
It's a lot taller
than anybody in the house.
So could it be somebody
on the outside
walking back and forth?
- No.
I keep the blinds shut
all the time.
All right. Anything else?
In the living room, a flashlight
flew off of the coffee table.
Gave me chills.
Couldn't it have just
rolled off?
It is completely square.
There's no way it can roll off.
The scary part is
if it could do that,
it could have
flung it at your head.
Who's to say they won't
pick it up and throw it
at Easton,
being so young?
You know, it could kill him.
This old man,
I'm trying to get out of him
all the...that he does
to the living.
Do they see him?
I think they do see him
when he's pitching a fit.
Why do you get mad?
I'm seeing him getting mad
and throwing things
around violently.
He's showing me plates flying.
He says,
"This is my spectacular."
He says, "That scares them."
He likes that.
It scares them.
So, Leonora, obviously,
this is your bedroom. Right.
And this is where your
youngest sleeps with you?
Yes.
Have you ever seen him
have an experience?
He's been
physically attacked.
I've seen him being shoved
really hard in the back.
- You sure he didn't trip?
- His neck and back,
it looked like somebody
had physically shoved him.
Did he tell you
who shoved him?
He just said,
"The big man."
Was that the only time
you've see him get attacked?
No. I have a photo.
He has woken up
with bruises.
It sounds like
he's getting the brunt
of a lot
of this physical stuff.
Now what about you?
What's going on with you?
I'm getting a feeling of being
very sick to my stomach
all of a sudden and the life
being sucked out of me.
I feel drained,
just nauseous.
Now, is that only in this
room you feel this way?
Mostly in here.
It just hits me.
It's pretty bad.
If you walk outside,
does it stop?
Yes. It does go away.
Have you been to the doctor?
- I go for normal checkups.
- Right.
They can't find anything
that would cause that.
Okay. Anything else?
My TV comes on by itself.
The TV will just
pop on or pop off.
Okay. Have you had
the electric checked?
I have.
You really got a lot
going on here.
You did a real incredible
thing saving this kid,
and then you sacrificed
everything to buy a home
so everybody could have
a good place to live,
and it backfired on you.
Nothing feels safe.
You're my last hope.
It sounds like it.
I'm getting all kinds
of crazy in here.
It's this damn old man.
He likes this room a lot.
He looks better.
I think he's reverting
to a stage before he got sick.
I think he thinks
this is his room.
How would he affect
the living?
He likes to jump on the bed.
You know, he likes to watch
the television,
so I think, for the living,
the TV would come on
and off by itself.
This room is just filled with
a dead person's energy,
and I think it's making
the person sick and throwing up.
And for a living person to be
exposed to that for a long time,
they're absorbing
way too much dead energy.
It would be extremely
detrimental.
They're dying.
So, Will,
Mom said you're 14.
Yep.
Did you ever experience
anything you can't explain?
Sometimes, like, I'll get
this uncertain feeling in here
like there's just constantly
somebody just stalking me,
just always watching me.
You feel like it's a man
or a thing?
I haven't really
put a label on it.
Okay. Anything else?
Yeah. I was sitting
in front of the TV,
and it looked like somebody kept
on popping around the corner.
Can you describe him for me?
I mean, it was like a black
figure kept on looking at me.
How did you react
when you saw this thing?
It really freaked me out.
I mean, I know I wasn't
just seeing things.
I knew it was there.
What do you think
this thing wants?
I think they're just somebody
just trying to pick
on the family, really,
just trying to tell us,
basically, "Get out."
This feels horrible in here!
God, I feel so sick. Okay.
Constant nausea.
The person in here has abilities
without a doubt,
probably mediumship,
I'm thinking.
I see a war between whoever
is in here and the old man.
The old man is sitting
by the bed,
whispering into their ear --
disrespectful, lazy, stupid --
everything this old man disliked
of anybody when he was alive.
He thinks that this person
is a waste of space.
I feel like he is
physically doing things,
flicking their ear
and their head...
...smacking 'em, pushing.
What would the long-term effects
be for this living person?
Giving them horrible nightmares,
anxiety issues,
post-traumatic stress syndrome.
The dead guys just
wants them the...out.
So, Amber, I was
talking to your mom.
She thinks that
whatever is here
is going after you
and your brothers.
- You agree with her?
-100%.
I'm terrified for my family.
Okay.
So tell me about
some of the experiences.
I was looking in the mirror
in my bathroom,
and out of the corner
of my eye,
I saw something zoom
past down the hallway.
And what was it?
It was a dark,
shadowy figure.
So I know you saw it quick,
but can you get a sense
if it was an adult
or a kid?
I'm thinking it was adult.
I think it was male
because it was kind of taller.
And you're sure it wasn't
coming from somebody else?
No, everybody was asleep.
Anything else?
I feel someone watching me
or being around me
all the time.
Okay. So is the presence
like a peeping Tom,
or is it, like,
somebody trying to hurt you?
It's kind of just like
somebody is, like,
staring at me all the time.
It's, like, stalking,
and it just watches me.
It doesn't matter where
I'm at in the house.
It's always, like,
right there.
And it's only
when you're here?
- Mnh-mnh.
- Okay.
I went to work the other day
in Knoxville,
and it followed me there.
It was the same presence
as it is at the house.
- Okay. Anything else?
- I have nightmares.
Can you describe 'em?
One in particular that I had,
all the doors were rattling,
and when I woke up,
I was telling it
to get out of the house.
What were you
telling to get out?
I don't know. It was
something very mean, though.
I woke up shaking.
Anything else?
I was laying in bed, and I had,
like, my hand up like this,
and something just
touched my elbow.
So what kind of touch? Did it
feel like a man's finger?
Yeah.
You ever get touched
like that again?
Actually, about a month ago,
I got scratched.
I felt a burning sensation
on the back of my calf,
and when I had looked, it was
a whole bunch of scratches,
and I have a photo.
And what do you think
is in this house?
Something very mean,
um, and it's trying to hurt
my family.
- Here, sweetie.
- Thanks.
I just want it gone.
There's another dead guy here
who claims to be a cowboy.
He's a predator.
I think that he's a sick...
I'm seeing him with this girl.
I don't know if this is
this girl or some girl
he had when he was alive,
but she is uncomfortable
and is not happy now,
knowing that this is not right.
Is he able to physically
interact with the living?
I think so, yes.
There is a molestation there.
So this person here,
I would assume,
would have horrible nightmares,
screaming, scared, seeing a man.
I'm worried. I'm just worried.
I feel sick again.
Leonora told me a previous
owner died in her house.
Now the local police
aren't cooperating,
so I had a P.I.
look into it for me.
He just called back
and says it's true.
I'm on my way to meet him now to
find out exactly what happened.
Eddie, thanks for meeting me.
I appreciate that.
What were you able
to find out about
the previous owners
of my client's property?
Kenneth and Patricia Goodykoontz
was a married couple.
They bought your client's
residence in 1964.
This is a picture of Kenneth.
- He was retired Air Force.
- Okay.
And he worked as
a local machinist.
All right. So what do
we know about Patricia?
She worked at a local
manufacturing company.
On the phone, you said they
lived there for over 40 years.
Was their time there
good, bad?
Well, there was
some hardships there.
Kenneth lost his mother,
his father,
lost his sister,
lost his brother.
This guy practically
lost his whole family.
So how does Kenneth
wind up dying?
He was diagnosed with cancer.
Well, he finally dies
in May 2006,
right there on
your client's property.
So how old was he
when he died?
- He was 74 years old.
- Okay.
So what about Patricia?
Does she stay in the house?
Yes, and she also
died there as well.
All right. So what were
the circumstances of her death?
Well, August 18, 2015,
the family hadn't heard
from her,
so they sent the local sheriff
out for a welfare check.
What's he find?
He found Patricia's dead body
laying on the living room floor.
- Okay.
- Here's the incident report.
Okay. All right.
So she was 77.
What was the official
cause of death?
Unfortunately,
the coroner's office
never revealed
a reason of death.
He's blocking me on this.
I'm trying to figure out who
this angry, old man was in life.
Can you describe him?
He's, like, 5'5", rail thin.
He's white. He's bald.
I think he had
a really hard life.
I'm seeing him from two
different stages of his life.
When he's looking healthier,
I feel the 1980s.
I would say that he was in his
late 40s, early 50s then.
I think he was in his late 70s
when he's dying or dead.
He looks extremely ill.
Does he have any kind of
connection to the property?
He probably owned it, I guess.
I think he died here
or, like, was dying here.
I'm thinking that he probably
died from cancer.
There was a whole --
another person talking.
It's a dead chick.
It seems like it was some kind
of housewife or some...
The chick was crying
and screaming over it.
That is not good.
So far, I've got
a family being terrorized
by physical attacks
on a property
where the previous owners
died in the house,
but I want to see
if there's anything else.
Searching through old records,
I find an article about a man
name Richard Drummond.
Turns out Richard was hanged
by an angry mob in the 1890s
less than a mile
from my client's property.
I need to know more about this
hanging near Leonora's house.
Heading over to meet
with an historian
who says the whole thing started
with a fight at a brothel.
Well, Stephanie,
thanks for meeting with me.
I appreciate that.
Now this guy,
Richard Drummond,
I know he got hung pretty close
to my client's property.
What were the circumstances?
In 1893, there was the fight
that broke out
in a local brothel
here in Briceville.
All right. So do we know what
started this whole fight?
Some of the soldiers came by
from the nearby Fort Anderson
to enjoy the company of
some ladies at the brothel.
They must have upset somebody
because the local sheriff
was called in to kick them out,
and one of the miners,
named Richard Drummond,
stepped up
to help the sheriff.
And I actually have
a picture of him.
Drummond is helping the sheriff.
What happens next?
Richard Drummond
and the sheriff
were trying to get
the militia out.
In the melee that happened,
Richard Drummond shot and killed
a private named
William Laugherty.
- Does the sheriff arrest him?
- No, he didn't.
Okay. So now Drummond is free.
What happens next?
Well, 2 days later, 16 of
William Laugherty's friends
from the fort
rounded up Richard Drummond
and hung him from the bridge.
- All right.
And how far was that bridge
from my client's house?
About 4,000 feet
from your client's property.
Okay. So his buddies
came back for revenge.
Yes, they did.
As a matter of fact,
Richard Drummond is buried
in an unmarked grave
in this cemetery.
- Right here?
- Yes.
Okay. So did they wind up
arresting the soldiers?
Yes, they did, but in
the middle of the trial,
they dropped the charges.
- Any reason why?
Well, it seems that the military
at the state level
had enough clout to stop
the trial mid-trial.
Nobody goes to jail
for any of this?
No.
I'm seeing that
creepy cowboy guy again.
He's all, like, dressed up.
His outfit looks like
he just went to, like,
a cowboy nightclub
or something.
Any idea when this is?
He was saying that
he was around here
in the 1850s.
I'm skeptical about his claim
to have been
from that time period.
This guy comes and goes.
He comes from somewhere else,
like a bar.
He used to go there.
I think that's where he died.
He's saying that somebody
shot his head off.
There's something sexual
with him,
and he likes them young,
if you know what I mean.
He goes out hunting,
just like any pedophile.
Back in his day,
it wasn't a big deal, though.
That wasn't a thing
that he was persecuted for.
He got shot.
He...deserved it.
For more information
about the show
and if you need us
to investigate
unexplained activity
in your home...
Please visit
travelchannel.com/thedeadfiles.
Click on "Help Me Dead Files!"
to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
You know, another thing
caught my eye in research.
There used to be a coal mine
right near my client's house.
Now, in 1911, there was
a massive explosion there.
I'm on my way to meet with
a local historian who says
it was one of the deadliest
coal-mining accidents
in U.S. history.
So, Boomer, this explosion
I came across,
it looks like it happened pretty
close to my client's property.
What can you tell me
about it?
The entrance of
the Cross Mountain mine
was an adjacent ridge
about a mile
from where your property
your investigating is.
Okay.
...mile and miles of them.
It's very possible that some
of them might have gone
right underneath the property
your investigating.
So, Boomer, do me a favor.
Take me through the day
of the accident.
What happened?
December 9, 1911,
early in the morning, 7:20 a.m.,
the first shift of 89 miners
went into the depths
of the mine,
and shortly after
they entered the mine,
there was a violent explosion.
I mean, how massive was it?
It was massive enough
to be felt, you know,
miles away in all directions
and, you know, shook
the mountainside basically.
Big smoke cloud, you know,
boiled out of
the entrance of the mine
probably 100 feet in the air.
And people came
from all over
the adjacent mining camps,
trying to help.
For the most part,
they were unsuccessful.
You know, here's a photograph
shows a lot of the rescue teams
that had been gathered
around the front of the mine
to see what
they could do to help.
Wow. Everybody came together
during this explosion?
Yeah, during disasters
like that,
miners will come
from the other mines,
you know, the competing mines
to help their brother miners,
any help they could.
All right. Boomer,
so 89 men go down there.
How many get out?
They were able
to rescue five men.
Some of the tunnels
partially collapsed.
...anybody that wasn't killed
by the explosion
suffocated to death.
5 guys are alive,
84 dead.
Any of those bodies
get recovered?
It took 9 days to get everybody
out of the mountain,
but they were able to get
all the victims out.
Some were burnt
beyond recognition,
but the last two that were found
had barricaded
themselves off and hoped,
but the rescue never came.
They were too far back
in the mountain.
They couldn't
get to them in time.
Jeez.
What a horrible way to go.
So I'm getting a lot
of death.
There's bodies on the floor,
all together
and buried in a hole together.
I don't know what that's about.
And there seem to be
a lot of stairs.
Everything's a slick,
solid black
that had something to do
with this location.
I'm looking down,
and it turns into soot
and then, like, charcoal.
This is really not good.
I saw several disturbing things
on my walk, but two stood out.
First, the angry old man.
He was probably
in his 40s.
He was balding,
and he kind of had
big round eyes,
heavy lids.
Next, I described
the creepy cowboy
tormenting a living girl.
She is laying.
There's a male in the room.
Well, he is placing his hand
between the girl's legs.
Is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients
for the first time.
So, Amy, I'd like you
to meet Leonora.
This is her daughter, Amber.
Leonora is about as dedicated
a mom as I've ever seen.
She bought this house
so her three kids
could have a better life.
I actually have a photo of
the rest of the family
right here.
This is her son, Will, who's 14,
and her son, Easton, who's 4.
Leonora adopted Easton to save
him from a bad living situation,
but with all the activity here,
he's not really
in a safer place.
As a matter of fact, nobody is.
With that being said,
I'm gonna ask Amy to,
talk about her walk for us.
There are a couple dead people
here that I am concerned about.
The first one is an extremely
angry, elderly male.
For whatever reason, his
favorite location in the house
is back bedroom
to the left.
Now the bedroom you're talking
about is Leonora's bedroom,
and that's where
she sleeps with Easton.
Interesting.
One of the things that
really stood out about him
was his distaste
for children.
He referred to them
as "the pests,"
and he takes
a lot of pleasure
in torturing kids.
Tell her how Easton got shoved
and wakes up with the bruises.
I have pictures of bruises
from his rib cage down
that wasn't there
the day before,
and then I watched him walk,
and it looked like
somebody shoved him
really hard from the back.
Okay. Interesting.
Some of the other things
I saw him doing to the living
was him, like,
stomping on the floors
and making
as much noise as possible.
When he's really upset,
he'll throw things.
Describe what happened
with the flashlight to Amy.
It was a square flashlight.
It was sitting on a table,
and it flew off of the table.
Was anybody else
in the room at the time?
My son was asleep.
- Which son?
- William.
Interesting.
I felt like the living
would be able to see him
because he wants you to.
So he would go in
the hallway,
and he would stand
at the end of the hall
and wait for somebody
to come out of their room.
Both of you guys have seen
dark figures in the hallway.
Yes.
I was standing in the bathroom,
facing the mirror,
and I just caught out
of the corner of my eye,
there was a tall, dark
shadow figure moving very fast.
Now, you see it a lot
from your bedroom?
I do.
Yeah, it's very scary.
Also, I saw him really
screwing around a lot
with the television, like,
flipping through channels,
stations changing, the TV
turning on and off by itself.
Tell her what happens
to your TV in your room.
It will come on and off.
He has really put his energy
in that room.
It's dead energy.
It would make you feel
exhausted,
make you sick and nauseous.
It'll just hit me
all of a sudden,
um, come out of nowhere
and, um, just hit me
pretty hard.
And what that does
to a living person
absorbing dead energy
is it's gonna start
slowly killing you.
When I was in
the middle bedroom,
he basically told me
that he has declared war
on the person in that room.
Yeah, that's Will's room.
We all know that room
is the bad room.
He absolutely
just can't stand him.
He specifically said,
"I have hated him
since he first came here."
I saw him flicking his ear,
smacking him in the head.
I saw him try to give this
living person nightmares,
basically him
just being relentless.
To make things worse,
the living person has abilities,
and he is a medium
of some sort,
but it makes him much more
vulnerable to these attacks.
If he's exposed to this
for a long period of time,
he can develop PTSD,
anxiety issues,
depression issues, all of
these kinds of things.
And what the old man
really wants to do
is just get him
out of here.
He said that
he had saw a face.
Like, he wasn't exactly
completely asleep,
and he felt something
was there,
so he had opened his eyes
and saw a face.
Okay. Interesting.
It's very scary
just to think
that this guy hates him
that bad.
Any idea who this guy was
when he was alive?
What I got was that he possibly
owned this place,
that he lived here.
I got the impression that
he had a really hard life.
There were two ages
that I got him at.
When he was elderly,
he was frail and thin,
and then I saw him
in the back bedroom,
and he looked
a lot healthier.
I would say
he was in his 50s.
I got that when he was healthier
was in the '80s, the 1980s,
and I felt like
he died in the house
from either cancer
or kidney issues or both.
I got a pretty good idea of
who the guy is that you saw.
Now the previous owners
of your house
were a couple named Kenneth
and Patricia Goodykoontz.
They bought this place
back in 1964
and lived here
for over 50 years.
You said this guy hates kids.
I can't say for sure
that this guy, Kenneth,
didn't like kids,
but they didn't have any.
You said he had a hard life.
Now he had
a pretty tough time here.
While living in this house,
he lost both his parents.
His sister and his brother died.
You said the guy you saw was
in his 50s during the 1980s.
Kenneth turned 50 in 1982.
In 2006, Kenneth was diagnosed
with cancer at the age of 74.
He died in this house
in May of 2006.
Matter of fact,
his wife, Patricia,
also died in this house
9 years later in 2015.
Wow.
I got a photo of Kenneth
when he was younger.
Is it possible this is
the guy you saw?
I did have a sketch done.
Yeah. This is him.
You guys tell me.
It's very close, yeah.
You think this is the guy
you saw?
Yeah.
This is the...that
hit your kid.
To be so mean to a child,
I can't comprehend it.
He needs to get the hell
out of my house.
So the other person that
I'm worried about is a male.
He's dressed like a cowboy,
but this guy was perfect,
clean-shaven.
I was like,
"That is weird."
And I got that
he was around here
in the 1840s, in the 1850s.
I think that he came
from somewhere else,
like a bar or a saloon,
and I think he died there
and that he was shot
in the head.
I really feel that
he deserved that
and that he should have
gone to hell.
Amy, I gotta tell you,
a few things you talked about
make me think of a guy
I came across in my research.
Back in 1893, there was a man
who was shot and killed
at a brothel right down the hill
here in Briceville.
Now, his name
was William Laugherty,
and he was 33 years old.
Laugherty was a soldier
that was stationed
at Fort Anderson near here.
That might explain
the strange outfit you saw.
One night, Laugherty
and his military friends
were partying
at the brothel in town,
trying to pick up women.
He and his buddies
pissed somebody off,
and they had to call
the sheriff in to kick him out.
The sheriff had a hard time
trying to get him out,
so a local miner jumped in,
and things got worse.
The miner shot
and killed Laugherty.
The sheriff let the miner go,
but 2 days later,
Laugherty's soldier buddies
came back and they lynched him.
What?
This is the article on it.
Now could Laugherty, the guy
who got shot in the bar,
be the man you might have seen?
Yes.
Now you said you were concerned
about this guy.
What's his story?
I got that he is
an extremely sick individual
who prefers young females.
He was an extremely
sexual person,
and I am pretty certain that
he's some kind of a pedophile.
You might have the feeling of
intense fear when he's around.
He's a very dark,
bad person.
He also likes
to influence people
through very vivid nightmares
and night terrors.
All of the things he's doing
to living individuals
is because he's a hunter
and he's on the prowl always.
Amy, Amber's going through
a lot of the things you're
talking about.
Really?
Well, talk about
the nightmares.
I had one nightmare where I was
telling something
to get out of the house,
and I had woke up actually
saying, "Get out of my house."
Now you said this guy
is like a predator, right?
- Yeah.
- Now didn't you tell me
you felt like somebody
in your room was stalking you?
Always, at night, yeah.
He's, like, in the corner,
watching me.
I don't like it at all.
It scares me a lot.
Did this guy
do anything else?
The biggest thing that I got
is that he can
physically touch the living.
Amber has been touched.
She's been scratched.
You know what? Tell Amy.
I felt something behind me.
I felt a burning sensation.
I looked, and there were
a whole bunch of scratches.
Okay.
Also, I saw a disturbing
situation in the back bedroom.
I had a sketch done of what
I saw going on back there.
Jeez.
I'm sorry, ladies. It's...
He's touching my baby.
Could --
could he have touched me
like that without me knowing?
'Cause I don't wanna
be touched like that.
So he's probably the one that
follows me around all the time?
Yeah. Yeah.
Easton has talked about a man
in a white cowboy hat.
He has called him
the Big Guy.
That's not good.
And, like, when you were
talking to me, and you're like,
"Well, he's got bruises and this
and this," and I'm like,
"I know the old man
is not doing that to him."
It's this sick jerk.
I knew some things were going on
with Easton, but I had no idea.
If this monster is going to
terrorize any of my kids,
I feel very guilty.
You okay, sweetie?
I just... I don't
want that to happen to him ever.
So, Leonora, you were worried
your children
were in danger here,
and you are 100% right.
But we still haven't answered
the big question --
Can you stay here safely
with the kids,
or do you need to pack them up
and get the hell out of here?
Now for that answer, I'm gonna
turn it over to Amy.
There's a lot
you have to do.
The first thing is to bring in
a medium to sit down
and have a very clear discussion
with this elderly man.
They need to go over the fact
that he's deceased.
It's time for him
to move on.
Okay, so now once
the old guy is gone,
is Will gonna stop
getting messed with?
Yes. All that stuff's
gonna stop.
Okay. Now the cowboy.
Obviously, this guy is
just a piece of...
that needs to go, period.
You need to bring in
a male and a female medium
and a demonologist.
Tell the mediums that
it's gonna be a rough one.
He might get physical
with them,
and that's why you have
the demonologist there.
So the demonologist can
step in if this pervert tries
to get rough
with the mediums?
Absolutely.
So it's kind of like,
okay, you know,
"We're going to try
and do this the nice way.
You get pissy, and we got
our big gun here."
Basically, they do
a type of exorcism.
Both of your sons
have abilities.
Will is going to
naturally close down,
but Easton won't, so the last
thing I want you to do
is he needs to see
a child psychotherapist.
He's going to have
experiences,
and it's better to go
through those experiences
with someone that he can
talk to and who can help him.
He needs to learn as many
protection measures
as he possibly can,
and that'll help him
to prevent PTSD,
anxiety, depression,
all of these things.
So when you adopted Easton,
you adopted a lot more
than you thought.
I'd do it again.
Well, you might have saved
this kid's future
by finding out this stuff now.
- Yeah.
I know it's a lot, but you're
gonna take Amy's advice?
Most definitely.
Knowing what to do
to protect us now
and protect Easton
and even Will...
Right.
...they will be a lot better
overall after all this is done.
And I feel like
we have a path now,
a way that we can
make things better
and that I know we can
help Easton in life,
and we will take this journey
right along with him.
It's a lot of work.
- It's worth it.
- Yeah.
He needs to be protected.
I really hope Leonora
and Amber contact a demonologist
and mediums
to remove the old man
and the cowboy
terrorizing their family.
If they do that and get Easton
the help he needs,
they can free their family
of evil
and lead a peaceful life.