He is pissed,
and he does not want us
to go back here.
He was doing some sort
of witchcraft.
Witchcraft is done,
so it's almost like a curse.
Somebody is on top of me,
choking me.
They felt somebody.
I want to leave.
I just want to move.
I'm panicking.
I want to get out of here.
This is not a good situation.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's death here.
Don't wanna go down there.
I see dead people.
They hide in the walls
and they watch.
I speak to dead people...
She's definitely
a serial killer.
...and they speak to me.
She is going to torture them.
But there's only one way
to know if my findings are real.
They were all murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
So is this the only time
you're been physically attacked?
I know every person,
every house has secrets.
There is no question in my mind
that he was talking about Satan.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who do you think
possessed you?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
Well, you're not gonna want
to see this.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Hell, no.
Or time to get out.
Everyone is in jeopardy.
I'm in Murrieta, California.
It's about an hour and a half
in from L.A.
I got a call from a woman
named Lina. Sounds real bad.
She's convinced
whatever's in the house
is going after her husband
and her 15-year-old daughter.
Now, this is a woman
who is religious,
doesn't like to mess around
with the paranormal,
but she's so desperate,
she called us in.
I really hope we can
help her out.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area
of any leading information.
This home has
a lot of photographs
and religious symbols,
so it's important that I cover
or remove them all.
When I'm done, the location will
be ready for tonight's walk.
There's so much noise out here.
It's...like, ridiculous.
I don't like it.
It's making me feel
extremely uncomfortable.
I'm panicking.
I don't like this.
I want to run.
I want to get out of here.
This is very bad.
So, Lina,
I'm glad I'm here.
I mean, you sounded really upset
on the phone when we spoke.
Now, what do you think
is here?
I think it's something evil.
Whatever it is,
I think it's something
that is just wanting
to harm my family.
How long have you guys
lived here?
We've been for 11 years.
Now, have you had activity
since the beginning?
We only started having activity
about the last 31/2, 4 years.
You have any theories
as to why?
My husband, we had
an acquaintance
that was dealing with
some occult things,
and my husband
brought something home.
Help me out here.
What exactly do you think
this guy was involved with?
All I know is that
he told my husband
that he was doing
some sort of witchcraft
to become more popular.
Almost like
a deal with the devil.
Yes.
Was your husband involved
in this stuff?
No, but he is
very sensitive.
Okay. So, Lina, who exactly
lives in the house?
- This is my family.
- Okay.
That's my husband, Sal.
my son, Allan, who's 21,
myself,
my daughter, Mei,
who is 20,
and Emily is 15.
All right.
Lina, do me a favor.
Give me an overview of what
you guys are going through.
We've got noises.
We've got things
moving on their own.
We've got physical attacks,
nightmares,
and personality changes.
All right.
Personality changes -- what
are you talking about here?
Mostly in my youngest
daughter and my husband.
Let's start with Sal.
What kind of personality changes
are we talking about?
He'll change from being
normal and happy
to being completely depressed
for no reason.
All right. Now, was he
ever like this before?
- No.
- Okay.
So your daughter Emily,
how has she changed?
With her, it's very severe
anxiety and depression.
She doesn't leave
the house anymore.
It's very hard on her
and myself as well.
How you holding up?
I'm exhausted all the time,
lethargic.
I mean, you break my heart
when I listen to you.
And you have nobody
to turn to?
No. You know, this is
my last resort,
and I want to have my family
whole, back together again.
Okay.
There's these things.
They look like little lizard
gremlin things.
They're running around
and they're, like,
doing this weird...
pitched laughing giggle.
To me, what I'm thinking is that
they're little, like,
low, low, low level demons.
They create an atmosphere
of depression and lethargy.
I don't know why they're
attached to the living here,
but they are.
They just make it impossible
to get anywhere in your life.
It's almost like
they're sent, though.
There might be something behind
that where witchcraft is done,
and so it's almost like a curse.
So, Lina,
what's going on in here?
We've had several
experiences around here.
One of them was
the door here
slammed by itself
very aggressively.
All right. So how hard are
we talking about?
- I mean, did it...
- Very hard.
- Like that?
- Yes, if not harder.
Okay. So you didn't have any
of the windows in here open?
- No.
- All right. Anything else?
I saw a very tall, dark figure
running through our house
from the hallway
into the kitchen
and with very,
very heavy footsteps.
How tall do you think
this thing was?
About 7 to 8 feet tall.
Are you sure it couldn't have
been anything from outside?
No.
So, Lina, obviously,
you cannot go on like this,
you or your family.
I need help, and I want...
It's okay.
You want your family back.
I want them
to be healthy again...
- Okay.
- ...and back to normal.
You've put a lot
on your shoulders.
Hopefully, we'll have tears
of joy when we're done, okay?
I hope so.
Not good. Really not good.
I just saw a body
in the ground here.
I believe that this is...
a female.
There's something with her,
an illness,
and I think that is affecting
the living here.
Do you know how it's
affecting the living?
Sudden onset of nausea,
being extremely drained.
They feel exhausted
all the time
and also, like, this anxiety.
Fear.
She does not like the person
in this room at all.
At all.
Why?
Basically, she's calling
this person a beast.
So, Sal, I was talking
to your wife, Lina,
and she's worried about
your youngest, Emily.
Yeah, she's not doing well.
It's the worst pain, that real
pain in my heart, you know?
Lina, she said that your
personality has changed.
I mean,
you agree with that?
Yes.
I get angry really fast.
I wasn't like that before.
And then anxiety
and then depression,
and it's getting worse.
Sometimes I just cry.
You're going through
a lot, Sal.
Yes.
So, Sal,
I was talking to Lina,
and she has a theory
that about 4 years ago,
you were talking to some guy
that was practicing
some kind of
weird witchcraft.-
And that whatever
he was doing,
something might have
attached to you.
Do you agree with that?
Yeah, because I'm actually
open to that stuff somehow.
I don't know how.
So what about
experiences, Sal?
I have terrible nightmares.
Can you describe them
at all?
I feel like somebody, like,
is, like, on top of me
and won't let me move.
Have you ever been tested
for any kind of sleep disorder?
- No.
- Okay.
To me, it sounds
like sleep paralysis.
But what do you think it is?
I think he is a real devil.
The demon is, like,
on top of me.
He's grabbing me
and choking me.
- Okay.
- So I can die in the nightmare.
The dead girl wants to leave.
She wants out.
This living person is aware
that something paranormal
is trying to kill them.
I know that they felt, you know,
like somebody trying
to strangle them.
I don't think they know that
they're actually not dreaming,
so they are awake.
They're being strangled.
They're being smothered.
The dead girl, she's figuring
out how to...kill this person.
I was talking to Mom and Dad.
You're the oldest, right?
- Yeah.
- How old are you?
21 years old.
Do you have any concern about
dad and your younger sister?
Yeah, they have changed.
They feel so different
and distant.
Everybody seems to be having all
kinds of different experiences.
What about yourself?
I have really bad nightmares.
Now, your father
described nightmares.
Yeah.
Now, what kind of nightmares
are you having?
All of a sudden, something,
whether it be, like,
a person or anything,
it would just become, like,
a dark shadow
that'll eventually become,
like, a human-sized figure.
- But is it threatening to you?
- Yeah.
All right. So anything else?
When I'm sleeping, I'll feel
like something is shaking me,
and I'll wake up
in real life.
Okay. So you're sure
it's not a dream,
or do you think you're being
really physically shaken?
I'm being really
physically shaken,
and it'll feel like
a shake enough
to where
it will move me back.
What do you think
is going on?
I feel like whatever is
happening is kind of trying
to divide my family,
at least when it comes to my dad
and my youngest sister.
They're like two different
versions of people
that I used to know.
Okay.
I'm seeing, like,
this angry dead man, old,
and he is...pissed.
and he does not
want us to go back here.
He doesn't like living people.
He hates this...family.
They don't respect him.
They all deserve what they get.
Okay.
So I'm seeing kind of
a weird thing here.
So I'm seeing a person
laying in the bed.
It's a male, probably anywhere
from, like, 15 to 21.
The little old man
is on top of this male.
There is some sketchy...
going on here.
Seems like there is a lot
of things going on in the house.
Have you had any experiences?
Yeah, I always hear
running along the roof.
- Does it sound like an animal?
- No.
It sounds like a person
with really heavy shoes.
Okay. So anything else?
I have been felt like
I'm being watched all the time.
Where do you feel it?
Usually sleeping, and then
I'll randomly get up
and, like, look at
every corner of my room,
and I'll feel, like,
a really heavy stare on me.
But does it feel like somebody
that wants to do you harm?
Yeah.
This is the worst room.
It's interesting,
with the curtains.
Literally, like,
a doorway for the dead,
coming and going,
coming and going.
So this person, definitely
a medium, without a doubt.
They're getting bad,
crazy-ass dead people.
I do think that they would
cause this person
to feel overwhelmed and sad.
Your mom called us in, and she's
really concerned about you.
She thinks you've
changed emotionally.
- Yeah.
- Do you agree with that?
- Yes.
- What's going on?
I have anxiety and depression,
and, like, ever since
the activity started,
I never want to leave
the house.
That's not really normal
for a 15-year-old.
- You know that, right?
- Yeah.
Is it affecting you
physically, too?
Yes, I am really drained
of my energy.
Sometimes I'll stand up
and I'll, like,
see black for, like, a minute.
If we can figure out a way
to fix whatever the hell
is going on here,
would you want to stay,
or do you still want to go?
I want to leave.
I just want to move away
from this property.
Okay. That's sad, honey.
One of the things that
I'm getting about this area,
and then specifically now,
this room,
is these tall beings,
that are ancient.
They were here before man,
and the dead were talking
about them coming from the sky,
and so that does make me
think that these are aliens.
I see them coming in
and abducting people
in this house.
How might they be affected
by that?
Irrational fears.
Most abductees have issues with
certain noises and frequencies,
sleep issues, nightmares.
And the harm it can do, I think,
to a person physically
and mentally
and emotionally
is pretty severe.
Sal is such a sweet
and sincere guy,
and I know he believes his
nightmares and sleep paralysis
come from the paranormal.
But I called a local doctor,
and he says it could just be
symptoms of sleep apnea.
So I had Sal do a home test.
He put on this contraption,
went to sleep wearing it,
and all the data was recorded.
Right now, I'm heading over
to meet that doctor
to go over these test results.
Well, Doctor, I appreciate
you meeting with me.
So my client is suffering from
nightmares and sleep paralysis.
Now you mentioned sleep apnea
could be the cause of this?
What are the other
symptoms of that?
It can cause insomnia,
fatigue,
mood swings and depression.
Okay. Now, would he feel like
he was being choked?
Sometimes people feel like
they're gasping.
They can't get enough air,
and they'll wake up...
feeling like they're choking.
If this goes on for a long
time, what could happen?
Typically, that's going
to be hypertension,
high blood pressure,
sometimes heart failure.
So, Doc, I know you normally
test people here at your office,
but my client slept with this
contraption at home last night.
So you had a chance
to look at the results?
- Yes.
- All right, Doc.
So what are we looking
at here?
So what we're looking at
is breathing pattern up here.
All right. So does this mean
he has sleep apnea?
It does not appear to be
sleep apnea at all.
So all the symptoms he's got
as far as nightmares,
the feeling of being choked,
depression,
all this other stuff, it's not
coming from any sleep disorder?
It doesn't seem like it's coming
from obstructive sleep apnea.
Okay.
I'm seeing
the dead girl again.
I don't think the living
can sleep while she's around.
I think that they're aware
enough that they know
that something really bad
actually is happening.
I think they're like,
"No," you know,
"that was just a dream,"
but they are fighting it.
They're fighting it.
Something weird's going on.
So I made my usual calls,
and this local historian
reached out to tell me
the Native Americans
got a raw deal in this city.
Listen, I hear that
pretty much everywhere we go,
but she says this is different.
There were two major incidents,
and one of them involved
the original owner
of Sal and Lina's property.
What can you tell me
about the Native Americans
that inhabited the land here?
'Cause I know we're close
to my clients' property.
Yeah, they were the Luise単os,
and they lived here
hundreds of years
before the Spanish settlers
came in the mid-1800s.
You mentioned on the phone
there were two incidents
involving
the Native Americans.
What's the first one?
Well, the first one is,
the Luise単os had some horses,
and there were Spanish settlers
called Californios
that came in
and stole their horses.
Okay.
The Luise単os took the law
into their own hands
and killed all 11
of the Californios,
along with
a 13-year-old boy.
- Over horses?
- Yes.
All right. So did
the Californios get any revenge?
Yeah.
They were furious.
So what they did is,
they set up an ambush,
and from that,
they massacred them all.
How many of these guys
did they kill?
About 38 to 40.
All right.
So that's a lot of bodies.
Did they just
leave them there?
This is why I brought you here,
because they had a mass grave,
and they buried them
somewhere over here.
- By the shopping mall?
- Yes.
All right. So did they
at least dig up the bodies,
or did they
just build over it?
They just built
right over it.
There are
a lot of dead people here,
just wandering the streets.
There were three
or four places of burial,
and I think that
all of these burial areas
were from different
time periods,
like, 1600s, 1700s.
These areas where bodies
were placed
that were just ignored
and built upon,
and so they're not at rest,
and they haven't
ever been at rest.
These dead people are
kind of pissed about it.
They're not happy.
All right, Yvette,
you mentioned on the phone
there was a second incident
that involved the original owner
of my clients' property.
- Who was this guy?
- His name was Juan Murrieta,
and they actually named
this town after him.
Okay.
He was born and raised
in Spain,
and he arrived here
in California in 1861.
Here is a picture of him
when he was in his early 30s,
and then here's another photo
when he was in his 80s.
All right. So what did he
wind up doing with the property?
He ended up raising sheep
on the property,
and he built this house
on the property.
Okay. So you said
there was an incident
with the Native Americans.
What happened?
Murrieta's sheep were getting
into the Luise単os lands
and eating up
the crops and whatnot,
and so they got into
an argument.
Okay.
So what did Murrieta do?
Well, Murrieta decided
to evict them,
and here is their decree
right here.
Okay. So he throws them off
the property?
How many?
- There were 200.
- What happened after that?
They were living in squalor
for at least 7 years,
and many of them
were starving and dying.
So this guy Murrieta
from the photo
looks like he lived
a long time.
Yes, he died in 1936
at the age of 91.
- He died a rich man.
- Guy's a real piece of work.
I'm seeing
the angry old man again.
Do you have any idea
who this person was in life?
He was not born
in California,
so I think he does speak
another language.
I think he did come from Mexico.
He was more than likely
pretty poor,
and then he either came into
money or made his own money,
and he's showing me animals
that he had or something.
He thinks it's his house.
"These people need to go.
This is my house.
Everybody stole it from me."
He's just going nuts.
He's crazy.
For more information
about the show,
and if you need us
to investigate
unexplained activity
in your home...
Please visit
travelchannel.com/TheDeadFiles.
Click on "Help me, Dead Files!"
to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
So far I have a family
living in the middle
of a paranormal war zone
on a property where
Native Americans were abused,
neglected, and killed.
But I want to see what else
happened here.
Searching through old records,
I find an article
about a young girl
who was brutally murdered
in 1996.
Turns out the homicide
took place less than a mile
from my clients' property.
All right, I called the cops
about this homicide,
but they said they don't want
to talk to me about it
because one of the suspects
is still on the loose.
So I'm meeting with a true crime
author who says this murder
was one of
the most savage crimes
in Murrieta's history.
So, Aleida, thanks for
helping me out with this case.
Before we get to
the homicide,
what do we know
about this victim?
Well, her name
was Sophia Briseno.
She was only 13 years old.
She lived only about
900 feet from the property
that you're investigating,
and she had a boyfriend that
she'd been secretly dating.
He was 17 years old.
His name was
Crispin Solorio Garcia.
All right.
So what happened?
Well, on February 12th of 1996,
Garcia calls Sophia,
and he asked her to meet him
at this local grocery store.
And so she meets him there,
and he is there with his
friend, Francisco Ochoa.
Okay.
Well, they all went
to a local cemetery,
which is a place that a lot
of the kids would party at.
And I actually have a picture
here of the cemetery.
- I mean, a cemetery, really?
- A cemetery.
So, Aleida, how far is this
cemetery from my clients' house?
It's only about 2,400 feet.
Okay. So they're there partying.
How'd it go bad?
Well, Sophia started
irritating Garcia.
He gets upset, and he
tells her to shut up.
"Just shut up,
or I'm gonna kill you."
At this point,
Sophia doesn't stop.
She keeps going, and, according
to the police, he tells Ochoa,
"Go to my truck
and get some screwdrivers."
Garcia takes a screwdriver
and he just starts
to viciously stab Sophia,
and as he's stabbing her,
he shouts at her,
"Do you believe me now...
that I'm gonna kill you?"
This dead girl is in
so much pain.
Did you get anymore
information on her life?
I know that she was young.
She had black hair.
There's something
with her jaw...
...with how she died. It hurts.
And then her back.
Okay. So this is
a pretty savage attack.
I mean, when all is said
and done, what was the damage?
Well, she was stabbed
64 times.
She was stabbed in the chest,
in her face, in her jaw,
in her neck,
in her head, in her back.
I mean, she was
just stabbed everywhere.
And I actually have
her death certificate here.
These guys are animals.
I mean, real savages.
- Absolutely.
- What do they do next?
Well, they just leave her body
there to rot, out in the open.
The day before Sophia's body
is actually found,
they flee to Mexico.
I know one guy was
apprehended. What happened?
So in 2007,
the FBI locates Garcia.
He's extradited
back to the United States
and then he stands trial
for her murder.
This is actually
his mug shot.
He is convicted
of first-degree murder
and sentenced
to 25 years to life.
He is incarcerated
in California.
And what about Ochoa?
Well, Ochoa has
never been caught.
He's still out there.
All I know
about this dead chick
is that she definitely
was murdered.
It was fairly recently.
When would you say then?
I would say
maybe the 1970s, 1980s,
could be even closer than that.
Was her body literally,
literally here?
She doesn't know.
So she died in the ground?
So she's showing me
she's in the ground, right?
Now she's looking at her body.
She's naked.
Her hair is all wet,
caked with mud, you know?
And she's looking at herself,
and then she's lifting up,
and she's in the house.
And that's the last
she remembers.
There is a lot of activity
in this house,
but one of the things
I'm really worried about
is the pathway of dead
in one of the bedrooms.
The dead that I saw,
they were translucent.
They did have, like,
little wispy arms.
And they were
all over the place.
Amy, is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients
for the first time
Well, Amy, you're looking across
at a family in crisis.
This is Sal.
This is his wife, Lina,
and their son, Allen.
They also have
two other daughters.
This is Mei, who is 20,
and this is Emily, who is 15.
Now everyone is having
experiences, but Sal and Emily
are getting the worst of it.
They brought us in to stop
whatever's here
before someone gets hurt,
and so they can go back to being
a loving and caring family.
So now that Amy knows
a little bit about you guys,
I'll ask her to describe
her walk for us.
When I got here,
I saw these little things.
They kind of looked like a cross
between a lizard and a gremlin.
There was about 12 of 'em.
They have little tails
and little horns.
What these things are,
are, like, low-level demons.
The things that they can
cause are, like,
feelings of depression,
feelings of being
completely overwhelmed.
They also can make you feel like
you're not succeeding in life.
Sal, why don't we start with you
and talk about the anxiety,
the negative thoughts,
the depression?
It's been, like, 4 years
since this happening to me.
That makes me really sad.
That's where I'm getting all
my anxiety and my depression.
The thing is, is that
these things are summoned.
I got that someone
practicing witchcraft
brought them here
as a curse.
Now, Lina, do me a favor.
I want to you to tell Amy what
you think, how this all started.
I suspect that Sal brought
something home with him
on one occasion.
He had an acquaintance
that was dealing
with some sort of
witchcraft.
He started having
nightmares that night,
woke up crying and just
hysterical that night,
and that's the point in time
where all of this started.
Now, is that what you think
may have caused all this?
Yeah.
So do you think this guy
put a curse on Sal?
Yeah.
I think that this
person got offended
that you were judging him.
I'm not surprised.
Sal, don't talk
to this other guy anymore.
- No.
- I will not.
'Cause that guy needs a beat.
All right, so what else?
The next thing that I saw was
this dead woman in that bedroom.
Okay. So that's
Sal and Lina's bedroom.
I got that she was, like,
keeping you awake at night,
not letting you
have peaceful sleep.
I think
she does cause nausea.
She also makes you feel
very tired.
She's extremely draining.
I feel the feeling of drain,
like you were explaining,
that I'm always exhausted.
I think that you've woken up
and been, like,
feeling like you're having
a heart attack.
Maybe you were trying
to just be like,
"No, these are
just nightmares,
and this isn't really
happening," and, you know,
but it really is happening.
Everything you're describing
is what Sal's going through.
Really?
Sal, do me a favor
and describe
the nightmares
that you're having.
When I was sleeping,
this man attacked me.
I feel him, that he is on top
of me, and then he's choking me,
and then he doesn't me--
to move at all.
I start crying.
It feels really horrible.
Now, when Sal told me
what he was going through,
I thought it might
have been sleep apnea,
so I called a local doctor,
who said that condition could
cause those kinds of symptoms,
including depression.
So I had Sal tested.
The results came back,
and everything was negative.
You don't have sleep apnea, Sal.
Unfortunately, there's gotta be
another explanation for it.
Any idea about this dead girl,
or who she was
or anything like that?
I got that
she was pretty young.
What I saw of her was that
she was kind of, like,
a little bit caked in mud,
and she was nude, and that
she had long dark hair.
Just, like, a lot of jaw pain,
and her back was
excruciating pain.
I know that she was
caught off guard.
She was definitely murdered.
I was getting, like, maybe it
happened in the '70s or '80s,
or she might have been born
in the '70s and '80s
'cause it could've happened
even more recently.
A few things you said remind me
of a pretty gruesome homicide
I came across.
Now the victim's name
was Sophia Briseno.
She lived in Murrieta,
about 900 feet from this house.
She was only 13.
She was secretly dating a boy
named Crispin Solorio Garcia.
This kid was 17,
and on February 12, 1996,
Garcia invited Sophia
to meet with him
at a market in Murrieta.
Now Garcia was also
with a friend
named Francisco Gonzalez Ochoa,
and then they headed
to that nearby cemetery.
At the time, it was a place
where teenagers would
hang out and party.
Sophia started to get
on Garcia's nerves.
Garcia told her to shut up,
and she started
making fun of him.
Next thing you know, Garcia got
ahold of a screwdriver
and began stabbing her.
Now you said the girl was
in pain in her jaw and her back.
Well, this bastard
stabbed her 64 times...
My goodness.
...all around her face,
her neck, her back.
Now he basically left her
in the cemetery to rot
because they didn't find her
for 6 days.
No.
The two of them
then took off for Mexico.
Garcia was finally caught
and extradited in 2007.
He's doing life now, and I got
a mug shot of this psycho.
This is Garcia right here.
Unfortunately, Ochoa is
still on the loose.
I feel horrible that
that happened to her,
but I can't forgive her for
what she's doing to my family.
I feel so much anger.
All right.
So what else do we have?
I encountered
an angry old man,
and I do believe
that he is a big problem.
He kept claiming that
this was his house,
and he wants to push the living
out so he can be alone.
I know he can
move objects around.
I felt like the living would
more than likely see him
as a type of shadow person.
We see this shadow thing
running from that living room,
straight through here,
back in through the kitchen,
toward the pantry.
I saw him often in
the middle bedroom, I think.
That's Allan's room.
I got that he was bothering
a young male
between 15 and 21 years
of age.
Allan's 21.
I saw the male
laying on the bed,
and I saw him
on top of that male,
and I did see
the young male, like,
freaking out and struggling
and trying to get away.
In the nightmares that I have,
I'll feel like I'm being
moved in the dream,
only to find that I'm being
waken up or shaken in real life.
So him feeling like somebody
is actually shaking him
is actually happening?
- Yes.
Who was he?
Do you have any idea?
I got that
he was in his 70s.
He was not born
in the U.S.
I believe he was Mexican,
but I wasn't sure.
I got that initially
he was very poor
and that he either
came into money
or he made his own money,
and he's pissed off
because he felt like
everybody stole from him.
I know that he had quite a few
animals when he was alive,
but now he thinks
that he owns this house
because he owned the land.
But things are confusing
'cause they're not exactly
how they used to be.
I think I know who
you're talking about.
His name was Juan Murrieta.
You know, they named
the town after this guy.
Juan was born and raised in
Spain, but he came here in 1861,
and he bought this property
in 1873.
He lived here, but obviously
in a different structure.
I actually have a photo
of his house.
He came from a pretty modest
background, this guy,
but he ended up
making a lot of money
and he died pretty wealthy.
This guy was
a real piece of work.
After he bought the land,
he put sheep on here
and had them grazing.
Back then, the Native American
tribe lived in the area, too,
and they were called
the Luise単o.
So now he would let the sheep
run rampant all over their land
and eat their crops, so they
weren't too happy about it.
They got into it with Murrieta.
In 1875, Murrieta retaliated
by getting 200
of the Native Americans
kicked off the land.
Meanwhile, Murrieta did
pretty good for himself.
He lived a long life,
made a lot of money.
I actually managed to track down
a few photos of this guy.
This is him when
he's in his 30s, his 40s,
and then this is him in his 80s,
right here in the middle.
So is it possible
this is who you saw?
It is him.
Wow.
Pretty crazy walk so far.
What else is going on?
Then I ended up in
the first door
to the left down the hallway.
That's Emily's room.
That, to me, was
the worst room in the house.
I got straight-up that
she's a medium and very open.
So with that being said,
she is inadvertently attracting
a lot of dead people
into her room
through the window.
Lina, why don't you talk about
how Emily's changed?
Emily has developed all
of a sudden terrible anxiety,
depressive spells,
nervous breakdowns.
She doesn't leave the house.
It's a completely new person.
Yeah, that breaks my heart
in a million pieces
'cause I'd never seen her
like that before.
It's, again, very similar to
what my dad's going through,
but with Emily,
it's so scary.
When you're growing up
as a medium,
you do develop a lot of fear
'cause you've experienced
a lot of death already.
She probably
spontaneously opened
when all this stuff
came in the house.
- You mean the curse?
- Right.
Are these dead people literally
coming through the window?
Okay. So I had a sketch done
of what I saw happening.
Wow.
I- I honestly don't know
what to think.
It breaks my heart, knowing that
I can't step in front of her
and say, "I can take care
of this one."
- And is that a shadow person?
- No, no, no.
These things,
they're older than man.
They've been here forever,
and they come for the stars.
They're aliens, like,
alien aliens.
I don't think the entire family
has been abducted.
Okay. Who's been?
I think that specifically,
probably the male line.
My god.
So Sal and Allan
have been abducted?
I think that possibly
that they are abductees, yes.
I- I don't know what to say.
I don't know who to worry
about first.
Do I worry about me? Do I worry
about my little sister?
Everyone has their own
thing to deal with,
and I'm just trying
to figure out,
who should
I worry about first?
We knew there was something.
We didn't know it was that much.
So you guys look shell-shocked
and I can't say that
I blame you,
but it does explain
why Sal has changed so much.
So now the big question is,
what can you do
to have Emily go back
to her old self
and make this
a happy home again?
For that answer, I'm gonna
turn it over to Amy.
So the first thing
that I would like you to do
is take care of the curse.
My suggestion is
to go and see a curandero.
What exactly is a curandero?
Native Americans, they would
have a witch doctor,
and this is similar to that,
but for Latin American cultures.
Once it's reversed,
those little guys will
be gone.
All of that extra weight that
you've been carrying around,
the intense depression,
all of these emotions
and things
will just be gone.
So when he goes to get
the curse removed,
will that get rid
of the dead girl as well?
I'm really hoping that
she'll go immediately.
And the next thing
I would like to see
is that you have
a male medium
come and move on
the angry dead guy.
Okay.
As far as the alien issue,
there's really not anything
that can be done about that.
There are support groups.
- What if they moved?
- No.
No, no, no, no.
It would follow them.
What I would like to see
with Emily
is that I do think that
she needs to see, like,
a psychotherapist.
They're amazing
with treating PTSD,
which I think she does have.
So if Emily does
what you told them to do,
she should be pretty much
back to her old self?
Yeah.
You got good news.
Well, it's comforting
to know that, you know,
at some point in time,
she could be back to herself
and just have
a normal teenage life.
That's all we'd want.
So, Sal, are you gonna take
Amy's advice?
Yes. Definitely.
I appreciate her help.
The things that we are
able to control,
we're definitely gonna -- we're
gonna do what Amy is suggesting.
I think your family, as a whole,
pretty strong and tight,
so if anybody
can pull it off,
it's probably you guys.
Yeah, definitely.
This is, you know,
what we needed,
somewhere to get started.
Even though there is little
this family can do about
the aliens,
they should be able
to break the curse
with a curandero
and move the angry dead guy on
with a medium.
Once that's done, Emily can
get the help she needs,
and this family
can find the peace
they've been searching for.