There is a lot of
physical phenomena.
There is a vortex here.
It's just out of control.
I'm getting attacked.
She's, like, praying and crying
and praying and crying.
I saw a dark figure
standing right there.
They can kill
the living person here.
He died instantly.
It's not okay to be
in this location at all.
This is not a good situation.
My name is Amy Allan.
There is death here.
Don't want to go down there.
I see dead people.
They hide in the walls,
and they watch.
I speak to dead people...
She is definitely
a serial killer.
...and they speak to me.
She is going to torture them.
But there is only one way
to know if my findings are real.
They were all murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
So is this the only time
you've been physically attacked?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
There is no question in my mind
that he was talking about Satan.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who do you think possessed you?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
Well, you're not gonna
wanna see this.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Hell no.
Or time to get out.
Everyone is in jeopardy.
I'm in the small town
of Elkview, West Virginia.
It's about 15 miles
north of Charleston.
I got a call from a mother
of two named Sara.
Now, she says something
in her house is attacking her,
scaring her kids,
and she thinks someone
is gonna get hurt.
She sounded really bad,
and I'm hoping Amy
and I can help her out.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area of
any leading information.
This house is filled
with family photos,
so it's important that
I cover or remove them all.
When I'm done, the location will
be ready for tonight's walk.
Boy. Boy. Boy.
Boy. Boy.
There is at least
three time periods
of different dead people here,
and they're stuck
with each other,
so they're always fighting.
So it's kind of a mess.
This location here is kind of
caught in the crosshairs
of this crazy...
It's really bad.
You know, Sara, when we spoke
on the phone,
you sounded terrified.
What the hell's going on
in this house?
I'm at my breaking point.
The activity now
has got violent,
and it's just out of control.
I'm getting attacked.
My boys are being scared.
We need help.
If something can't be done,
it's gonna tear
my family apart.
All right. So who exactly
lives in the house?
Myself. We have my husband,
Mark, our youngest boy,
Tanner, he's 10,
and we have Lane that is 13.
All right, so how long have
you guys been living here?
We bought the house in 2002.
We had Tanner in 2006.
By the time that he was 2,
that's when we really
started noticing things
going on that
we could not explain.
- Do you think he caused it?
- Yes.
Nothing happened here
until he was born.
What type of experiences
are you guys having?
We've heard voices.
We have seen things
move on their own.
We've seen shadow figures.
We'll have nightmares,
and it's finally
getting physical.
We are...scared.
Now, is everybody in the house
being affected?
To some degree.
But it seems like
I'm the one that's seeing
and hearing
the majority of it.
So why don't you just move?
We just really love this place,
and I want to fight
for what's ours.
Something going on here.
There is a vortex here,
but it's huge.
It's massive.
Dead people can come and go
through it, also beings,
entities, like, things
that have never been human.
It's very concentrated
energy, very focused.
This is too much energy for
living people to be exposed to.
Being near this vortex
can cause a lot
of physical issues
with the living.
You're not gonna be
able to sleep here.
You're gonna have...
insane dreams here.
You're gonna lose time here.
You're gonna see crazy...
It's not okay to be
in this location at all.
What's going on down here?
I was down here one day,
and I go to walk up the stairs.
I see the bottom half of
an apparition as plain as day.
Where were you
when you saw this?
At the back door.
Any chance it could've
been one of the kids?
They were upstairs.
After I saw the apparition,
I got this intense pain.
It felt like lightning had went
from my head to my toes.
All right. So what else?
I have heard, say, two people
having a conversation,
whispering, almost like
they didn't want me
to hear what they were saying.
Does it sound like
it's a man and a woman,
a couple of men,
couple of women?
It varies. I've heard all.
Could the TV be on upstairs,
and it's just filtering
down into --
There is no television
on at these times.
This was late at night.
We don't leave TVs on.
Okay.
What else is going on?
One night, it was, like,
someone was shaking
the door violently.
Could somebody have
gotten into the garage?
That was my first thought,
and I was ready to call 9-1-1.
Did you investigate it?
I actually was too scared.
Wow.
There's Native Americans.
This is theirs, man.
I honestly thought
they were all men,
but I'm seeing all of these
Native American women
here with children.
I think that the living would
have experiences of feeling,
like, back it up.
I think that the living
would have a hard time
being down here for very long.
They would definitely
have experiences,
hearing children
laughing and playing,
hearing women's voices.
There is a lot of
physical phenomena.
The Native Americans are
constantly, like, moving things.
They don't want anything
down here or person,
and it really
bothers them, you know?
They want it all out.
Okay. So what's going on?
The other night, I had a dream
that there was a man
that was chasing me
down the stairs
with a knife.
Okay. How often are you
having those?
Several times a month.
All right.
Listen, I have nightmares.
Why is it paranormal for you?
These nightmares have just
started this year
when the activity
really started ramping up.
And I've never had nightmares
like this before.
Okay. All right.
What else is going on in here?
One night, I woke up
and there was just a shadow
leaning over me.
Where was the shadow?
It was along that wall
right there.
It couldn't have been somebody
outside casting a shadow.
No, no.
At nighttime, I always
shut our blinds.
Bad dreams.
Seeing shadow figures in here.
What else is going on?
There is times that
I've woke up, that it feels like
I've been in a car accident.
It feels like someone has taken
a baseball bat to my ribcage.
Do you ever see
any markings from it?
- We've taken some pictures.
- Okay.
This is my calf.
I mean, this is bad.
You know that.
Yeah.
Anything else physical
like that ever happened?
I'll go to bed feeling fine.
I will wake up in the middle
of the night
and have a migraine to where
it will make me so sick,
to where I'll get nauseous,
my head just feels like
somebody has just caved it in.
How the hell are you
living like this?
It's really scary sometimes.
And I'm just trying
to get through it,
make everything
okay for my boys,
my husband and just
try to block it out.
I see a woman here
with straight dark hair.
Is this a living person?
I think it's a living person.
I feel like she's being
beat up, like,
physically assaulted
by a dead male.
She's, like, praying and crying
and praying and crying.
This person in here
is sick already
and is sicker
because of living here
because it's such a bad
place to be physically.
- So, Lane, how old are you?
- I'm 13.
So I was talking to mom.
She says things in the house
are pretty scary.
Yes.
Are you having trouble
sleeping here?
I've had nightmares in here,
and that's caused me
to not sleep.
So, Lane, what have you seen
that you can't explain?
Downstairs, I saw the rocking
chair rocking by itself.
Now, Lane, is it possible
one of your dogs
might have ran by
the chair and hit it?
No, because it's only happened
whenever I'm down
there long.
Okay. What else?
One time, I saw a dark
figure standing
right there looking at me
through the doorway.
It scared me so bad, my heart
just, like, leapt out of me.
So what did you see?
What did it look like?
Like a man.
It was, like,
darker than the room.
Do you think what's here
could be dangerous?
Yeah.
Boy.
I'm seeing a group of men.
They look weird.
They're dressed up
like pirates or bandits.
It makes them look
really creepy,
but they're all in shadow except
their eyes are white, like,
this intense,
bright, white light
comes out of their eyes
and puts them into shadow.
Living people here
are seeing them.
They wake up at night,
and they're being stared at.
Very scary.
Mark, talking to your wife,
she said that the activity
kind of started
maybe two years after
your youngest son was born.
I mean, did that
make sense to you?
Yes.
There is something going on
with the youngest.
Any experiences you could
tell me about?
Absolutely. Yeah.
We were all down
in the kitchen.
Okay.
And there was this
real loud beep.
It was really, I mean, you know,
it made your ears ring.
Now, Mark, smoke detectors
make that noise
when the battery
is starting to go.
Was that the case here?
I searched everything down
there, I mean, everything.
There was nothing.
Nothing logical
could explain it.
Okay. Anything else happen?
One time, I came in and fell
asleep on the love seat
and had my head back.
And it just felt like
somebody grabbed my jaw
and slammed it shut.
- You sure it wasn't a dream?
- Yeah.
And then afterward,
the bottom of my chin tingled
and then my teeth
started hurting.
I'm like, "Holy crap."
I mean, it hurt my teeth.
Working with Amy, knowing that
things are really physical here,
this is not a good thing.
- Yeah.
I worry every day, especially
when I'm out of town.
It's tough.
I'm really worried about
the boys being mentally scarred.
These pirate bandit people
are causing a lot
of stress for the living.
One of them tried to talk to me.
It made this weird noise.
I've seen them, like,
creeping up on a male here
as he's going up these stairs,
and there's a little dead guy
jumping on this
living dude's back.
This living guy just explodes.
He's feeling choked.
He's feeling like the wind's
being knocked out of him.
He's feeling pushed.
A lot of really
brutal experiences.
- Tanner, how old are you?
-10.
So, Tanner, when I was
talking to your mom today,
she told me that you were
having a tough time
with the activity in the house.
- Does that sound right to you?
- Yeah.
Any experiences
you could tell me about?
In the TV room,
the ceiling fan light,
it was off then
it flickered on by itself.
- That kind of scared you.
- Yeah.
Anything else?
I had a headache that
progressively got stronger.
And you think this was caused
by the paranormal?
Yeah.
Did you have them ever again?
Yes.
Your mom mentioned
she gets headaches.
You ever been around mom
when she got them?
Yeah.
I got them the same time
as she did.
If things are so bad here
for everybody else
and they've got to move,
would you be okay with that?
Yeah.
There is about
two or three women here.
I think they're whores.
I guess they probably had
Syphilis, I'm thinking.
They're rotting.
One of them doesn't
have a nose, you know?
The other one is, like,
missing, you know,
pretty much her whole face.
And they look scarier than...
You know if they interact with
the living in any way?
These whores are pulling
memories out.
I think that the living
have headaches from that,
and I think that they have
nightmares from that.
It's very unhealthy.
They like this room.
They're attracted to this
living person here
'cause they're
a physical medium.
These whores think that this
person has been neglected.
They basically want
to adopt this person.
- Is this person in danger?
- Yeah.
The whores have been
attached to this person
for their whole life
and make bad...
happen, and they can kill
the living person here.
Look, Elkview is a tiny town,
barely over 1,200 people.
So when I made my usual calls,
just about everyone knew
Sara and Mark's property.
I'm heading over to meet
with an archivist who says,
one of the original owners
suffered a lot
of tragedies there.
Now, Matt, you mentioned
on the phone
that the Pauley family
suffered some tragedies
while they were on
my clients' property.
When did they get
my clients' property?
Daniel Pauley bought your
clients' property in about 1858.
So how much property
did he have?
Well, he purchased 670 acres.
Wow.
Does he move on the property
right then and there?
Yes. Yes.
He and his wife, Cinthya,
and their eight children,
they moved their immediately
and built a house.
You mentioned on the phone,
there were some deaths
in regards to the family.
What happened?
Cinthya gives birth to
a baby boy named Benjamin.
But unfortunately, Benjamin dies
when he's only 4 months old.
4 months?
Yeah, same year they move
onto the property.
This is the death record of it?
- That's right.
- What happens after that?
Several years later,
the American Civil War is
going on.
Daniel goes off
to fight for the North.
I mean, how old is
he at this point?
He's 50.
All right.
So let me get this straight.
The guy's 50,
joins the Union Army.
That's correct.
And we do know that the company
he served in lost
about 200 men to disease,
probably dysentery.
And a lot of that was due
to the, you know,
the sanitation conditions.
So in these camps, it just was
not a very healthy place to be.
And that's
a horrible way to go.
Yes.
I'm seeing that
group of bandits,
and they don't look good.
They all got sick,
and they all died
horrible deaths
from this illness.
And they are damned
to wander here.
The leader of these bandits
is a colonial rogue soldier.
So can you describe this guy?
He looks to be in his 40s,
I would guess,
very tall and he had on this
very rich velvet blue
Military jacket.
He was in the military,
and I believe he went rogue.
How does it go for him
after that?
He's able to come home
to Cinthya and the children
unscathed at the end
of the war in 1865.
As time wears on, though,
on October 5, 1888, he dies.
- Do we know how old he was?
- Yes.
He was 73 years old.
Okay.
What are we thinking, stroke?
More than likely a stroke.
All right.
So Daniel is dead.
Does Cinthya remain
on the property?
She does, and she
winds up dying in
February of 1890
when she's 72.
- And on my clients' property?
- That's correct.
What happens with the property?
Well, it stays in the family
and it is Daniel's grandson,
George, who actually
buys the property.
In 1894, he and his wife
have a young son named Romey
who dies before
he's even a year old.
What happens after that?
Well, George actually
is the final chapter
of the Pauley tragedies.
In 1906, when he's
only 36 years old,
he dies very quickly,
very mysteriously.
All we have to go on
is his obituary.
So we don't know if it was
an accident, illness.
It doesn't tell us
what happened to him.
But we do know
it was very unexpected.
I think there are so many
dead people here
because of the vortex.
Dead people can come
and go through it, also beings,
entities, like, things
that have never been human.
They can come and go through it.
And how would the living
be affected by the vortex?
They would feel anxious.
They would have
equilibrium issues.
It could cause
long-term illnesses,
also neurological damage.
This thing is really dangerous.
I think that it can kill people.
A local EMT just called me.
Now, he says Elkview has been
completely flooded
several times.
It turns out, one of the most
recent ones was deadly,
and one of the victims died
right near
Mark and Sara's house.
Now, Tim,
thanks for meeting me.
I really appreciate that.
You mentioned on the phone that
one of my clients' neighbors
perished during this big flood.
What happened?
Little Sandy Creek
runs along the property
that you're investigating.
In June of 1998, a big powerful
storm hit the Elkview area.
Okay. So how bad did it get?
İt got pretty deep, and it
destroyed a lot of property
and took some lives.
Wow. All right.
So obviously, the water rose.
What were the flood levels
at my clients' property?
Wow.
It got really high.
Okay.
So what do we know
about the poor guy
that died in this flood?
Well, Mr. Richard Varium, he was
an 83-year-old guy that lived
about 1,000 feet from
the property
you're investigating.
I have a picture of Mr. Varium
when he was younger.
He had been living alone
for quite a while.
He was bound to a wheelchair
and also blind.
He was in a bad situation.
What happened?
Family tried to get him out,
and they got him to the porch
and realized that the water
was too swift, muddy,
with a lot of debris
and then went to get help.
By the time they got back,
he had washed away
along with the porch.
And he was found
downstream about 1/4
of a mile in some trees.
There was something about
water issues here and flooding
'cause I saw water
come down, like, a wall.
These water issues
are due directly
to the paranormal
phenomena here.
That's not good.
The problem here is the land.
Exposure to the land
seems to trap the dead here
or bring them back
to be trapped here.
For more information
about the show
and if you need us to
investigate unexplained activity
in your home...
Please visit
travelchannel.com/thedeadfiles.
Click on
"Help Me, Dead Files!"
to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
So far, I've got a family
being tormented
in their own home on a property
where at least five people died.
But I want to see
if there is anything else.
Searching through old records,
I find an article about another
member of the Pauley family.
It turns out he was murdered
right next to Sara
and Mark's property.
I'm heading over to meet
historian and old friend,
Jim Casto.
He's looked into
this case for me
and says it's got all
the ingredients for violence --
friendship, love, and betrayal.
Well, Jim, it's good
to see you again.
Now, the homicide, it happened
right near my clients' property,
and it involved
one of the Pauleys.
So what can you
tell me about it?
The victim was 27-year-old
Clarence Pauley,
and he and his wife
and his three kids lived
just down the road
from the property.
There is a photo of him
in his Navy uniform
during his World War II service.
Despite being a married man,
Clarence was
conducting an affair
with the wife
of his best friend,
Arnold Eldgewick,
and her name was Mary.
What happened with
the homicide?
On the night of
May 27, 1947,
Clarence drove Mary
to her sister's house,
where she had been staying.
- Okay.
What they didn't know was that
Arnold was there waiting on them
in the dark, shotgun in hand.
They pulled up.
Mary saw him standing there.
She got out of the car.
He fired a shotgun blast
to her but missed.
She fled and went down the road.
Clarence gets out of the car.
But before he gets
out of the car,
he picks up a heavy hammer
and he starts toward Arnold.
The guy's got a shotgun,
and he grabs a hammer?
- It seems odd.
- Yeah.
Arnold fired again.
This time, his shot
hit its mark.
It pierced Clarence's chest
right into his heart.
He died instantly.
Okay.
So Arnold kills this guy.
Do the cops arrest him?
Well, they didn't have
to bother looking for him.
He drove himself straight
to the county jail,
turned himself in,
confessed what he had done.
And when they asked
him why, he said,
"I thought I had
done a good deed."
Here is a mug shot taken
at the West Virginia prison.
He's got psycho
written in his eyes.
I can tell you that.
- Absolutely.
- All right.
So how much time
did he wind up getting?
He served three years
in the West Virginia State Pen.
He got away with pretty
much premeditated murder.
So it would seem.
Something happened where
this woman is freaking out.
I'm hearing, like, men's voices
talking, yelling.
Some jealousy issues,
I heard a gunshot.
I'm getting just
a lot of sadness.
I saw a lot of dead
during my walk,
but two groups
concerned me the most.
First, the gang of bandits,
these figures
are completely black.
Their eyes were white.
They look like kind of
these mutant monsters.
Next, I describe the prostitutes
terrorizing a young boy.
He is pissed off.
He's like this because
they keep him up all night.
One of them is kind of
missing half of her face.
It's been rotted off already.
The other one,
her nose fell off.
Amy, is this what you saw?
Yes. That's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients
for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to meet
Sara and her husband, Mark.
Now, they live here
with their two young sons.
I've got a photo.
This is Lane, who is 13.
This is Tanner, who's 10.
Now, Mark here travels
a lot for work,
so Sara and the boys
are left here a lot
to face the violent
activity alone.
She told me,
with everything going on,
this place is just
a house, not a home.
But they're both hoping
we can change that.
So now that Amy
has met you guys,
I'm gonna ask her
to describe her walk for us.
When I got here,
I saw something
that is really not good
for living people --
a vortex.
It's something that's
always been here,
and this one is so large
and is very powerful.
People who live in areas
like this
will have a lot
of paranormal phenomena
because entities and dead people
come and go through vortexes.
The dead here, due to this
kind of energy, are stronger.
They're gonna be
much more physical.
They're gonna be able to do
a lot more to the living.
And for the living, it makes
you guys a lot weaker.
If you have a lot of
dead people around you,
you're gonna have
a lot of dead energy
which isn't
particularly healthy.
And also, because the movement
of energy is so intense,
the living here would be,
like, constantly falling,
having vertigo-type
experiences.
Now, we never talked about
equilibrium problems.
You or anybody in the family
have any problems with that?
Yes.
Months ago, it was just, like,
someone had spun me
around 50 times.
I could not get out
of the bathroom.
This vortex can also cause you
to have nightmares
and bad anxiety.
I feel high, high anxiety
for no reason.
Mark, do you or the boys
feel that way at all?
- The boys definitely do --
- Okay.
...especially Lane.
Plus,
you mentioned nightmares.
Yeah.
You feel like when you wake up,
you have to look
around to be like,
"Where the heck have I been?"
And I spoke to both boys,
and they're having
nightmare issues as well.-
Long-term, what is this
gonna do to us?
Being exposed to just
the vortex alone
on a consistent
basis can develop
into long-term
and terminal illnesses,
things like brain cancer,
dementia, Alzheimer's,
heart issues.
Do you guys suffer
from anything like that?
High blood pressure, yeah.
But it seems like it probably
got worse when I came here.
Exactly. That's the vortex?
It could be, yeah.
What else did you get?
There are three groups
of dead people here.
They are each from
a separate time period.
One of the groups
is Native American.
And basically, they've taken
over this basement area.
There is a lot of
physical phenomena.
Native Americans are constantly,
like, moving things.
They don't want anything
down here or person,
and it really
bothers them, you know?
They want it all out.
So I thought the living would
hear maybe the women talking,
the children laughing
and playing, objects moving.
When I spoke with Sara
down here in the basement,
she told me about hearing voices
down here, conversations, right?
Just whispers.
Imagine just people, you know...
Yeah, I'll hear that.
Now, you've also heard
someone screwing
with the basement doorknob.
Tell Amy what
happened that time.
Imagine somebody walking up
the stairs and can't get up,
got angry and just did
one of those.
Now, Mark, did Lane tell you
about the story
with the rocking
chair down here?
Yeah. Just out of
the corner of his eye,
he would see this
rocking chair move.
Now, does that make sense
with all
the Native Americans down here?
Yes.
There is one dead male
I saw very clearly.
He is the leader of
the second group
of dead people that are here,
and I'll get to those
guys in a minute.
This guy was extremely tall,
very thin, very pale.
He looked to be in his 40s.
He was wearing
an interesting hat.
He also had a royal blue
Military-style jacket.
I think he was in the military,
and he went rogue.
And like I said,
he had a team of men.
I mean, I kept calling them kind
of, like, pirates or bandits
because of how
they dressed and acted.
Eventually, though,
all of these men
became extremely ill
from some kind of illness,
and they all died
horrible deaths.
Some of the stuff you're talking
about reminds me
of one of the original
owners of your property,
and this guy goes back to 1858.
He bought 670 acres, including
the property the house sits on.
Now his name was Daniel Pauley.
Now, you said the guy you saw
was in the Military
and might have had
a Military jacket on?-
Pauley served in the Union Army
during the Civil War
which would have been
a blue uniform.
He was 50 years old
when he joined.
You said you saw a bunch of men
dying of some horrible illness.
Now, when Pauley was serving,
200 of the guys he served
with died of dysentery.
But he managed
to survive somehow.
Now, is it possible Pauley
could be the guy you saw?
I kind of think it's unlikely.
I didn't really feel
like they lived here.
Okay.
At least we know who it's not.
Now, does this guy in blue
and his men do anything
to the living here?
- Yes.
I think you might hear them
and I tried to speak to them.
But because they can't
physically manifest words,
this weird noise came out.
It's like this crackling
weird noise.
Well, it's funny
you mention that
because I just looked at Mark.
He told me about hearing
these, like, a beep?
Yeah, just a beep
out of nowhere.
It sounds like it's right
next to you,
but there is nothing there.
I got that there is one male
that they don't particularly
like here, that they do focus
on and pick on often.
One of them attacked
this male here.
I saw him jumping on his back,
pushing him up the stairs
there into
the family room area,
maybe feeling, like, an,
you know, a hit here maybe,
maybe choking sensation,
maybe feeling like, you know,
the wind's getting
knocked out of you.
It sounds to me like
you're talking about Mark.
Tell her about the experience
you had on the couch
'cause that was pretty bad.
One night, okay, my mouth was
wide open and I was snoring.
And it just felt like
somebody had come up
and took their hand
and slammed my mouth shut.
And the bottom side of my chin
tingled for at least
an hour or two.
You mentioned you'd saw
a male getting attacked.
- Yeah.
- But I got news for you.
I got photos of Sara
waking up with bruises.
Here, look at these.
Wow.
It feels like somebody has taken
a baseball bat to my ribcage.
Is there any other way
Mark and Sara
would experience these guys?
It's possible that the living
could see them.
They were in shadow and I had
a sketch done of what I saw.
Wow.
I have seen a dark apparition,
a shadow figure,
that I thought was Mark,
and he backed into the wall.
So it sounds like these bandits
are what they're seeing?
Correct.
These guys are always around.
They don't ever leave.
You said there were three
groups of dead people
you were concerned about.
- Yeah.
What was the third one?
So there is this other group
of dead people
that are here
that are prostitutes.
There's two or three of them.
I think that these women
suffered from syphilis.
For instance,
one doesn't have a nose.
There is another one
who has the sores.
It can be a rotting disease.
As far as what the living
would experience,
they will go into your minds
and pull out
really bad memories,
causing wicked headaches
and nightmares.
You and Tanner
both have headaches.
I mean, we're talking
full-blown migraine to where,
you know, you're nauseous.
The other thing that's going
on is, they love children.
They wanted the child
who's in the yellow room.
That's Tanner.
They're attracted to him
because he is a physical medium.
A lot of this activity started
after Tanner hit about 2.
Is there a connection
between him turning 2
and what's going on here?
- Yes.
He's becoming a little bit
more cognizant, you know, aware.
So he can interact
with them in a way
that a lot of other
people can't.
You didn't have a surprised
look on your face
when she said he was
a physical medium.
You were like, "Yeah."
- We kind of suspected it.
- You did?
Yeah. I'm really worried
about him because ---
...what's his life
going to be like
and what do we tell him now?
He strikes me as a kid,
when you talk to him,
as somebody that has
been through a lot.
A lot, exactly.
I did have a sketch done of him
being agitated by these women.
That's gonna be tough
for you to see.
Wow.
I mean, I've seen him sit
in his bed like that.
You can tell that
something bothers him.
All right.
So what do these prostitutes
want with Tanner anyway?
These women are nuts.
What they're trying
to figure out right now
is if they want to take him
or if they want to
attach to him.
And if they were
to attach to him,
they would then cause
issues throughout his life.
If they decided to take him,
that would result in death.
So Sara and Mark, you guys got
a lot of information tonight,
probably a lot more
than you bargained for.
But we still haven't
answered the big question.
Is there anything you can do
to stop the activity here
so that you guys can protect
Tanner and live in peace
as a family again?
For that answer, I'm gonna
turn it over to Amy.
Okay. So here we go.
Basically, what can be done
about the vortex
is a reversal
of the vortex energy.
Take it from negative
to positive.
That way, the entities aren't
anymore coming out at you.
They're going in,
and then they're moving on.
And negative energy
would dissipate over time.
So how can they make
that happen?
The one that I know,
she is a psychic knower
and a Reiki master.
Okay.
And she also specializes
in working with vortex.
It's an extremely
difficult task.
I would give the odds 50/50.
You'll know within a week, after
the practitioner were to leave,
if it worked or not.
Obviously, if it doesn't take,
I would recommend that you move.
If it did work, then you would
need to find a physical medium
and a shaman to move on the rest
of the dead that are here,
the ones who think
that they're trapped.
What about the whores?
They're gonna be
harder to grasp,
but the medium
will be able to do it.
Yeah. They're not gonna have
another chance to kill my kid.
They are not harming him
ever, ever, ever again.
Even if all of this works,
you have to start dealing
and learning about
the abilities that your son,
Tanner, has, especially
focusing right now
on protection measures
and meditation techniques.
If you were in their shoes,
what would you do?
- I would be out of here.
- Shoot.
If they move and Tanner learns
how to deal with his abilities,
should they be okay?
- Yeah.
You know, normally,
I stick it to the clients.
I'm like, "You're gonna do
what Amy advises you."
This is one of those cases
where it's, like, you guys
really got to figure this out
and, you know,
this is your family.
Not a tough decision
when it comes
to the well-being of the family.
- This is just a physical place.
- Yeah.
I don't see how we can stay.
We're definitely
gonna move.
There is no guarantee
that a psychic knower
and a Reiki master
can reverse the vortex on Mark
and Sara's property,
so I really hope they take
my advice and move.
If they do that and teach Tanner
how to deal with his abilities,
they should be able to
lead a peaceful life.