The house just feels bad.
I hear a dangerous telepath.
And they think it's
physically attacked.
He can't breathe.
He's hyperventilating.
He's freaking out.
I heard him yell out,
"Leave me alone."
We have reports
of him threatening
to kill anyone
who approached him.
And I feel bad for the kid.
No wonder he's all...up.
So I don't know if this
person is insane or a sensitive.
This is not a good situation.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's death here.
Don't want to go down there.
I see dead people.
They hide in the walls,
and they watch.
I speak to dead people...
She's definitely
a serial killer.
And they speak to me.
She's going to torture them.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
They were all murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective...
So is this the only time
you've been physically attacked?
And I know every person,
every house, has secrets.
There's no question in my mind
that he was talking about Satan.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who do you think possessed you?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Well, you're not going
to want to see this.
What we uncover is if it's safe
for you to stay...
Hell no.
Or time to get out.
Everyone is in jeopardy.
I'm in Waterford, Connecticut,
about 50 miles
south of Hartford.
I got a call from a woman
named Linda.
Now, she sounded really bad.
Told me whatever is in the house
broke up her marriage,
and now it's torturing
one of her kids.
She told me she's
barely hanging on,
and we are her very last hope.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area
of any leading information.
Photographs, personal items
and even religious symbols
have to be covered or removed.
When I'm finished,
tonight's walk can begin.
I don't feel good.
Somebody here
is making me
excruciatingly sick.
I seriously want to vomit.
It feels like it's a male
who's very angry.
We might have to go to the
hospital, like, right now.
So, Linda, when we spoke
on the phone
you sounded terrified.
There's something
really bad here, evil,
terrorizing my family,
ripping us apart.
How long have you been
living here?
I inherited from my father,
and we moved in 2009.
What did he pass from,
if you don't mind me asking?
He never told us
what he passed away from,
but the death
certificate said cancer.
That's the kind
of person he was,
just kept things to himself.
Did he die in the house?
No, he didn't.
He died in a hospital.
Okay.
Was he sick while
he was living here?
Yes, he was.
You know, he doesn't sound
like much of a talker,
but do you know if he had
an experiences here?
He did mention he would
hear footsteps,
people walking around,
jiggling door handles.
I wrote it off as him, maybe,
going a little senile.
Now, Linda, do you have
any knowledge
of the history of
this house or anything?
The only thing that I was that
somebody had committed suicide
in the basement
and hung themselves.
Well, I'll look into that.
Okay.
So, Linda, who exactly
lives in the house?
Well, here's a picture.
It's my husband,
me and younger son,
Eric, and I have
an older son, Nathan,
who lives here that doesn't want
to be part of this at all.
What do you mean doesn't want
to be of, of this investigation?
Yeah.
He's bothered too much
by what's here.
He just doesn't want
to be involved in it.
I don't know how good
this investigation can go
without me knowing
everything I can
with him not talking to me.
Yeah.
I feel helpless.
I don't know what to do.
So, Linda, give me an idea what
you guys are experiencing here.
Well, we've been experiencing
growling, mood swings,
our health is getting bad
and physical attacks.
Tell me more about the sickness.
What's going on with that?
Chest pains, nausea,
trouble breathing.
Now, you said the house
causes mood swings.
We argue a lot.
Things have gotten so bad
between Robie and I
that he had moved out
6 months ago.
His moods changed.
I've changed.
You know, nobody
got along anymore.
Relationships, they go bad,
so I don't know
if that's a problem
with the house
or if it's personal.
How was Robie before
you guys moved in here?
He was fun to be around.
We come here and he's, like,
doesn't want to talk
and just, kind of, moody and...
What about you?
How were you before
you moved in here?
I was a happy-go-lucky
person, and I come in here,
and now I'm, like, miserable.
I've got to be blunt.
I got to ask you.
Why don't you just get
the hell out of here?
I'm a little stubborn.
It's my house.
I'm hoping that we can
correct the problem
and get rid of what's here
and live a normal life,
and live a peaceful life
with no arguing, fighting,
or anything else that goes along
with what's in this house.
The guy who is making me sick,
it's like his energy
fills the walls.
He's so, almost,
a part of the house.
To me, I don't know how anybody
could be in here without,
like, just vomiting.
And it's not only his horrible,
horrible anger issue,
but also his sickness.
It's, like, embedded in
the walls,
and really thick.
The house just feels bad.
Okay.
So Nathan sleeps here?
Yes.
Which bed does he sleep in?
Top.
The bottom is supposed
to be for the dog,
but he won't come in.
Interesting.
Okay.
So now, since Nathan
won't talk to me,
can you describe to me
what he's experiencing?
Well, he's experienced
growling and howling.
Where?
The basement.
Now, have you heard this, too?
I've heard the howling.
How's the howling sound
to you?
Does it sound like an animal?
The animal
I've never heard before.
You've got woods back here.
Are you sure it wasn't an animal
that got into the house?
No. No.
Okay. What else?
Nathan gets physically
attacked a lot.
Okay.
Describe some of them for me.
He feels stabbing pains
in his legs
and his neck and in his back,
and then he's been in the shower
and he's been pushed.
Okay.
Anything else?
Just that he sees
this little creature
hopping down the hallway
and then squatting in
his room tormenting him.
My God!
I'm seeing all kinds
of crazy...
going down on the bed.
What I'm seeing,
it's predator looking.
So it comes up and it
slithers along,
and then it's got arms
when it goes down.
It kind of reminds me
of those weird jellyfish things.
This thing has a face.
More human looking, I think.
It's always changing its face.
I don't even know what thing is.
I don't know if anybody
could sleep in here
because if somebody is up here,
they're getting
the full-on experience.
The bed would be shaking.
They're feeling irritated
not being able to sleep
because of the constant energy.
This would make
anybody go crazy.
Okay. So now we talked about
your son's issues.
Let's talk about you.
What's going on?
I wake up sometimes
with bruising,
and I didn't go to bed
with the bruising.
Did they ever check
your white blood cell count?
Anything wrong with that?
I get physicals every year.
And nothing is going on?
Nothing.
Okay. Anything else?
Well, I woke up to my bed
violently shaking.
How violently are we talking?
Can you show me?
Like enough to wake me up.
And then I feel like
I'm in a ring of fire.
So when you say a ring of fire,
do you, like, wake up
and you see flames around you,
or you just feel that way?
No. I feel it.
Like I'm burning in hell.
It happens quite a bit.
All right.
So how are you and Nathan
dealing with all this?
Well, I talk to him.
He pulls out his bible a lot...
Okay.
And he calls to God
and Jesus
to help him, and...
That's okay.
Trying to get through
this whole thing.
Yeah.
I try to help.
He gets mad because I don't read
the bible as much as I should.
You're trying, though.
Yeah.
Okay.
I've tried all the options.
You people were my last resort.
Boy.
I'm hearing dangerous telepath.
I guess the person in here
has telepathy
and might be influencing
other people in the house
who might not really
be having experiences,
but rather they're
induced by this person.
So this telepath thought, I want
to protect who's ever in here,
but their true intention is
they want something to happen,
so inadvertently
they create something
that is actually
going to scare.
So is that jellyfish thing
you saw on the bed real?
No. This thing is a
manifestation of
that person's true intentions,
so it would be terrifying,
I think.
So, Eric, I was talking
to your mom earlier
and she's having a lot
of experiences here.
What about you?
Have you seen anything
you can't explain?
One time I was in the kitchen
and I seen the cat
get swept off its feet.
All four feet.
It got swept on its side.
Well, you know, Eric,
cats do funny things.
You know, they say animals
see things that people don't.
It's seeing something.
Definitely.
So anything else?
No.
No experience.
So I'm curious.
Why do you think everybody else
is effected, but you're not?
Personally, I just,
I believe in it,
I just don't let it get to me.
I just won't let it.
Okay.
That's fair enough.
Your mom, she thinks that
whatever is in this house
is causing everybody
to fight with each other.
Do you agree with that?
Yeah.
I agree.
My mom, my brother
and my stepfather,
it's like a triangle.
They all fight.
Is there a drastic change
in their personalities.
Yeah. Yeah.
Big time.
Now, it's funny
you mention brother.
He doesn't even want
to talk to me
about this whole situation
that's going on here.
No.
He keeps it bottled up inside.
He doesn't really
talk much about it.
Yeah.
Have you seen it affect him?
Yeah. I've heard him yell out,
"Leave me alone,"
and "stop bothering them,"
and he's even cried before.
So whatever it is it's not good.
I'm getting panic, panic, panic.
I see a younger person in here,
and I see panic
and, like, sweating
and freaking the...out.
He can't breathe.
He's hyperventilating.
He's freaking out.
He's crying.
Okay. So this person
is hearing
and seeing things.
This is causing, like,
super-duper,
crazy panic attacks.
So he was a awake and he saw
and heard something,
literally doing one of these,
covering his ears
trying to make it stop.
It almost feels like the walls
are closing in on him.
So I don't know if this person
is insane or a sensitive.
Robie, I understand
you are Linda's husband.
Yes.
This paranormal stuff,
do you believe in it
or did you believe in it?
I didn't.
I do now.
So what was it that changed you
from being a skeptic
to a believer?
I believe it was the howling
that I heard.
Linda actually heard it also.
All the hairs
on my arms stand up.
Okay.
It was like something
you would hear in a movie.
All right.
Anything else?
Some health issues.
Okay. Like what?
Ulcerative colitis.
That put me in the hospital
for a couple weeks.
I get dizzy a lot.
I don't know what it is,
you know?
The doctors ever figure out
what the hell was wrong?
No. They don't know
what was wrong with that.
How do you feel now
that you're not here?
I mean, I feel good.
Any problems with
your colitis and all?
No.
Interesting.
Okay, so, anything else?
I've seen shadow figures.
Okay.
Where?
In the dining room area, there.
They were just fast
moving shadows.
They moved so fast I really
couldn't get a shape on them.
Now, have you ever seen other
shadow figures any place else?
In the kitchen in front
of the kitchen sink.
Now, Linda mentioned to me
that she thought your mood
and your personality changed
when you moved here.
Yes.
You agree with that?
Yes, I do.
I think my attitude,
it got worse.
I don't know.
It just seems like little things
were bothering me, you know?
Now, what about Linda?
Basically, the same thing.
But let me ask you a question.
If my partner turns around
and says, "Listen,
a paranormal in this house
is what caused you guys
to fight all the time,"
would you consider getting
back with your wife?
Personally, yes I would.
My feeling is I would
like to get back.
I'm seeing a deceased female.
She is 16.
She seems extremely confused.
She looks like a dissection.
She's got, like,
various stages of tissue,
and then there's muscle,
and then there's bone,
but it's also rotting
and there's, like, maggots.
So she's a mess.
She was dancing with, I guess,
a male that she had a crush on,
and then that same
male attacked her,
and then he threw her down
a hill, and then she's dead.
She says, "I want to make
a nest so I can sleep."
She says the living keep
waking her up so she gets upset.
She's showing me her walking,
and it's weird, so
I'm not sure if they're seeing
her, like a shadow person.
She wants to nest,
I think, in the closet.
Okay.
She doesn't like it in there.
What happened?
She... freaked the...
out and went...
She, like, went into my head
and went out my neck,
and it hurt.
That hurt.
Linda says she's been
scratched and bruised,
and I don't doubt
her for a second,
but she also said she hears
howling and growling
sounds indoors.
To me, not everything
is paranormal
so I'm heading back
to the house to meet
with a pest control expert
to see if some kind of
wildlife could be responsible.
So here's the deal.
My clients in the house
are complaining about waking up
with scratches
and hearing howling noises
and growling inside the house.
They're convinced
it's the paranormal.
Call me crazy, call me kooky,
but couldn't it be wildlife?
There's a number of things
it could be,
anything from a raccoon
to a squirrel.
Could be bats.
So if you could do me a favor
and give the house
a thorough once-over...
Yep.
And inspect it for me
and let me know what you find.
Absolutely.
Excellent. Thank you, buddy.
Thank you.
With all the strange sounds
Linda and her family
are hearing I know I have
to rule out the obviously first.
And if there isn't
a physical explanation,
our only hope for answers
will have to come from Amy.
Okay.
So what'd you find?
Less than nothing.
Not even mouse droppings.
You found no evidence that
an animal
or any kind of wildlife
could have caused scratching,
growling, howling,
any of that stuff?
Correct.
Well, I appreciate
your time and your help.
Thank you so, so much.
Thank you.
I'm seeing that dead
teenage girl again.
How might the living
experience her?
I know that when she gets upset
she might scratch people.
She also, you know, can make
people feel really,
really cold or hot.
Dead girl is out here,
and I hear crying
from back there, weeping.
So I'm thinking maybe
the living are hearing
a female crying and weeping.
So far I've got a client
who believes the paranormal
is ripping her family apart.
She also believes someone
killed themselves in her house,
so I'm at the library
to see if that's true.
Sure enough, I find a man
named Anthony Ventamiglia
who hung himself
right in Linda's basement.
So I got a local P.I.
looking into this suicide for me
and he tells me the poor guy who
hung himself in Linda's house
had a long, sad history
of mental illness.
Okay. So what did you find out
about this guy's background?
Well, we know that
Anthony Ventamiglia
came to the United States
son of Italian immigrants.
His father, Vincenzo,
was a laborer for
the Boston and Maine railroad.
At some point in the 1920s
Vincenzo started to develop
mental health issues.
He was hospitalized
at the New York State hospital
until his death in 1938.
Okay.
So it's 1938, Vincenzo is dead,
so what happens to Anthony?
Anthony ends up enlisting
in the United States Army
and actually serves
in World War II
as a warrant officer.
Okay.
That tells me a lot
about the guy already.
I mean, he had to be
enlisted at some point,
becomes a warrant officer,
which, when I was
in the Marine Corps,
was a lot more respected
than your regular officers.
Correct.
All right.
So, Jimmy, when does
he wind up here?
In 1959, Anthony
and his mother, Domenica,
buy this house, right here,
and actually are the first
residents of this house.
Wait, so him and his mother?
Correct.
Okay. Married? Kids?
He never got married,
and he didn't have any kids.
All right. So, Jimmy,
when does this guy
start going a little crazy?
Well, it's hard to pinpoint
an exact time.
By the mid 1980s, he was
having psychotic episodes.
We have reports of him running
around the neighborhood
in his underwear wielding
a knife threatening
to kill anyone
who approached him.
Okay. Does he ever get
arrested for that?
No. He never gets arrested.
All right.
Do we know if he ever
had counseling, medication?
It doesn't appear that he did.
It appears that he became more
and more of a recluse
and confined himself
to the house.
When does he kill himself?
November 14th, 1987.
Anthony is 70 years old.
I actually have
the death certificate.
All right. So where does he wind
up hanging himself?
According to the police report,
he hung himself right here
in the basement
on the center beam.
Okay.
So it's possible he hung himself
right here, literally.
Correct.
Okay. So now Anthony is dead.
What happens to the house?
Believe it or not,
Domenica is still alive
and she's forced
to sell the house
and move into a nursing home,
and she dies in 1989
at the age of 102.
That's a pretty sad story
because this guy
had a lot of potential.
He did.
Unfortunately, he had some of
the same mental health issues
that his father had.
Wow. It doesn't feel good
in this area.
I hear a man crying over there,
and he's sitting on a chair
and he's crying.
Maybe he's, like, 50.
Maybe a little older, like,
more probably 60s.
Something very traumatic
happened to him
and he's not dealing
with it well.
But I think people would feel
that depression down here, I do.
Yeah.
I just feel anxiety.
I feel cold over there.
I feel stressed.
I feel chaos.
It's, kind of, making me
a little crazy in my mind.
My head spins.
You know, somebody
dropped dead here.
Male, dead, boom.
For more information
about the show,
and if you need us
to investigate
unexplained activity
in your home...
Please visit
TravelChannel.com/TheDeadFiles.
Click on "Help me, Deadfiles!"
to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
You know, another thing got
my attention in research.
Back in the '90s a dead body
was found a couple of thousand
feet from Linda's house.
I'm heading over to meet
a former cop
who's familiar with the case,
and he says the victim
was a rich kid
who got in way
over his head.
Well, Mike, I appreciate you
helping me out with this case.
Now, the body they found right
by my client's property,
what can you tell me about that?
It was the body of James Connor.
He's an individual who went
to a prestigious private school
and he went to college at
South Connecticut
State University.
His nickname was Captain Jim
because he had a business
piloting yachts in the area.
Okay. So this guy sounds like
he came from
the upper crust of society,
right?
Yeah.
Okay. So what happened?
I think he fell into
the wrong crowd,
got addicted to crack cocaine.
Well, on August 23rd, 1998,
that's when Connor
leaves a bar in Essex
and he drives down
to New London
to a drug haven to score some
crack cocaine from three thugs.
One of them was named
Gregory Pierre, aka Coyote.
I can see where this is
going already, but all right.
So what happens next?
Coyote and two of his thugs,
they decide to rob Connor
instead of selling
the crack cocaine,
and I think, basically,
they beat him to death
with metal pipes,
but they also shot him
twice in the head.
Okay. So, Mike, what was
the official cause of death?
Initially they believed
the cause of death
was the gunshot wound and
probably the loss of blood...
Okay.
But as they further
looked into it,
there was multiple blows to
the head with these metal pipes,
and actually,
one of the reports, Steve, says
they actually put a pipe
down his throat
and snapped his neck.
Okay.
So they kill this rich guy.
What do these thugs do next?
They try to hide the evidence.
They dump his body, probably,
within 1,000 feet
of your client's house.
Well, then they drive Connor's
down here and they, actually,
try to sink it in this pond,
right here, which is crazy
because the police department
is right next to the pond.
Okay. Thank god they're stupid.
Yeah.
The police found the car
early the next morning
because it didn't sink.
It was only partially submerged.
All right.
So how'd they wind up
catching these three mutts?
Well, they were
sloppy criminals, Steve.
They actually end up
leaving a lot of blood
stains in Connor's car...
Okay.
And they went around
talking about it publicly,
you know, bragging
about their crime.
Here's a article on the arrests.
All right, Mike, so what did
these guys
wind up getting charged with?
They were charged
with felony murder.
They go to trial and they up
getting convicted.
All three of them
got 85 years in jail.
All right. So, Mike, you and I
both worked the crack epidemic
back in the day.
Yeah.
Very rare, though,
did you see somebody
from an affluent community
get mixed up with crack.
Obviously he had
no street smarts.
Yeah. It doesn't sound like
he was smart enough
to know what was actually
going to happen to him.
Okay.
I saw a flash of a male.
Very tall, he's like 6 foot.
I think he's between 40 and 42.
He was very wealthy.
Do you have any idea
how he died?
He tells me he was
strangled or choked.
He wasn't exactly sure.
He knows that he felt
pressure around his throat.
He just wants to
find his way out.
There was a male involved,
and he said about his male,
"I guess it was blind jealousy.
Always wanted what I had."
Something very traumatic
happened to him,
and it was really bad.
I encountered several
disturbing things on my walk,
but two stood out.
First, the strange-looking
creature in the bedroom
with the bunk beds.
It had, like, these feather
things around its head.
It would change its face.
The body was kind of
like a jellyfish.
Next, I described
the dead teenage girl
attacking the living.
There's this deceased female,
and when people disturb her
she tends to lash out
and scratch them.
Amy, is this what
you saw?
Yes. That's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients,
for the first time.
Well, Amy, this is Linda and her
soon to be ex-husband, Robie.
And I got to tell you,
this investigation
was very frustrating for me
because the person who's
getting the worst of it here
refused to talk to me.
Linda's son, Nathan,
wanted absolutely
nothing to do with us.
Bottom line is I'm still glad
we took the case
because things here
are getting violent,
and Linda's afraid somebody
is going to get hurt.
So now that I introduced
Amy to you guys,
I'll have her describe
her walk for us.
So when I first got here
I suddenly felt
overcome with nausea.
I almost felt like I was just
going to start vomiting,
and I thought, okay,
if I feel this way,
then I would assume that
the living people here
would feel this way,
and feel it very often
because this was
absolutely debilitating.
I was nervous that I wouldn't be
able to even perform the walk.
Amy, you're hitting on one
of the reasons called us in.
Tell Amy about
the health issues, here.
Yeah.
Nausea, chest pains,
never feel good.
My son, Nathan, remember?
He'd always come in gray
and run to the bathroom
and start vomiting.
I mean, everybody never felt
good around here at all.
So when I walked
into the house
I felt an incredibly
terrible energy
that was emanating
from a dead guy
who, I think, was here
in the '80s or the '90s.
His energy just, kind of,
was absorbed by the home
and is, like,
pouring out of the walls.
The living people
would definitely be
affected by this energy,
and it's a lot of anger,
irritation.
I felt like you would hear
yelling and screaming.
And then, I felt like there was
a definite living male
who's here,
who resides here,
who is experiencing
this severe anger.
Nathan.
Okay.
So before we get into Nathan,
now is probably a good time
to tell you about one of
the main reasons we're here.
Now, Linda and Robie
are about to divorce
after 9 years of marriage,
and both of them
think it's because
the house changed
their personalities.
Everything was okay for a while
and then we just slowly,
we didn't realize it,
we would argue and bicker
and argue and bicker
over nothing.
Do you think it's the house
that did this to them?
It could be a result
of the negative energy.
And then you guys are
projecting this yelling
and screaming
into the walls as well,
and then it's all
playing back in.
As far as Nathan goes,
did you notice a personality
change in him?
Yes.
He always had a negative
answer to everything.
Nathan is very angry.
He's just so nasty.
Next, I came into your basement,
and I saw a depressed dead man.
He was in his late 50s,
early 60s.
It was kind of hard to tell.
It felt like he died here.
He died down here.
When I saw him
he had experienced
some kind of massive,
major loss,
and he was not
taking it well at all.
He was extremely distraught,
crying, depressed.
When I was around him I felt
anxiety, stress and chaos,
and it was kind of making me
feel a little crazy.
I'm pretty sure I know
who she's talking about.
I want to tell you about this
guy named Anthony Ventamiglia.
He was the first owner
of this house.
He and his mother lived here
for almost 30 years.
Now, Anthony's family had
a history of mental illness.
When he was little,
his dad was sent away
to an institution
and never came home.
He would wind up dying
in a mental hospital.
Wow.
Shortly after moving here,
Anthony started
to go crazy himself.
I talked to a local P.I.,
and he told me in the '80s
Anthony used to go out
in the streets
here in his underwear
with a knife
and threaten anybody
that came near him.
Now, on November 14th, 1987,
Anthony hung himself
right here in the basement.
He was 70.
This is a copy of his death
certificate.
After hearing this, you pretty
sure it's this guy
Anthony?
Yes.
More than likely
we have his energy
as the initial baseline
that was absorbed by the house.
So you guys move into a house,
and so you're walking into that,
and you're going to be
feeling that way.
Okay.
Anything else?
So the next person I encountered
was a deceased female
approximately 16 years of age.
When I encountered her,
side of her was, like, rotting
and, you know, kind of bony,
you know, like, decomposing.
And she was murdered,
and she told me that
the reason why she's here
is because she's trying
to build a nest,
and her nest happens
to be in the closets.
She will lash out
when you guys disturb her.
She scratches people
when she gets irritated.
I went into the other closet
up here.
I opened that,
and she freaked the...out,
and she whooshed
into my eye
and out my head,
and it was ice-cold.
She's always watching, always
watching, always listening,
so I felt like the living here
may feel like they're
always being watched.
And I also heard her crying.
It was outside.
I heard her crying.
You may see her
as a small shadow figure.
Now, I didn't come
across a homicide
that fits that description
in my research,
but a lot of the experiences
you're talking about,
these guys are having.
I seen that shadow person
in the kitchen.
You've also heard
strange noises, right?
I've heard them out back
in the woods.
I've heard screaming
and yelling.
Yeah.
Now, Linda, you told me
about scratches you had.
I've woken up with scratches,
like, on my arm
or maybe on my neck,
Nathan, on his leg.
He would be scratched
in the shower.
So when you guys said that
you had been scratched
and also heard growling
and howling down in the house,
here, I had a pest
control expert come in to see
if some kind of wildlife
could have been doing that.
You know what?
He checked this place
from top to bottom,
and he gave this place
a clean bill of health.
He said he couldn't even find
evidence of mouse droppings.
Wow.
Amy, did you get
a good look at this girl?
I had a sketch done.
This is a little creepy?
My God.
It kinda looks like me.
This is creepy, knowing that
somebody can sit there
and reach out and grab you
as you're walking by the closet.
Yeah.
I don't like it.
So I walked into all three of
the bedrooms in the house,
and I saw some pretty
disturbing things.
When I went through
the front door
I went first
to the right.
That's Eric's room.
Eric's room.
Yeah. I got a photo of Eric,
right here.
Wow.
Wait a minute.
How old is he?
He'll be 31 in August.
I saw this person sweating
and freaking out.
He was crying and he was,
basically, losing it,
and it just felt like everything
was closing in on him.
That sounds like Nathan.
Eric actually talked to me.
He told me he doesn't
experience anything, here.
You're his mom.
Is the crying and freaking
out sound like Eric?
No, no, no, no.
It doesn't.
That doesn't sound
like Eric at all.
It's a small house.
Is it possible you could
have been picking up
on Nathan's energy
in Eric's room?
Yeah.
It's a possibility.
Energy is energy,
and it's not always
just contained to one room.
So then I went into the bunk
bed room and, damn,
that room is active.
I saw a very strange
thing in there.
There was this long, like,
thing that slithers along,
goes onto the bunk
bed up on top.
It had, like, a clear,
jelly body.
So I think if somebody slept
on that top bunk, specifically,
I don't think
they'd get much sleep.
This is a lot of
uncomfortable energy.
I think they'd be
very irritated.
Okay. So, obviously,
Nathan's room, right?
Yeah.
Describe what Nathan told you
he sees in the room, there.
Yeah.
He said he sees something on
the floor that stares at him.
You know, kind of, just squats
and stares at him.
Eric has told me
he's heard him yell,
"Get away from me.
Leave me alone.
Just leave me alone,"
and then Eric will go by
and see him crying,
and just crying,
crying, crying.
Now, this is what's frustrating
about not being able
to talk to Nathan...
Yes.
Because he could have explained
to me what the hell this thing
really looked like to him.
Right.
I mean, what do you think
it looked like?
I did have a sketch done
of what I saw.
That's pretty messed up.
Holy...
That's awful.
My God.
No wonder he's freaked out.
Wow.
That's freaky, man.
I feel bad for the kid.
No wonder he's all...up.
That's freaky, man.
I feel bad for the kid.
No wonder he's all...up.
That must have been
what he saw, maybe,
squatting on the bottom
and staring at him?
Now, what I'm about to tell you
is extremely difficult.
Just listen, okay?
When I walked into
the master bedroom
I heard "dangerous telepath."
That's my room.
So am I in danger?
No.
What they're...
It means I'm
a dangerous telepath?
Yes.
What am I doing?
A lot of the haunting in this
house is coming from you.
You, inadvertently,
created this monster.
It's not real.
So this thing is made by Linda?
Yes.
And so I would say
maybe 50 percent
of what you're experiencing
is paranormal as far as,
yeah, the girl is pissed off
and scratching people,
yeah, there's a dead guy
wandering around,
but 50 percent
is living-created.
I don't want to cause
any harm to anybody.
Now, here's the thing is that
telepaths typically develop
that ability when they're
young, when they're children.
So you developed that ability,
but you moved into this house,
and I think that's where
the problem really starts.
Okay.
The residual energy is not
conducive to a person
with that type
of ability to be here.
And it starts with the crazy
guy that hung himself?
I believe so.
Now, Linda, I know you've always
had the best of intentions,
but from what Amy is saying,
it sounds like you're
haunting your family,
and, honestly, I've never
heard anything like this
in all the years
I'm working with her.
Now we got to figure out
to fix this mess,
so for that I'm going to
turn it over to Amy.
Okay. So you are dealing with
a lot of things, here.
You have a lot of negative
residual energy
that was placed here, I believe,
by the previous owner,
the individual
who killed himself.
So the first thing
that needs to be done
is the residual energy
needs to be removed.
The first thing that you
would need to do
is have a Reiki master come in
and cleanse the house,
and what they're
basically going to do
is remove the old
negative energy
and bring in positive energy.
As far as the dead girl
is concerned,
I'm going to take
her home with me.
I'm going to move her
on at home.
You got a freebie on that one.
Now, what about Linda
and her dangerous telepathy?
What I would like you to do is
Makko Ho exercises, stretches.
So its going to help you harness
and balance your energy
in a positive way.
So that will get rid of this
thing in his bedroom,
Nathan's bedroom?
Yes.
So once this is all done,
and if I do everything
and everything gets done,
will this house be okay?
Yeah.
It's like indescribable
how different it would be.
Your home will be
a completely different space.
You'll be a completely
different person.
You want to hold off
on that divorce,
or you want to do it anyway
and see what happens?
I can't answer that right now.
If I were you
I'd hold off on it.
You may be very different
in 6 months, is what I'm saying.
Yeah.
Give it some time.
Allow this healing to happen.
Allow your home to be
cleansed and renewed.
Now, Robie, you said you would
give her moral support.
What about cleaning up?
Would you help her with that?
Sure, I would.
All she's got to do is call.
She knows that.
I'll help her with anything
she needs help with, so.
I really hope Linda
contacts a Reiki master
to remove the negative
residual energy from her home
so she can focus on herself
and learn how to get
her abilities under control.
If she does that, the family
might finally be able
to find the peace
they've been hoping for.