Something doesn't want us here.
I feel like I'm being
strangled by human hands.
Somebody grabbed me.
You shouldn't have had
a park here for children.
Why would anybody build
an amusement park
out in the middle
of nowhere?
People are being
brutally murdered.
We found these children
dead, scalped.
I don't feel safe here.
I just hear death,
too much death.
This is not a good situation.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's death here.
Don't want to
go down there.
I see dead people.
They hide in the walls
and they watch.
I speak to dead people.
She's definitely
a serial killer.
And they speak to me.
She's going
to torture them.
But there's only one way
to know if my findings are real.
They were all murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
So, is this the only time
you've been physically attacked?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
There's no question
in my mind
that he was talking
about Satan.
It's my job to reveal them.
Who do you think
possessed you?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end...
Well, you're not gonna
want to see this.
...when we uncover
if it's safe for you to stay...
Hell no!
...or time to get out.
Everyone is in jeopardy.
I'm in Lake Shawnee,
West Virginia.
It's about 90 miles
south of Charleston.
I got a call from a guy
named Chris.
Now, he owns an abandoned
amusement park,
and it's been
in his family for years.
Now, here is the problem.
The activity is bad,
and it's getting worse.
Chris thinks it's just
a matter of time
before someone gets hurt.
Hopefully,
we can help this guy out.
I'm going to start
with the easy part,
removing any information
in the house,
but this is a huge property
with an abandoned theme park,
so I need to cover
any signs or memorials,
which could influence
Amy's findings.
When I'm done, the location will
be ready for tonight's walk.
There's something bad here
in the ground.
It's, like, not good.
It's not pure.
It puts off a vibe,
a bad, bad vibe.
Now, Chris, when we spoke
on the phone,
you had a real sound
of concern in your voice.
What's going on?
My mother lives on my property.
Activity is picking up.
I just want to make sure
that my family
and also the volunteers
and the tourists
that come here
to visit the property,
I want to make sure
everybody is just safe.
So, Chris, you got to
help me out here.
I notice it was
an amusement park,
but I see a rusted out
Ferris Wheel.
What do you do
with this place?
So we give a history tour,
and we do ghost-hunting tours.
Listen, I don't know how
Amy is going to feel about that,
but just be ready.
She may ask you to cut
the ghost-hunting stuff out.
Do me a favor.
Give me a list of what's
going on as far as activity.
Guests or volunteers,
they're hearing voices,
seeing
full-body apparitions.
They are being
pushed and shoved.
Chris, you mentioned
on the phone that this place
has been
in your family a while.
My father had bought
this property in 1985.
His dream was to restore it
back to an amusement park.
So now, Chris, your father,
is he still around?
No, he passed away
in 2010.
He died from cancer,
but this is a picture of him.
Now, did your father die
on the property?
No, he lived here for
the last 10 years of his life,
but he died
in a hospital.
Okay,
so besides your mother,
any other family
members live here?
My brother lived
on the property,
but he died
from a heart attack.
How old was he?
He was 51.
And this is
a picture of him?
Picture of my brother.
I got to ask the question,
you don't think anything
with the paranormal
activity had anything to do
with any of the deaths here,
do you?
I really can't tell.
That's why I called you guys.
Okay.
Why don't you
just cut your losses
and just sell
this property?
I'm sure you can do
pretty well by selling it.
Because it's too important
to my father,
and it's too important
to the community.
All right,
so this was your dad's dream,
to restore this
to an amusement park.
I mean, what about you?
Do you want to do that?
We pretty much let the land
do what it wants.
Okay.
If the land wants to create
back into an amusement park,
we'll let it happen,
but if it doesn't,
we just follow the land.
I have no idea
what you're talking about,
but it's your place.
It's your property.
All right.
So what do you think
is causing the activity here?
I feel that my father
and my brother is here.
I mean, you don't think
your father and your brother
are causing any of the pushing
and shoving that's going on?
Absolutely not.
I think there's
other activity here.
Okay.
I'm trying to focus,
and it's hard because
there's probably at least
12 conscious entities
around here.
I don't feel safe here because
something doesn't want us here.
Obviously, there were
Native Americans here
because they're saying that,
"This is, like, spiritual,"
you know,
"A sacred place for us.
Don't take it."
And we did anyways.
And so, Chris, this is
where your mom lives?
Yes, she lives on
the property by herself.
I mean, this is in
the middle of nowhere.
I mean, you got to be
worried about her
even though you live close.
Yeah, she'll call me
late at night,
and I just come down to check
on her, make sure she's safe.
So now, we talked
a lot about your guests,
your volunteers
having experiences.
What about you?
Have you had any?
Yeah.
Sometimes, whenever I'm in the
park doing a little bit of work,
I'll catch images
out of the side of my eye,
just like shadows.
So what makes you think
it's not an actual shadow
from somebody
or something?
It's a big lot.
Nobody is allowed on it.
Okay, anything else?
One time, there was
a paranormal investigator.
He came to the park,
and he stepped inside
of one of the ticket booths
we had here.
- Okay.
- And whenever he stepped inside,
he'd come flying
backwards out of it,
and it looked like something
had shoved him out.
Listen, I run into
a lot of these people,
and they tend to exaggerate
a lot of things.
The way he flew out
of that ticket booth,
I don't think he could
have done it by himself.
Okay, so it looked
legit to you.
To me, it did.
Okay, so you've seen somebody
get physically attacked.
Anything like that
ever happen to you?
Yeah, whenever I was over
at the swing or the Ferris Wheel
and mowing grass,
I could feel a pressure
on my shoulders
and around my back.
Now, does this happen every time
you're out there working?
It's happened several times
but not every time.
So it sounds like you've had
some pretty scary experiences.
Now, is being here
really worth the trouble?
Well, my father had experiences
while he was here,
and he wanted to protect
the place
for the living
and the deceased.
- Okay.
- I'm the same way.
I want to protect the place
to keep it safe for both.
I'm feeling, like,
sick and nervous.
I feel like I'm being
strangled by human hands.
It's the Native Americans.
They really don't want me
to keep going.
I'm seeing, like, blood.
Where are you seeing
the blood?
It's, like, dripping.
It's on all of the chains.
The Native Americans caused
something bad to happen.
So, Jewell, I was talking
to your son, Chris,
and he thinks you may not
be safe with all this activity.
Do you agree with that?
- No.
- You don't?
Chris wants me to go live
with him, but I won't do it.
All right,
so have you had any experiences?
Personally, yes.
Okay, so can you tell me
about some of them?
There's things
always moving.
Sometimes, it's a pencil, keys,
just papers, sometimes.
I misplace stuff
all the time.
I mean, are you sure
it's nothing like that?
No, there is things
that I misplace, too.
Okay.
But these things will be things
that I just put in a place,
and then I walk out and walk
back in, and they're gone.
Okay, so anything else?
Yes.
I've seen an apparition
of an Indian warrior.
Why do you say it's a warrior?
How do you know that?
Because of the way
he's dressed.
He has no shirt, and he had some
type of instrument in his hand.
Okay, so it appeared
like he was ready for battle.
Right.
Kind of brushed
the side of my face.
I think, if I walked in,
and there was an Indian
warrior holding a weapon,
I think I'd be
a little uneasy about it.
Maybe, you would be.
- But you weren't.
- No.
I feel like maybe
they've experienced stuff
from the Native Americans.
I'm feeling like
someone who's alive,
they're panicking
about things being moved...
and I do feel like there
would be depression here.
I want to extend
my condolences.
I understand you lost
your husband and your son
while they were
living here.
Yes.
When you guys were
all living together,
did they have experiences?
Yes, they both did.
Jewell, your husband's passion
was turning this place
into another amusement park
and making it work.
But when that didn't happen,
how did he take it?
I think he thought
we were failures,
that we couldn't get
the business going,
anything working for us.
Do you think that had
something to do with,
maybe, whatever is here
doesn't want
another amusement
park built.
Yes.
I think that whatever is here
wanted to be the attraction.
I don't think
it wanted anything else.
I understand your son's death
was pretty sudden.
Chris told me
he suffered a heart attack.
He was a young man.
He was about 51?
Yeah.
Do you think the paranormal
had anything to do
with your
other son's death?
Never thought about that.
There was a living person
associated with the property,
as having heart issues.
Someone has had
a heart attack, male.
It's a result of being
exposed to the energy.
I believe it stems
from the Native Americans
who don't want anybody there.
I just hear death,
too much death.
So, Christian, I was talking
to your dad today.
I understand
you might have had
some scary stuff
happen to you here.
- Yes.
- All right.
Can you tell me
about one of them?
When I walk around here,
sometimes I feel like there's
people walking behind me.
All over the place
or in certain spots?
It's at random times
in certain spots.
Do you hear
anything behind you?
I feel like I hear footsteps
and people walking in the grass.
Okay.
Anything else happen?
When I was down over
at the swings,
and I felt like
somebody grabbed me
and held my arms
to my body.
Okay, you mean, like, somebody
grabbed both of your...
Like that?
Yes.
So when you got grabbed,
do you think
it was somebody trying
to tell you something?
Yes, like there's a bad spirit
maybe in front of me,
so they were trying to stop me
and make me turn around.
Now, would you ever stay here
by yourself overnight?
No, not really.
Okay, what about staying
at grandma's home?
- No.
- No?
Okay.
This is weird.
There's something trying
to protect the living here.
It's not human,
and it was very, very large,
at least eight feet tall.
It was behind us on the road.
It had, like, robes on.
You know what's weird is that
that thing that's here
with the robes is not
Native American, but it's old.
He's more trying to
keep people away
because bad things
happen to people,
so I don't think he's
exactly bad, but he scares me.
After meeting with Chris
and his family,
I started talking to people
who had spent time at the park.
I never feel alone.
It always feels like
there's somebody around me,
with me, that feeling
of being watched.
It is definitely
an uneasy feeling for me.
And each one of them
has some damn good reasons
to be terrified.
I saw an apparition of a man
walking right here on the road,
and he take four to five steps,
and he vanished into nowhere.
But one thing
they all had in common,
they were seeing shadows,
lots of them.
There was a time where
I've seen a shadow figure.
It was like
a figure of a man.
There was this overwhelming
sense of anxiety,
and I just felt like
I had to get out of there.
I'm trying to focus.
There is this other thing,
a child,
a male between
8 and 9 years of age.
He has taken it upon himself
to be, like,
a guard or something,
and he's, like,
watching all the time.
I think that people would
absolutely mistake him for,
like, a shadow person because
he's completely solid black.
Like, he feels like
it's stronger
than just looking like a person.
They shouldn't have had
a park here for children.
I don't like it.
It makes me uncomfortable.
Like, I'm scared,
feel like I'm being watched.
There's a bad person here.
I know it's a male.
This person is crazy
and isn't thinking straight,
anger, lots of anger.
Like, I want to throw up.
It's almost like
he blanks out from the rage.
I don't like this.
All right, I'm going to start
my investigation
with the obvious question,
who the hell built an amusement
park in the middle of nowhere,
and why did it shut down?
I'm heading back
to the property to meet
with a local historian
who says it's a story
I'm definitely going to
want to know about.
Pat, I want to thank you for
helping me out with this case.
So why would anybody build
an amusement park
out in the middle of nowhere?
It is the intersection
of two main roads
where there are
a lot of people coal mining
that had nothing to do.
Who opened this place?
A man named Conley Snidow,
and here's what it looked
like in its heyday.
He opened it in 1926.
The biggest attraction
was the swimming pool.
Over here
was a fishing hole.
There was paddle boating.
There were canoe rides, and then
right here, where we were,
was the bath house,
which had Saturday-night dances.
- Are you from this area?
- I am.
I came here a lot
when I was small.
You mentioned on the phone
there was some information
I was going to
want to know about.
What did you mean
by that?
There were three deaths
that were connected
with Lake Shawnee.
- All right.
So let's go through
these deaths one by one.
What was the first one?
In 1927, Conley Snidow's
3- year-old daughter, Eloise,
was killed at the hotel
where they lived.
One day, she ran for
the elevator to get on it.
She grabbed for the floor
of the elevator,
and it pulled her up and crushed
her between that and the doors.
That's a pretty
sad death.
What about
the second one?
Second death
actually happened here
at Lake Shawnee
in the swimming pool.
It was a 6-year-old child
named Wayne Harman.
That happened in 1961.
Evidently, he jumped in,
and no one paid attention,
and someone brushed up
against his body
at the bottom
of the pool,
and they came up
and yelled to the lifeguard,
and they pulled him out,
but it was too late.
What about
the third one?
The third one happened
July 3, 1966,
right in the pool here,
John Richard Tolley,
who was 11 years old.
Here's an article
about it,
and he was stuck in the drain
at the bottom of the pool.
What a shame.
So in the matter
of five years,
he has two drownings
in the same pool.
That was the straw that broke
the camel's back
for Mr. Conley Snidow.
He closed it down,
never reopened it.
Anybody who can relate to
what those parents went through,
it was him.
- Absolutely.
It must have weighed very
heavily on his conscious for him
to close down a park
that was making money for him.
Right.
So, Pat,
I wouldn't normally ask
a person like you
this question,
but you told me you
came here as a kid.
Now, was there anything that
happened that you can't explain?
Yes.
I was swimming right here
as a 5-year-old,
and something grabbed me
by the bottom of my leg
and pulled me under,
and I went down into a hole.
My father had to pull me up
by the hair on my head.
Any thoughts about what might
have happened to you here or...
Something grabbed me.
It felt like a hand.
When I heard about
those children,
the first thing that
came into my head was,
"What grabbed them
and pulled them under?"
The water repels me.
There's been losses.
I'm feeling tragedies
associated with this.
I think that people died there
when it was a park.
I'm seeing two, so I don't know
if two people got hurt
or they died.
- How recent?
- '70s?
maybe it is '60s.
Native Americans caused
accidents to happen.
It's just horrible.
So I'm walking over
to meet a genealogist
who was doing some research
on this place for me,
and he came up
with something big.
Turns out, the original
owners of this land
got ambushed
by local Native Americans,
and it was a bloodbath.
Well, Dan, I appreciate you
helping me out with this case.
You said on the phone
there was a pretty brutal
Indian attack
on this land.
That's correct.
Okay, so before we even
get to that,
what do you know
about the original owners?
The original owner was a man
by the name of Mitchell Clay.
He was from
Eastern Virginia.
He was a wealthy
tobacco planter, a slave owner,
and in 1775,
Mitchell Clay, his wife, Phoebe,
and their 14 children
moved onto the land,
and this would have
been the cabin
that they built
and lived in.
Okay,
so they settled here.
What about
local Indian tribes?
There were no permanent
local Indian settlements here.
However, the Shawnee Indians
would pass through here
periodically to hunt.
Did Indians ever inhabit
this land at some point?
In the 1400s,
there were certainly
Indian settlements here.
In fact, the current landowner,
back in the late '80s,
accidentally excavated
a grave site
just on this corner
of the property over here,
21 sets of remains,
and 13 were children,
and it's possible that there
are many more remains here.
Okay, so let's get
to the attack.
What happened?
In the fall of 1783,
Mitchell Clay
and his two oldest sons
had gone hunting.
They'd left two of the boys,
Ezekiel and Bartley,
to build a fence around
some of their fields.
Shawnee Indians fired a shot
and killed Bartley on the spot,
only 17 years old.
Bartley's sister, Tabitha,
rushed to his aid.
She wound up being
stabbed repeatedly,
and she died
on this very spot.
Once Bartley and Tabitha
were dead,
the Indians scalped
both of them and then grabbed
and kidnapped their 16-year-old
brother, Ezekiel.
Short time later,
Mitchell Clay returned
with his oldest sons.
He found his children dead
and scalped.
What does he do?
He then gathers a posse,
and they pursue the Indians
who had taken Ezekiel
about 150 miles
into Ohio.
Does he find them?
He finds them,
but he finds them too late.
By the time
he catches up with them,
they have tortured
young Ezekiel
and burned him
at the stake.
All right.
Mitchell Clay,
three dead kids.
- Yes, sir.
- And he comes home?
No.
He sells the farm,
and then they move
many miles away
back into Virginia,
and he lives there the rest
of his life with his wife,
and they die there.
There's a bunch
of happy people.
They were all white.
It's all good vibes.
You know, people
are singing and dancing.
There's, like, a covered-wagon
thing, I think 1760s.
Then, the Native Americans
got really mad,
and then it kind of
went a little nuts.
And I'm hearing
screaming and yelling
and people running around.
They were caught off guard.
People are being
brutally murdered.
Then I'm with this mother,
and I think I want to die,
want to kill myself.
It's survivor's guilt.
There's a lot of pain here.
These souls are not at rest.
For more information
about the show
and if you need us
to investigate unexplained
activity in your home...
Please visit
travelchannel.com/thedeadfiles.
Click on
"Help Me, Dead Files!"
to submit your story,
and we'll help if we can.
So far, I've got a client
who fears
for the safety of his mother,
volunteers, and guests
on a property
where two kids drowned,
two other kids were murdered,
and where Native American
remains were found,
but I want to see
if there's anything else.
Searching through old records,
I found an article
about a brutal murder
that took place in 1935.
Turns out, it happened
right along Chris' property.
So I called the local cops,
and they don't want to
talk to me about this case,
but my old friend
Matt McGrew does.
I'm heading over
to meet with him now,
and he says this murder turned
out to be a crime of passion.
So, Matt,
it's good to see you again.
I appreciate you helping out
with this case.
Now, what do you know
about this perp?
Well, his name is
James Craft Belcher.
He's a local guy,
25 years old.
Belcher,
the name sounds familiar.
I think it came up
in my title search.
His grandparents actually
owned the property
in the early 1900s.
So there's
a good possibility
the perp spent time
on my client's property.
Definitely, and he would
have grown up there.
All right, so what do we know
about the victim?
He actually was seeing
a woman named Myrtle Taylor.
She's 19 years old.
She's a local girl.
They've grown up
in the same area.
All right, so now, take me
to the night of the murder.
On the night
of May 11, 1935,
Belcher goes into
a restaurant and sees
Myrtle eating dinner
with another man,
so as you might imagine,
they start fighting about it.
Okay.
And she doesn't
want to leave.
You know,
she can tell he's upset,
but he forces her
to leave with him
and forces her
into the car.
I don't feel good, and I am
getting, like, a pain, like,
here and here,
really bad, actually.
I think somebody got hit there.
I think it's a woman.
I think between
14 and 16 years of age,
she seemed to be from
a long time ago, like the '40s.
I feel like
there's a bad person here.
I don't know who this person is.
I know it's a male,
and she knows him.
Do you know
what happened?
I know that his intentions
were not good.
Okay, so this guy basically
kidnapped his own girlfriend.
So what happened?
Somewhere along
Rock-Shawnee Road,
which is right along
your client's property,
they stop the car,
and they get out.
He pulls out a gun, and he
shoots her in the head twice.
I'm assuming she gets killed
right there and then.
No, he puts her back
into the car.
She's still alive, and
he drives her to the hospital,
but obviously, she's basically
in a coma at this point.
She dies
a few hours later.
Does he confess to it?
He goes to trial, and he
actually makes an insanity plea.
The jury doesn't buy it.
They convict him.
- All right.
So did this guy ever get parole,
or did he die in prison?
No, he dies in prison in 1993
when he was 85.
I've seen this
a thousand times.
I mean, it's a crime of passion,
a lot of rage here.
That's right.
It's a shame
he never hung, though.
That guy that she knew
was attacking her.
God, it hurts.
There was blood in her mouth,
and the pain was horrible,
and she was, like, basically
going into shock at that time.
This female, I believe,
was abducted or murdered
by this man.
The sun is, like,
just starting to go down
when all of this happened,
and there's, like,
a lot of adrenaline and anger,
Rage, just blind rage.
During my walk, I saw several
disturbing things,
but the teenage girl who
was murdered really stood out.
She was younger.
I'd place her between
14 and 16 years of age.
Her eyes were more
rounded in shape.
Her hair was brown
or dark blonde.
Amy,
is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal
our findings to each other
and our clients
for the first time.
Well, Amy,
let's start with the obvious.
I mean, I'm sure
you figured out by now
that this used to be
an amusement park.
Chris owns it here
with his mom, Jewell,
who lives
on the property alone.
We'll get into the reasons
why this place means
so much to them later,
but for now, Chris called us in
because he's not sure
if it's safe for his mom
to be here alone
or for anybody else
that comes onto the property.
Now that Amy knows
a little bit about you guys,
I'll ask her to describe
her walk with us.
This walk was really
overwhelming
because I encountered
at least 12 conscious
entities that are here.
It would take all night
to go into each one of them,
so I'm just going
to focus on the ones
specifically who can directly
influence the living.
The first individual
I encountered, actually,
a little boy,
I would say he was about 8 or 9,
and what he's doing is
he's taken it upon himself
to kind of, like,
be a guard here
and watch everybody's
coming and going.
Obviously, I think you would
feel watched by him.
You might be able to see him,
like a blocky shadow person.
Everybody I spoke to
and interviewed
had the experience of feeling
watched or seeing shadows.
Now, you told me you saw
shadows, right, Chris?
Yes, out of the side
of my eye,
I would catch a shadow
every once in a while.
So, Chris, do me a favor.
Tell Amy how your son feels
like he's being followed.
Yeah, whenever he goes
around the park,
he feels like somebody
is following him,
and then whenever he stops,
he hears two more
steps behind him.
Interesting.
There was another dead
male here who was an adult.
What I got mainly off of him
was a lot of adrenaline,
a lot of anger,
and a lot of rage.
If a living person was exposed
to that energy consistently,
they could feel intense anxiety
like they're being stalked.
I interviewed a guy named Bob
who does volunteer work
for you on the property.
Now, he told me he got hit
with some serious anxiety
by the old school bus
that's right over here,
but it was so bad that he had
to run off the property.
Wow.
Next, I ran into a very old
and very strange thing.
It's, like, 8 feet tall,
and it has all these robes on.
I was really uncomfortable
at first.
So he's actually someone
who's trying to warn
and protect, which I found
freaking fascinating.
Well, let me ask you
a question because
when I spoke to your son,
he told me he felt
like he got grabbed.
Now, he told me he felt like it
was somebody protecting him
to stop from going
into a bad area.
Could be.
You told me you get touched
while you're on your tractor.
Yeah, I feel a little bit
of pressure
on my shoulders
and stuff,
like something
is behind me.
Now, who do you think that could
be, touching his shoulders?
There's a lot of people.
Possibly, your dad.
Could be.
One thing that I got
throughout my walk
was the overwhelming feeling
of sadness and despair
because of the deaths
over the years,
and I got that people
did die when it was a park.
I got that two deaths
specifically, I thought,
happened in the '60s.
Frankly, I was like,
"Who would build this here?"
Like, the energy is not good.
It's funny because when
I showed up here, I was like,
"Who the hell would build this
place in the middle of nowhere?"
When this was an amusement park,
it was called Lake Shawnee,
and it was built by a guy named
Conley Snidow back in 1926.
I got a photo here
of what it looked like
when it was pretty much in
its heyday as an amusement park.
Now, you said you got a couple
of deaths in the '60s.
Well, get this,
back in June of 1961,
a 6-year-old boy
named Wayne Harman
drowned in that pond
right over here.
Here's an article on it.
Then, in July of 1966,
an 11-year-old boy
named John Richard Tolley
drowned in the same pond.
Now, the guilt was
so much for Snidow
that he ended up closing
this place for good
at the end of that summer.
Now, I almost never ask experts
if they've had experiences,
but the historian I spoke
to used to come here
when she was a kid
and swim in the pond
until one time she felt
like somebody grabbed her foot
inside the pond
and pulled her down.
Now, she almost drowned,
but she's totally
convinced to this day
that it was a paranormal event.
Interesting.
I think now is probably
a good time to tell Amy
why this property is
so important to the family.
It meant the world.
Now, Chris' father,
Jewell's husband,
bought the property in 1985.
His dream was to own it
and restore it,
but nothing worked right,
and so finally,
we just had to
kind of give up.
Now, would you mind telling Amy
about how your husband passed.
It ended up being
colon cancer.
And when he passed,
he was still living here.
Right.
Chris, you're trying to preserve
your father's dream.
Yes.
I think our intention is
to preserve the property
just the way it is.
So I know that you guys have
paranormal investigators
and all of this
kind of thing.
We do.
Anything else?
I ran into
a deceased female,
and I would have put her
between 14 and 16 years of age.
She seemed to be
from a while ago.
There was a male
that she runs into,
and I think that
this male killed her.
Now, I think
you're describing the murder
I came across in my research.
Now, the killer was a local guy
named James Belcher
who was 25 years old.
His grandparents actually
owned this property
in the early 1900s.
Belcher was separated
from his wife
and had a mistress
by the name of Myrtle Taylor.
She was only 19 years old.
And on May 11, 1935,
Belcher walked into a restaurant
and sees her with
another guy, having dinner.
Well, he freaks out,
and he basically kidnaps her
and forces her into the car.
Now, what he does is pulls over
right on the road right here.
Belcher grabs a gun and shoots
her twice in the head.
Holy...
I actually have a photo
of both of them.
Is it possible
that's who you saw?
I had a sketch done
of the girl I saw.
I mean,
the nose, the eyes.
I mean, the photo is not great,
but it's very possible
that this is the same girl.
It looks exactly alike.
So, Mom, you think
it could be the same girl?
I do.
You can see it, yeah.
The mouth, to me.
Another thing that I saw
was very disturbing,
and it took place
a long time ago,
and it was near
a covered wagon.
Everybody is happy.
There's kids.
They built a bonfire,
singing and dancing,
having a good old time,
and then I'm hearing
screaming and yelling,
and I got that it was,
like, really awful murders,
and I think it was safe
to assume that Native Americans
had committed this attack
on what looked like
a white family.
I knew that these people
had been caught off guard.
They totally did not
expect this to happen.
There was a thing about
the Native Americans
being all pissed off because
they felt this was sacred land.
Do you have a time frame?
The 1750s or '60s.
Wow.
I think I know exactly
what you're talking about
and what you saw.
This property is the site
of the most brutal Indian attack
in the history of this area.
In 1774,
a guy name Mitchell Clay
bought over 800 acres
and moved onto the property here
with his wife, Phoebe,
and 14 kids.
Now, they were the first
white settlers
in this part of the country.
I got a picture of the house
they lived in, actually.
Now, in 1783, Clay went hunting
with his two oldest sons
and left everybody else home.
As soon as he left,
a group of Shawnee Indians
stormed the property.
First, they shot and killed
Clay's 17-year-old son, Bartley.
Then they slashed their teenage
daughter, Tabitha, to death.
Then they scalped
both these kids
and then kidnapped their
16-year-old brother, Ezekiel,
and took him to Ohio.
When Clay found out about this,
he rounded up a posse,
and he went to Ohio
to try and save his son,
but by the time he got there,
it was too late.
Ezekiel had been tortured
and burned at the stake.
Holy...
They mentioned the attack
was retaliation for the land.
The expert I spoke to told me
that the Shawnee Indians
didn't actually live here
when the attack happened,
but they did have a settlement
here way back in the 1400s.
In fact, back in 1989, Chris'
family was excavating land here,
and they uncovered human remains
that belonged to those Indians.
They found more than 20 bodies,
13 of which were kids.
Now, there's a good reason
to believe that
there were more bodies
still here.
I actually have a photo of one
of the remains they uncovered.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
It's hard to believe that
something like this happened
on this piece of land.
Maybe, it is an amusement park
for the dead.
So now, are these
Native Americans still here?
Yes.
They're upset and active.
They didn't want us here
doing the investigation.
Possibly, at times, they would
make the living here
feel intimidated and nervous.
Unfortunately, one of the things
that they were indicating
that they'd resorted to
is making the living sick here,
putting emotions
onto the living people,
trying to get the living
to hurt one another
and causing accidents,
and one of the things
that I got was
that a male associated
with the property
was having a heart attack
or heart issues.
I was hoping we wouldn't
have to talk about this,
but, Jewell, can you
tell Amy about your son?
He had 26 heart attacks
before he passed away
with a massive
heart attack.
And he was, like, 51?
And he lived on the property
at the time.
- Yes.
- Wow.
I actually have a photo of her
son that they provided me with.
Wow.
Okay.
I saw him during my walk.
Does it make you happy
or kind of sad?
Makes me --
I'm okay with it.
I think he's here protecting
and protecting my mother.
All right,
so what else?
Well, then, I went over
to the house.
And that's where
you live, Jewell.
Yes.
I got that the Native Americans
are very active there,
and because of that,
I think that there would
be experiences sometimes.
I got that they can show
themselves and interact
with their surroundings.
I did see something being
moved around in the house.
Tell Amy what goes on.
Sometimes, I'll lay something
down and go to another room,
and when I come back,
it's in a different place.
Sometimes, it's gone, and then
a couple days, it shows back up.
Now, you had told me
you saw an apparition
of a Native American warrior.
Yes.
He had no clothes, was
holding something in his hand.
The big question, I think,
is, what do these Indians
want from these guys?
So basically,
the Native Americans believe
that this is their land,
and they want it back, and
they don't want anybody here.
Their goal is
to get them off this land.
I do know that they did possibly
affect your son's health,
so that's troublesome.
I feel
that we need to maybe see
if there's some way
we can resolve this.
If it's moving her off the
property, that's what we'll do.
I don't feel it's me
that they want off the property.
So, Chris, I know that one thing
you're passionate about
is honoring your dad's memory
and keeping his dream alive,
and that means making this park
safe for volunteers, guests
and, most of all, your mom,
but to see what
that's going to take,
I'm going to turn
it over to Amy.
It's really hard
for me to say,
"Stop doing events
and investigations here,"
because I feel like
it should be investigated.
What I'm thinking is maybe
that you kind of really screen
who's coming here
and why
because you really
don't want antagonistic people
that are, like, you know,
"We're going to drink and party,
and we're going to,
like, hunt ghosts."
You know what I mean?
And I think that after
every event
and every investigation,
an offering needs to be left
because the Native Americans
do not feel respected
at this time.
So now, when they make
the offerings,
do they have to say anything?
Is there any kind of a ritual?
They'll be guided
as to what to bring.
Like, these Native Americans
are very hands-on, I guess,
guiding what they want
and how they want it.
You're nodding your head
yes like you know
what she's talking about.
Yes.
Do you know what
she's talking about?
I do.
Then, you guys are ahead
of the game, then.
What about these
physical attacks
that are happening
to people that come here?
Will that stop with
the offerings?
Yeah, the offerings
are going to help a lot.
Okay, so what else
do they need to do?
As far as the dead here,
I would like to see at least
the murdered girl moved on.
You just need to have
a medium come and call out
to her and move her on.
My question now is, are you
going to take Amy's advice
and do what
she's telling you?
- Absolutely.
- Yes.
And I know 100% that they
will be followed through with.
I think it's a big relief
that we know at least
we can keep
everybody safe.
Okay, how do you think
your father would have felt?
I think he's pleased.
I know he's happy.
I can feel him.
That takes a burden
off of him.
It takes a burden
off of us.
It just totally
relieves me.
I'm just so happy,
and I know he's happy.
Chris and Jewell have a lot
of work ahead of them,
but if they contact a medium
to remove the dead girl,
screen people
who want to visit the park
and make consistent offerings
to the Native Americans,
Chris will be able to keep
his dad's dream alive,
and maybe, one day, Lake Shawnee
will be back open for business.