David Coleman.
Tonight on "Dead Files Revisited"...
****!
A second look at some of Amy and
Steve's most terrifying cases.
- That didn't freak you out?
- New information...
I was the most afraid
that I've ever been.
Startling revelations.
I was part of the problem.
First, a return to
Huntington, West Virginia...
I did hear, "murder".
Where a dentist struggles
to save his practice.
He said, "get out of here".
And Amy and Steve uncover the
truth behind a mysterious death.
He killed her.
Then, we travel back
to Garrett, Indiana...
I am scared to death to
be down here right now.
To reopen a case so disturbing...
Something's in bed with them.
It pushed a client over the edge.
Did they listen to Amy or
continue to live in fear?
There's no way that you can prepare
for whatever Amy's gonna tell you.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing's, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people.
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her?
It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were
ghosts in this house.
Like most people, I'm no
fan of going to the dentist,
and our investigation into the office of
Dr. Grimes in Huntington, West Virginia,
didn't make me any more comfortable.
The doc had concerns that paranormal
activity might ruin his business,
but what disturbed me was how attached
he'd become to the ghost of a little girl.
And after what Amy and I
found out in our investigation,
I'm pretty sure the doc
will never be the same again.
So, Dr. Grimes, what's going on?
We have a problem here.
I've been in this building
for nearly 40 years.
Starting out, things were just
noises that could be dismissed,
but I no longer have just sounds.
I have visual things going on.
As far as your employees go, I
mean, how are they dealing with it?
They're afraid of it. They
won't go upstairs at night.
I called Steve and Amy because,
it really bothered me that my staff were
afraid to come upstairs in my own office.
And the fact that I can't seem to do
anything about it is even more of a problem
because I'm supposed to be able to
handle these problems, and I'm not.
It is, after all, my building.
Are you concerned that whatever's
going on here is dangerous?
Yes. It's my concern that I could
actually frighten my patients away.
I...
Have this elderly gentleman with me.
He's really tall, and...
Something happened,
but I'm not sure what.
I knew it was a bad sign, seeing that old
man waiting for me outside the location.
He wanted to keep me from going in,
but I wasn't going to let him stop
me from figuring out the truth.
Something happened in his office.
I did hear, "murder,
murder, murder, murder".
Okay, so what's going on in here?
This was a place where I started
seeing the vision of a little girl.
In fact, she was standing right
there at that door on the stairwell.
- Could you describe her for me?
- Yes, I can.
As a matter of fact, I've painted
a painting of her several years ago,
and I have it right here.
As you can see, she's very sad.
I have tried very hard
to reach out to her.
Because of the empathy I feel for her.
I've interviewed a lot of clients
who say they've tried to
communicate with ghosts.
And usually, things
don't turn out so good.
I hate the stairwell.
I hate it.
Something in that space...
It's not good at all.
With every step I
took up those stairs...
I could feel my stomach
turning in knots.
I know now it's because I was
about to see something disturbing.
Someone, like, died, like, right here.
You know, she's, like, a teenager.
And her heart's pounding.
Her heart's pounding.
So much pain, and...
She broke her legs or something.
I was walking through this hallway
late one evening, turning things off,
and a voice came to me...
a man's voice, very deep.
And he said, "get out of here".
He goes up and down these stairs.
You can hear him stomping, literally.
Because of his aggression, I'm concerned
that he might actually hurt somebody.
So, she died, like, right here.
This guy is laughing.
He's just laughing.
I sense the large, angry man
was the dead girl's father.
And listening to him spew his hatred,
there was no question he
completely resented her.
"She was a useless ****.
I didn't have a use for her anymore".
He killed her.
****
What the ****?
What happened?
He poked me.
He doesn't want me to
really talk about it.
Because he got mad and ran away.
After talking to Dr. Grimes' daughter,
I found out his whole family
had seen the same little girl.
So, I decided to see if someone outside
the family could corroborate their story.
I tracked down one of the
doc's former employees.
She was reluctant to
meet me at the office,
and after hearing her
story, I don't blame her.
The doctor himself, I mean,
he explained some bizarre things
that he's experienced here.
Now, how about yourself?
I was assisting Dr. Grimes
in doing a root canal.
And I glanced up.
And there was a girl standing
right behind where you're standing.
I will never forget it.
I can see it's upsetting for
you to even be in the building.
This room doesn't bother me as bad...
As a room upstairs.
I went up to get a file, and I could
feel someone in that room with me.
- Did you see anything?
- No.
I just felt it.
I felt like something came over me.
Like...
Like someone was watching me.
Coming up next...
This guy is just laughing.
Amy confronts a sadistic spirit.
He tossed her over.
And in our second investigation...
- What's coming in?
- Death.
Ordinary people face off against evil.
I was the most afraid
that I've ever been.
Looking into the history of
Dr. Grimes' dental practice,
it wasn't long before I
uncovered a death in the building.
According to newspaper
articles from 1929,
a 21-year-old girl named
Lavina Wall died after a fall.
The details about her death were vague.
So I met with an expert who ended up
changing my whole perspective on the case.
Lavina was sort of a woman of mystery.
Her story was a very tragic one.
Her mother, Bernice...
Was married to this
gentleman named Cyrus.
Okay.
Apparently, he liked
to drink, and when he
was drunk, he liked to beat on his wife.
And then in 1913, Lavina, her
elder sister, and her mother...
Left and moved into the duplex
on 20th street in Huntington.
- Where Dr. Grimes' office is now?
- Exactly.
We don't know if the father ever
came back or tried to find them or...
We don't know.
I feel like there's...
People that are arguing.
There's a male, and he's a liar,
and there is the two ladies.
And he's chasing...
Like, he's following them.
Every time I saw the dead girl's
father, he was surrounded by violence.
And she wasn't the
only target of his rage.
His wife...
Ran away, because he's coming
in and he's pissed off now.
This is happening right now?
Yeah.
Once I realized how screwed
up Lavina's father was,
I needed to clear up some
important details about her death.
It says she died from a fall, but the
articles are vague and they just...
The articles are not just
vague, they are contradictory.
Right.
I have here her death certificate...
Which actually says that she died...
From acute alcohol poisoning.
So, death certificate says one thing,
the newspaper articles say another.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Her legs are messed up.
There was a pain here.
A really bad pain here, like a crunch.
And this guy is laughing.
He's just laughing.
Do you think this was an accident?
No.
He's happy about it.
I think...
He threw her down.
I think he tossed her over.
At this point, I had uncovered
two causes of death for Lavina...
A fall down the stairs
and alcohol poisoning.
But which one was it?
It wasn't until I called on one
of the County's top paramedics
that I realized these two causes
of death might've been related.
So, Steve, the death certificate lists
alcohol poisoning as the cause of death.
Now, it's 1929, so this is prohibition.
Right. The federal government was still
producing alcohol for medicinal purposes.
And they would put small traces
of poison in that alcohol...
To prevent people from using
it as a recreational drink.
So, Steve, if she started to ingest
this poison liquor, what would happen?
As she swallows it, it's gonna cause
burning going down her esophagus,
down into her stomach, and it's
gonna aggravate her stomach lining.
Would moonshine cause
that same type of symptom?
Yes.
Death certificate says one thing,
the newspaper articles say another,
so I wanted to get your opinion.
It looks like Miss Wall either
was drinking, fell down the steps,
suffered some type of head
injury or internal bleeding.
Or she had fallen, and
after she had fallen,
she may have been trying
to lessen that pain
by using, whether it be
legal or illegal spirits.
Okay.
The daughter that died on the stairs...
There was a sickness with the throat.
It's really this intense pain...
Going all the way down.
And it's all raw and burning like that.
The image of that girl's death was so
horrific, I couldn't get it out of my head.
That's why I decided to sketch the man
who was responsible for killing her...
Her father.
He's approximately sixty to sixty-five.
He has a very rugged...
Thick skin.
His hair... it's a nice silver gray.
Amy, is this who you saw?
Yes.
Next...
She was dead.
Amy and Steve reveal
their disturbing findings.
My God.
But did the client follow Amy's advice?
So I thought I was
doing the right thing.
When I first saw Amy, I was
beginning to get concerned.
This practice is my
life. It's my livelihood.
This is where I have staked my past.
It's where I have staked my future.
Dr. Grimes thinks he may
be losing patients because
of some of the things going on there,
and he needs to know what's happening.
So, I started going up
one of the staircases.
And I saw this girl...
Laying there and...
She was dead.
She was in absolute agony.
There was a young girl that did die.
Back in 1929. Her name was Lavina Wall.
The newspaper articles
say she died from a fall.
My gosh. Really?
You know, you've had an instance
where you've seen a young girl.
I would turn and look at the doorway
at the top of the stairwell...
And I would see a
flash of a little girl.
I could see pain in her eyes.
And a longing for someone
to understand that pain.
I did do a sketch of the scene
that I saw on the staircase.
My God.
The picture that Amy presented to me...
Shocked me. It shook me to my very bone.
It was almost like I fell
down the stairs with her.
There she was...
In pain, suffering.
And that was what she had
tried to tell me for decades.
The good doctor here is quite a painter.
He actually painted a picture of her.
Wow.
- So, you think it's her?
- Without a doubt.
Seeing that painting, I
could tell Dr. Grimes had
a strong connection with the
spirit of the little girl.
So it didn't come as a surprise,
when he told me he was trying
to communicate with her.
I don't know if I'm doing
the right thing or not.
Is that a good thing or
a bad thing he's doing?
Really bad. We can become
a little too attached.
That attachment can actually be something
else that kind of holds them here.
So, I thought I was
doing the right thing,
but I was part of the
problem, not the solution.
And that stung.
What else did you see?
Um, I also encountered...
Really negative male.
At the top of the stairs.
Who I believe is her father.
I have heard a man stomping.
- He's aggressive.
- He's very violent.
- Violent?
- Yes.
Her, her mother, and her older sister...
Fled Ohio from Cyrus,
their abusive, drunk father.
Okay.
So, I did a sketch that
I think might be him.
Look at this photo. Now look
at this sketch. You tell me.
Here was a face on that thing that
was bothering me all those years.
And it was a real person and,
the only thing that I can say
that I responded with was anger.
I think...
He, killed her.
He was at the top of the stairs,
picked her up, and threw her.
My God.
I never even dreamt of that.
It was a shock that
someone that I really knew,
really cared about over
a long period of time
had suffered something worse
than I had ever dreamed.
It was murder, and it was
a brutal, brutal murder.
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy, and
hopefully, she will have an answer.
The first thing that I would
recommend is getting rid of her father.
The next step is going to be...
Having a talk with her
and letting her know...
That it's okay for her to go.
Doc, are you gonna
be able to let her go?
Because you're really, like, almost
a fatherly figure right now with her.
Amy gave me very explicit instructions
as to how I could rid the
office of Lavina's father.
I decided that I would have to wait
until everyone was out of the office.
None of the employees, no patients.
Just me and him.
Amy gave me three objects...
she gave me black salt,
some holy water, and some incense.
As I was going through
this ritual of cleansing,
I could feel like the pall of sadness
had been lifted from this place.
I could feel something that
was enlightening and lifting.
After I got rid of her father, there was
a big difference in the way Lavina acted.
I heard her laugh for the
first time ever in 38 years.
The next step was a
sit-down talk with Lavina,
and I explained to her that it was time
for her now to move on to a better place.
And since then, I feel that
she might have done just that.
I don't feel her like I used to.
And to find that I'm
alone now and she's gone,
that's something of a sad thought.
It's like letting your child go.
I know all too well that severing
a connection with the dead
can be just as painful as
saying goodbye to a loved one.
For Dr. Grimes, it's been a difficult
journey to accept that Lavina's gone,
and I can only hope he'll find comfort in
knowing that her soul is finally at peace.
Buying a home is every
newlywed couple's dream,
unless you're our clients
in Garrett, Indiana.
Leah's new house terrified her.
And her husband, Rudy, refused to believe
in the existence of anything paranormal.
Until Amy blew them all away.
Revealing what really
happened inside their house.
So, Leah, why don't you
tell me what's going on?
I am hearing things.
Stuff is touching us.
We can't sleep at night. My
family won't even come over.
We really want to start a
family, but I am not comfortable
raising kids in a house
that I'm afraid to be in.
So, what about your husband, Rudy?
He does not believe in any of this.
I feel like I'm alone.
Without anyone else here to talk
about it, I felt almost like...
"What if I'm crazy? What if this
stuff really isn't happening?"
And I started, then, to feel hopeless...
Like no one else is ever gonna
believe these stories that I'm telling.
You okay?
- Yeah.
- Just hold my hand.
What is it about this basement that
creeps you out, what's going on?
I am scared to death to
be down here right now.
Even with me right now?
You know the feeling when
someone's watching you,
and you can't see them
but you know they're there?
I feel, like, eyes on me.
Not too welcoming.
As soon as I walked into the house,
I felt a heavy, dark energy
drawing me into the basement,
and what was waiting down
there nearly made me pass out.
I feel really dizzy, I feel really...
Anxious, panicked.
There's lots of people.
There's something down here that...
Draws them in.
There's an old man who
is wandering around.
Lost.
Definitely there's...
the entrance is down here.
What do you mean?
Where they're coming in.
What's coming in?
Death.
Next...
It wants to chop them
up and mutilate them.
Amy fights for her life.
It's, like, trying to get my heart.
This thing is, like, really attacking me.
Amy and I were
investigating a home where a
young woman was having some
traumatizing experiences.
What she encountered in her bedroom
had left her terrified
and desperate for answers.
I was laying in bed one night,
and I just had the urge
to look at the doorway.
And I seen a woman standing
there. She was just looking at me.
When I would think about this lady
watching me while I'm sleeping...
I really felt like my
privacy was invaded.
- How are you sleeping at night?
- I don't.
I think she's mad
because this is her house.
You think she's dangerous?
Yeah.
I feel like...
There's so much, like...
Wrong here.
This...
Woman.
She is...
Confused.
Does this woman... does she
interact with the living in any way?
Yes. She tries to help them.
She thinks they're afraid of her.
She says there's real monsters.
She said, that will meet them.
Whoever this woman was, she
wanted to protect the living.
Unfortunately, she was no match
for what was hiding in the bedroom.
**** me.
Okay.
This is how this thing is getting in.
What thing?
This nasty thing.
Looks like a freaking monster.
And then it's looking.
It's looking for the people.
It wants to take them...
Into the basement.
Why?
It wants to take them down there and,
like, chop them up and mutilate them.
So, Rudy, I was talking
to your wife, Leah,
and she was explaining all the
stuff that's going on in the house.
What about yourself? Have
you experienced anything?
I don't really believe
in all that stuff.
But your wife, she's scared to be here.
How do you feel about that? I mean,
you don't seem too concerned about it.
Well, there's really not much I can
do about it if there is anything here.
Rudy, let me ask you
something, have you experienced
anything paranormal in this
house, anything unusual?
There was one night I was
sleeping in bed for a couple hours,
and all of a sudden, I
felt something touch me.
And it woke me up.
Were you in bed with your wife, or...
No. She wasn't home yet.
- That didn't freak you out?
- No.
Did you tell Leah about this?
Yeah. Which, obviously,
was a big mistake.
Rudy's wife was freaking out,
and he didn't seem to care.
I could tell it was gonna take
something pretty terrifying
to get this guy to see the truth.
Something's in bed with them.
- What?
- This thing.
Like, maybe black mist.
Or a blob shadow.
But it just moves. You
know what I'm saying?
That house had serious problems...
A dark entity hiding in one room
and what seemed to be some kind
of shadow figure in the bedroom.
- This thing is in bed with them?
- Yeah.
It's just, like, this blackness.
It just lays there, freaks
them the **** out.
It's not every day you
come across a father
who's more scared of something
than his own daughter.
So when Leah's dad refused
to meet me at the house,
I had to find out what could drive
a grown man to that level of fear.
Steve, what's the story with
the house that you won't go in?
It's a bad feeling when
you walk in the door.
Have you seen anything in the house?
We went over to feed the dogs one
night while Leah and Rudy were gone.
I walk into the living room, and
I says, "is there anybody here?"
Make some noise if you're here".
And immediately, it was...
Taps on the table.
- Okay. Have you been back since?
- No.
- Your daughter's pretty scared.
- I know she is.
- Do you think she's in danger?
- She could be.
This thing can go in your body.
And it can, like, possess you.
Mediums put themselves at risk any
time they connect with an entity.
Sometimes this can be life-threatening.
Now it's, like, grabbing
and trying to get my heart.
- You hear it?
- Yeah.
It's gonna make me sick.
This thing is, like,
really attacking me.
I was freaking out. The shadow figure
kept trying to force its way into my body,
and I didn't know if I could stop it.
- Do you need to leave?
- No. I got to get this.
****!
I am so not gonna vomit.
You can **** off.
Next...
He had had a heart attack.
Steve uncovers shocking secrets.
How does he wind up with two wives?
And what happened
after the investigation?
I was ready to fight these things.
After doing some research
on Leah and Rudy's home,
I found out that the previous
owner had died from a stroke.
So, I tracked down his former employer
to see if there might be some kind
of connection to Leah's encounters.
Conducting an investigation
on a house in the neighborhood.
I came across the name of a guy named
Ralph, who passed away last year.
- Did you know him?
- Knew him well.
What were the
circumstances of his stroke?
He had it in the house.
He was up in the bedroom.
He had fallen, and, you
know, it was some hours later
before someone came in to find him.
Did he have health issues to begin with?
He had had a heart attack six
or seven years prior to that,
but beyond that, he
was a very healthy guy.
There's, like, a male who...
There's something with the heart.
Like, a male having a heart attack here.
Having just escaped the shadow
figure who tried to crush my heart,
I wasn't surprised when I encountered a
dead man who experienced the same thing.
I feel it's, like, fairly recent.
Also, like, something with maybe...
Like, I don't know if the heart's
causing, like, little strokes.
Something... something with the heart
and strokes, or something like this.
That house was over 100 years old,
so I knew there were other residents.
That's how I found
out about Ed Hammers...
A rail road worker who was struck and
killed by a train in the early 1900s.
That guy had been married to
two women at the same time,
and the widows ended up battling
it out in court over his estate.
So, I understand this is the courtroom
where this estate trial took place.
Between this guy Ed Hammers' two wives?
Yes, it is. Yeah.
First of all, how does
he wind up with two wives?
Well, he was married to Susan
Hammers and had three children.
In fact, he deserted them. In today's
parlance, he'd be a deadbeat dad.
He was arrested for failure to pay child
support on the kids that he deserted.
He met this woman who was
working at the jail, named Carrie,
and fell in love with Carrie.
Once he was out of jail, he
decided to get married to her.
What happened at the trial?
I mean, how did it turn out?
Susan, I think, got all of the
damages from an insurance claim.
Carrie got the house and
part of the personal property.
Carrie resided in that
home for a few years,
lost it for failure to
pay real-estate taxes.
All I know now is that she's buried
next to Edward Hammers in Garrett.
Okay.
This...
This woman.
She feels so...
Lost.
She, like, cries...
Loudly.
Wailing.
She was depressed
in life, very much so.
Do you have any idea why?
I don't think she had,
like, a very good marriage,
so I don't think she
was ever really... happy.
There was a lot of
activity inside that house,
so I felt it was important
to do two sketches.
First the woman who wanted to
protect the people who lived there...
She is very thin.
She has light brown...
Sandy-blond hair.
Then the shadow figure that
physically tormented me.
There's this...
Entity that is in the bed.
I want to just show
the female laying down.
Is this what you saw?
Yes.
Coming up next...
That is who I saw.
Amy's sketch reveals pure evil.
And for the first time, what
happened after the investigation...
I was the most afraid
that I've ever been.
On "Dead Files Revisited".
Leah and Rudy here are newlyweds.
Leah's dad, Steve, won't
even come into the house.
That's why we're doing
the reveal in the garage.
When I was going to meet Amy for the
first time, I was scared to death.
I was concerned that she
wasn't gonna find anything,
and that I was gonna be this crazy
woman living in this crazy house.
I'm gonna have Amy start and tell
us a little bit about her walk.
So, the first person that I
encountered was an older man.
Either he had a heart attack first,
or it was a stroke and a heart attack.
And this was recent.
You know, Amy, it sounds like
the guy you're talking about
is this guy, Ralph, who lived here
right before you guys bought the house.
He passed away from a stroke.
But he had a heart attack six years prior
to the stroke, so maybe seven years ago?
Yes.
I saw him in the basement, and
he's kind of just lost down there.
There are a lot of
dead people down there.
And it seemed like there
was some type of an entrance,
for these dead people down there.
It explains why it feels like I'm
being stared at while I'm down there.
It explains the feeling I
get when I walk in the door.
I can feel that.
So, what else happened during your walk?
I went into the laundry room...
And this woman comes out.
There's no way that you can prepare
for whatever Amy's gonna tell you.
She was sad.
Really, really, really sad and
really lonely and really lost.
To know that Amy saw the same
lady that I had been seeing,
I was relieved that I'm not
crazy, but then I'm like...
"My God. This is real".
I have seen this lady also.
She scares the crap out of me.
Do you want to see the sketch?
You know what? You guys take a look.
That is who I saw.
I could tell Leah was relieved by the
fact that we had seen the same woman,
and she wasn't here to hurt her.
Unfortunately, there was a
lot more she needed to know.
I went into the first bedroom and...
I felt this thing come
in through the window.
I just felt like it was negative.
Then I went into the second room,
and there I saw, like, this shadowy
figure come out from under the bed,
and then it climbed into the bed.
It can enter people's
bodies fairly easily.
I was sleeping, and I felt like something
was holding me or pressing me down.
- Really?
- That sort of thing.
When Amy said that thing
was laying in bed with us,
I think Rudy was shocked, and I
think that's really what pushed him
to want to do something about it.
So, I did do a sketch,
of the main bedroom
and what I saw in there.
That's how I sleep.
That is a little creepy. That is
the side of the bed she sleeps on.
And the shadow thing
is right next to her.
Could this girl be Leah?
It could be.
Can we take a break?
When I started to cry
and I went into the house,
I really expected to just be, like, by
myself, and then I heard the door open
and it's Rudy coming through there.
And so, I was, like, relieved.
It was the first time that
Rudy really acted like,
he's gonna help me and
that he believes now.
- You okay?
- Yeah. I'm sorry.
It's overwhelming.
Well, it's been a long
night, so with that,
I'm gonna turn that over
to Amy for some answers.
I think there's a way
that this can be resolved.
What you guys will be doing
is a step-by-step process of...
Releasing the dead.
What this means is that no
dead person, even the nice ones,
are going to be able to remain.
Nothing will ever be able
to enter your house again.
Okay?
You got to make me a promise that
you're gonna do what she tells you.
After Amy told us what we had to do,
I was the most afraid
that I've ever been.
But I wanted it done
as soon as possible.
I wasn't messing around with this stuff.
As scared as dad was to come in the
house, he really wanted to help me.
I was ready to fight these things.
We had to go into the basement,
and we had to set up this...
Holy water and black
salt protection barrier.
So, dad and I
stood back-to-back,
because I didn't want
anything to sneak up on us.
When we went upstairs to do
the cleansing of the bedrooms,
I felt a lot of resistance.
Like, this thing was really
trying to fight us off.
It was, like, the worst fear that
I've ever felt in that bedroom.
After being attacked in that house,
I felt Leah had every
right to be terrified.
But the cleanse had to be done.
When we were done, the
house was totally different.
It felt really empty.
Like, I was all alone,
but in a good way.
Now that the house is
clean and everything's gone,
my family feels safe coming over, and
Rudy and I are ready to start a family.
Any time a client is willing
to take immediate action,
the impact can be extremely rewarding.
With the support of her family,
I'm confident Leah will continue
to keep her home free of evil.