David Coleman.
Tonight on "Dead Files Revisited"...
He wants to kill me.
A second look at some of Amy and
Steve's most terrifying cases.
If I heard that, I'd reach for my gun.
New information.
It was just disturbing.
Startling revelations.
I felt like Amy could look into my soul.
First...
A return to Parkersburg,
West Virginia...
I want it to be over...
Where a demonic Creature
tortures a family.
We can't continue to live in fear.
And Amy reveals the horrifying truth.
He wants to hurt you.
Then we travel back
to Wichita, Kansas...
It made my heart stop.
Where evil lurks around every corner.
He hates them, living or dead.
And the client faces a grim reality.
Is that me?
Did they follow Amy's advice...
You guys are gonna do this stuff?
Or continue to live in fear?
I have felt hopeless.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing's, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people.
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her?
It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were
ghosts in this house.
It takes a lot to rattle my cage,
but our investigation in Parkersburg,
West Virginia, still haunts me.
Our client's family had been terrorized
by paranormal activity for years,
especially her 17-year-old
daughter, Torie.
I'll never forget the
look of fear in her eyes
when Amy revealed what was
really going on in their house.
Well, Tisha, tell me why
you called Amy and I in.
We are having some
activity in the house.
Some of us have been physically touched.
The kids are scared.
Well, just last night,
our oldest was hysterical,
and I spent a lot of
the night consoling her.
I was at a place, as a Mom,
where I had felt hopeless
about protecting my children.
When there's something in
your house that you can't see
and you don't even know what it is, you
can't really keep your kids safe from that.
You think that whatever's here
can be harmful to you guys?
We can't continue to live in fear.
What's going on?
Well, there was, like,
someone who was drowned.
There's a male who's following us.
Somehow, these two
incidents are related.
I already sensed that
the house had a dark past,
but I didn't even have
to walk in the front door
to know that the man
protecting it was evil.
He just keeps smiling, and the
smile is, like, really maniacal.
He wants to kill me,
and he's waiting for me.
Okay, what's going on up here?
We're lying in bed at
night, and we hear sounds.
They're usually coming from this floor.
And it sounds like...
- Just like that.
- That noisy?
All night long.
If I heard that, I'd reach
for my gun and come running up.
Yeah.
Well, you can only imagine
the toll that it took on us.
I was tired, the kids were
having trouble getting up
and going to school
because of late nights.
So, it took a huge toll on
our bodies and on our souls.
There's, like, lots of **** people.
Upstairs is just full of...
Crying... and people...
That really don't belong.
I couldn't believe how many dead
people were trapped in that attic.
But out of all of them,
one stood out from the rest.
There's a dead little girl here.
She stumbles into things all the time.
Where does this happen...
that she bumps into things?
All over the **** house.
Jason, Tisha says you're a
skeptic. Is that accurate?
I'm always trying to find the
logical, you know, explanations.
But as time goes on and things happen,
you know, you start to
run out of explanations.
Usually, the man of the house will
play the skeptical card with me.
Jason was no different.
But once I pressed him,
it wasn't long before he admitted
that he was also a believer.
Did any experience that you
had here change your mind?
Yes.
I was shaving in the bathroom,
and my daughter usually comes up, you
know, to give me a hug, and I felt that.
And I looked around and
there was no one there.
Is that the defining moment
that changed your attitude?
- Yes.
- Okay.
There's a teenage boy here.
And he's laughing, and he's a prankster.
Does he do stuff to the living here?
Yes.
He watches them, always...
Breathes on them...
Likes to walk around and, like,
walking up right behind them.
At first, I just assumed
that boy was nothing more
than an entity who
liked causing trouble.
But something about him was deceiving.
And then I saw there was a
sinister side to his pranks.
He likes to surprise them.
Sometimes, like...
Get in there and asphyxiate them.
It was one thing to hear
Tisha and Jason's stories.
But as a father,
it was tough seeing how those
experiences were torturing their daughter.
So, Torie, I was talking to Mom,
and she told me you had a
pretty bad night last night.
I was laying in bed, and I kept
hearing furniture moving upstairs.
So, I called Mom and she
tried to calm me down,
so I slept in the same
room as my grandpa.
I was so scared to sleep in my room
that I would crawl in bed
with one of my family members.
And being 17, that's really
embarrassing for me to,
tell other people or my
friends about that, because...
I don't want people to
make fun of me about it.
Your Mother mentioned that she felt
like she was always being watched.
- Yeah.
- Where do you feel that?
Definitely the bathroom
on the second floor.
Just, when I take a shower, I
always got to open the curtain,
look out, because I feel
like someone's standing there.
That's when it starts.
The boy from upstairs...
the prankster...
He watches everything all the time.
No privacy here. No. None. None.
And he said, "I don't care
if they feel violated".
It's really mean.
You know, Torie, I have a daughter
myself. She's a little bit older than you.
Couldn't imagine her going
through this every night.
It's got to be tough on you.
Okay. Wait a minute.
This is really scary.
And I worry about the kids all the time.
I'm worried about my Mom, too.
I want it to be over.
Yes.
- Next...
- **** it hurts.
Amy is under attack.
I got to get him out. I got to...
And in our second investigation...
If you run, they're gonna follow you.
Lives are changed forever.
For us, the final chapter
hasn't been written yet.
After doing some research
on Tisha and Jason's house,
I found out two people were killed
on the property about 100 years ago.
And the cause of their
death was so bizarre,
I tracked down a local
author to explain it to me.
In 1885, the city of Parkersburg built
two large water tanks on Quincy Hill.
And then on march 19, 1909,
the South tank ruptured,
and the force of the water
caused the North tank to rupture.
2 million gallons of water just
instantly flooded Parkersburg.
And there were a lot of homes
in the surrounding area that were
ripped off their foundations and
thrown into the streets below.
So, now, a young couple gets killed.
Yes. Their house was swept
down into Avery Street.
Were their bodies ever found?
A few hours later,
their bodies were found.
Their hands and arms
were over their mouths,
as if they were trying to
get another breath of air.
Wow.
Like, seeing the water again.
Shaking, and I'm
falling, and I'm falling.
Like ****!
Down, down.
Covered up, covered up. Shh!
All I could see around me was
death and destruction, and then...
**** it hurts. Aw...
Are you okay?
An entity forced his way into my body
to make me experience his suffering.
The pain was so unbearable, it took
every ounce of my strength to break free.
****
I got to get him out. I got...
I got to get him out of me.
He just wants everybody to
know that he was **** killed.
The water towers were built by
a prominent Parkersburg family.
At the center of that family
was General John Jay Jackson...
A well-respected man with an
impeccable military record.
On paper, that sounds nice, but
after talking to a local historian,
I learned that the General
wasn't always such a great guy.
I came across the name of
a General John Jay Jackson.
Yes. He was a Founding Father
of the city of Parkersburg.
So, Bob, how did he make a living?
In the 1840s, he purchased
a Parkersburg newspaper.
And then soon thereafter, he
became involved in the oil industry.
What kind of a businessman was he?
Anytime you're buying land
and speculating, there's...
Often controversy.
And this certainly may have been
the case involving General Jackson.
Okay. Now, what about family?
Legend has it that his son...
John Jay Junior, that had fallen
in love with a girl in Parkersburg,
named Jane, whom he
planned to marry himself.
However, this happened to be the
same Jane that his father married.
So, he married the Jane that the
Son was looking to hook up with?
- Yes.
- Okay.
So, now I'm seeing this guy, and
he's just wearing a long black duster.
I was nervous being near that man again.
I saw him when I first arrived at the
house, and he threatened to kill me.
He was here from...
Way back.
Eighteen sixty's.
And he was a prominent person.
He...
Was...
Instrumental in this town's growth.
All of a sudden, his body changed
and he revealed himself to
me as a horrific Creature.
An entity like this can be extremely
dangerous to both the living and the dead.
So I knew I needed to
sketch him for our clients.
He is very tall...
And he is...
Like a skeleton with a layer of skin.
He's wearing a very
thick leather jacket.
Is this who you saw?
Yes.
Next...
He wants to do harm.
God.
Find out what happened
after the investigation.
My Mom was screaming.
In the name of the Father and the
Son and the Holy Spirit, get out!
Amy, this is Tisha and Jason.
They're engaged to be married.
They've been going through
some terrifying things.
Torie, especially. Torie's
their oldest. She's 17.
I was so excited to see Amy
sitting at our kitchen table.
I felt like, finally, finally,
we're going to have answers.
And we're gonna have a
way to protect our kids.
But I had one big concern...
that Amy was going to say,
"you need to move out of your house".
When I first came onto the property...
I saw that somebody had drowned.
I already knew that the two water tanks
ruptured and flooded the town in 1909.
Three people died from it.
And they found them with their mouths
covered, as if to stop water from going in.
But I never expected that Amy would
have seen that tragedy in such detail.
And I felt, like, this
blow, then I heard...
"Down, cover up, cover up".
Anything else?
Okay. So, there's two
people on the second floor.
One is a younger girl.
She tends to accidentally
bang into things.
The other one is a younger male.
He also likes the bathroom a lot.
- He likes to be in there.
- God.
When Amy told me that she discovered
the little boy in the bathroom...
I got really emotional,
because I was worried.
For myself and my siblings.
If one of them had to go through this,
I can only imagine how
hard it would be for them.
He watches all the time.
He wants to hurt you.
God.
Seeing Torie break down
like that was very difficult.
I didn't know what to say to her,
and I didn't know what to do for her.
And at that moment, I
felt like I had failed.
I failed my child.
What else did you see?
The other person...
He is the man in the black coat.
And he wanted to kill me.
He's from the 1860s or '70s...
And he was very instrumental
in creating this town.
That sounds just like John Jay Jackson.
He owned the property
that your house sits on.
He was one of the Founding
Fathers, actually, of Parkersburg.
Do you think the apparition
you saw is General Jackson?
Yes. Yes, I do.
But he also showed me another side of
himself in a really dark, sinister way.
I sketched him that way because
it really was disturbing.
Take a look, guys.
He has no pupils.
God. The man's eyes. He
didn't even have eyes.
It was the creepiest
face I had ever seen.
It just... when you look at it, you feel
a bad presence just even from the picture.
It was just disturbing.
He's a collector.
With his life, all of the
collecting he did then of, like,
maybe property and
money and all of this.
The only thing in death that
you can really collect are souls.
He and the little boy
are one in the same.
He has this part of himself
that's this little boy...
That can do all these horrible things.
While his other self is
literally roaming the town.
I know this is a lot of
information to digest in one night,
but the most pressing question...
Is it safe for your family to be here?
I can't answer that, so for that,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
You have so much residual
energy here, it's ridiculous.
So, the first thing
to do is a cleansing.
Yeah.
The other thing is, in each room,
you're gonna take salt and throw
it in the four corners of each room.
They're gonna all be attracted to this.
This will cleanse all the residual
energy, and you're sealing the property,
so nothing else negative can enter.
Promise me you guys are
gonna do what she says.
Amy gave us the advice that we needed
to do the cleansing of the house.
And I looked at Torie and said,
"that's it. It's getting done".
As quickly as we could, we
were cleansing the house.
We ask that all negativity
leave this space.
You're no longer welcome in this home.
Then we went into the basement, which
is a place that I had never gone before.
We ask that all negative
energy leave this place today.
You are no longer welcome in our home.
Only love, light, and peace may enter.
And doing the salt...
sweeping it out of the house.
During the cleanse, I was still scared,
and the mood didn't
really change at all.
And then we went into the bathroom,
that I am terrified of,
and right when we walked in,
I felt something pull on my hair.
Mom, something just pulled on my hair.
Okay. We're done.
In the name of the Father and the
Son and the Holy Spirit, get out!
We ask that all negative
energy leave our home.
Leave our home! Leave us in peace!
My Mom was screaming.
Get out of our house! This is our home!
She was telling it to get out of here
and it didn't belong in our house.
I was so angry.
Leave us alone. This is our home.
Get out!
I knew he was there with us.
And that just gave me
more energy and drive,
to get the house cleansed
completely that day.
After the cleanse, this house
felt completely different.
Everything felt lighter.
The house was warmer.
It was an obvious change.
Now I can sleep at night.
I can go to the
bathroom without anybody,
and I don't have to be
scared to be at home alone.
I'm not sure if it's a coincidence...
But Jason and I have planned
our wedding four times.
He has canceled it three times.
Since the cleansing, he's
in a much better mood,
and we were finally
married two weeks ago.
Tisha and Torie have
taken the right steps
to release the dead from their home.
But they should continue the
cleansings on a regular basis.
The man in the black
coat is still out there,
and there is no telling
when he's coming back.
A couple in Wichita,
Kansas, called us in
to investigate frightening
activity on their property.
Turns out the problem wasn't just
their building, it was one of them.
And even though Amy
and I were able to help,
this is one story that's far from over.
Jeff, you sounded
concerned on the phone.
Well, I am concerned.
You know, really, I'm fighting
to save two businesses here.
- My wife has the salon here in front.
- Okay.
And then I have my
garage here at the back.
Give me an idea of what's going on.
We've heard things, we've
been touched, pushed.
I'd like my kids to be able
to take over the business.
But right now, I'm not even
comfortable having them in there.
This is a big part of our lives.
We've spent so much money and so
much effort building this business up,
and we've been very successful here,
so it would be very difficult
just to pull up and move.
What about yourself... have you ever
seen anything or experienced anything?
I just finished working
on some vehicles.
- Okay.
- And I looked up and saw it.
Looked like an older gentleman, maybe.
I'm guessing him to be in his
mid to late 50s, with a beard.
All of us went inside.
We found out that there
was nobody in there.
Okay.
There's one kind of creepy dude.
He's kind of like a greaser dude.
And he likes his area.
To me, he's, like, just
a tough guy, you know?
He's like, "I'm tough.
I'm bad. I'm big. I'm bad".
During my walks, I often encounter
entities who act very territorial.
Usually, it's because they want to
protect their space, but the greaser guy...
He wanted revenge on the
people who had invaded his home.
Like, would you say that he's dangerous?
Yes.
He's kind of **** up.
Next...
He can get physical.
Amy has a sickening encounter.
It's, like, really hurting my head.
Amy and I were investigating not one,
but two family-run businesses,
both on the same property.
The activity had gotten so
bad that the owner, Jeff,
was concerned that his reputation
wasn't the only thing in danger.
So, what's going on in here?
I remember a time I was
leaned over the back of a car,
and then suddenly someone
whispers in my ear.
I stand up. There was nothing in here.
Anything else, Jeff?
We started to notice that
tools would come up missing.
If you can't find them,
you can't work with them.
Do you think that anything that's
going on in the garage can be dangerous?
Yes.
I was really worried
about everyone's safety.
Because I felt like,
if it could move something small
or throw, like, a roll of tape,
that it could definitely
throw something big or sharp.
He doesn't want anybody in
his space. He hates them.
Living or dead, he just doesn't
want anybody in this space.
Some people think of the
dead as transparent beings
who have very little
interaction with our world.
That's somewhat correct, but the stronger
ones can actually break the physical plane.
And if provoked, they can touch the living,
move objects, or do something worse.
He can get physical if he wants to...
Grabbing or pushing.
- Okay.
- Likes to throw things.
Could he hurt anybody?
I think he... I think he could.
Jeff had his fair share of
problems on the property,
but he wasn't the type
of guy to just run away.
His wife, on the other
hand, was ready to split.
But soon, we were all about to find out
there was no way she could
have run away from this.
So, Emily, I was talking to your husband,
Jeff, and he basically said you're ready
to put the "for sale" sign on this place
and get out of here. What's going on?
From the first time we unlocked the door
here, it's never felt like it's been ours.
Why do you say that?
Stuff moves, people get pushed, you
hear people whisper in your ears.
Okay, so you're losing business
because of what's going on?
Absolutely.
So many people have
had experiences here.
It's a small town, and word gets around.
So, I don't want to get a bad
name for being the haunted salon.
I'd love for it all to stop and go away,
but I just don't know if
that's what's gonna happen.
All right, so you feel that
whatever's here wants you out?
Absolutely.
There's a lot of stuff
coming in from outside.
I'm, like, seeing
this woman who's alive.
The dead are just, like, following her.
And then they're inside.
That was the moment I realized,
the dead there were attracted to a
specific person for a very specific reason.
Why are they following her?
Because she has abilities.
Okay, so what's going on here?
My daughter talks about seeing things.
She even drew a picture of, like,
a black figure with red eyes,
and she said that's
something she saw here.
- Where's the picture?
- I threw it away immediately.
It made my heart stop, because I
don't want to be putting her in danger.
Emily, your daughter's 9?
Yes. I want to preserve her innocence.
I don't want her to be scared.
Okay.
This is creepy.
What is?
The thing that's in here.
It makes me feel
uncomfortable and scared.
It looked like... like a Grim Reaper.
The classic image of
death is the Grim Reaper...
A skeleton wearing a dark
cloak and carrying a sickle,
but I know death looks
nothing like that.
But I think it's, you know,
just a regular dead person.
So, when I saw a Reaper, I knew it was only
a projection meant to scare the living.
And the person hiding
behind that illusion...
Was the greaser man.
Now I'm picking up on his death state,
and feeling everything that
he went through physically.
It's, like, really hurting my head.
I just feel very, very sick.
You gonna be all right?
I'm out of it. Like,
my equilibrium's off.
I'm... disoriented.
It **** hurts, man.
Next...
I think the death is suspicious.
Steve follows a trail of tragedy.
Were you surprised when
they found him dead?
And what happened
after the investigation?
I wasn't expecting that at all.
Emily and Jeff ran two
businesses out of their property.
But before that, it was
just a residential home.
My first move was to meet
with the former owner.
Talking to her, it sounded like
anyone who spent time at that house...
Wound up dead.
Cheryl, I got called in to
investigate your old home.
- How long did you live there?
- About five years.
What did you use the garage
for, or was it always a garage?
We did a lot of hangouts
with friends in there.
People came by every
day, and it was like...
They lived there.
People that are living
there now are claiming
there's a lot of paranormal
activity going on.
Did you ever experience
anything like that?
We lost three of our dear
friends within a year.
- Really?
- Right.
This is Kevin.
Kevin was hit by a car on his
motorcycle, and he was killed instantly.
And then we lost Tony. He
had a stroke and he died.
And then we had Mark. He had previously
lived in the basement of that house.
And what did he die of?
He had some problems and some issues,
and he lived in an apartment complex that
had a lot of people that did drugs in it.
Whatever he was doing, he just
looked worse every time I saw him.
He went to bed and didn't wake up.
Were you surprised when
they found him dead?
No.
The greaser dude...
He's tall, he's wearing a
black, like, '50s biker jacket.
He killed himself when
he was intoxicated.
Now that I knew how the man
had died, I was concerned.
He needed to leave that location,
and only I could help him.
Unfortunately, his temper was
the one thing getting in my way.
He's mad and walked away.
He's not gonna talk to me again.
At this point, I had three deaths that
were loosely connected
to Jeff and Emily's place.
But I wanted to know if anyone
had actually died on the property.
A local journalist gave me just that...
A former owner who fell down the stairs.
Her choice of a meeting spot was odd.
But as soon as I got there,
I understood the meaning.
This is actually where
Helen Hillman is buried.
She was married when she was 19 in 1917.
Then they moved from Arkansas to
right outside of Wichita, Kansas,
on the property that
you're investigating.
Now, what were you able to find out
about the circumstances of her death?
Well, according to her death
certificate, it's a massive head injury.
Even though she was 79, according to
her descendent, she was in good health.
She was active, she lived independently.
All right, so it was
odd the way she died.
She had lived in that house for so long,
and the distance between
the stairs and the floor
wouldn't be enough to
kill someone, typically.
I don't know if that fall
can cause injuries like that.
Yes, and that's why I think
the death is suspicious.
There's another person.
I think she broke her neck.
Early to mid '70s...
that's when she died.
She was dead, like, fast.
God, it **** hurts.
When I do a sketch, the idea is to put
a face to one of the entities I saw.
But sometimes I need to
take it to the next level.
And in this case, I wanted
to show how one of the living
was the source of that
property's problems.
I saw this woman at the
door, about to open it.
Behind her...
Is this really tall man...
And he is wearing, like, a black cloak.
Hey, Amy, is this what you saw?
Yes.
Coming up next...
He wants you out.
Amy exposes a disturbing secret...
Is there a reason why
you're running from it?
That changes the
clients' lives forever...
For us, the final chapter
hasn't been written yet.
All negativity must leave.
On "Dead Files Revisited".
This is Emily and Jeff.
Jeff actually runs the garage here.
Emily runs the salon up front.
When I first met Amy,
I felt like she could look into my
soul when I looked into her eyes.
Her green eyes kind of just felt
like they looked right through you.
When I started my walk, I came
into contact with this creepy male.
His hair is greased back. He
hates anybody in his space.
When he gets upset, he likes to
yell, he likes to throw things.
Of all the deaths on that property,
the guy Amy described
reminded me of Mark.
He actually lived in the
basement of your salon.
And Jeff agreed with me.
This guy look familiar at all?
Yeah. I remember distinctly seeing this.
When Steve took that out,
I connected with the eyes.
He had the distinct
glare, looking down at us.
I honestly thought that it
wasn't safe to stay here.
Would he hurt me or somebody out
here or is he just trying to scare us?
No. He wants to hurt
you. He wants you out.
So, what else did you see on your walk?
A woman up in the attic area.
Her death was so fast
and extremely painful.
And I did get that she died in the '70s.
There's a woman... Helen Hillman... who
lived in the house that your salon is in.
1977 is when she died.
She fell down the
steps into the basement.
Wow.
That was really sad, knowing
that someone has died here.
By falling down the staircase.
That's horrible to think of...
falling to your own death.
So, what else did you get on the walk?
What I saw was...
Your typical Grim Reaper.
So, as I'm looking deeper, I can
feel and tell that it's a dead male...
That he... hid in life a lot.
And now he's hiding again in death.
Basically, he wants to cause pain...
And to hurt people.
I could tell my findings
about the Grim Reaper
were definitely
startling Jeff and Emily.
Unfortunately, my most troubling
revelation was yet to come.
The other thing that
I saw was a sensitive...
Who lets the dead into the main house.
They just kind of follow her in.
This includes the Grim Reaper guy.
I was ready for just...
This is what happened, this is
the facts, this is what we saw.
And bless the place, and it's over.
And that's not what it was all about.
Amy went deeper and found out more.
I did do a sketch of what I saw...
As far as this individual leading
several dead people into the house.
Is that me?
What kind of experiences have you had?
A lot.
It kind of took my breath away at first.
I've never shared this
with anyone before.
It's not something
you really talk about.
I didn't want to look upon
as being a freak or something.
Is there a reason why
you're running from it?
It's something that, if you
run, they're gonna follow you.
And it's hereditary.
It runs in families.
I see it with my daughter.
The most important question is,
is it gonna be safe for you guys,
your employees, customers,
most importantly, your family?
The first thing is to take
care of the girl in the attic.
Get some Sage and some salt. Go ahead
and Sage the building inside and out,
then taking the salt...
And drawing a line all around the
outside of the building, as well.
What about the Grim
Reaper and the greaser guy?
So, the greaser guy and the Grim
Reaper are actually the same person.
Occasionally, I'll meet a dead person...
That forms an attachment.
So...
I'm going to go ahead
and take him home with me.
I try not to make it a habit of
removing entities from a location.
But Jeff and Emily couldn't
handle that guy on their own.
He needed someone like
me to help him move on.
You need to learn how to
control your environment
and your daughter's environment so
she can protect herself, as well.
You gonna be alright doing this with your
daughter, you gonna be comfortable with it?
The night after the reveal,
we immediately went and
performed the cleansing.
Emily was definitely overwhelmed,
knowing that she had the
power to remove these things.
So, that's just a lot of weight
on a person's shoulders...
To know that it's their
job to move these things on.
All negativity must leave this location.
I was very concerned. I just didn't
want to put anyone in jeopardy.
I didn't want to cause
anyone fear or pain or hurt.
It's very interesting, but since the
cleansing, we've had more activity.
Stuff moves, you hear
people whisper in your ears.
It's very scary.
As we saw things still
progress, we did more cleansings.
We've done two more since then, and we're
working to continue to cleanse the house.
I do feel the pressure that
I'm the one that needs to help
these spirits or these
entities pass over.
Only light, love, and peace
may enter this location.
And that's very heavy.
For us, the final chapter
hasn't been written yet.
Emily's gonna have to learn
to work with these things.
This is a lifelong process that she and my
daughter have to both be able to do this.
No negativity may enter.
And these cleansings are just
going to be a part of life now.
I'm still concerned
about Jeff and Emily.
Regular cleansings might eventually
help calm things down here,
but learning to control your
abilities is a lifelong struggle.
And Emily's journey has just begun.