Subs created by: David Coleman.
There's a lot of past violence.
Somebody's terrified.
I'm afraid of being hurt.
I've been touched.
She definitely makes physical contact.
Three scratches starting to draw blood.
- Something went through me.
- She throws a fit.
You need to get out of here right now.
They're just in hell.
Living people have messed
with the dead here a lot.
That was a mistake.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing's, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people...
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me...
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective...
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her?
It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were
ghosts in this house.
Our clients turn to Amy and me
when they've run out of options.
I dig into the property's history,
looking for witnesses and
hidden details of the past...
While Amy conducts her own
investigation speaking to the dead.
I'm in Death Valley
Junction, California.
It's about 90 minutes
outside of Las Vegas.
Less than 20 people live in this town.
One of them, a guy
named Rich, called us in.
He runs a historic hotel that's
connected to an opera house...
And says the activity there is so
bad, he's losing employees and guests.
He's afraid of losing his business, and I'm
hoping Amy and I can do something for him.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area of anything
that could influence her findings.
This hotel has a large collection
of historical photographs,
and antique memorabilia that
have to be covered or removed.
When I'm finished, the location
will be ready for tonight's walk.
So, I don't even know where to start
because I'm kind of overwhelmed.
But I do feel like
there was unusual deaths.
There are people in the ground.
I get, like, many people dying.
They can't breathe. They can't
breathe. They just suffocate to death.
And somebody said, "we walk upon the
bodies of the dead and their souls, too".
Now, Rich, when we spoke
on the phone, you sounded
pretty concerned about the
business here and maybe losing it.
- What's going on?
- We've got...
Voices, full-blown apparitions...
It's even gotten physical at this point.
We've got scratches, people being touched.
I'm losing employees.
I'm losing business.
They're leaving in the
middle of the night,
or they're deciding
not to stay here at all.
- Do you live on the property at all?
- Yeah, I do.
- You do?
- Yes.
Okay, do you live alone?
No, actually, my girlfriend, Mary Lee,
who works with me here, as well, is here.
- Why don't you just leave?
- Leaving is not an option.
I've got my life invested in here.
I made a promise to the founder
of this particular place...
Okay.
And I gave her my word that
I would stay here and...
- Carry on her vision and legacy.
- Who owns it?
- Her name's Marta Becket.
- Okay.
- She's 88 years old...
And she's got a famous opera house here.
As well as many other
structures on this property here.
And she owns all 268
acres of the facility.
Okay.
I'm just getting, like...
A lot of people being
treated like [Bleep]
A lot of people being murdered.
So much has happened
here over the years.
This is not good.
This... this is not good.
As far as guests go, what have they
complained about in the bedrooms?
They complain of voices.
They also have a shadow figure that they
see at the foot of their bed, as well.
Now, you mentioned
scratches on some guests.
An older man came to me,
and he was right-handed...
And actually had two
scratch marks across there.
- Have you seen them?
- Mm-hmm.
What about his nails?
Were they sharp, long?
They were short and well-manicured.
What else has happened?
Guests are coming back to their rooms after
the day, and the maids have made their bed
and it's like somebody has
actually sat down on the bed,
and there's even hand
prints on some of them.
Are you sure it's not one of the employees
coming in and maybe just relaxing,
or maybe trying to get
another employee in trouble?
You know, I've asked
them, and I don't think so.
Do guests get pissed
off because they think
somebody's been in their room
when they weren't supposed to?
Absolutely.
There's a woman who
goes in all these beds.
She goes in all the beds.
She's been here for a
long time... long time.
I see her getting kicked.
She's getting destroyed.
I just see men beating her
face in, and she's naked.
You have any idea why?
She's dirty. She was doing drugs.
There's, like, nothing you
can do to cover this up.
It's a mess outside.
It's a mess in here.
Now, this is the older
part of the hotel?
It is, Steve. This is a side that's
not open to the public, generally.
It hasn't been used
since the '30s or '40s.
And we affectionately
call it Spooky Hollow.
It's always been called that, so
we just carry on the tradition.
So, are you experiencing stuff
in this part of the building?
This side of the hotel
is totally different.
It's got a different feeling.
There's an overwhelming male energy
that tends to not like people in here.
Does this thing frighten you?
I do try to avoid it. It's
not comfortable for me.
So, there's a man here, and he...
He's very much in charge of everything.
I think he really hates living people.
Well, I know that that's his space.
I don't think he likes
people back there.
Feeling like somebody's
standing right there...
And just feeling, like, terrified...
Absolutely terrified.
Is he actually dangerous?
When he feels like the
living are [Bleep] with him.
He can become whatever scares them.
He can take your breath away.
He can make you feel
that fear in your stomach.
What else is going on?
A lot of paranormal people
like to come back here.
What do you mean, paranormal people?
Well, people that are doing
investigations on their own,
or they want to have an experience.
They like to come back here.
Rich, do you think that
you might be making it worse
by letting these
investigators come in here?
I think maybe that it's a possibility.
I actually had a friend who came
here who's kind of an investigator.
She asked for a sign, you know,
show me that you're back here.
And they ended up being scratched,
and, so, she went ahead and showed me,
and what I saw were three scratches...
- Okay.
- Right across the back.
And actually starting to draw blood.
- On her back?
- On her back.
He's been tortured by the living.
He wallows, and...
He has no intentions of
going anywhere else...
And I think that this
place has been investigated.
The living people have messed
with the dead here a lot...
In really negative ways.
That was a mistake.
What is it exactly that you do here?
Well, I'm an artist, and I
volunteer my time to come up and do
reproductions of the original
signs that were on the hotel.
Okay. So, when you come
up, you stay overnight?
I do. It's like my second home.
So, tell me what you've
been experiencing, then.
I have experienced a lot
of different things here.
From seeing apparitions...
I've heard voices...
I've even been touched.
So, when I do stay
here, I don't sleep well.
All right. Now, what's the most
terrifying experience you've had up here?
First time I was here,
there's a corner right next to
where I was working on a sign.
I suddenly felt this energy
come into the corner that was...
Really menacing...
Like a mob mentality, and
I could hear them say...
"Lady, you need to get
out of here right now".
It's a really strong feeling of anger.
It can get so strong that it... It
makes me feel sick to my stomach.
Like where you get
nauseous or something?
Get nauseous, I feel dizzy, and sometimes
almost as though I'm gonna pass out.
In this area, there was a group of men.
There's a lot of fighting.
This is a long time
ago. This is maybe...
1870s...
1880s.
People are asking for help.
A lot of pain... physical pain.
It's just too much. It's just too much.
The hallways of this hotel are crawling
with dead people from a long time ago.
They're in a great deal of pain,
and I'm experiencing their suffering.
I feel like I'm sick.
I can't walk. I can't... move.
There's too many things
that have happened here.
Like, some people are really sick, and
then there are some people who are...
Hurting themselves.
And there are some people
who kill each other.
Like, it's just a [Bleep] disaster.
So, Mary Lee, I understand
that you and Rich live together.
- Right. Mm-hmm.
- And you and him run the place.
- Exactly. Yeah.
- Okay.
Now, Rich is concerned
about the business...
Losing business because
of what's going on here.
Well, we've had people leave.
Just like that?
- I won't stay here.
- You won't?
- You live on the premise right?
- Mm-hmm.
On the property? But you
wouldn't stay in the hotel.
Mm-mm.
So, can I assume you've
had experiences here?
- Yes. I've had several.
- Okay.
I've seen shadows, apparitions.
- I've been channeled.
- Channeled? What does that mean?
Where something went through me.
I've been afraid to, like, be
in different places by myself.
Things, recently, have gotten worse.
It's just really hard.
I think that people see
a lot of dead people here.
So I feel like...
You know, if the people say
they see something back here...
I think that they would feel
kind of out-of-body-ish...
And...
Very uncomfortable...
And not themselves.
Mary Lee, let me ask you a question. Have
you expressed to Rich how upset you are?
He knows I'm afraid, but I don't
think he realizes how afraid.
And why is that?
Because we're here so much, I
don't want to feel like, um...
Like I'm a chicken.
I don't think that he realizes...
That um, I'm afraid of being hurt.
- Okay.
- I'm really, really scared.
I spoke with some locals who told me,
Death Valley has a
rich mining history...
And that one used to operate
right next to the hotel.
I'm heading over to meet with a
local historian, who also happens to
be a Park Ranger to see if he's
got any information to help my case.
Bob, I understand that the hotel I'm
investigating used to be a mining area.
- Is that correct?
- That's correct.
Okay, what kind of mining
are we talking about?
They were mining for a
very rich form of borax.
It's an industrial product
that's used in welding.
- What was it like for these guys here?
- Brutal.
These men were working in tunnels
on average about 4 feet high.
Wow.
Just wide enough for two men with
picks and shovels and dynamite.
There were no specialists. You
had to know how to plant dynamite.
So I assume there had to be some accidents
and deaths associated with the mine.
There had to be accidents and that kind
of a thing, there had to be collapses.
Oh, it was a pretty short
and pretty hard life.
And there's these
people who are trapped.
There's a lot of men, and
the men are... are wrecks.
I keep encountering this large
group of men all over the property.
Each time I see them, I
begin experiencing their pain,
both physically and emotionally.
You can move better if you crawl.
Because otherwise, it's too difficult.
Because your legs are useless,
especially at the end of the day.
Everybody's [Bleep] miserable.
They're just in hell.
Do you have any idea what was on that
property before the hotel was there?
A lady by the name of Shotgun Kitty...
- Okay...
- Ran a brothel and a bar.
That's her and her husband and two kids.
Now, where'd the name Shotgun come from?
She got the name Shotgun Kitty because,
evidently, she didn't go anywhere
without her shotgun, and she was
known to be an extremely good shot.
She ran the town, basically.
I mean, these miners made a minimal
amount of money, you know, pennies a day.
And what little they did have, they
would spend at Kitty's businesses.
They'd spend it in the brothel,
or they'd spend it in the bar.
She ruled the roost.
When Shotgun Kitty said something,
that was it, you didn't argue with her.
I don't care how drunk
you were or anything else.
There's this older woman.
She's, like, probably in her 50s.
She's rather short.
She's kind of chubby.
I feel like she was a caretaker.
If she was an owner, she
was very, very hands-on.
She just feels like, yeah, that's
mine, and I need to still be in charge.
Like, she was very business...
all about the business.
She's unhappy about
how this place is run,
and it's almost like her dream is
just falling apart before her eyes.
So, she's pissed off that [Bleep]
not being the way she wants it to be.
But she's not trying to help.
She's just making it worse.
What is she doing
that's making it worse?
When she sees something not being done
the way that she wanted
it done, she throws a fit.
She definitely makes physical contact.
I'm at the library to see what I can
find out about the
property I'm investigating.
Digging through the archives, I
uncovered an article about a hotel
employee named Thomas Blower
who took his own life in 1947.
The location where he hung himself...
The Amargosa Hotel.
Now that I know someone who lived and
worked at the Amargosa hung himself,
I need to find out more
details about this case.
I've contacted a local who calls
himself a historic explorer.
And says he's got lots of
information to help me out.
Tim, why'd you bring me to
this part of the building?
The gentleman, Thomas Blower,
that you're investigating,
actually hung himself in this area.
- Right here?
- Correct.
Okay.
So, what were the circumstances
behind the hanging?
In 1947, he was a
65-year-old janitor.
During lunchtime, when everybody
else in the staff was having lunch.
He came down here, tied
a rope, and hung himself.
What would make a 65-year-old...
which is kind of old for a suicide...
Do that?
He might not have been very happy
with the outcome of his life.
In what way?
He is actually kind of
an interesting character.
Even though he was listed as a
janitor, he did a lot of traveling.
He actually traveled a lot between Canada,
The United States, England, and Australia.
This is a 1930s travel voucher
for a Mr. Thomas Blower.
It shows that he actually crossed
from The United States into Canada,
with $2,500 in 1930.
- $2,500?
- Yes.
So, where the hell's he coming
up with this kind of money?
One of the speculations is that he might've
actually been a road agent at the time.
Road agent you're talking about
somebody that does robberies?
Yes.
A road agent is an
individual who would...
Stop a traveler and take anything
of value and then disappear.
Okay. So, now he's 65 years old,
he had money at some point...
Yes.
And out of nowhere, he goes
from being a highway robber,
to being a janitor and
then hanging himself.
Yes, and to anybody who actually
was making the money that,
it's obvious that he was
making or obtaining...
That's a major blow to somebody's ego.
Do you want to go in there?
Not really. That's kind of his area.
This angry man wants me to know that
he controls this section of the hotel.
He hates living people, and he
has disturbing ways of showing it.
When I first saw him, he scared me.
He still kind of scares me.
Like, I know what he can do.
He...
He did a lot of bad things in his life.
What sort of bad things?
He wanted to be respected.
He wanted to be...
Feared... and...
You know, he was... he was.
He didn't care if disrespected.
He didn't care if he took.
He did whatever he needed
to do to gain as much power
and respect from his
people as he possibly could.
He doesn't know how to be good.
I feel pain around my neck.
I feel like...
He's strangling.
Now that I know about
the hotel's troubled past,
I'm going to meet up
with its current owner.
- Hi. Marta?
- Hi.
I need to see if she's experienced
anything strange during her time here.
So, Marta, I was talking to Rich, and he
told me that you've been here a long time.
Oh, yeah. 43 years.
Okay, what brought you out here?
We were kind of looking for a
place to settle out in the west,
and I fell in love with the place.
So, you're not afraid of this place?
No, no. I love it.
So, Marta, let me ask
you a question about Rich.
He's telling me about some pretty
bizarre things that are happening.
Have you ever experienced anything?
Well, there was a sound
at the foot of the stage,
every night when I'd
put my costumes away.
It went like this... oh!
So, you heard a voice?
Oh, yes, but it was always when I was
alone in here, hanging up costumes.
Okay. So, has anything
else strange happened here?
Well, we had a maintenance man, and
he came running in, and he said...
"Marta! Marta! There's a
dead man in the sewer house!"
Okay.
He said, I just climbed
up the ladder and saw him.
He still has his glasses
on, but he's dead.
His name was Tom Moore.
And he said he was in the sewer house?
The sewer house is a big,
white building across the road.
- Okay, so, it's on the property?
- Oh, yes.
Did you ever find out what they
said was his cause of death?
No, it's all been a
mystery. It still is.
I need to check out this sewer house
where Marta said a man was found dead.
Turns out, there's a
local documentary filmmaker
who did a lot of research on his death.
He says there's a lot more to
this case than meets the eye.
Well, Ted, thanks for meeting me.
This guy, Moore, were you able to find
out if what Marta told me was true or not?
He did die, and the reason
that I brought you here,
is because this is where his body was
found, they say in the rafters, apparently.
Now, when did this happen?
1976, we understand, is
when the death happened.
Were there any police reports
they were able to find out?
Well, actually, there's an
article on the death of Mr. Moore.
Okay, so, he was 64 years
old, goes missing in mid-July.
This article's in September.
- So, he's missing for two months.
- Correct.
And, I'm telling you,
from July to September,
those are your hottest months
in this neck of the woods.
And up in those rafters, the heat... a
body would really decompose really badly.
How did they determine
who the hell he was?
They determined from the dental records.
All right, did he have any identification
with him, any money, what was the story?
Well, they did find his billfold,
but no money was taken, you
know, anything like that.
Why a 64-year-old would go up
into this thing makes no sense.
They did an autopsy. They really
couldn't figure out how he died.
- Cause of death is undetermined.
- Undetermined.
Could've been a multitude of things.
In New York, it would be an open case.
It's still circumstances undetermined,
pending police investigation.
Right, right. And there's been
speculation that it could've been murder...
That there could've been
some foul play of some kind.
Okay.
You know, there's only rumblings
that he may have gotten into a fight,
and that there was a gun shot.
So, there's a man here, and he
gets a gun right to his head.
It's him and this other man.
He was hiding from this guy, you
know, but the other guy found him...
And the guy just shoots
him right in the head.
He gets his [Bleep] head shot in...
And he doesn't die for
awhile. He feels it for awhile.
Do you have any idea when this is?
Mm, I'd say, like, 70s, 80s.
Okay.
The guy who was shot...
he's very confused.
He's walking around a lot.
I think he's nuts.
I don't like him at all.
He makes me sick.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations...
We're ready to reveal our findings to each
other and our clients for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to
meet Rich and Mary Lee.
They're the couple that
actually run the hotel here
and actually live on the property.
They're afraid about losing this place
because they're very passionate about it.
They called us in because
in the last three months,
the activity here has gotten really bad.
They have employees that won't stay,
some guests come, and they
wind up leaving in the middle
of the night and just
leave the keys by the desk.
They're scared for their safety.
They want to know if it's safe for
them to keep this place running,
and if they can keep it going.
So, that being said, we'll turn it over
to Amy and hear about her walk a little.
When I first got here, it was
extremely overwhelming for me...
Very painful, physically, and uh...
Definitely, by far, one of the
worst locations that I've done.
The first thing that
I encountered was...
A group of sick men.
The feeling that I got from them
was the feeling of being trapped.
One person said, you know, if
you crawl, you can move better,
and it feels like hell for them.
Well, it makes sense. This was a
mining town back in the early 1900s.
They used to mine for
a mineral called borax.
These mines were very narrow, like 4 feet,
and these guys would have to crawl in...
And actually stick dynamite in and
then crawl back out and blow it up.
The average miner only lasted about 6
months because of the health hazards.
Whoa!
So, the next thing I saw
over in the bedrooms...
I saw this lady.
She was very young...
in her 20s, very thin.
And she seemed to be drugged out.
There's a woman who
goes in all these beds.
I just see men beating her
face in, and she's naked.
A lot of times, there's different,
like, hand prints and uh...
Somebody sitting in different
areas in different rooms here.
- Like someone had been sitting.
- With both hands on it.
On the bed... or their
hands are on the bed.
After it was made up.
You mentioned the beating, before the
hotel was built, there were brothels here.
And, you know, the miners would frequent
this place, and they were pretty,
you know, rough customers.
Interesting.
Um...
The next woman I met, I
met in front of the hotel,
and she was tiny and a little
chubby, and she was in her 50s.
She had spent the
majority of her time here,
and she feels like this place is hers.
And that she still
needs to be in charge.
She's very unhappy with
how the place is being run.
If she sees something's being done
differently than how she would do it,
she kind of throws a fit.
And she does definitely
make physical contact.
Now, one of the reasons
we're here is because your...
- Customers are getting scratched.
- Mm-hmm.
Different areas of the hotel
were having situations where...
People are actually
physically being scratched,
drawing blood, and so
I'm getting concerned.
You know, my employees are
freaking out. They're being touched.
And, so, that's kind of
why I called you guys.
We may go belly-up.
Well, let me tell you
about the woman that ran
this town, basically,
before this hotel was built.
Her name was Shotgun
Kitty. She was 4'11...
- She weighed over 200 pounds...
- Okay.
And I got a photo of her
actually in her younger days.
Now, the reason she was called
Shotgun Kitty is because she
always carried a shotgun with
her, and when she ran the brothels,
she was always breaking up fights
between the miners and the prostitutes.
She didn't take no crap from nobody.
So, do you think this
might be the woman you see?
Granted, she's much older when
I saw her, but other than that...
I think so.
So, the next thing I saw was a
confrontation between two men.
This was in the 70s or the 80s.
So, this one man is
sitting in the room...
And this other man comes
charging into the room and...
Shot him in the head.
So, he's a little confused about...
What ended up happening, so he
kind of stumbles around that area.
I mean, there was only one
mysterious death in this area.
Back in the time frame you're
talking about, that we uncovered.
Back in '76, a guy named William
Thomas Moore went missing in July.
I have his death certificate here.
He was found two months
later in the sewage plant.
Right on the property here.
His body was so decomposed
that they actually had to
go through dental records
to identify who he was.
There's local folklore
going around that prior to...
Moore being found dead, there was an
argument and that he might've been shot.
So, how'd the rest of your
walk go? What did you see?
So, the next part is um...
The hallway.
They have a name for that
area called Spooky Hollow.
So, there were a lot of
upset and angry dead people.
They're sick and tired of
being messed with by the living.
They feel like they're being tortured.
They said that there had been
a lot of investigations here.
The living were messing with the
dead here in a very negative manner.
I could actually see where that might be a
possibility because we do have people that
do come here and do investigations.
And I didn't realize
that it would affect uh...
The non-living in that way.
I've been saying all
along to leave them alone.
Because it would bug me, living,
to have somebody constantly...
- In your face?
- Yeah.
So, I did a sketch of
the people that are here.
Um, some are angry, and
some are asking for help.
There's a hallway, and...
There's fifteen, twenty people.
And they're all not looking good.
Well, that's... that's pretty creepy.
Got a lot of people there.
Wow.
There was one man who confronted me.
He stood out from a lot of them.
He's very advanced and very
powerful, and he's very upset.
He despises living people.
He kind of runs the dead back here.
And he's the one who really lashes out.
There's an area here... it's at
the very end of Spooky Hollow...
Where I'm confronted by this individual.
And it's overwhelming to me.
I don't go back there because I
feel like I'm invading somebody...
It's going into somebody else's home you're
not welcome to... like, that feeling.
That's not good.
What's the story with this guy?
He... was not very good in life
and took whatever he wanted in life.
And he wanted a lot of
power, and he wanted respect.
I felt his death, and I felt
that it was from strangulation.
- You're kidding, really?
- Yep.
There was a man who worked and
lived here who was a janitor
that actually hung himself right
in this hallway back in 1947.
It's interesting that you talk about
this. This is the guy here, Thomas Blower.
He waited until everybody went on their
lunch break, and he came back here,
and he hung himself.
The funny part about this guy is when
I talked to an historian about him,
before he was a janitor, he used to
travel the world with quite a bit of money.
And he was checking into Canada in
1924, he had $2,500 in cash on him.
Which was basically a
fortune back in 1924.
I actually have the manifest here.
Now, you said the guy
wanted power and respect.
The guy I talked to said he
may have been a highway robber.
To come across that kind of
money didn't make any sense.
So, here's a guy that was probably a
thief in life, robbed a lot of people.
But he died broke working as a janitor
right here and then hanging himself.
- Does that make sense to you?
- Well, yeah.
He can make you feel true fear.
He can reach into your mind
and project back what will...
Make you scared, and it
makes you want to run.
And he is a fighter, and he
absolutely has no intention of leaving.
He's sick of the living
messing with him, and...
He is absolutely ready to fight back.
He wants to drive the
living out of this place.
And he's sick of the living
messing with him, and...
He is absolutely ready to fight back.
How frightening is this for you?
Last time I went back here,
somebody followed me...
All the way around.
And they kept touching, and
I never came back here again.
Mm-hmm.
There's places I just
straight will not go...
Day, night, doesn't matter.
I know we gave you a lot
of information tonight.
But the reason you brought us in is,
is it safe for you guys to be here,
for your employees to be here, and,
really, most importantly, your guests.
For that, I'm gonna turn it over to Amy
and see if she's got an answer for us.
This place was so occupied by the
dead and the residual energy...
That there's, like, no room for life.
This could be a place where,
instead of having Ghost Hunters
come, you have people who...
Are spiritual.
Now, you're going to need
a few various holy men,
and they need to do
funerals and blessings.
Does it matter what denomination
the priest or the pastor is?
No, it doesn't really matter.
They're each going to do
a different type of ritual,
blessing, cleansing,
or moving on process.
It will clear a substantial
amount of people out of here.
But there's still going to be
people who don't want to leave,
or people who don't click with
anybody, people who just want to stay.
So, the angry guy that's back here,
will he stay or will he move on?
Oh, he's gonna be thrilled
about what we're talking about.
He wants to stay, but he
wants to be left alone.
You know, the ghost hunting's have just
got to stop, or it's gonna get worse.
Okay.
I think we need to come back here
and talk to the spirits a little bit
and apologize and move it forward.
So, is that why it got crazy here?
- Because they were, like, fed up?
- They're done. Yeah.
And, I mean, this isn't
gonna happen overnight.
But if in the long run it gets better...
- Then that's good.
- Yeah.
Let's get started now.
I think it has started.
With all of the dead
surrounding this location,
Rich and Mary Lee have
their work cut out for them.
But I'm confident that
if they follow my advice,
they should be able to keep their
employees and guests safe from harm.