Subs created by: David Coleman.
There is a lot of
sadness and a lot of fear.
It scares me.
There is something in this
house that I can't see.
I was pulled into the closet.
They get pissed. They attack.
I have definitely stirred things up.
Amy's not gonna like that.
It's kind of demented.
They're trying to get
out, and they can't.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing's, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people.
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her?
It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were
ghosts in this house.
As a former Detective, I
know most cases can be solved,
if you know where to look.
That's why I look into the location's dark
history and interview living witnesses.
While Amy communicates with the dead.
This is an interesting case.
I did some homework, and I'm kind of
suspicious of our client's motives.
So I'm not willing to disclose exactly
where I am until I find out more.
I got a call from a guy named
Todd, who's a single dad.
He went and bought this mansion in
hopes of turning it into a hotel...
But he says things there are out of
control, and he thinks it's not safe.
Worst of all, he thinks it's his fault.
He still deserves an
honest investigation.
At least until I can find out
what his exact intentions are.
Before Amy arrives, I have to clear
the area of any leading information.
This house doesn't look lived in,
but it's still important that I remove
anything that could influence her findings.
When I'm done, the location
will be ready for tonight's walk.
There's a lot of people
here, and they're sick.
None of 'em are thinking right.
It's overwhelming me because
they're all kind of, like, coming.
I'm very nervous to go upstairs.
I feel very uncomfortable about that.
It's disturbing.
Todd, when I spoke to you on the phone,
you sounded like you were
in a pretty bad place.
What's going on in this house?
I want to make this into a hotel and
be able to pass this down to my son.
So, what's stopping you?
There's just so much
activity in this house.
We hear people's footsteps.
We can see apparitions.
People are being physically touched.
Hanging around the neighborhood
and talking to people,
they told me that you turned
this place into a haunted house.
So, what's the story with that?
Well, during the Halloween season, I
would open up as a Halloween attraction.
I ran that for eight years,
and around approximately 30,000
people came through every October.
I could tell you right now,
Amy's not gonna like that.
- No?
- Because you're exploiting the dead.
I believe Todd's story,
but he's also making money off of what's
going on here, so he's got a conflict.
I've seen this happen before,
and it never ends well for these
guys once Amy does her walk.
I believe over these years, I
have definitely stirred things up.
Beyond a reasonable doubt, there is
something in this house that I can't see.
Ugh.
I just feel people freaking
themselves out constantly.
It's this thing that
living people left here.
Residual fear.
You're, like, oh, oh, God.
Oh, God, I'm so scared.
But it's not... it's not real.
They're showing me people who are
alive, and they're laughing at them.
Like, they're just
like, this is ridiculous.
- The dead are laughing at the living?
- Yes.
Todd, why'd you bring me
up here? What's going on?
There's been a lot of
groups come through here,
exploring and investigating,
doing their EVP sessions.
So, how many groups
are we talking about?
I would say approximately
maybe 100 groups.
100?
Yeah, over all these years, they've
come in and done their investigation.
You still continue to
have people come in?
No, there's no more
investigating whatsoever.
- And when did that stop?
- Probably about two years ago.
From what the city says,
the building is unsafe.
It's just been sitting
here vacant by itself.
It seems to me that...
The living have put more
negativity into this place,
than the dead.
A lot of stuff has been cleaned here.
You mean, like, entities?
Mm-hmm. It's, like, psychics.
And people trying to talk to them
all the time and things like that.
They think it's...
[Bleep] Up.
When I come in, I say, just let me
know what you want people to know.
This is all they want people to know.
This is [Bleep] up. This is sick.
Anything else in this room?
- I was decorating this wall right here.
- Okay.
Out of my peripheral vision,
I could see a full-figured black
entity standing at this doorway.
- This one here?
- Yes.
And within a second, it rushed me.
It just came from that
doorway straight up to me.
I jumped, I screamed, and it was gone.
You got a lot of traffic
out in front of this place.
You sure it couldn't have been,
like, a light reflecting something,
and then, as it moved,
it came towards you?
I have never been more sure of anything.
That it was that black figure,
and it came right up to me.
That frightened me.
I think people have
had experiences in here.
Do the dead interact with them at all?
Yes. They attack.
The dead here are fed up
with people harassing them.
Now they're fighting back, trying to
force the living out of their space.
They get pissed.
And they will...
You know, really jump on the living.
So, what do they do?
Pushing, they try to be very physical
and push the living people out of there.
I think it's really important that you
know that this used to be the Sanitarium.
What kind of patients we talking about?
- Mentally ill patients stayed here.
- Did they leave any records behind?
They did. Up on the fourth floor. You
are more than welcome to go through 'em.
Okay.
And over here is where
the hospital wing was.
It was a wing?
There was a 10,000-square-foot wing
right here that housed 17 bedrooms.
So, what happened to it?
I demolished it all.
Okay, now, did you have
an experience in there?
Yes. When I was in the hospital wing,
getting ready to open up
for the Halloween attraction,
something came up behind me and
physically touched me on my lower back.
It felt like a human hand.
And I turned around quickly to see
if someone else needed my attention,
and no one was there.
I think there were a lot of
people here who were mentally ill.
It just kind of creeped me out because
it's, like, they can't communicate, really.
They just look...
Weird.
Either way drugged out, so
it made them, like, be like...
No, I really think that they
were nuts because of how they...
Are moving.
How do they move?
Just, you know, you have, like, the
ones who are crawling on the walls.
Ooh, I don't like 'em.
So, Glenda, thanks for meeting me here,
but it seems like you're a little...
Uneasy being in the house.
Mm-hmm, yes, I am.
I just get the shakes
every time I come in here.
One of my friends, when she
came here, got violently ill.
It was like she was
having a heart attack.
As a matter of fact, she went
to the hospital for three days.
What was wrong with her?
To this day, six years later,
they still haven't figured it out.
Okay, have you had experiences?
Yes.
We were in one of the rooms upstairs,
and I got touched right here.
And then, just a few minutes later,
they started touching my head, hard.
Okay, what did you do?
I ran into the other room and just
stayed put for the rest of the night.
- I wouldn't go anywhere else.
- Now, let me ask you a question.
The night this stuff
happened you sure nobody was
messing around with you
being that it was dark?
No, there was nobody around me.
- At all?
- No.
Pretty much since that night, every
time I come in here, I get touched.
It scares me.
I don't particularly like it down here,
because the dead people...
Hang out down here a lot.
There is a man who's very agitated.
So I think he could actually
be pretty aggressive,
as far as trying to
reach out and get help.
In life, when they were locked
down here, trying to get out,
they're trying to get
out, and they can't.
It's very chaotic.
Just hearing the movement,
scratching on the walls,
screaming, banging on the
walls, trying to get out.
Like, those noises.
I don't like it at all.
What do you think about
Todd owning this place?
At first when he bought it,
I encouraged him, you know?
Oh, my gosh, it's like a
gold mine type of thing.
You know, he was doing
the Halloween attraction.
And then as things start
happening, and I see things,
and I feel things, I'm
like, I'd get rid of it.
What do you think your brother
should be doing with this house?
Bulldoze it down, and then... I
mean, it's on commercial property.
Do something else.
Let me ask you a question. Would
you stay here overnight alone?
- Absolutely not.
- Okay.
I will never stay here again.
I will not shut my eyes in this home.
Something here has been getting
physical with people inside the mansion.
So I've reached out to one
of Todd's former employees,
from when this place was
a Halloween attraction,
who says she had a terrifying
experience while on the job.
Laura, I understand that you
actually used to work here.
Yes. I would just pop
out and scare people.
Laura, Todd told me that you
had a pretty bad experience here.
Why don't you tell me about it?
I was standing here in this closet
wearing a black cloak to not be seen.
And before we opened the
house, I was pulled back,
into the closet, like,
hands grabbing me.
And I had to jiggle away.
I turned on my flashlight to make sure that
I didn't get caught on a nail or anything.
- Okay.
- And I...
So I just kind of tugged
away and ran out of here.
Okay so you looked behind you with the
flashlight, you didn't see anything?
Didn't see anything.
And anybody else couldn't have
been in the closet with you?
No.
When I ran out, my boss said that,
you look like you saw a ghost.
And he goes, well, what are you doing?
Go back in, we're getting ready to open.
I said, no, I quit.
- So, you quit that night?
- I quit that night.
I checked Laura's employment records.
And sure enough, she did
quit her job that night.
Okay, so, have you been back here since?
- No.
- Okay. How do you feel now being in here?
Very nervous.
This isn't good. It isn't
cute. It's not funny.
It's kind of demented.
That's what they just said.
Who's they?
The dead.
As I walk through this mansion,
I keep hearing the dead yelling
about how they've had it with
the living antagonizing them.
They're repulsed, really repulsed.
Do you know if that's the sort of thing
that living people might pick up on?
I think that they yell at them and...
Try to push them out with their energy.
It can be pretty violent.
Todd mentioned his mansion
used to be a Sanitarium.
So I'm heading over to
meet with the County Coroner
who knows all the history
about the building.
He says the stuff that went on behind
those walls is gonna turn my stomach.
So, Dr. Hadden, the
place I'm investigating,
I found out, used to be a Sanitarium.
Yes.
And I was wondering what kind of
patients would have been there.
When it first opened, they
took Tuberculosis patients.
Okay.
I have here an ad that we
found in an old phone book.
And it looks like a lovely home.
They make it look inviting.
Yes, but I suspect inside,
it was anything but inviting.
Tuberculosis is very contagious.
TB patients are spitting up
blood, coughing uncontrollably.
There was loss of weight,
inability to breathe properly.
It was a very, very unhappy place.
I see uh, a woman.
She's kind of leaning against the wall.
But she's this kind
of weird beigey color.
Like she's sick.
Like, I feel, like, nauseated.
Like, I see a guy
throwing up in the corner.
Yeah, there's, like, a lot of illne...
I'm feeling a lot of illness here.
Tuberculosis was the second leading
cause of death in The United States,
so you can well imagine that there were
lots and lots of people dying from it.
So, I can assume, a
lot of dead bodies went
through the doors of the
place I'm investigating.
Yes.
We have stories about
how they'd be five or six,
bodies at any given time in
the basement of the facility.
They had nothing to do with them
but put them in the basement.
Until the mortician
comes to pick them up.
Okay, so, once the person's
dead, are they still contagious?
Yes. It's an incredibly
bad thing to do because,
it can help spread the disease
as the body breaks down.
Okay.
There are dead bodies...
Down here. I'm not sure how many.
It rotated, it seems like.
They kind of travel as a pack.
And they don't really
want to be bothered.
They want to be left alone.
There's a lot of sadness
and a lot of fear.
You mentioned there were some
horrible things going on in that place.
What are we talking about?
It was very crowded. We know that
they had 1 nurse for 20 patients.
- Okay.
- And these are desperately ill people.
These are people who are dying, and one
nurse cannot administer to all their needs.
Okay.
Now, the TB epidemic, did it ever
kind of slow down at some point?
Yes, it did, when therapeutics came
in, and that would be in the '50s.
And the medicine worked pretty well, so
sanitariums kind of went out of business.
Okay, so, what happened to
the place I'm investigating?
Did they ever get
different patients, or...
Well, they looked for a new clientele.
So they took in the mentally ill.
You could have severely
depressed patients.
You could have schizophrenics.
You could have bipolar.
Okay, so, now they have mental patients,
in this facility where they
used to have TB patients.
Did their conditions get
better for the mental patients?
Well, I think they got worse.
We do have a list of
transgressions of mistreatment.
And these are people who have filed
complaints against the institution.
They would treat mental
patients very poorly.
They would chain them
to toilets and sinks.
They would have them
lying nude in the hallway.
Some did electroshock
therapy and lobotomies.
Or they'd over medicate them
and make them barely conscious.
Why did this place actually close?
I can only suspect what happened is, as the
state inspection became more stringent...
They could not meet the new standards.
They had desperately ill people, and they
just did not know what to do with them.
I feel someone being held down...
Against their will. They're
trying to fight back.
They're struggling and trying to get
away, and this guy is, like, getting...
Like, his head is, like, slammed
into the wall or something.
There's a lot of crying.
Men and women are crying.
They're screaming.
There's, like, this...
Humming noise. A male, like...
Mmmm.
People just died here from
mental or regular illnesses.
Things did happen here.
Accidents that resulted in death.
Todd told me that a bunch of
old records were left behind,
from when this place was a Sanitarium.
As I dig through them, the
same name keeps turning up...
Carl Lamoreaux.
I need to find out more about
his connection to this property.
I'm on my way to meet with a local
attorney who did some digging for me.
And she said she found some information
that could really help my case.
This guy, Lamoreaux, his
name's all over everything.
I mean, patient records,
insurance claims, staff lists.
What were you able
to find out about him?
Well, he ran the facility
from about 1973 until 1985.
He died in 1985 at his own facility.
He was only 57 years old at that time.
From what I was told, there was a lot
of abuse in this place at some point.
There were many, many allegations and
complaints brought against the facility.
And many of the claims came out
after his death, interestingly enough.
Why would all these
claims come after he dies?
Well, it appears that Lamoreaux
was somewhat of a public figure.
He was a hospital administrator, and
he was somewhat of an intimidating guy.
If he's such a prominent, public figure,
I mean, why would he allow this to happen?
Well, what we discovered
is that he's not just
the administrator for
the Clovis Sanitarium.
He is the administrator for
many other facilities, as well.
And so, he might have been
a little overextended and
might not have really paid a lot of
attention to the Clovis Sanitarium.
Okay.
However, we discovered that a Gladys
Brashears and her husband, Lee,
actually ran the facility from about 1942
all the way until Lamoreaux took over.
Okay, what about them, any
claims that you saw against them?
Well, there's been a lot of complaints and
allegations, as well, against the facility.
However back in those days
there wasn't a lot of oversight,
and a lot of the patients
safety-safeguards that we have,
weren't in place back then.
This man and woman oversaw or were
living here or owned this place.
They're saying that they
took care of things very well.
But I don't trust them.
I think they're liars.
And these two are saying
that they did a good job.
We did a good job. We did
a good job. We did good job.
I'm just, like, no, you know, like,
I don't know what the [Bleep] you did,
but you didn't do a good [Bleep] job.
And then I hear partners in crime.
It's very bad.
I'm at the library to
see if I can find anything
more about Todd's property
prior to it being a Sanitarium.
I don't get any direct hits, but
one article catches my attention.
It turns out a guy named Tony
Andrews originally built the place...
But lost it in foreclosure.
Now that I know the original owner
of the property was foreclosed on,
I need to find out more
about this guy, Tony Andrews.
I've contacted a local genealogist,
who tells me losing the house was only
the beginning of this guy's tragic story.
Donette, thanks for meeting
me, I appreciate that.
This guy, Tony Andrews, what
can you tell me about him?
Tony Andrews was from an
Italian immigrant family.
- He's first generation.
- Okay.
He had a lot of dreams.
He had a big ego.
Okay.
He met his beautiful wife, Della.
She liked nice things, and he decided to
build her this beautiful, huge mansion.
Okay, so, now, how did
he wind up losing it?
He just overspent.
- Okay, so, he lived way above his means.
- He did.
He ended up making an agreement
with one of the neighbors,
that if he could live on
a house on their property,
that he would harvest their grapes.
- What about his wife and kids?
- His wife and kids came with him.
- Oh, so they all lived?
- They all lived in the small house.
They went from their beautiful,
huge mansion to a small home.
And they got room and board for
working the crops on the property.
So, what ended up happening to Tony?
He worked the vineyards
for a couple of years,
and then, unfortunately, he passed away.
He dies at age 36, and I found
his death record right here.
- 36?
- 36 years old.
What did he die of?
Cirrhosis of the liver?
Correct.
So, there's this little guy...
And he says that he
rules the roost here.
He...
Is saddened by the state...
Of this location.
Because it was quite something.
I feel like he was kind of forced...
To let it go.
It wasn't something he wanted to do.
- Do you know when this was?
- I want to say 1920s.
He never liked people being here.
It's a violation of his privacy.
He's just absolutely
disgusted about everything.
I had this, like, really
bad, bad feeling about him.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations.
We're ready to reveal our findings to our
clients and each other for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to meet Todd.
He owns this mansion.
This is his sister Glenda.
She's had some bad experiences here, and
as far as she's concerned he should just...
Cut his losses and sell the place.
Todd's dream is to
turn this into a hotel.
The activity's gotten so bad
here that he feels it's not safe.
His dream is crumbling around him.
So, with that being said,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy,
we're gonna hear about her walk.
So, the first thing that I want
to start off with is that...
There was this guy outside.
And he was telling me how
he once ruled the roost here.
We were looking at the
outside of the structure,
and he was saying how sad he was,
that this used to be quite
something when he owned it.
What I got was that he
lost this place in the '20s.
He was put in a position where he
had to sell it, he had to give it up.
That makes a lot of sense. The
guy that built this place...
Was a first-generation
Italian, Tony Andrews.
And he wound up building
this place in 1922.
You mentioned that he
got in over his head.
Yeah, what happened was, the house
wound up getting foreclosed on in 1927.
And the sad part is that,
when he did sell the house,
he had to go live on a very small bit
of a shack with his wife and two kids.
He died young. He died at 36 years
old of cirrhosis of the liver.
There's his death
certificate right here.
The house foreclosed
in '27. He dies in 1929.
- Wow.
- Do you think that's who you saw?
- Yes.
When I first walked in here, at
the top of the stairs, I see people.
And their energy was not healthy.
They were severely mentally ill.
And they were crawling um...
On the ceiling and down
the side of the stairs.
The ones that were coming down the stairs
were very aggressive, very scary-looking.
And it's almost like this chaos that's
within the mind is now their body.
And some guys vomiting all over the
place, you know, it was pretty uh...
Gross.
You looked pretty upset when
she was talking about that.
I'm sorry. I don't mean
to get so emotional, but...
I don't know. I just...
it makes me sad to think...
That they're like that.
I'm sorry.
Well, maybe I can explain to
you what you might have seen.
When Andrews lost his house, it went
through various hands over the years.
Around 1940, it became a Sanitarium.
It housed a lot of elderly people,
and you mentioned about throwing up.
- Now, they housed TB patients here.
- Oh.
Matter of fact, I got
an ad from back then.
This is from the beginning right here.
One of the symptoms of
TB is coughing up blood.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Once the TB subsided...
They started bringing in mental
patients, schizophrenics...
All the things you mentioned were
the people that they housed here.
I've had people come in here with me,
and out of nowhere, they have thrown up.
Yeah, and I had a friend
that we were in here.
Kind of went through the whole
house, and she got violently ill.
Violently ill. She did throw
up. I took her to the hospital.
She was in the hospital for
three days, and to this day...
They don't know what was wrong with her.
I did a sketch of a scene I
saw when I first walked in here.
There were several dead lined up.
They're very, very thin.
And then I saw this man
shifting into this...
Black thing on the second floor.
It's creepy and sad at the same time.
Oh.
I don't like that.
It gets me choked up because...
It feels like there
are people everywhere.
What else did you see on your walk?
I saw a lot of mistreatment.
And there was a woman who was
being held down and beaten.
And I saw in the kitchen another...
Patient having his head beat in.
I talked to the County Coroner.
During the time when this
place was run as a Sanitarium,
he said the conditions
here were horrible.
People naked laying on the floor.
They chained people to toilets.
You know, they did electroshock
therapy, even some lobotomy.
- Oh, geez.
- Some of the treatment that happened.
I just can't believe that this
place was actually utilized that way.
It's funny you say that because
it wasn't only just this house.
There used to be a structure
here that housed mental patients,
and Todd had it knocked
down five years ago.
We had big trucks come
in and bulldozers and...
Smash everything up and haul it away.
But activity started increasing and,
people started experiencing a lot more
things in here, in the mansion itself.
Wow.
The next thing I saw was creepy.
I was upstairs, and...
There are these two
people, a man and a woman.
And they were standing in the hallway.
They kept repeating
that they did a good job.
They were, like, almost
trying to convince themselves.
I felt that they were liars
because there was all of this death,
and mistreatment around me
and it was just really...
Disgusting.
That's interesting.
Let me tell you about a couple
of people that ran this place.
Carl Lamoreaux was in
charge from '73 to '85.
I ran through some records in the attic.
There's stacks here of complaints.
Lamoreaux's name is all over
all the paperwork up there.
Now, prior to that, before
Lamoreaux came into the picture...
- You mentioned a woman.
- Mm-hmm.
There was also a woman
named Gladys Brashears.
Gladys Brashears ran this place for 40
years during the worst time of its abuse.
She sold this place to Lamoreaux in '73.
He passes away here in this
building in '85 at the age of 57.
This is his death certificate.
- Hmm.
- Wow.
So, what else did you see?
So, then, I went into the basement...
And I saw lots of bodies.
They were being rotated.
Like, bodies were coming and going, coming
and going, and they were trying to leave.
And they were, like, confused and
trying to reach out to get help.
When they reach out, though, would they
reach out to us, like, living people?
They're trying to, yes.
You constantly get
touched when you're here.
Down there, always, mm-hmm.
Now, why her?
They'll reach out to whomever
they think can hear, feel, see.
So, you're probably a
sensitive in some respects.
I think I can explain the
bodies in the basement.
During the TB epidemic, it was
so bad, the bodies were piling up.
They were dying, they'd
pile 'em in the basement.
It could be five, six days before the
mortician would come for these bodies.
The other thing I got was, I'm
feeling fear from the living here.
Over many, many years...
The living have left their fear behind.
And it's not healthy.
I mean, it's tangible fear.
I got that there are
sensitives walking the place.
I got seances.
People trying to communicate
with the dead here.
Unfortunately, when that happens, it...
Leaves scars.
I'm gonna call you on
the carpet now, all right?
Why don't you tell Amy what you've
done to make money in this place,
to turn this into a
dream hotel for yourself?
Well, when I first bought the
property, my goal was to...
Eventually make it into a hotel, a
beautiful place, but in the meantime...
I had a Halloween attraction here.
So, over the 21/2 weeks that
we were open for 8 years...
- Over 30,000 people came through.
- Holy [Bleep]
Why don't you explain to her how
many paranormal investigations...
A lot of paranormal investigators
have come in over the years.
You told me at least 100
teams came through here.
Oh, yeah, absolutely, mm-hmm.
And my ultimate goal would be to completely
refurbish it back to a beautiful home.
- And pass it down to my son.
- Mm-hmm.
And have it opened up for the
public to come in and stay the night.
As a nice hotel?
- As a nice hotel.
- Not a haunted hotel?
Well, if people have an experience
in here, I can't control that.
But if people do want to
come in here, it's up to them.
But would you advertise
it as a haunted hotel?
If people have an experience
in here, I can't control that.
But if people do want to
come in here, it's up to them.
But would you advertise
it as a haunted hotel?
Yes.
How would you like to die
and be tormented and stuck?
Think of the most [Bleep]
that happened in your life.
The worst [Bleep] you've ever been through,
and you're reliving that every single day.
And now you're gonna be
[Bleep] with through eternity.
Really think about that.
I'm just saying, it bothers me.
You know, like I said, when I walk in, I
say hello, I have respect for what's here.
And so you should.
Because you have a lot
of dead people here.
And most of them want help.
They are kind of at their wits' end.
They're going to really
start to become aggressive.
I ain't coming back here, Todd.
Well, Todd, you've seen the
results of the investigation,
and what we came up with.
You still caused a lot of the problems
here, but the big question is...
Can you turn this place into
the dream hotel that you want to?
I can't answer that, but hopefully
Amy can give you some answers.
You need to provide...
Counseling for the dead that are here.
It would be great if you can
find a transpersonal psychologist.
Transpersonal psychologists are
trained to deal with the mentally ill.
And a lot of them are sensitives,
so they should be able to
help with the people here.
Unfortunately, for the ones who
don't respond to treatment...
These are probably going to be the more
aggressive individuals that are here.
And they'll have to be probably
more aggressively moved out.
How do you aggressively get
rid of the rest of the dead?
Exorcism would be the way I'd go.
They're not human anymore.
The exorcism would knock those
suckers right out of here.
I mean, these are sociopaths.
These are killers.
Well, it sounds like you have
all intentions of not listening,
and making it a haunted hotel.
Correct.
Since you're gonna list this as a
haunted bed-and-breakfast or whatever.
If you do that, the people that
stay here do it at their own risk.
Also let them know that the
dead that are still here,
at that time are aggressive.
You're putting yourself at risk.
I'm just gonna tell ya, you are.
And the guests who stay
here will be at risk.
Now, would you at least follow Amy's
advice before you open the hotel?
Absolutely.
I appreciate that Todd was honest
about opening a haunted hotel.
But that doesn't mean we're gonna
lead people to the front door.
If you really want to help him torment the
dead, I'm sure you can find his location.
But you're gonna have to
deal with the consequences.