Subs created by: David Coleman.
She knows she's freaking scaring them.
There's something here.
I can hear footsteps walking behind me.
You can feel that you're being watched.
She had been stabbed and hacked.
He killed her.
I'm not gonna walk away.
She's inside of me.
This is going to be a
difficult walk for me.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing is, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people.
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her? It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were
ghosts in this house.
Amy and I are called
in to investigate cases,
when our clients have
nowhere else to turn.
I interview living witnesses and
dig into the history of the location.
Looking for secrets buried in the past.
While Amy communicates with the dead.
I'm in Cambridge Springs, Pennsylvania.
It's about 100 miles
north of Pittsburgh.
I received a call from a woman
named Brenda, who owns a local hotel.
She says things have gotten so
bad that her employees are scared,
and her guests are having
terrible experiences.
She says if we can't help,
she may lose her business.
Before Amy arrives, I look for anything
that could influence her findings.
This hotel is filled with
historical photographs,
that have to be covered or removed.
When I'm finished, the location
will be ready for tonight's walk.
This is going to be a
difficult walk for me.
I feel dizzy and...
Confused... very confused.
There's a lot of death.
Someone did suffer...
Major head trauma here.
It was agony... absolutely just agony.
Mm.
- Brenda?
- Yes.
Very glad you're here.
- How long you owned this place?
- This is the beginning of our fourth year.
Way back in 1986, my husband and I pulled
up in front of the hotel, and we said...
"Man, if we ever won the lottery,
I would want to buy the Inn".
Um, about four years ago,
the opportunity arose.
Didn't win the lottery, but we sank
every penny we have into the place.
So, at what point did you
realize you have a problem here?
Well, after we talked
to some of the employees
that had worked here over the years.
I realized that we had a couple
that were afraid to work in
the dish room by themselves
because they had seen things.
Talking to different customers, I realized
that there are a lot of things going on.
People being touched, things
disappearing out of the dinner theater.
Quite a few things.
- Is it hurting business?
- Absolutely.
Nobody wants to go into a
hotel that they don't feel safe.
One guest leaves here saying,
oh, something happened in my room.
He tells 10 other people.
I think there are people that
really would be afraid to...
Come and stay at a place
that they think is "haunted".
My main concern is that this inn
stays here for the next hundred years.
And you got how much savings
invested in this place?
Everything.
- So, for you to shut it down would...
- I'd go bankrupt.
There's a lot of inner conflict
with the dead people here.
There's a lot of issues
between them, a lot of fighting.
There's even, like, cliques.
I'd say there's about three
cliques of dead people here.
And they fight a lot.
The entities here are
so angry with each other,
they are separating themselves
into three warring groups...
The old people, the young people...
And this third group that I can only
describe as juvenile delinquents.
There's this old man here with a cane.
He's a very dominant presence.
He has a beard and mustache,
which are gray and white.
And he beats the younger people
with his cane when they fight.
The living actually
can hear or feel this.
It would be really scary to them.
Brenda, this is a pretty interesting part
of the hotel, why'd you bring me in here?
This is where at one point in
time, my husband and I came up,
and the lights flickered, doors slammed,
and we were the only people in the hotel.
Okay, did the breaker go
or something like that?
Nope. Nope. Not at all. We flipped
the lights off, flipped the lights on.
- They'd come back on again.
- Anything else going on up here?
Well, when I come up here
myself, I always feel watched.
Just a general feeling of
eyes being on you like...
Whoever or whatever might be sitting in one
of these chairs just watching you pass by.
Do you feel that way now?
I always have that feeling that
there's always somebody watching me.
These are where the juvenile
delinquents hang out.
They are plotting and planning in here.
There's at least five kids, and
they like to watch living people.
They're like little spies creeping
around and watching people.
You know, a little
inappropriate behavior.
Like what?
Like shower watching or
people going to the bathroom.
Do you know anything about
the history of this place?
Back in the turn of the century,
it was known as a resort,
kind of like a Fountain of Youth.
Okay, my question to you is,
what if Amy told you that it's not
safe for your guests to be here?
I have no idea what we would do.
I really, really don't.
- Okay, she may tell you that.
- I know.
Okay?
I know you got your heart
and soul in this place.
We do.
Everything we have is right here.
I'm not gonna walk away.
Larry, I was talking to your wife, and she
said that you've been experiencing stuff
down here in the theater.
You can feel that you're being watched.
In what way, like, somebody's peeking
around the corner at you, or actually just
like, sitting next to you, watching you?
Like maybe just sitting, watching
you, or standing there watching.
It can be disturbing.
Anything else going on?
Mostly things disappearing here.
Like what?
Props, shoes. They disappear for
two weeks, and then they reappear.
You sure it's nobody borrowing
this stuff and bringing it back?
Positive, because I have the key.
I personally had a costume
go missing backstage...
And three months later, it
appeared at the front desk.
And nobody could
explain how it got there.
The younger people are
far more rambunctious...
And angry than the old people.
They get all pissy.
They work each other up,
and then they run amok.
So, to the living
people, it seems constant.
There's always something
that's been moved.
Like what?
Uh, anything and everything, really.
So, what else have you seen?
Lights that turn on
and off by themselves.
The building is locked in
the winter when we're closed.
I've had people call and say there
are lights on on the third floor.
I, myself, have come over,
unlocked the building, gone
upstairs, the light is not on.
You sure it's nobody
breaking in, the kids doing...
I want to find a ghost
here or something like that?
Uh, security cameras show nothing.
And we've had the electrical checked, and
there's no problem with the electrical.
I got to ask you a
question... if Amy tells you,
that it's not safe for your guests
to be here, what are you gonna do?
That would be crushing.
This has been a lifelong dream for us.
We've invested our life savings into it.
And then, with the kids,
the juvenile delinquents.
They are fascinated with,
like, equipment and, like,
electronic issues, like,
with the television.
I don't know yet about them.
I think they're the bad seeds.
- Kristi, I was talking to Brenda.
- Mm hmm.
- How long you been working here?
- Nine years.
Now, she told me that you've
had some experiences here?
Yes.
I'll be leaving here, and as I'm walking,
I can hear footsteps walking behind me.
- And nobody else is in the hotel.
- Unh-unh.
And how far behind you do you hear it?
I turn around to see if they're right
there, that's how close it sounds.
- That's how close?
- Yes.
Have you experienced anything else?
In this room, I was
meeting with a bride.
It was in the middle of the
winter, so there was nobody here.
And she goes, I see somebody
walking down the hall.
And I go, really? The doors are locked.
So I turned around, and
we both see this shadow.
Went and looked out this
door, and we saw nobody.
Okay.
- Did it look like a human being walking?
- Yes.
Okay, so, it didn't look
like a mist or anything?
No.
Okay. These things that are going on
here, is it hurting business at all?
I have a couple brides that are leery.
Why do you stay here?
I love my job. I love the hotel.
Now, Brenda was saying how she put
her life savings into this place.
- Are you worried about her?
- Yes. Very much.
You said there were three cliques?
Yes.
Would they be seen at all?
It's possible that
the elderly people are.
But the kids, I would
think that maybe people...
Could possibly see them, just because
they're all about spying and hiding.
Um...
So, like...
There's a lot of people
who are unhappy here.
And then the living people
have negative experiences.
And kind of become negative.
So, Marie, I was talking
to your sister, Brenda,
and she said that you've
had some experiences here?
Yes.
Okay. Can you explain
some of them for me?
I've spent nights where my sister
and I were the only ones in-house.
And I hear, like, what is heavy
furniture being pulled across the floor.
And the one night, we're
up on the third floor.
Well, there's nothing above
us on the third floor, but yet,
I could still hear that noise.
- Does it wake you up?
- It has, yes.
- Okay, so it's that loud?
- Mm hmm.
What else have you experienced?
We were checking curtains in rooms,
and Brenda and Pat, my
other sister, was in front.
And I felt a tug on my shirt.
And I turned around.
There's nobody there.
You didn't get caught on anything?
No. I was right in
the middle of the hall.
Anything else?
Uh, one night, in one
of the rooms, Pat and I,
she was in one bed and I was
in one bed next to the door.
And it was probably 5:00
or 6:00 in the morning,
and I heard, like, a key in the door.
And that's what woke me.
But nobody came in, so I thought,
oh, somebody just has the wrong door.
Okay.
And then it wasn't even
like 15 seconds later...
The sheets and blankets raise
up above where I'm sleeping.
And then I feel this weight, like
someone's laying right on top of me.
I was... I was scared to death.
I tried to wake up Pat, but when you're
that scared, nothing will come out.
It's like you can't
get your voice to work.
It was terrifying. I
couldn't go back to sleep.
Well, let me ask you a question. Have you
ever experienced anything before the hotel?
No. I've never been
a believer in ghosts.
Then that happened. It's like,
okay, there's something here.
There's two women in particular
who do a lot of screaming.
One of them is very depressed.
And she is mad.
And she is always dressed in black.
This is, like, her zone.
This is, I think, where she's seen...
The most and has the most
interactions with people.
Everything she does is creepy.
She has a violent temper.
Brenda told me that her hotel was
once marketed as the Fountain of Youth.
So I'm heading over to
meet with a local historian,
who said that what happened at the
Riverside will definitely help my case.
So, my client said that the
property I'm investigating
might have been a
fountain-of-youth type of a place.
- It was.
- Okay. Now, who owned the property?
Well, that was Dr. John H. Gray.
He's in the photograph here.
He was the one that
discovered the mineral waters.
He was out probing, looking
for oil on his property.
He discovered not oil,
but rather a spring.
So he had it tested, found
it was high in iron, sodium...
Uh, magnesium, potassium, quite
a long list of minerals there.
So, he starts prescribing to the locals.
Here's an advertisement
here that is promoting
what was available
for these individuals.
So, Dr. Gray thought this water
could cure just about anything?
That seemed to be the idea.
Dale, this guy sounds
like some kind of a quack.
Well, it does seem like quackery
by today's medical sciences.
But that's what people
believed back at that time.
Something is not right here.
This used to be nicer grounds.
More...
Lush...
Bigger gardens.
And there's, like, this wetness...
Like oil or...
Water.
And it looks really
nice, but it's, uh...
Not. It caused the misfortunes.
And then I do hear "convalescent"?
It's very...
Strange.
When did he start treating
people with this mineral water?
It was 1884.
This is a photograph that shows a
large number of people at the original,
Gray Mineral spring house.
People would stand 100 people in a
line waiting to buy a glass of water...
Take a seat, drink their water, get
back in line, and do it all over again.
Okay. What kind of people went to him?
A lot of these people would have come
with pre-existing medical conditions.
Everything from gout and diabetes
to disorders of the stomach, kidneys.
Okay, so, did anybody
get cured from this stuff?
There were those that
believed that they were better.
But we're seeing that large
amounts of magnesium...
Uh, can actually lead to serious issues
to the point of even death for some.
All right, so, do we know if anybody
died at the property I'm investigating?
Well, there were about six.
Now, did Gray get in
any trouble for this?
Actually, no. Um, he
lost the hotel in 1890.
They got behind on taxes,
and a year later, he died.
It seems like this place
did serve a lot of purpose.
What do you mean?
There's, like, people coming
and going and coming and going.
I literally see, like, gurneys?
I think that there were
a lot of ill people here.
You okay?
I just feel sick.
I'm a [Bleep] mess.
Dale told me that the
waters at the Riverside,
could have done a lot
more harm than good.
I need to find out what a heavy dose
of magnesium will do to the human body.
So I've called on a
Physiology Professor,
who says the cure could've been
a lot worse than the disease.
The property I'm investigating,
apparently, at one time,
there was a Dr. Gray there that
ran it as a Fountain of Youth,
where the mineral water that
was filled with magnesium,
he said, would cure all diseases.
Now, is there any truth at all to that?
No, absolutely not.
It would seem like
to me, even back then,
that this would still be an
outrageous claim to treat illnesses.
Okay.
This is one of the bottles
I was actually able to find,
that was being sold at the Inn.
So, what would the symptoms be if
somebody had too much magnesium in them?
Well, things like nausea,
dizziness, flushing.
Okay.
Now, I understand there were
six deaths at the location.
Okay.
Could too much of the
mineral water kill somebody?
With the levels of magnesium that
are in that water, it's possible.
Now, were there any diseases that would've
been worsened by taking this stuff?
Certainly. If they had diminished
kidney function or kidney disease...
Or stomach issues.
Then, if it got to be high
enough amounts of magnesium,
it could be respiratory failure and
cardiac arrest, in the worst-case scenario.
There's a lot of physical
pain in this area.
It hurts.
People are crying out in pain.
Really...
Sick.
Very much illness here.
I feel like lots of breathing problems.
Like people might have some...
Seizures.
[Bleep]
Ugh.
I can't even, like, talk. Like, it's...
I'm at the local library to see what else
I can uncover about the property's past.
While looking through
newspaper archives,
I discover a drowning that
occurred right on the hotel grounds.
Now that I know that a kid died right
in the creek on my client's property,
I need to find out what happened.
I'm on my way to meet
with a local crime writer,
who says that tragedy is one of
several that hit the Riverside.
I came across this kid that drowned right
here on the property I'm investigating.
- Yes.
- What can you tell me about that?
That happened in August of 1979.
Okay.
Young man's name was Robert Griffith.
Here you go.
He was swimming with some
friends in the river here,
and was taken under and drowned.
All right. So, this was an accident?
It was an accident, yeah. And they...
Were kind of common in French
Creek, as a matter of fact.
What do you mean by common?
Well, there was a young man who drowned
in the river almost in the same spot.
The very next year. His
name was Michael Catalano.
And I happened to find a
picture of him here for you.
Uh, it was similar circumstances.
He was in swimming and
was taken under and uh...
- And drowned.
- Now, is the river that bad?
Well, the river is kind of deceptive.
It looks calm, but it runs deep.
There's a lot of current in it
to trip you up and pull you under.
French Creek has taken a lot
of lives up and down its length.
There's some people in the water.
They're bloated. I think they're dead.
And there's a woman, this mournful
woman, and she's desperate.
She likes to jump people.
She wants to make
people go in the water.
Would you say this depressed
woman by the river is dangerous?
Yes.
She's, um...
Trying to get me to go in the water.
Can you describe it at all?
She's in me.
Well, inside of me.
So, Don, I've exhausted,
about everything I can investigating
the location, but you had mentioned
on the phone that there were some
other things that might help my case?
You might be interested
in the Doris Hatch case.
- What year was this?
- It was the summer of 1953.
Doris lived literally two
minutes away from here, walking.
Okay.
She was a young lady, 22 years old.
Um...
She worked as a bookkeeper
for a local hardware store.
Okay, so, what happened to her?
She stepped out of the
hardware store and vanished.
Police, once they started investigating,
settled pretty quickly on a
suspect for her disappearance.
And that was William Turner,
her boss at the hardware store.
He's 33.
The day that Doris vanished,
Turner took a business trip.
He was very evasive when he
was questioned by authorities,
as to what that business trip entailed.
Was there any motive behind why
she would have been murdered?
There were persistent rumors
that they were seeing each other,
there was some sort of a romantic
relationship between them.
Don, how long was it before
the body was discovered?
Two 1/2 years later, a
hunter found the body.
She had been stabbed and hacked with
a large bladed weapon, like a machete.
He was tipped off...
To the authorities finding
the body by an Erie newspaper.
And told his wife that he was gonna come
back to Crawford County to clear his name.
Then he took a walk to clear his head.
And when police moved in to
arrest him, he wasn't at home.
They found him propped up against the sea
wall looking out at the Atlantic Ocean.
Dead from a self-inflicted
gunshot wound to the chest.
Did either one of these
people frequent this hotel?
I would say without a doubt,
they have been at the Riverside.
The Riverside, at the time, was a place
for weddings, dinners, Christmas parties.
All that type of thing happened here.
I think there was a dude
who killed a chick here.
It's like there... there...
there was, like, a fight.
They're fighting a lot.
So he killed her. He strangled her.
She says that's what ended her life.
He also seems much older than her.
They were intimate.
She thinks he had it planned out,
like he was gonna murder her anyways.
Like, I'm... hearing them arguing.
And then she's on the floor...
And he's got his knee in her chest.
Like, really squeezing it.
He wants her out of here.
I encountered dozens
of entities on my walk.
He's probably about...
75 years old.
But the leader of the older
clique was the most prominent.
So I decided to sketch him.
He has a cane.
He has a mustache and a beard.
And he has very light, intense eyes.
Is this who you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations...
We're ready to reveal our
findings to our clients,
and each other for the first time.
Amy, I want you to
meet Larry and Brenda.
They're a married couple.
Their dream was to own the hotel.
And a few years back they actually obtained
that dream, but it came with a price.
The activity's so bad here that the guests
and their employees are scared to be here.
They're afraid that if we
can't help and figure out what's
going on in this place, they
might have to lose the business.
With that, I'm gonna ask Amy to
tell us a little bit about her walk.
And see what she uncovered.
I was out on the grounds,
and I felt like I was...
Seeing this substance.
But I didn't know if it
was oil or water or both.
I felt like it had
caused a lot of problems.
And that it's still here.
That's interesting.
The original owner of the property...
And of the hotel itself was
a guy by the name of Dr. Gray.
This is Dr. Gray here.
Mm.
Interesting.
Back in 1859, when he acquired the
property, he started looking for oil.
But what he did discover
was mineral water.
Oh.
And he found out there were
high levels of magnesium in it.
He decided that, with the mineral water, to
make this place into a wellness Sanitarium.
Oh, wow.
Here's a picture of what
it looked like back then.
Interesting, because I
heard the word convalescent.
I saw...
A lot of sick people.
I saw women dressed like nurses,
and I saw a lot of gurneys.
Now, this is one of the original
ads we were able to find.
And basically it says that whatever ails
you, this mineral water would cure it.
Now, I want to show you what
the mineral water looked like.
This is interesting.
They actually bottled
it here in the basement.
You see, it's 1886, Riverside Inn.
- So, they'd just come here and drink it?
- Yeah.
The people that did come
here, they were all sick.
Really? Because I was
sick the entire walk.
Very dizzy, a lot of confusion.
There was severe pain in my head.
I almost vomited at one point.
The living here would
probably experience...
Uh, headaches and nausea.
Hmm.
I might be able to explain that. I
talked to a Professor of Physiology.
He told me magnesium
would never cure anything.
But high contents of
magnesium in your body.
Can make you very sick.
Problems breathing, vomiting,
diarrhea, flushing of the face,
low blood pressure, and dizziness.
And in extreme cases, people have
cardiac arrest and actually die.
We know that at least six people
dropped dead right on the property.
Oh, my gosh.
So, most of the people were
kind of O.D.'ing on this?
Yeah. Basically, yeah.
So, instead of getting better, people
might have killed themselves doing it.
So, what else did you see?
What I noticed was that there were
three different cliques of dead people.
So, there was, like, the group
of elderly people, young adults...
And then what the elderly referred
to as the juvenile delinquents.
The leader of this
elderly group of people
was this guy who had
white hair, a white beard.
He walked with a cane.
And he was just yelling about how...
These two other cliques were obnoxious.
He was very um, authoritative.
You get a good look at this guy?
I sketched the man I saw.
Well, let's take a look at the sketch.
To me, this actually looks like
a younger version of Dr. Gray.
You guys take a look.
See, the nose, to me,
is what's so accurate.
And even the eyes.
- Yeah, the nostrils.
- Mm hmm.
Yeah.
The expression looks the same.
So, do you think that the
guy with the cane is Dr. Gray?
I think so, yeah.
Now, do these cliques do anything that
can affect the people that are living?
There were specifically three
ways of experiencing them.
The young adults, they're into movement,
moving objects, things like that.
And they're fascinated by the
electricity and what it can do
and what they can do with it
and all that kind of stuff.
And then the little juvenile
delinquents are really bad.
They spy on people.
That's their big thing.
The living will often feel watched...
Um, by them.
Literally, any time I'm
walking the hallways upstairs.
I know I'm being
watched. You just feel it.
For at least 10 years...
There have been lights
that come on by themselves,
and when we're closed for the
winter, the building is locked.
Somebody will call and say, oh, there was
a light on on the third floor last night.
And I know nobody's been there.
The other thing she brought up was
another thing we talked about...
Stuff moving, disappearing.
Props, costumes, disappear,
but they always come back.
It's like they're playing
games. They always are.
Could they do a lot more
damage in the future?
Oh well yeah, more and more
devices, will be affected,
as they learn how to do
this really, really well.
Just like the living, the dead can become
fixated on developing their abilities.
And the more they practice, the
more they learn to manipulate energy,
and their surroundings.
So, a lot of stuff
so far. Anything else?
Mm-hmm.
The next thing I saw was a bad
scene when I was on the second floor.
I saw a man who killed a woman.
They were intimate with each
other. He was much older than her.
They were fighting.
I saw him kneeling on her chest
and strangled her in a weird way.
I did come across one murder, but I'm not
sure if it's the one you're talking about.
A woman by the name of Doris
Hatch. She was a 22-year-old girl.
She lived a two-minute
walk from the hotel here.
This is Doris Hatch.
Back in '53, she goes missing.
The person they think responsible for
her death was this guy, William Turner...
This is him.
You had said that she was
younger and he was older?
Well, she was 22, he was 33, and
they were intimately involved.
- Was he married?
- He was.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
She doesn't get found for two 1/2 years.
And when she does get found, her body's
so decomposed that the best they can do
is figure out that she was
hacked to death with a machete.
Oh.
I think that they were in the
building and they did fight here,
but I didn't see him
hack her up for anything.
- But you got that she was murdered?
- Yes.
What else did you see?
I saw people on the
ground, and they were dead.
And their bodies were bloated,
so I got that they drowned.
Well, that's easy enough to explain.
This is French Creek out here.
It actually runs over a hundred
miles. It's actually a river.
And there's been a lot of
drownings associated with it.
Two of those drownings actually
took place right on the property.
Back in '79, this kid here,
Robert Alan Griffith, 17 years old.
Went in the water and he drowned.
A year later, a kid named Michael
Catalano, right here again, drowned.
He was 24 years old at the time.
When I was trying to leave,
I kept going to the water.
I saw this woman. She
jumped inside of me.
She was trying to make me
go in the water and drown.
Oh.
She was feeling very desperate,
and she was in mourning.
She's the only entity that
I came into contact with...
That I felt an immediate threat from.
Now, when you say she jumped you,
she went into your body physically?
Yes.
You don't think that she's responsible
for the death of these two kids?
It's a possibility.
What about the guests that go near
the water, could they be at risk?
Yes.
She's capable of jumping other people.
Now, when you say she jumped you,
she went into your body physically?
Yes.
You don't think that she's responsible
for the death of these two kids?
It's a possibility.
What about the guests that go near
the water, could they be at risk?
Yes.
She's capable of jumping other people.
You got that look that you guys are a
little worried about your guests now.
That makes me concerned. The
water has always been a concern.
Guests are here all
the time for weddings.
You know, a wedding
reception that's outside,
kids running around, we certainly
don't need anyone helping them go over.
Mnh-mnh-mnh-mnh.
Larry and Brenda, listen.
You got hit with a lot of
information today, a lot of history.
The big question is,
is it safe for you guys,
your employees, and
your guests to be here?
For that answer, I'm
gonna turn it over to Amy.
Obviously, I don't care
for the woman outside.
I think that she is possibly...
A threat to the living.
So, what I would recommend
is to find a psychotherapist.
You can go to the local university,
go to their Psych Department.
But this psychotherapist
also needs to be a medium.
This individual should come
and work with the woman outside.
Just to talk to her, find out what's up,
what's going on, why is
she here, all of that.
The second thing is to do a
cleansing of this building.
And what this will do is help with
the removal of some of the residual...
Uh, that's here, and also
some of the dead that are here.
Then what I would recommend,
is you teach the housekeepers
how to do this basic cleansing.
And that one time per week they
incorporate it into their regular duties.
As far as the cliques that I
encountered, the three main cliques...
I don't feel personally
threatened by them.
They're just more chaotic
within each other's groups.
It's not with any malevolent or...
Malicious intent towards the living.
It's up to you if you want to tell
the sensitive to remove them or not.
Um, some may just leave anyway
if they're tired of being here.
Let me ask you. What about the medium?
Will she move on our Dr. Gray?
I wouldn't try to move him on.
Um, but if he chooses
to go, then he can leave.
- He's not a threat?
- No.
The ultimate question is once they do
all this, do you think they'll be okay?
I think so, yes.
Now, you guys got to be relieved. I mean,
this was your dream to own this place.
- Oh, yeah. Absolutely.
- Absolutely.
I'm really glad that we can
actually aid people in moving on.
If they need to move on
and keep our guests safe.
That, above all, is
very important to us.
Just knowing that there's a solution.
And that everyone is safe.
Our guests are safe, we're safe.
Our employees are safe.
It's a big relief.
With so much death
surrounding this location.
Brenda and Larry had their
work cut out for them.
I really hope they follow my advice
and get rid of the woman by the creek.
Or their next event might
not have a happy ending.