Tonight
on "Dead Files Revisited"...
It's freaking creepy.
...a second look
at some of Amy and Steve's
most terrifying cases...
What's with the face?
...new information...
What Amy told me
completely shocked me.
...startling revelations.
I went straight for the priest.
First...
...a return
to Bloomington, Illinois...
I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
...where an uncontrollable
psychopath...
He's **** crazy.
...preys on a family.
Am I the target?
Then we travel
back to Seattle, Washington...
I'm experiencing
20 to 30 deaths.
...where a scornful monster...
I think she kills them.
...puts lives in jeopardy.
And I don't want to die.
Did they face their fears?
What are you gonna do?
Or is the nightmare continuing?
I cast you out, Satan,
and all you demons
and your minions.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing's, like,
a monster.
I speak to dead people.
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to know
if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York City
homicide detective.
I cannot help you
unless I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her?
It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you
stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
...until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's safe
for you to stay...
I want to know the truth.
I want to know
what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you
there were ghosts in this house.
Nothing gets to me more
than a case involving kids.
That's why our investigation
of a family home
in Bloomington, Illinois,
was so intense.
Diane and Mark
had their share
of strange,
unexplained activity,
but their son, Zack,
was getting the worst of it.
After Amy and I figured out
what was really going on,
it was clear we'd gotten there
just in time.
Okay, Diane.
So, what's going on?
Ever since we built the house
about eight years ago,
we've seen an apparition.
He appeared to be,
like, a rancher,
and it has begun
physically touching us.
And that has me
really concerned
because my son, Zack,
has muscular dystrophy.
Geez.
How old is he?
He's 15, and it's left him
using a wheelchair full-time.
Okay. Why are you
calling us in now?
What's the story?
It's gotten to the point
where he's having issues
that doctors cannot explain.
It was really hard living
with this for so many years.
We didn't know
if we were dealing with
something that was evil or dark.
But after I had
some bad experiences
of being physically injured,
I became very frightened
for my son's safety.
That was really scary.
Do you think
it's something in the house
that may be causing
the problems?
I think it is.
I saw this man with an axe.
He smiles at me,
and I feel sick.
I ended up getting stalked
by that man the entire night.
This made my walk
extremely difficult
because he had an energy
I could barely stomach.
I'm seeing
the man with the axe.
Can you describe him?
He's pretty solid.
And usually, the solid ones
are more capable of interacting.
He's crazy.
Like, sociopathic.
He was a murderer.
Ever since we moved in,
anytime I've been down here,
I kind of catch something
on the corner of my eye.
It looks like a dark figure,
kind of short.
Looks kind of like it has
maybe a hunchback.
Just goes by real quickly.
I knew deep down inside
that I had seen something.
But I kept making excuses
for it, saying,
"That's just my imagination.
I didn't really see anything."
I kept making that same excuse
for almost nine years.
I saw it
today when I was down here.
It made me feel
really sick.
You okay? Yeah?
Yeah.
I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
So, I see this doll thing.
It was over there,
and then it ran.
It, like...
went in here.
And it's all black --
like, solid, solid black.
The man with the axe
and the little doll thing
are related.
It was clear to me
that the man with the axe
could somehow control
the doll creature.
Anytime one entity
can influence another,
that's a really bad sign.
Is it dangerous at all?
Yes.
After talking to
Diane's husband, Mark,
there's no question
the two of them needed our help.
What do you think
is going on?
It just seems like everything's
revolving around Zack,
and I'm concerned.
I mean, we don't know
what to do, really.
And now I was about to find out
why they were so concerned.
I was about to meet their son.
So, what are you
experiencing?
One night,
I was laying in bed,
and I saw these kids
playing on the floor.
And then they looked up,
and they just vanished.
Okay.
What else
are you experiencing?
Well, one night,
I heard someone
rummaging through the drawers
out in the kitchen.
And I was so scared.
I thought
someone was in the house.
I did not feel safe
in my house,
but having Steve here
made me a lot more comfortable
than what I was.
I kind of feel more secure
around him.
Are you having trouble
sleeping?
Yeah.
Are you hearing anything?
Yeah, whispers --
like a female whisper.
And what is she saying?
It's kind of mumbling.
Something like this,
like, really quiet.
Zack's life was
already challenging enough.
I was hell-bent on helping him
and his family
figure out what was going on
in their house
and how to stop it.
Like, I'm hearing
a child's laughter.
So, it's, like, this girl --
she's developed
a twisted sense of humor.
Do you have any idea what --
what she's doing?
She's messing with the people.
I've seen this before.
Dead children don't always
understand that they're dead,
and the bad ones end up
tormenting the living.
And what she does is,
like, crawling under the bed
and doing bad things
under the bed,
like coming up and out.
It's freaking creepy.
Next...
It was a very tragic thing.
...a sibling rivalry
ends in bloodshed.
And I hear a gun go off.
Dead.
And in our second
investigation...
I think she kills him.
...life hangs by a thread.
I thought I was gonna die.
Diane's house
in Bloomington, Illinois,
was fairly new,
and nothing about it
gave me any clues
to what was really
happening there.
But after all this time
working with Amy,
I know the house
isn't always the problem.
And it was a local historian
who helped me prove
Diane and her family
weren't the first people
to suffer on that property.
The house
I'm investigating --
I was wondering
if you could help me out
and tell me what was there
before that.
It was a farm,
over 300 acres at one time,
owned by William King
in 1836.
How's life for them?
They had
a great many challenges here.
At the age of 29,
his first wife, Amelia,
died in childbirth,
and two of his boys died
when they were young.
What can you tell me
about William King himself?
What kind of guy was he?
He was a remarkably tough
individual.
Okay.
But he died on the farm
at the age of 41 years.
It was a very tragic thing.
The man with the axe --
like, I don't even know
where this guy came from.
Do you have any idea
why he's here?
I see him, like,
working on the land.
Like, maybe he owned it.
Okay.
When the dead don't want me
to know their story,
they'll sometimes alter
their appearance.
This makes it tougher for me
to see what's really going on,
and the man with the axe
was no exception.
The weird thing is
now he's wearing a suit,
pants -- nice pants --
like he's wealthy.
And he's probably,
like, in his 40s.
I was on a mission
to help a teenage kid
and his family
figure out what was actually
happening in their house.
And now that I knew one
of the previous landowner's sons
had died mysteriously
at a young age,
I needed to find out more.
George was kind of
a wild kid.
He'd been a partyer,
a drinker.
- Now, did George ever run the farm
or take over at any point? - No.
The farm went to his younger
brother, Zephaniah,
not George.
Which is not common, right?
No.
There's these two men,
and they're yelling.
They're yelling.
This one guy really, really
wants to see the other one dead
because he's preventing him
from having what he wants.
I think it's a land thing.
Ordinarily, it would've gone
to the oldest son
that was available
to run the farm.
But George was unreliable,
and the family couldn't
turn it over to somebody
they couldn't trust.
Okay.
Do you get any names on them?
I get a George.
But people don't like him
because, you know,
he's **** crazy.
Now, I heard that George died
kind of mysteriously.
Do you know
anything about that?
Apparently, George was
over at the house for dinner.
He took a nap on the couch,
and a gunshot was heard.
He's, like,
in this little house.
And there's a table,
like, to eat at.
And I see him,
like, in darkness.
And I hear the sound
of a gun go off.
Dead.
I had seen a lot of threatening
entities in that home,
especially
the man with the axe.
But what concerned me more
was how vulnerable
the living were
when they were sleeping.
There's one person
in the bed,
kind of
in the middle of it.
This kind of sheet
of, like, gray mist
is coming out
from under the bed.
Is this what you saw?
Yes.
Up next...
Am I the target?
I think
everyone in the house is.
What happened
after the investigation?
But I will do anything to make
sure my son is protected.
All spirits in this house,
I command thee,
come to the light,
come to the gate.
Mark, Diane, I want you
to meet my partner, Amy.
They have a son, Zack,
who is confined to a wheelchair.
And from the minute
they moved in,
they've been
experiencing things.
The night of the reveal,
we were really anxious.
We were really concerned
that Amy might say,
"Look, it's not safe."
We have this home
specifically built for our son
so that it
would all be accessible,
and it would be really,
really difficult
to try to start that over.
Down here in the basement,
I actually witnessed
a huge fistfight.
There was a male
named George.
He was in his 20s.
And I heard a gunshot.
And I think George...
was killed.
I got to tell you something.
This is the most amazing thing
I've heard
as far as, like, nailing it.
William King, who settled here,
had a son named George.
George was
the oldest available son
that should've been
taking over the farm.
But he didn't get it.
It went, actually,
to his younger brother.
Now, George came here
to the farm,
and he accidentally
shot himself.
So, what else did you see?
I encountered a male
who had an axe.
The bad thing about him
is that he's absolutely crazy.
I would say
he's a sociopath.
And he's able to manipulate
his surroundings.
The next thing
that I ran into
was this weird
little doll.
It's all dark.
It's, like,
made of darkness.
It's this little thing
that the axe man created
that can do his bidding...
to, like, torture
and drive you nuts.
That was frightening,
but it was good
finding out
that there was something
going on in the basement.
It explained my dread
of going down there,
that it wasn't my imagination,
that I wasn't crazy.
This guy William King,
who settled here in 1836--
he lost two sons.
They died on the property.
Does that make
any sense to you?
I did get two children
in the house.
I have sensed for years
that there is a child.
I could hear
the little footsteps
come by me, next to me,
when I was getting ready
to go to bed.
Yeah, the girl here
is very active.
She likes to hide
under the beds.
This is her form
of entertainment.
What about this?
That actually
could be your son.
There's something called
spontaneous psychokinesis.
So, with any ability,
you're going to have
experiences like this.
How old is your son?
15.
It can be hormonal.
Usually, it's around children
who are teenagers.
Does Diane's son
have abilities?
Probably, yeah.
Because Diane does.
What Amy told me about Zack
completely shocked me.
I didn't want to accept
the concept
that Zack could cause
physical things to happen
without even
physically doing anything.
I really didn't know
how to take it.
I did do a sketch
of what I saw
in the master bedroom
with the girl.
That's usually
where I sleep.
Am I the target?
I think everyone
in the house is.
The most terrifying part
of this whole thing
was this little girl.
I didn't know
if she wanted to hurt us
or get rid of one of us
or what.
It was really hard
sleeping in my room again.
It felt invaded.
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy
and see if she has
some answers for you.
You need to have
a medium come in,
and she's gonna have to get
this little girl out of here.
We also do a cleansing
around the property
to set up a boundary
against the man with the axe
and other various dead
who might wander through.
My question to you now is,
are you gonna follow
Amy's advice?
After the reveal,
I felt like it was
my responsibility as a mother
to take Amy's advice to heart.
Anyone who knows me will know
that I will do anything
to make sure my son
is protected.
And I don't just give up.
When the medium came in,
it was really intense
at the house.
It was really scary.
All spirits in this house,
I command thee,
come to the light,
come to the gate.
Come to the gate.
Go through to the source.
You could just sense how many
ghosts or spirits there were.
So that the entities in this
house may go through the gate
and find the light
so they may find their freedom.
Once the entities
had crossed over,
we felt like this
was our home finally.
We felt like we owned it.
We felt like we belonged here.
The whole air felt
a lot lighter, felt like --
like a weight's been lifted off,
and so it's a lot better now.
We want to make
the most of Zack's life
because he has
this serious illness,
and it's really important
for him to feel safe.
It makes me a lot happier
having my mom not worry
about different spirits
bothering her at night
or worrying about me.
After coming into contact
with the spirit world,
I feel more accepting
of Zack's illness
because it helped me
deal with the grieving process
and that you need to let go.
He needs every moment,
and he needs his moments
to be happy.
It's clear
that this entire experience
has been challenging
for Diane and her family,
but I'm hopeful that their
efforts to cleanse the home
will make their time
in that house peaceful and safe.
Amy and I have investigated
our share of restaurants,
but the Merchants Cafe
in Seattle, Washington,
left an unforgettable
impression.
The activity had sent business
into a nose dive,
and the owner's help
was going with it.
And by the end
of our investigation,
it was clear that the problems
there were even more severe.
Hey, Darcy.
What's going on?
I just got this business
a year and a half ago,
and I've had guests
that believe
they've been pushed
down the stairs,
guests that have seen
apparitions.
I've seen apparitions.
I could go on and on.
Okay.
And this
is affecting business?
It is.
People come in here
all the time and say,
"Why are you still here?
Why don't you just get out?"
And it's not an option.
How about previous owners?
You ever talk to them?
The only thing
I really know
is there were seven owners
in the last eight years.
And I can't afford to be
the eighth in nine years.
I can't do it.
There's, like, too many people.
What's going on?
I'm experiencing
about 20 to 30 deaths.
And it's wreaking havoc
on my body.
From the moment
I entered that building,
the dead completely
overwhelmed me,
and with that many people
fighting for my attention,
the only thing
I could think was,
"Will I be able
to help them all?"
I have all these lives
going through my mind.
There is some crazy ****
Some of his face is missing.
Next...
All the wine
thrown across the floor.
...evil runs rampant.
Get bad people in a bad place,
bad things are gonna happen.
The Merchants Cafe in Seattle
had been around
for over 100 years,
yet it couldn't hang on
to an owner
for more
than a year at a time.
But as soon as the current owner
started showing me around,
it made sense why the turnover
at the property was so high.
Darcy, why'd you bring me
to this spot?
One night at closing,
my manager was here,
and we were arguing,
and it just got misty.
Like a fog?
Like fog.
There were so many times
where I ran out
of this restaurant
over different events
and to the point where
I could not even bring myself
to walk back in the door.
See anything else up here?
One night, I closed up,
and the next morning,
all the wine was literally
thrown from this wine rack
all the way across the floor
and broken.
And this was intact?
This didn't fall down
or anything?
No, it did not.
There's a guy here.
He looks real bad.
Some of his face is missing.
He doesn't like
to be interfered with.
At that point,
I couldn't tell
how that man had gotten
into such rough shape.
But one thing was certain --
his uncontrollable temper
led to many violent outbursts.
I feel like if he's being
in a particularly angry mood,
you'd feel him.
And he moves a lot of things
all the time.
Like what?
I don't know --
just stuff around the bar.
It's weird 'cause he doesn't
want to be here.
This isn't --
isn't working for him.
I've had
a number of customers
that say that they see a woman
go into the bathroom
and shut the door.
So they'll wait and wait,
and then, finally, they go in,
and there's nobody there.
A lot of them will just
ask for their check and leave.
I've set up
a really comfortable,
homey environment here,
and that's not really
what my guests are feeling.
Instead, people would leave,
and they would
probably not come back.
You're having trouble
keeping customers, obviously.
I mean, how are you
dealing with all this?
Not well.
I actually was in the hospital
for five days in a row.
They can't figure out
how I got that sick that fast
when I'm healthy.
How serious did it get?
You know, I didn't
even actually know
if I was gonna live
through it.
There's this religious woman.
I think that living people,
they see her.
She's, scary.
She, like, picks people.
What do you mean?
She picks the weak, women...
sickly people.
From the moment
I saw that woman,
I knew I was looking
right into the eyes of evil.
And what she wanted to do
to the living
had me concerned
for the people who worked there.
What does she do?
I think she **** kills them.
How does she do that?
It's a touch.
They **** die.
With all the activity happening
in the restaurant,
Darcy couldn't pay her employees
enough to stick around.
So before she lost
another one,
I decided to help her bartender
face his fears.
So, Matt, how long
have you been working here?
- About a year and a half now.
- Okay.
This is my first time down here
in over a year.
What have you experienced?
I'd come down here
with a glass
very similar to the one
that's right here on the bar.
I'd put the glass down.
I made my way around
the back side of the bar here.
When I came back,
I reached for my glass,
and it had slid about 4 feet,
and all I saw was it hitting
the lip and going over the edge.
Hearing the actual smash --
I mean, that sound is something
that I'm not gonna forget
for a long time.
Now, if I walked away
and left you here,
would you be freaking out?
And it just took
that one incident for you?
That's all it took.
- It made me a believer.
- Next...
They're all burned.
They're all nasty.
It's bad.
...the dead
rise against the living.
They're bent on revenge.
And what happened
after the investigation?
The woman downstairs
is trying to kill me.
Something really
had to be done.
It sounded like
the paranormal activity
in Merchants Cafe
was out of control.
But broken glassware
and a creepy fog
didn't give me much to go on.
So, I had to start
with my only lead --
the fire that destroyed
the building in the late 1800s.
The two-story wooden structure
that originally was on that site
was burned during the great
Seattle fire of June 6, 1889.
This is a picture taken of
the aftermath of the fire.
Now, did anybody die
in this fire?
Yes.
A young boy
died in the fire,
and one wall came down
and ended up killing
a gentleman.
Were there any other fires
in or around the Merchants Cafe?
The only other one that
I know of took place in 1885.
It was a huge fire where
two people did lose their life.
Okay.
Before this building was here,
there was another structure here
that was smaller.
I think it burned down
a few times.
I'm experiencing
a lot of other people's deaths.
How many?
Probably about 20 or 30.
They died in a fire.
They're all burned.
They're all nasty.
It's bad.
In a location
where an unexpected,
tragic event has happened,
it's common for me to see
many lost and confused souls.
But that wasn't the case
in that basement.
Instead, the dead had united
and were out for blood.
They're very bent on revenge
for what happened to them.
They'll go after that person.
After the great Seattle fire,
the new owners had big plans
for the future
of the Merchants Cafe.
But according to
a local historian,
that location was about to spend
the next 100 years
plagued by tragedy.
One of the first owners
was a man named John Osner,
who opened the Merchants
Exchange Saloon in the basement.
In 1893, Osner
got desperate for revenue
and decided that he would take
the basement
and turn it
into an illegal card room,
and then the upstairs hotel
became a brothel.
Okay. So, he had
a gambling parlor.
He had the bar
and the brothel.
That's right.
There were people,
lots and lots of people,
laughing and having
a good time,
and there were prostitutes
but dressed nice,
like, old-fashioned.
Any idea when?
1880s?
There was
really friggin' bad people.
Get bad people in a bad place,
bad things are gonna happen.
I had a lot of facts
but nothing I could really tie
to what Darcy
and the staff had seen.
But all of that
was about to change.
So, did Osner run it
the entire time?
No. In 1898, they sold
a big portion of the business
to a fellow
named F.X. Schreiner.
Schreiner's wife, Mary,
was not approving.
She was a very devout woman.
She died of consumption,
or what we call "tuberculosis."
He was broken and went back
to Germany for a period of time.
What happened
to the business?
The other partners
brought in a new bartender
by the name of Otto Hink.
Was he a body builder
or something?
He was a wrestler, actually,
and he became the barkeeper.
He had a wife and children
in town,
but he also had a habit
of frequenting
the brothels himself.
And so the party, for him,
was over at age 42
because he had already
contracted
syphilis of the brain.
And he began to have
dementia.
He ended up being committed
and lived in sanitariums
for the rest of his life.
He's very, very,
very physical.
Like, I see iron fists --
like, ran this place
with, like, an iron fist.
He's, like, a pretty buff guy.
Like, he fought a lot.
Based off my first impressions,
I felt that man was evil.
The injury on his face alone
suggested he'd have no problem
hurting me.
But I'll admit,
in my line of work,
things aren't always
what they seem.
Something about a child
or children,
and he wants to
take care of them
but can't and doesn't.
He's angry, confused, hurt.
And he...
doesn't understand
what's happening.
Coming up next...
I was a mess -- a mess.
...Amy exposes
the shocking truth.
- Now, what kind of a risk are we
talking about? - She'd kill her.
And the story...
I went
straight for the priest.
...comes to
a terrifying conclusion.
I cast you out, Satan,
and all your minions.
Darcy bought this place
about a year and a half ago.
She never believed
in the paranormal at all.
Then she started working here.
Going into the reveal,
I actually really wanted to know
what Amy found
and if Amy was gonna say
it was safe to stay here.
Matt works here.
Matt's so afraid
to go downstairs,
he's losing shifts.
So, with that,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
I felt like this was
a really bad area at one time,
but I got in here parties
and dancing and prostitutes.
What time period
are you talking about?
It was like the 1880s.
During my research,
I came across a guy
by the name of F.X. Schreiner,
who owned the place.
Up here was the booze.
And then there was
a brothel upstairs.
Interesting.
What else did you wind up seeing
on your walk?
I was up here,
and I met a guy
behind the bar,
and he was very forceful.
He probably ran this place
and ran it
with, like, an iron fist,
but he's very confused
about what's happening.
Let me tell you about a guy
named Otto Hink.
When the wife
of F.X. Schreiner died,
Otto Hink took over
running the place.
He was a wrestler --
strong guy.
He was the bar guy.
You said he was confused,
right?
Yeah.
Okay. He liked to visit
the brothel himself.
Apparently, he contracted
syphilis of the brain.
So at a young age, 42,
he started going
a little mental.
He's very, very territorial,
especially back there.
And if you get in his way,
he can push you out of the way.
I wasn't surprised
about Otto Hink.
I hadn't seen him,
but the staff have seen him,
and guests, as well.
But, you know,
he's just trying to work.
It's his job, loves his job,
trying to work.
You think the guy
you saw is Otto Hink?
I think it's very likely.
I did a sketch of this man.
Some of his face is missing.
There's, like, a scar here.
He's from way back.
Wow.
****
What's with the face?
It was an injury.
I don't know if he was shot,
stabbed, cut.
I don't like him
looking at me.
To tell you the truth,
seeing a sketch of an entity
that is in this restaurant --
I was freaked out,
especially since
I hadn't seen him before.
It had a face, and then it,
to me, became way scarier.
In the basement, I saw people,
and they died in a fire.
They're very angry about that,
and they want revenge.
If you were to see them,
it would look like
a child-sized black mist.
Back in 1889,
there was the big fire here.
It was probably the worst fire
in Seattle's history.
You said it was a mist, right?
One night, it just got misty
over in the corner.
It was dark, like where
you could not see through it.
And then we ran out.
My gosh.
What Amy told me about the mist
hit home a little bit.
I was really surprised
at how accurate that really was.
And, to me, that is terrifying.
How'd the rest of the walk go?
So, I'm downstairs,
and I'm by the bathrooms,
and this lady comes out.
She was really,
really religious,
and she has a lot of power.
She goes after people
who are weak...
and especially women.
And when she touches
people...
it's like a death sentence.
21/2, 3 weeks ago,
I had pneumonia
in my right lung.
Then the bacteria
from my pneumonia
had actually got
into my bloodstream.
My gosh.
And I thought
I was gonna die.
I was a mess -- a mess.
I think it was her.
When Amy said
the woman downstairs
was trying to kill me,
that's when
I became freaked out.
The wife of F.X. Schreiner --
she was a very pious,
religious woman.
Didn't like the fact
that her husband
was making money
with prostitutes.
Her name was Mary.
Do you think the woman you saw
is this Mary Schreiner?
It could be.
So, Darcy, you've seen the
results of the investigation.
The big question is,
is it safe for you,
your employees to be here?
It's not really safe for you
to be here right now.
The way to get rid of her
is to find a medium
who has a background
in counseling.
If the medium isn't making
any headway with her,
then you're going to have to
make her leave,
and that involves
a type of exorcism.
Now, what kind of a risk
are we talking about with her
if she doesn't listen to you?
Well, she'd kill her.
As far as he's concerned,
I think he should stay.
I know you
don't want to hear that.
If we can play along well,
then I'm okay with that.
Darcy, it sounds like
we got here just in time.
What are you gonna do?
Amy told me to get a medium
and if that didn't work,
to get a priest
to do an exorcism.
I opted out of that.
I figured,
"Well, if the woman downstairs
"is trying to kill me,
why waste my time
with a medium?"
And so I went
straight for the priest
to do the exorcism.
Holy Mary, mother of God,
grant us protection
under your mantle,
for we seek refuge
from all worldly dangers.
When he was doing the exorcism,
the restaurant
seemed to get colder...
Give us strength
to defend our mortal souls.
...and colder and colder.
And treat the Lord of Peace
to cast Satan down
under our feet.
I cast you out, Satan,
and all you demons
and your minions.
And then, after the exorcism,
he blessed me.
Have mercy on Darcy
and heal Darcy's sickness,
and on the day of Darcy's death,
strengthen her soul.
Deliver Darcy not into
the hand of her enemies --
to the Father and to the Son
and to the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
Since the priest
did the exorcism,
I'm not sick anymore,
and I'm hopeful that my guests
won't be uneasy any longer.
But I still have concerns.
Evil could come back.
But either way,
I would still continue to run
this restaurant the way I do.
While I think Darcy's decision
to have an exorcism first
was premature,
I do understand her reasons
for making such a drastic move.
But an exorcism on its own
is never a guaranteed cure,
and I just hope
it'll be enough
to keep the activity
under control.