Subs created by: David Coleman.
There's this darkness.
And it makes me feel sick.
I started to feel like
I was being choked.
Very, very painful.
I've been pushed down the steps.
Some kind of physical abuse.
They could have been dismembered.
Does not want us here at all.
It's just waiting to just tear us apart.
There are secrets here that
some don't want discovered.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing's, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people.
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her?
It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were
ghosts in this house.
Amy and I work the same case,
but from two separate angles.
I gather witness testimony and uncover
secrets about the property's past.
While Amy communicates with the dead.
I'm in Buchanan, Virginia, about
30 minutes north of Roanoke.
We've been called in by
a scared mom named Tysha.
She tells me that whatever's on her
property is attacking her family,
and making everyone sick.
Hopefully, Amy and I can
get some answers for her.
Before Amy arrives, I need to clear
the area of any leading information.
This house is filled with photos of a
young family, so I need to remove them all.
To avoid influencing
Amy during her walk.
This place is really busy.
There's, like, a ton of [Bleep]
people around that are dead.
Like, how many?
I would count, like, 15
people that were walking by.
There's a lot of pain and despair here.
- Around the whole property.
- Okay.
I think something bad happened in there.
You know, Tysha, this
kitchen doesn't look lived in.
What's the story?
The activity in the house
just became outrageous,
and it just became too
much for our family.
And we decided to build a
modular house three years ago.
Is that the other structure
that I saw driving up?
Yes, Sir.
Okay, so let me ask you a question, did
it get better when you moved over there?
No, not at all.
So, give me an idea. What happened
while you were living in this house?
We have everything from, like,
seeing apparitions and noises.
I've actually been choked before.
And I have nightmares all the time.
I cannot sleep.
On the phone, you said this
was affecting your health.
Yes, Sir.
The doctor said that he had
diagnosed me with a chronic
pain condition called
Fibromyalgia, and...
My pain was just so amplified,
I was getting to where I
couldn't function at all.
Now, what about everybody else, are
they getting affected health-wise?
My two children... I have a
middle son that has Asperger's.
- And my little one has autism.
- Oh, geez.
- All right. So you got your hands full.
- Yes.
Do you know any history
about this place?
- We think it was built in 1847.
- Wow.
My father-in-law lived here as
a bachelor for a very long time.
Now, is your husband's
father still alive?
No, Sir. He passed away.
Okay. I'm sorry to hear
that. Did he ever mention...
Oh, yes.
- He did?
- Yes, Sir.
And what did he make of it?
I think he had a lot
of fear of things, too.
- He did?
- Yes, Sir.
Did you and your husband ever
consider moving off the property?
Financially, it would be
impossible for us to move.
And I would never be able to do
that. It would break my heart.
Okay.
So, do you want to move back into
this house if we could help fix things?
Yes.
It seems like there were
a lot of people here.
It's stressful.
Very stressful.
That would not be good.
This place is crawling with dead people,
who have the ability to affect
the living in horrific ways.
And I think it would make you terribly
ill, terribly ill to live here.
And it makes me feel sick.
What sort of stuff do you think
people would experience here?
Men's voices.
Arguing.
Seeing apparitions.
Watch your step.
Geez, you weren't kidding.
This really is a dungeon.
This is probably the worst place.
I just do not come down here.
I have terrible feelings...
Just dread, sadness, um, pain.
We were told, actually, that
slaves were kept down here, as well.
- Down here?
- Yes, Sir.
- Have you ever seen anything down here?
- I've seen apparitions. Yes, Sir.
I've seen a man with, like, dark pants,
and he just kind of
walked across the floor...
And just disappeared.
So, what are you actually
feeling right now?
Uh, really nauseous, kind
of light-headed and dizzy.
All right, you know what,
let's get the hell out of here.
Okay.
I see a lot of black men who
are dead, who are lined up,
and somebody's throwing water on them.
Like, just throwing
water on their bodies.
In particular, there's a woman...
A black woman... who's...
Splashing the water on them.
Does not want us here at all.
I don't think there are people
here who like white people.
Like, get out.
I just feel very
uncomfortable, and um...
Like...
I feel like she can do stuff.
Could she be dangerous?
I think so.
So, what happened here?
This is the most active part
of the house that we have.
One night, I was up here by
myself and I had fell asleep.
The bed started vibrating, and then I
started to feel like I was being choked.
It was like somebody was
sitting on top of my chest,
pressing down with their two
thumbs on my adam's apple.
Was your husband in bed with you?
- No. He was downstairs.
- Okay.
Well, anything else happen up here?
The scariest thing that
probably ever happened,
my son River... he was seven days old...
And I actually fell down the steps...
it was like I was being pushed...
And had him in my arms.
- Did he get hurt?
- No.
I just grabbed onto him as hard as I could
and just went down the steps on my back.
Did you get hurt?
I had some bruises on my
bottom and my back. Yes, I did.
Now, you mentioned that some of
the stuff that's happened here
- is happening in the new house.
- Yes, Sir.
I'm gonna have to go and take a look
so you can show me where it's going on.
- That's fine.
- Okay.
Now, Tysha, you mentioned you're in
this new house, what, three years?
Yes. Going on three years, yes.
- And nothing's gotten better?
- No, nothing's gotten better.
Exactly the same thing that has went
on at the old house goes on over here.
I still have the activity
of the pushing on the bed.
How heavy are we talking? Like...
Like a child would be jumping
from the head to the foot.
- Like a small child jumping on the bed?
- Yeah, yeah.
So, basically, all the [Bleep] people,
that were over at the
other place came over here.
So, there's just, like,
this one kid who...
Jumps around.
And the other one follows him.
And they kind of, like...
They attempt to be seen.
They're all over the house.
So, what about the kids? Are
they experiencing anything, or...
Yes, my son Blaze. He keeps talking about
seeing the same little boy apparition.
Describe it to me.
Blaze said he has a white shirt
that buttons up with overalls.
- Okay, have you seen it?
- I haven't seen the little boy.
It's pretty bad when, you know, you
think you're gonna build a new home
and have, maybe, a new beginning, and
the same things are still going on.
A black woman hates me so much.
I'm in, like, a lot of pain here.
Very, very painful.
Very, very, very painful.
What kind of pain?
There was something about her head...
Her neck, and her back, and it's...
Are you afraid of her?
I'm not really allowed to talk about it.
I'm in, like, a lot of pain here.
What kind of pain?
Something about her head,
her neck, and her back.
Are you afraid of her?
I'm not really allowed to talk about it.
Why can't you talk about it?
She has a way of preventing it.
This black woman wants to communicate
to the living what's happened to her,
but she says she doesn't
trust me because I'm white.
She also has this bizarre ability
I've never encountered before,
and it makes it impossible for me to
reveal details of her painful life.
I've never felt...
So much hatred.
So, Troy, I was talking to your wife.
She said that you grew
up on the property.
Yes, Sir. I've been on the property
pretty much since I came into the world.
Okay.
So, what have you experienced up here?
Well, we put all new drywall in, and
we had it stacked up against the wall.
And it started to shift over onto me.
And I spun around to try and get
out from there, and I jumped...
And it all came down and smashed me down
and pinned this foot down to the ground.
That's a lot of weight.
And excruciating pain.
And my son had walked in
right as that was going on.
That's why it was scaring me so much.
Could have killed me.
It could have killed him.
So, this drywall couldn't
have got just pushed?
- Like, I mean...
- No. I mean, I'm a brick mason.
- I deal around construction all the time.
- All right.
So, what else have you
experienced up here?
I've been pushed down the steps.
Busted my arm up pretty good.
Tysha told me she got pushed
when she was holding the baby.
Tysha also got pushed,
same place, same step.
So, when you got pushed, did you
feel like somebody shoved you?
Yeah, it did. Did feel like somebody
pushed right in the small of the back.
A good boom.
Well, I'm hoping that we can get
some answers to what's going on,
what's causing it, and how to stop it.
Yeah, before something bad
happens to one of the kids.
Okay.
The black lady...
She says, basically...
That she's given warnings.
What kind of warnings has she given?
Like, there's been some
kind of physical abuse.
Towards the adults.
Like what?
I feel like she... like, hitting...
Making them feel pain suddenly.
She's not a very tolerant person.
So, why'd you bring me in this room?
I was relaxing on the sofa, and I
seen a big, big mist right here...
A blackish-colored mist.
And I've seen that same
mist throughout the house.
And you've seen that
since you were a young man?
I was 8 or 10 the first
time that I'd seen it.
And now you're seeing
it again as an adult?
Yeah.
You guys are the first people that
I've talked about this besides my wife.
Okay.
Now, talking to Tysha,
she feels that her physical
ailment was actually
brought on by the house.
- Do you believe that?
- Yeah.
At first, it wasn't too bad.
It seemed like the longer we were here,
her health just slowly
started going down, you know?
I mean, you could look at her and see
she don't look like she's in bad shape,
but she's in a lot of pain.
Do you ever think about just moving?
That really, honestly, never
crossed my mind or anything
because it's something
I hold dear to my heart.
This place had been in
my family for so, so long.
And I've fought tooth and nail,
and Tysha has fought tooth and nail,
to keep the property.
And you have the two boys you want to...
Pass the property on to?
Now, what are you hoping for
at the end of the investigation?
What are you hoping we can get for you?
Just to get straightened out.
Figure out what's going on.
- I need a minute.
- Okay.
There's, like, no
redeeming quality here...
For this place.
It just shouldn't...
shouldn't be anymore, period.
I don't think that the
dead people that are here
want this place to
really even exist anymore.
Why?
I don't know. They get [Bleep] agitated.
And they're yelling, burn
this [Bleep] to the ground!
Tysha told me that she thinks her
property used to be a big slave plantation.
I'm on my way to meet with a local
genealogist to see if this is really true,
or a local legend.
Is it true that the property I'm
investigating was a plantation at one time?
- It was.
- Okay.
They raised tobacco.
And slaves lived a very hard life.
They were fed very little.
They got up early in the day.
They worked all day long,
from daylight till dark.
What about medical treatment?
There was probably not
very much medical treatment,
for the slave or the landowner because
medicine wasn't like it is today.
Do we know who owned the first plantation
on the property I'm investigating?
- The Burks family.
- And how many slaves did they have?
- We show that there were 60.
- And how do we know that?
Well, I have this
document here from 1855.
And it talks about the slaves
that he owned in his inventory.
10 years old, 11 years old.
Were they ever educated?
They were not schooled.
As soon as they were old enough to walk,
they were probably working, as well.
If they died on the property, would
they bury them on the property?
Yes.
There's a lot of black
boys... like, young boys.
Like, I'd say 12 and under.
I do see, like, a school of some sort...
Very small.
But I don't think...
The black kids would...
Would be being taught anything.
I think a lot of them
are buried around here.
I do. I think a lot of
them are buried around here.
There were 34 graves in all.
And most of them were children's graves.
After meeting Rena, I knew
these archives would hold some
pretty appalling stories
about the Burks family slaves.
But as I dig through them, I discover
something completely unexpected.
Some of the slaves had the same last
name as the owner of the plantation...
Nicholas Burks.
You know, I've got to wonder
if they might be his kids.
I'm headed back to Troy
and Tysha's property,
to meet with a local Professor
of African-American studies.
Who says she can answer
some of my questions.
That paperwork I sent you about the
plantation, I mean, what do you make
of the five or six young kids with
the same name as the plantation owner?
It was more common than
people like to think.
One thing did strike me, though, that one
of the five children with his last name...
This person, Monroe...
was listed as Mulatto.
Which is someone who's mixed
race, and that suggests to me
that it's very likely that he
was the plantation owner's son.
- Now, was it consensual?
- Not necessarily.
I mean, rape was very common.
If you own a human being, you
can do what you will to them.
Some guy's, like,
slapping this woman a lot.
Beating her up pretty bad.
It seems like he is wealthy,
and it's also like she's nothing.
Is there any way of figuring out who
might have been the mother of this kid?
There is someone on the
papers that you sent,
that looks like she could
be a good fit for his mother.
- It's a woman named Louisa.
- Okay.
And she was 45 years old the same
time that he was 18, listed together.
- So the age range works.
- Okay.
And they were also recorded as running away
during the same period, possibly together.
What would have happened
if they got caught?
Whippings to torture to threatening
to sell your family off...
To sell you off down South.
They could have been dismembered.
Now, what kind of a woman would
even take a risk like that?
A brave one. The domestic
slave trade was at its height.
The soil was dying out,
and farmers around here and planters
were struggling economically.
So they switched from...
Mostly doing crops to
doing human trafficking.
So, she witnessed a huge export
of her family and friends.
That would be one of the reasons
why she took off, I guess.
Absolutely.
That ultimate freedom or the
risk of not being sold down South.
Or maybe being separated from her son might
have been enough to make it worth leaving.
There are so many emotions...
With this black woman
that it's hard to...
Talk with her.
She is just showing me, like, that...
The only good thing in
life were... were children.
That was the only thing
that made her happy.
She didn't want anybody else to be
here, so she did things to try...
To set that in motion
when she was alive.
There are secrets here that
some don't want discovered.
They should learn from history.
What's going on?
She doesn't want me down here.
I'm in, like, a lot of pain here.
In my research, I found out the property's
tragic history didn't end with slavery.
I turned up a guy by the
name of Starke Robinson,
and it seems he lost a
lot of family members.
I'm on my way to meet with a local
librarian who did some digging.
And he says he's got some information
that'll really help my case.
Nathan, what were you able to find
out about this guy, Starke Robinson?
Well, actually, we were
able to find out quite a lot.
We found out that he is a
native-born Virginian, born in 1826.
He was a plantation owner.
He enlisted with the Confederacy,
and after The Civil War, of course,
going back to the plantation,
life wasn't gonna be the same.
So, in 1870, he buys the property
that you're investigating now.
Now, I also noticed through
the paperwork, he had some loss.
Yes, he in fact, had three wives throughout
his life, and he outlived all of them.
His first wife died before The Civil
War in 1857 when she was just 30.
His second wife, Ellen, in 1871... just
a year after he buys the property...
She died of complications that
occurred during childbirth.
Okay.
And the child that she gave birth
to also passed away at that time.
We have some of the
cemetery records here.
After Ellen dies, not long after, Starke
marries her younger sister, Elizabeth.
- Okay.
- And then she lived until 1904.
They were together over 30 years.
I'm getting these two little
white ladies, and they're sisters.
Do you know what kind of
connection these women might have,
to this location?
I feel like they owned it at some point.
One of them is young.
She's from, maybe, like
nineteen oh five or nineteen ten.
She has dead children.
And then somebody said, well, you know,
in the end, there's just blood, anyway.
Sickness and death. That's it.
I don't like it at all.
If we look at the cemetery
records that we have, we can see...
That Starke actually
ended up outliving...
7 of his 14 children.
Four died in childbirth.
So, this guy Starke
kind of had a rough go.
Yeah.
He actually dies in 1915.
I have the death certificate here.
He's 89 years old, which in
1915, was quite an advanced age.
Now, would they have been
buried on the property?
Yes, and in fact, there is
a cemetery on the property,
not far from the house
that Robinson lived in.
There's so much residual information.
I know there's other deaths here
because they're saying, like...
Like, at one point, they show
me, like, literally, like,
the floors are covered in blood.
For whatever reason, all
the people that lived here...
Met with darkness and tragedy.
There were several entities
that stood out during my walk.
But what has me the most concerned,
is the bizarre scene I
encountered in the basement.
There were several
dead black men laying.
Mm-hmm.
There's two black women.
They're pouring water on the bodies.
- Amy, is this what you saw?
- Yes.
After days of investigating
our clients' property,
Amy and I are ready to
reveal what we found.
Amy, I'd like you to
meet Troy and Tysha.
This is their house and property.
It's very close to their hearts.
Troy's family's had this
property since the early 1930s.
The only problem is Tysha
and her two young boys,
have been having health problems.
And they want to know if
there's any way they can stay.
This house is very
important to both of them.
So, with that, I'm gonna
turn it over to Amy,
and have her talk about
her walk for a little bit.
When I first got here, there were
like 15 dead people walking by the car.
It was extremely stressful just
how many there are on this property.
And the main feelings
that kind of permeates
this entire area was
sadness and despair and pain.
And I did get that there were
a lot of people buried here.
Well, we have bouts of depression.
Okay.
Well, there have been a lot of people
that have lived and died on this property.
But this may influence what you
saw, so I'm gonna hold off for now.
Okay.
When I was upstairs,
I did meet two sisters.
They were from the early 1900s.
They owned this property
at some point in time.
And I felt sickness and death with them.
One of the sisters
had children who died.
And I think that if people see them,
they're just kind of like a mist.
Why don't you explain the mist to her?
The mist I've seen has been
kind of a black-color mist.
Where did you see that?
Right above this doorway.
In the basement a lot, too.
Okay.
I could tell you about
at least four people...
That I know that are
buried on the land here.
When you mentioned sisters... there
was a guy named Starke Robinson
who bought the property
here and the house in 1870.
He moved here with his wife, Ellen,
who, within a year, actually
passed away at a young age.
About five years later,
he married her sister...
Elizabeth, who died in this house.
- Now, you mentioned dead kids.
- Mm-hmm.
This guy had 14 children, seven
of them which died before he did.
- Four of them died at childbirth.
- Geez.
So, Starke, his two wives, and one of
the children are buried on the property.
Wow.
- That make sense?
- Oh, yeah.
The one thing that became
apparent was that...
Some of the dead from this
house go over to the new house.
Specifically, I saw two boys.
And they're always running around,
laughing, and just messing around.
I got them being very active in the
hallway over there and in your bedroom.
Wow.
That's part of the reason we're here,
Troy and Tysha have been
living here for 10 years.
They lived seven years in this house.
- Okay.
- But things got so bad...
They decided to build over there, but...
Same things just continued to happen.
Your son is seeing...
- Apparitions of a little boy.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Wow.
Not good.
What else did you see?
So, when I went into the basement,
which is not a good place...
No.
I saw 4 to 10 black men that were dead.
They were all lined up, and
they were extremely thin...
Almost like the pictures from,
like, the holocaust victims.
And there were two women that were
throwing water on their bodies.
There are people down there
that really hate white people.
Well, it makes sense.
Back in its heyday, this
was a tobacco plantation.
Hmm.
And from the 1830s up
until around The Civil War,
it was owned by the Burks family.
They had up to 60 slaves.
And the basement of this house
was some of their living quarters.
- To tell you how they were treated and...
- I know how they were treated.
I sketched that scene in the basement.
Geez.
Take a look at that.
Wow.
I've always known that there
were slaves on the premises...
But it's sad to see that in the picture.
It's sickening to me.
Do you know why they
were throwing water,
because there were flies on
them or something like that?
- Maybe. I don't know.
- Okay.
These guys feel really
uncomfortable down in that basement.
Is this the reason why
they're feeling uncomfortable?
Well, the thing is, is that the
larger lady is still down there.
She's very, very present.
And she doesn't want anybody in
there, especially if they're white.
I'd never felt hatred like
that from an entity in my life.
One thing that she kept saying is that
she wants the living to learn from history.
And then she showed me children,
and said that they were the
only good thing in her life.
And she didn't want people here.
She didn't want to be
here, because she knew when
she got here that this
was not a good place.
A couple things you said,
made me think of a slave that used
to live here by the name of Louisa.
She was about 45 years old.
And there was another slave by the
name of Monroe who was about 18.
Now, this slave was
half white, half black.
And the paperwork has them
listed as being two runaways.
They ran away at the
same time, basically.
Now, from what the
historian I spoke to said,
she was probably raped by
one of the plantation owners.
She had this child that was
half black, half white...
And they took a big
chance and they ran away.
Now, if you ran away back in those
days on a plantation, you got caught...
You were either sent to another plantation,
which was a lot worse than here...
They'd dismember you, or they kill you.
That's really sad.
Her presence is extremely dangerous...
And incredibly powerful.
She's also trying to
give you guys warnings.
What kind of warnings
are we talking about?
To get out.
I was in extreme pain.
I did feel that there was probably some
physical abuse towards the adults here.
You saw physical abuse
towards the living adults here?
Yes.
It's not that she is doing it directly.
She controls the dead here.
We was redoing the room up there,
and there was a lot of sheetrock...
Like, couple thousand pounds.
And it was all pushed against the wall,
and the whole thing came over on me.
My aches and pains have
gotten worse, big-time.
I shouldn't be feeling this beat
down, like I'm 60-some years old.
How about the kids?
Do you think their health issues
might have been related to the house?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Getting worse.
One of them, he has autism, and
the other one has Asperger's.
And you've been in a lot of pain.
Oh, yes. It's, like, all over.
- Mm-hmm.
- It gets worse.
There's moments that it seems like I'm
away from the property, it's not as bad.
Well, she's extremely powerful, yeah.
She is the hoodoo practitioner.
What is hoodoo?
Hoodoo comes from Africa.
And it was certain tribes that had
gone through the Christianization.
When you first said that,
I thought you meant Voodoo.
No, Voodoo is a religion.
Hoodoo is not a religion,
but a system to place spells.
And she put them into
place while she was alive,
to ensure things would go the
way she wanted them to in death.
Because hoodoo is all
about gaining power.
And now she's got all this power...
She's got all these dead
people that she controls.
And she had put a binding spell out.
What do you mean by that?
Well, I couldn't have full
communication with the dead.
Like, I couldn't talk
about being whipped.
I could not talk about what I
was experiencing at the time.
Which is weird, because her message is
the main message that needs to be heard.
Well, if she has a message
she wants out, what is it?
What does she want from them?
She wants the house demolished.
Her message is the main
message that needs to be heard.
Well, if she has a message
she wants out, what is it?
What does she want from them?
She wants the house demolished.
That ain't gonna happen.
I'll just keep on with her, I guess.
I'm not gonna tear nothing down.
She's not the only
one who feels this way.
All of the dead want it gone.
So, how many ghosts do we have?
I would say hundreds.
I'm... I'm very concerned.
She wants this house gone.
She's bound everybody else around
her... all the other dead people.
I'm keeping the house up.
I'm not tearing my house down.
I don't give up on anything.
Plus you had plans on one day
passing this on to your kids.
Sure.
I'll be damned if I let any
kind of stuff like that stand,
into anything that I got to
do with my kids, you know?
You know, you're like me
in a way. You look pissed.
Yeah. I'm a really hard-headed guy.
And we'll butt heads
for right now, I guess.
If he wants to butt heads with
this woman, what could happen?
You're in for it.
Yeah. I'm not backing down
from where I'm at right now.
I've worked too hard to
be where I'm at right now.
I'd be letting a lot
of my ancestors down.
I don't know. I mean, I'm
really confused by the whole...
You know, we've tried
to protect this place,
and everybody's tried to
be respectful to the place.
You're white.
She won't listen to what you're saying.
Period. End of story.
Told you there was a lot more to it.
This has been probably one of the
most intense investigations we've done.
And obviously, this has
been a lot for you guys,
but the most pressing question here...
Is it safe for you to stay on your property
and pass this house along to your kids?
For that, I'm gonna turn it over to
Amy, see if she has an answer for you.
Obviously, the easiest way to go
would be to demolish the house...
Which it sounds like
you're not going to do.
So, my other suggestion would be to...
Find a hoodoo practitioner.
Because this is about gaining power.
You get another hoodoo person in
who would want to attain her power.
And they're gonna take her with them.
Because they're gonna then
have access to her power.
So, your advice to them is to get
somebody that practices hoodoo that...
Won't be afraid of
this, but want the power?
Right. Would want to take her.
I mean, I don't think you look up the
yellow pages for something like this.
I mean, it is hard to find
someone who practices true hoodoo.
But maybe going to the universities,
they might know practitioners.
Okay. That's where we'll start, then.
If we get this other one to
come in here and kick her ass...
Is all these other spirits
that's underneath her,
will they be let go and everything?
Yes.
Let me ask you a
question about this house.
Should they stay away
from this house until...
I'm not. I'm over here all the time.
- You're not even gonna try to stay away?
- No. Mm-mm.
If I were you, I would probably
be very, very, very careful
if I came into this house.
So, we'll take it a day at a time.
So, are you guys gonna follow Amy's
advice and find a hoodoo practitioner?
Yeah, most definitely. Most definitely.
Oh, yeah. Tomorrow.
Not gonna let her win.
She's done too much damage already.
I can't force Troy to do
something he doesn't want to do,
and I don't know if he fully
understands what he's about to take on...
But I'm afraid he's about to.