Tonight on "Dead Files Revisited"...
He said that he'd
kill me if I came here.
A second look at some of Amy and
Steve's most terrifying cases.
You've got a lot of activity here.
New information...
Ashley's been too afraid to come back.
Startling revelations...
I still feel like I'm being watched.
First, a return to
Belvidere, Illinois...
Very concerned for
the welfare of my son.
Where fighting evil...
It'll torment the people
who are living here.
Means breaking the rules.
I'll set it up.
Then, we travel back to
Clinton, North Carolina...
House of death.
Where the sins of the past...
There's dead bodies all over the place.
Continue to curse the living.
This is a lot of pressure for you.
Did they fight back...
So you're gonna take
Amy's advice and do this?
Or do they still live in fear?
I've never gone back there by myself.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing's, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people.
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her?
It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were
ghosts in this house.
When I arrived in Belvidere, Illinois,
I was expecting routine investigation.
We were looking into the
history of an old farmhouse,
and our client's paranormal
experiences ran three generations deep.
But as the truth unraveled,
Amy and I decided that the only way to
save this family was to break the rules.
Judy, you sounded really
concerned on the phone and upset.
- I mean, what's going on?
- Well, we're here at my dad's house.
About 10 years ago, my
son and I moved in here,
and ever since, we've heard
noises, we've seen apparitions.
And we've been physically touched.
I wanted to get my son
out of that situation,
so about three years ago, we
moved and it hasn't stopped.
I'm very, very concerned
for the welfare of my son.
We were terrified as I sat there
and saw my child just scared...
Running into my room... "Mom,
did you see it? Is it real?"
You don't know what to do, especially
when they're screaming bloody murder.
Well, you're a tough
woman. I give you credit.
I had to be.
So, there's, like, some really
significant stuff going on here.
While I was opening, there was like this
little boy, and he didn't have any eyes.
Looks, like, Angelic, but he's...
He's dark.
Before a walk, I do
what's called an opening.
This process can give me a preview of
what I'm going to see at a location.
But nothing could have prepared me for
the demonic energy of that little boy.
What the **** is
burrowing under the ground?
It's like some creepy...
Thing, like...
What are you thinking?
I think that the burrowing
monster is this child...
And I think that it'll torment
the people who are living here.
Judy's Father had his
own creepy experiences,
but nothing terrifying enough to drive
a tough guy like him out of his own home.
Looking back on this case,
he should have listened to his daughter
and gotten the hell out of there.
Franco, I spoke with your daughter.
She told me she was
getting physically touched,
pretty much traumatized by
everything that happened here.
I was wondering if you ever
experienced anything here.
I sure did.
In the dining room, a figure
walked in, and he looked at me.
And like he was
surprised, that I was here.
This was a real tall, slender man.
Had this old jacket,
almost like a suit jacket.
But again, from way back when.
Wow.
So, I hear this voice.
It's really grumbly,
like gravelly, like...
- Hoarse.
- Can you describe him more?
He's probably in his, like, late 30s.
He's thin.
- He's yelling at me.
- What is he yelling?
He told me that he'd
kill me if I came here.
In my line of work, I get death
threats from the dead all the time.
It's risky, but sometimes I
just have to call their bluff.
And I said, "yeah? Bring it on".
Now he's small and weak and
cowering, and he's crying.
He's like sad, depressed.
Judy was the one who called us in,
but her son Frankie was about to
become the focus of my investigation.
Hearing his experiences
for the first time,
I could tell deep down that
this tough-looking teenager,
was really just a scared kid.
Frankie, I was talking to
your Mom earlier and...
She basically told me you
had it rough growing up here.
There was one time I looked up
from the porch at that window.
And I seen this figure...
Moving back and forth.
I could see the rope around its neck.
And its head just hanging to the side.
When you see something like that,
it definitely sends
chills down your spine.
Since I've seen that man in the barn,
I've never gone back there by myself.
So, it looked like
somebody that was hung.
Yeah.
My head hurts so bad up here.
This male... he killed himself.
It happened here.
There's something with a rope.
How old were you when
this is all going on?
Around 9, 10 years old.
- How were you sleeping at night?
- I wasn't really sleeping good at all.
For a few years straight,
I had the same dream...
Of this man standing in
the yard, watching me.
I was able to tell Steve things that I
haven't told anybody
and kept them to myself.
It was a huge relief to be
able to tell him everything.
Describe him to me.
Wasn't that tall. Had a mask on.
It was a plain white mask.
Couldn't see his face, nothing.
Okay.
Those things, they're
just all over here.
Probably seven feet tall, human-shaped.
Very broad.
Big arms.
They were exchanging masks...
White masks.
Do you think living
people have seen these?
Definitely, I think they've
like seen them and then like,
had like encounters with them.
And **** freaked the **** out.
Because they are very scary.
Next...
I hear a gunshot.
Death invades the barn.
There's a lot of blood.
And in our second investigation...
I don't want to be here by myself.
Lives are changed forever.
So I took matters into my own hands.
Digging into the history of the
home, I got a hit on something big.
Two brothers committed
suicide on the property.
The newspaper details were slim,
but now there was some merit
to what Frankie said he saw.
But in order to get the full story,
I had to reach out to one of my own.
What were you able to find
out about these suicides?
Back in 1939, Thomas Smith,
a 24-year-old young man.
Was having an argument
with his girlfriend...
Took a.22 caliber pistol...
And shot himself in the heart.
Now what about the second suicide?
Well, in 1961...
Thomas' brother Raymond...
Also committed suicide using the
exact same gun, but he doesn't die.
So he decides to hang himself.
Have you ever heard
of anything like that?
No. Of the 23 years, I never
had anything like this happen.
There was really no indication as to
why he would want to commit suicide.
And there's the pain in my head.
Not everything I see
is always crystal-clear.
It can be bits and pieces of
information that I have to put together.
I think it's self-inflicted.
What do you mean?
I saw...
A noose, hanging from the beams.
There's a lot of blood.
I hear somebody yelling.
I hear a male yelling.
I hear a gunshot.
From the information around me,
I was almost positive that
a man had hung himself.
But the fact that I also heard a
gunshot in the exact same spot...
Didn't make sense.
Who's he that you're talking about?
The man who killed himself.
I've investigated countless
deaths, and the fact that I
couldn't find a motive for Raymond
Smith's suicide didn't sit right.
And after talking to a descendant of
the Smith family, I wasn't any closer.
What can you tell me about Ed Sr.?
This is my great-grandfather.
I heard he was a
hardworking kind of man.
The winters were harsh,
but he enjoyed doing it.
Because they knew they had
to provide for the family.
I got to ask you a question... how
did these suicides affect your family?
When Thomas committed suicide, they
were sad and they were heartbroken but,
they kind of saw it happening.
But when Ray died,
nobody was expecting that.
But it kind of erased the family.
It kind of made them just
go all their own ways.
There's something about
this old man, grandpa...
Like an Ed, Eddie, Edgar.
He's a farmer... literally
the image of a farmer...
Overalls, cutoff sleeves, big, rosy guy.
Anyways, he died.
While I was working out
the suicides that took place
in Franklin's house, I'd
gotten a frantic call from Judy.
She said the activity in her
house was getting a lot worse.
I had no choice.
I had to break the rules and
ask Amy to walk Judy's new home.
Okay, I'll set it up.
There's...
People. They've been called.
They've been asked to come
into the back of the house.
A walk requires an incredible
amount of my energy,
and can wear me down for days.
So doing a second walk that
soon took its toll on me.
But it was the right thing
to do for our clients.
My body doesn't feel comfortable here.
It's like, you know...
This annoying hum.
I feel like there are two people
that have been having experiences.
Is what's going on dangerous for them?
Yeah.
They've had nasty **** come in.
Next...
It's some kind of demonic presence.
It's scary.
What happened after the investigation.
I was really sweating bullets.
Our Father, who art in
heaven, hallowed be thy name.
Amy, I want to introduce you
to three generations here.
When I was about to meet Amy,
I was really sweating bullets.
But I had to stay strong
for everybody else.
Big concern here is, is
it safe for Franco to stay.
And have Judy and Frankie taken
something back to where they live now,
and are they gonna be okay?
So with that, Amy will start
and tell us about her walk.
The first thing that
I got was this little...
Creature, and, um, it would
burrow into the ground.
And it felt very, very negative.
And then I saw these Creature
things out in the yard.
They were like seven feet tall,
abnormally long arms, muscular.
They were wearing masks.
When I was a little kid,
I would go to bed...
And in the dream, I would see just one
man standing there, wouldn't do nothing.
He had a mask on, and I would
have that dream constantly.
My God. My God.
Okay, all right, I drew it.
To help describe what I see during
my walk, I bring in a sketch artist.
It's an important way to validate my
findings with Steve and our clients.
Wow.
Well, I think I'd be afraid if I saw
that in the middle of the night, too.
The sketch... that was really trippy.
It scared me because
just seeing it again...
All those years of haunting me and then
all of a sudden seeing it in reality,
that definitely, definitely
sent chills down my spine.
Yeah, that's...
Looks like him.
It's scary.
Frankie never got into detail of what
it was that he was seeing or dreaming of.
When I saw that sketch,
I think it finally hit me.
It wasn't a dream
anymore. It was real life.
Okay, Amy, what else did you see?
I saw this farmer.
He lived here. I know he died here.
He comes in the barn a lot,
and his name was Ed or Eddie.
You're kidding.
Ed or Eddie?
The guy that I saw in the
house was very tall, lean...
Very old-fashionedly dressed.
The original settler on this land,
was a second-generation farmer
by the name of Eddie Smith.
And he farmed this land
for probably 70 years.
Now that looks more like what I seen.
He looked just like that.
I seen him with my own eyes.
That's incredible.
I'm amazed every time our
findings connect like that.
But what Amy said
next just blew me away.
The other person that I saw
was right here in this barn.
He, like, was suicidal.
I saw an old pistol, and
then I heard a gunshot.
But I'm looking at these, and
I'm like, "he hung himself".
She almost nailed this down to 100%.
His son Raymond in 1961
committed suicide in this barn.
My God.
Apparently he didn't die right away...
- My God.
- So he took a rope and then hung himself.
Tell Amy what you saw that time.
I look up at the barn, and
I notice this white figure...
Peeking its head through the window,
but at the same time trying to hide,
like he didn't want us
to know he was there.
It really did frighten me to know that
the man in the barn was actually real.
I've never looked at the barn
ever since that in the same way.
The other thing that I saw was
a child, a 5-year-old little boy.
The child is not a child.
It's some kind of demonic presence.
And what it did to this family
was it caused two suicides.
It probably influenced
them to do it and...
Completely destroyed the family.
My absolute worst fear was,
that she was gonna discover something
is malevolent, is a Demon, and she did.
Well, there's obviously
a lot going on here.
Two biggest questions...
Is it safe for Franco at this house.
And did this thing follow you two guys
to your new home, and are you safe there?
In your house, you guys are
getting an influx of random
people and things coming in the
back door and the back window.
But all you need to do
is bring in a holy man...
Who will have a blessing
done and a sealing done.
Okay.
But this property, your situation
is a little bit different.
You know, this thing's been here for
a long time, it can affect people.
So you really need to
not only get the blessing,
but also you need to bring in a Shaman.
Who will seal up the property so that
the demonic thing can't get back in.
My concern is that if you don't
take care of this, what could happen?
It'd be bad.
It'll continue.
So you're gonna take
Amy's advice and do this?
When Amy said what had to be
done, I knew we had to take action.
Get it done the right
way, get it done quick.
Our Father, who art in
heaven, hallowed be thy name.
The priest came into the
property and blessed our house.
By the power of God, cast into
hell Satan and all evil spirits.
May this blessing
remain upon this house,
and upon all those who live
here now and forever, amen.
The priest also left us with some
Bible verses that we need to recite.
I do it every night to
continue to bless the home.
There are moments that I still
feel like I'm being watched.
Occasionally, I will see something
out of the corner of my eye.
When you see something like that, it
definitely makes your hair stand up.
I don't think the activity
will ever end for good,
and my worry for my son
will never end, either.
The problem is my Father hasn't
done anything to his home yet.
But we're hopeful that he will follow Amy's
advice, because the activity has subsided,
but it hasn't stopped.
Now that Judy and Frankie have blessed
their home, the dead should stay away.
At least for the time being, but
Franco's home is another story.
Until the property is sealed,
I believe that the demon
will be waiting for the right
moment to tear this family apart.
When I got the call from Kara,
the Director of the Sampson Arts Council in
Clinton, North Carolina, she was desperate.
Word had gotten out that
the place was haunted,
and her staff and students were
terrified to even go into the building.
And after what Amy and I revealed
about what was really going on there...
I don't blame them for being scared.
Well, Kara, tell me what's going on.
We've been having some experiences
here with volunteers hearing noises...
Feeling something touch
them, and seeing apparitions.
Let me ask you, what's
your biggest concern?
We have a lot of kids who
come to take art classes,
but their parents are
afraid to bring them up here.
Because of the things that are going on.
We might close down because of that.
Not only were we in jeopardy
of losing volunteers,
but, also, losing the
community's support.
The Small House is the center
of our community for the arts.
And if we had to leave this location,
it would just be devastating.
Do you know who lived here before
the house became the art center?
Well, Dr. Small was a general
practitioner here in Clinton.
He left the house in his
will to the arts council,
in hopes that it would
be used for arts purposes.
And we're just here to
fulfill that dream for him.
Would you stay overnight here alone?
Probably not.
Not too comfortable with this
house at night when it's dark.
There's, like, a lot of sadness.
There was an overwhelming amount
of negativity in that house,
which is never good.
And the first entity who approached me
had a warning that made my skin crawl.
There's a woman...
And she's talking.
The first thing she said when
she came up was "house of death".
Next...
- So, what were they doing?
- A **** Séance.
Amy uncovers the startling truth.
The dead begin to resent the living.
Amy and I were investigating the
Sampson Arts Council in North Carolina.
The center's Director had serious
concerns that paranormal activity,
was driving away her staff and students.
So, Kara, why did you
bring me in this room?
To show you the photos of Dr.
Small and his wife, Suzanne.
The legend is if you were to switch the
photos and hang them facing each other...
Dr. Small comes and gently
places it on the floor.
Okay, now, why would he want
'em facing the other way, though?
Dr. Small and his wife didn't
get along, and he said...
"I don't want to look at Suzanne
for the rest of eternity".
During the daytime, I
feel comfortable here,
but at night, when it gets dark,
I don't want to be here by myself.
This house just has a feeling about
it, like Dr. Small is lurking around.
Sounds like you've got a lot of activity
here, from what you're telling me.
We've had a couple of other
groups to come in and investigate.
- What do you mean, like Ghost Hunters?
- Yeah.
They've tried to talk with the dead but,
we haven't really had
much result from them.
Okay.
We weren't the first ones Kara
called in to help with their problems,
but we were definitely the last.
There's a round table.
People are sitting around.
So, what were they doing?
A **** Séance.
They're holding hands...
"Is anybody here? Can we talk to
anybody? Why are you doing these things?"
I was so angry. It was bad enough that
the house was full of dead people...
But to bring in a bunch of thrill
seekers to try and clear them out,
only made things worse.
So how would a séance
affect the dead here?
The dead begin to resent the living.
How would you like it if people kept
coming in your home and **** with you?
Next, I met with a former employee.
So far, she was the only witness
that had actually seen something.
And after we spoke, I started to get a
pretty good idea of who I needed to find.
Meredith, I understand
you had some experiences.
When I was maybe 5 or 6,
I was here for a party.
And a figure came from
that door over there,
and walked through the
railing and down the stairway.
- You mean like an apparition?
- Yes.
It was a man, maybe 40s or 50s.
What about now, how are
you feeling being here now?
There's no way I'd be here by myself.
There's like this guy who's really
depressed, and he wears a dark suit.
He's kind of tall.
I think that he's been seen,
and I think that he's been heard.
When I first saw that
depressed man, I thought...
"Maybe he could help me figure
out what happened in the house".
But the moment he started speaking, I knew
that help was the last thing on his mind.
- You all right?
- No.
This man is, like, preaching,
and it's, like, really disturbing.
Like he's getting off on death.
People are, like,
freaking the **** out.
At this point, it was clear a
lot was happening in the house.
But it wasn't till I spoke to one of the
center's current volunteers that I realized
what kind of impact the building was
having on people's health and their sanity.
So, Ashley, I was wondering if you
ever had any strange experiences here.
Um yes, the bathroom right
up here I won't go in at all.
- Why?
- Whenever I go in there, I get chills.
- It makes me physically sick.
- All right, you know what? Come with me.
I know you're scared, but just come
with me for a second, all right?
Okay. How are you feeling?
Just seeing it this close
is getting me a little upset.
You're really shaking.
- You all right?
- Just uneasy being near this bathroom.
All right, come on.
Let's go back out here.
Can you describe what you
physically just went through?
Shaky, trembly, it's a feeling
that I don't ever want to feel ever.
Would you stay overnight in any
other part of the house here?
Absolutely not.
Next...
Is anything unusual in this will?
The bodies start stacking up.
Sliced his throat right at the jugular.
And what happened
after the investigation?
I had an uneasy feeling.
The Sampson Arts Council got started,
when a local Doctor donated his
home to the County in his will.
By most accounts, Dr. Small
seemed like a decent guy.
But after talking to the
lawyer who drew up his will,
I got the impression that the Doctor
might have been hiding a few secrets.
Dr. Small... what can
you tell me about him?
Dr. Small...
Certainly was a unique personality...
To say the least.
I think he was eccentric,
in some respects.
So, Gene, you actually wrote his will?
Yes, I did. I have a copy of it here.
Is anything unusual in this will?
Well, he didn't provide for his wife.
I do recall that... I think
they slept in separate bedrooms.
As I understand, they had
separate bank accounts.
And when he would talk, it was
always in first person singular.
He would never say "we".
It's like... I want to
say, like, there's a Doctor.
Like, he knows a lot about the body.
And, like, pressure points.
You feel the pressure, and
then you'll feel, like...
Like you want to pass out or whatever,
because he's pushing these points.
I could see that the Doctor had
learned many techniques to cause pain.
And at night, when he could
hide under the cover of darkness,
he enjoyed using those
skills to torture the living.
He knows where to touch, like the
spots to make headaches come on,
to make people feel
like they can't breathe.
I don't like him at all.
Dr. Small told Gene
that the guy who owned
the house in the early
1900s had killed himself.
In those days, public records
of suicide were scarce.
Fortunately, a local reporter was able to
help me track down the gruesome details.
Dr. Leeman Matthews was our
Superintendent of Public Schools,
here in Samson County
from 1907 until 1918.
What about the suicide?
It was, probably very messy.
According to the death certificate...
He had locked himself in the
bathroom upstairs, in the bathtub...
And sliced his throat,
right at the jugular.
Okay.
Jeff, did he have a
history of depression?
Not that we've been able
to find any evidence of.
It just seemed to all
come across very sudden.
You know what's weird is there's
dead bodies like all over the place?
What do you mean? Can you describe them?
They're just dead people,
laying around in random places.
The darkness is just very bad here.
There's this male lurking
in the dark who can hurt you.
He lives in the dark, and
he **** with people.
I already had two deaths
tied to The Small House.
And after sitting down
with another historian,
it seemed like everyone who
lived there died tragically.
By the end of that interview,
I was determined to make
sure it didn't happen again.
Abraham Hobbs was born into a well-to-do
family in northern Sampson County.
Abraham joined the
Confederate Army in 1862.
And just after the end of the war, he
went on to become a gentleman farmer.
What about family? Did he have
wife, kids? What's the story?
Abraham and his wife had six children.
And the focus of the house would
likely have been on the children,
the gospel, faith, and their education.
- So he was a religious man?
- That's right.
Who died on the property?
Do you have any idea?
We know that one of his
daughters died in the 1880s.
His wife, Lizzie, died in 1897.
And his half-brother died
in the house, as well.
This depressed man... he
owned this place for sure.
He was preaching, and
he's, like, yelling.
He had a room that was dark and small...
And that he would do things
to human bodies there.
I think he was interested
in, like, what morticians do.
I think this guy was
really fixated on death.
I don't like him.
Coming up...
I don't really think it's safe here.
Wow.
Secrets come to light...
This is a lot of pressure for you.
And the living...
I would like to know...
Confront the dead.
What it will take for you to leave.
Next on "Dead Files Revisited".
This is Kara. She is the Executive Director
of the Sampson County arts council.
Going into the reveal...
I had an uneasy feeling about
what was about to happen.
We hadn't had any contact with Amy,
so the buildup about what
she saw was overwhelming.
Kara's worried about possibly
having to shut the place down.
Meredith used to volunteer here.
She doesn't do it any longer.
Ashley does volunteer here.
She doesn't even want to
be in this house alone.
So, Amy, why don't we start out
by you talking about your walk?
I encountered this one entity who um...
Knows, like, pressure points.
So I thought he's a Doctor.
It's funny you mention Doctor,
because one of the previous
owners was a Dr. Small.
I mean, he was considered a nice guy,
a gentle guy, but he hated his wife.
It was just amazing to
me that Amy saw Dr. Small.
And that it matched the
history that we have here.
And then what Amy said was frightening.
I don't really think it's safe
here at night because of him.
That's when he attacks.
Okay, what else?
So I was upstairs,
and I saw dead bodies.
So you're talking about the top
of the stairs by the bathroom.
It was in front of the bathroom.
This is a good time for
Ashley to tell you about
how she gets when she
goes near that bathroom.
The first time I walked in the bathroom,
I took two steps in and
got shaky, stomach hurts.
It feels like, you know,
a true feeling of dread.
I'm getting shaky talking
about it right now.
There was a guy that used to
live here before Dr. Small,
by the name of Leeman Matthews.
Never had issues.
He took a straight razor
and cut his jugular open,
and bled to death in the bathtub.
How do you feel about that
now that you know that?
It's a little shocking.
I feel like Ashley felt
a sense of relief...
In that Amy felt the same way when
she went into the bathroom upstairs.
But she also felt more
afraid in that it was real.
Okay, let's continue with
the rest of your walk.
One of the people that I did come into
contact with was a very depressed man.
Very, very sad about the war,
and he was also preaching a lot.
He would go into, like, rants.
I saw a figure walk out of the room...
Walk towards the stairway, through
the banister and down the stairs.
Well, one of the original owners of
this place was a guy named Abraham Hobbs.
He was a Confederate soldier.
The thing about Hobbs...
He was pretty religious and
very involved in the church here.
The depressed man that I saw...
He was the one who would put
the dead people around the house.
And he's the one who's responsible for
turning the house into the house of death.
And I'm getting concerned about
what might have happened here...
- Okay.
- Or is happening here.
I was really concerned when Amy said
that it was dangerous for us to be here.
You know, just wondering
about, would we have to leave?
The most pressing question
is, Kara, is it safe...
For you to keep this place open?
For that, I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
The first thing is to contact what
I like to call a living medium.
Which is someone who connects
the living with the dead.
They're going to connect Dr.
Small hopefully with his lawyer,
who can be his representative still.
Then Leeman...
The best thing there would be the
same type of scenario with you.
Then contact a death medium, like me,
who can come in and do a cleansing
from top to bottom, inside and out.
If this is done properly, it should get
rid of all the entities that are here.
Listen, are you okay? This
is a lot of pressure for you.
I'm a little overwhelmed.
I'm not gonna lie.
If you do do this, and you're strong
enough to do it, kids could come back.
Now, are you gonna be able to
follow through with all this,
and help out with this?
Since the investigation,
Ashley's been too afraid to
come back to The Small House,
and to be a part of the
cleansing with the mediums.
So I took matters into my own hands.
I brought in two mediums...
I ask for insight and guidance
and clarity as to why you're here.
And Mr. Gene Thompson to
hopefully release the spirits...
And cleanse the building.
On just a regular day, I'm
afraid to be here at night.
But to know that I had to come
back and communicate with the dead,
was just totally frightening.
I would like to know why you're here...
And what it would take for
you to be free to leave.
But I had a sense of relief as
she went through her processes.
I knew a fix was
coming. I could feel it.
Then, another medium and I went through and
cleansed every single inch of this house.
I felt like every spirit
in here was just lifted out.
The spirits have gone now.
May they rest in peace.
I immediately felt an easy feeling,
a feeling that they'd really moved on.
The Small House dates back to 1854.
Now that the house is cleansed
and the spirits are released,
we know that the arts
council will continue on
in providing arts
programming for the community.
I hope that Ashley will come
back and start volunteering again,
and that she'll feel safe here.
I'm impressed that Kara
accepted this responsibility,
and took control of
this difficult cleanse.
The decision to stand
in for Ashley was risky,
but from what I hear, the dead within
the Small House are finally free.