Subs created by: David Coleman.
This thing wants to make
someone here go nuts.
Whatever's happening
here is destroying us.
Oh, boy.
He says, ha ha. I've got you, [Bleep].
That's got to scare the hell
out of you, I would think.
He'll say, get out.
It's my house. Leave.
It's not something you
want to [Bleep] with.
You telling me the truth?
It made a believer out of me.
It's this sick, twisted environment.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing's, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people.
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her?
It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were
ghosts in this house.
When Amy and I take on a case, our
paths never cross until the very end.
I interview living witnesses and uncover
secrets behind the property's past.
While Amy communicates with the dead.
When we're done, we meet up and reveal
our findings to our clients and each other.
I'm in Flint, Michigan, one of the
most violent cities in all of America.
I'm heading over to meet with a
family who's being tormented by
the type of violence that would
never show up on the FBI stats.
Kathy, the mom, says her family of
seven are scared for their lives.
And she thinks Amy and
I are their last hope.
Before Amy arrives,
I need to remove anything that
could influence her findings.
It's clear from all these photographs
that a large family lives here.
So I need to carefully
conceal any evidence of this.
Only then will the location
be ready for tonight's walk.
I'm hearing growls.
It's, like, not an
animal. It's not human.
It's very, very dark.
This was brought here on purpose.
Yeah, there's pretty bad [Bleep] here.
Kathy, you sounded
really upset on the phone.
Things are pretty bad
here, it sounds like.
Yes.
We're seeing apparitions.
We're getting attacked.
- And who do you live here with?
- My husband and five kids.
Five years, we've been here.
There's people being scratched,
clawed, things thrown at.
And it hits the kids extremely hard.
- You okay?
- Yeah. Just... it's a hard subject.
I imagine it would be.
I feel like I'm a bad mother.
I mean, I didn't bring
them into the world,
to have something I
cannot see pick on them.
How can I defend that?
Have you ever done
anything to try to stop it?
We've had investigators come in.
We've done cleansing of the house.
We've done sea salt around the yard.
Okay.
But we've done
everything unsuccessfully.
And they've even tried
an exorcism on me.
- Oh, boy.
- And nothing's helping.
Okay.
Whether it's people now or
people that were here before,
you know, somebody was
definitely into some...
Dark stuff.
What do you mean?
They're into the paranormal but...
It seems like they're
uneducated about it.
Like, taking pictures and
video, like they're really...
Trying to figure it out.
Oh, boy.
Okay, so, what's going on in here?
We see black masses, and, I mean,
there's a lot of black masses in here.
So, what shapes and sizes
are we talking about?
Well, some of them come in human forms.
A lot of the times, it's a headless man.
He'll say, get out. It's
mine. My house. Leave.
But some of them are just widespread.
I mean, it's like they
spread across the wall.
And it's no reflection from
outside or anything like that?
No. No.
Well, that's got to scare the
hell out of you, I would think.
Yes, it does.
So, there is something that runs.
It went right through the wall,
as if this wall's not here.
- Was this the thing that was growling?
- Yes.
It's not something you
want to [Bleep] with.
I'm still not sure what this thing is.
But I get the feeling that it's out to
harm the people living in this house.
I think that some people have
seen it, like, a blackness.
But it could come to
them completely different.
It definitely morphs.
I just saw it, like, turn
into a big spider thing.
Very, very not good.
We're all close-knit,
very close-knit,
but when we're here, we're
at each other's throats.
We're all fighting, and,
I mean, this is not us.
How were the kids before they came here?
They were happy. I mean,
everybody was normal.
- So their personalities took a change?
- Yes.
My one son, he got mad and
punched a hole in the wall.
That's not like him.
Wow.
But as long as we're off this
property, we're back to normal.
We can sort through what just happened.
So, how long once you're off the
property do you start feeling better?
Just step off the property.
- That's it?
- Yes.
Whatever's happening
here is destroying us.
I'm hearing a lot of fighting...
Like, constant.
Um, screaming and yelling.
So I'm thinking that's a
direct effect of this thing.
I do see it, like, under the beds...
Like, slithering like a little
spider going under the beds.
I think that it wants to make
someone here or many, several go...
Nuts.
So, Kathy, why would
you bring me out here?
There was a time that I went
out here to talk to my husband.
He was out in the garage. And in the
middle of talking to him, I felt a hand...
Reach around my throat,
and I couldn't breathe.
I couldn't talk, couldn't nothing.
When I come running out of the
garage, I wound up vomiting out here,
but I felt the release of the
hand that was around my throat.
Wow.
That's probably the most physical
interaction I've heard about.
I haven't even told you the worst of it.
One night, laying in
bed, I was grabbed...
You know, I mean, sexually grabbed.
It woke me up out of sleep, and, of
course, I check on my one son, Mikey.
And I looked over, and his leg...
Somebody had his leg and
was pulling him off the bed.
I mean, he was literally
going from his pillow,
down his bed and about
to fall onto the floor.
What were they gonna do to him?
What's the next step from this?
How do you live like that?
It's not living. You're
just going day-by-day.
It may sound strange, but when you're off
the property, you just pray for a fire.
It'll be the relief.
I think it'll be the sigh, you know, that
you can actually breathe a little bit.
I see this woman who...
Is just...
Like, caught in this.
She just sees everything in her life...
Falling apart... like, not
sleeping, not really eating right.
And she's kind of the one
who takes care of everybody.
Okay.
And she's tough, but...
You know, she's broken
now. She's just broken.
Like, I think she's had thoughts
of burning down the house.
It's pretty bad.
- Zach, how old are you?
- 16.
I was talking with mom she's telling me
about the things that are going on in the
house I wanted to talk to you to
find out what you're experiencing.
- If anything.
- Well, I was scratched in the bedroom.
What do you mean? You got scratches?
I had the word "leave"
scratched on my stomach.
- Leave, huh?
- Mm hmm.
That sure as hell
does say that, does it?
Now, you didn't do this yourself, right?
- No, no.
- You telling me the truth?
- Yes.
- Okay.
What other experiences
are you having here?
I woke up, and there was a
guy sitting on the toy chest,
and he said, I can be a
real good friend for you.
Okay. Now, what did he look like?
The first time he came, he
looked like a normal human.
He was an old guy.
And the next night, he
started getting a little...
It looked like he was decomposing.
The next night, he got real
dark black, and he had no eyes.
- And this was the same guy?
- Yes.
Things here have gotten pretty bad.
I feel like it has made a consistent
contact with somebody here.
It's probably tricking someone.
Which obviously means that it can
do what scares you or bothers you.
And it's like a babysitter or something.
This entity is incredibly deceiving.
It projects itself into anything it needs
to get close to the people in this house.
It's a bad thing.
- Mike, I talked to Kathy.
- Okay.
I spoke with Zach. You
got a lot of problems here.
Yeah.
I want to hear from you
what you're experiencing.
One day I was out here
working on the truck,
and pretty soon, something
hit me in the back.
I happened to look down to see what it
was, and it was a piece of broken concrete.
Okay, you got no concrete on
the walls or the ceilings here.
- No.
- Anything else?
I had a one-inch wrench thrown at me, and
it hit me right in the middle of the back.
- Now, were you in here alone?
- Yeah.
- Do you keep the kids out of here?
- The kids were all in bed.
What's your biggest fear?
Oh... my biggest fear is
somebody's really gonna get hurt.
Right.
My plan was, you know, for us to
get married and be happy, you know?
And I wanted to start a
good life and take care...
Take good care of the
kids and everything, and...
We come into here, and
everything just went down.
So, there's been a lot
of chaos in this area.
I think the thing is in
here quite frequently.
And, I mean, it is interesting because
the thing doesn't like all this [Bleep].
Maybe because it doesn't look like
it did when it came here or something.
It makes it angry, and it
gets really, really physical...
Moving things very harshly
around, like it doesn't like it.
I'm trying to figure out
what this evil entity is,
and suddenly it reveals itself to me.
It's a Demon.
And it creates this sick,
twisted environment for...
Everyone.
Okay, Mike, why'd you
bring me in the bedroom?
A lot of stuff going on in
here that's just not normal.
Like what?
- Blankets being pulled off.
- Okay.
And I've been shook awake.
Your wife had told me you had a
lot of animals, could you be getting
touched at night, or the blankets
getting pulled, one of the animals?
- No.
- Why not?
We have the door locked at night.
I mean, it's got to be a little
bit tough for your marriage.
Yeah, it really is.
We never fought like
this until we got here.
There's been a couple of times that she's
actually threatened to just walk out.
Has your personality
changed since you got here?
- Yeah, very.
- In what way?
Real short fuse.
And apparently, the guy that lived here,
he had a very short fuse, too, you know?
You mean the guy that
lived here before you?
Yeah.
What kind of a guy was he, do
you know anything about him?
Um... all I know is what
his kids have told me.
He liked to throw things, and he drank.
Okay, so, you say he was. I
mean, did he die, I assume?
Yes, he died in the living room,
and they found him three days later.
And all the furniture stayed
behind, so we got his bed...
Both of his dressers.
- Is this his mattress, as well?
- Yes.
So you're sleeping on this guy's
mattress and using his furniture.
Yes.
Well, that's interesting.
I just see people fighting, and
this man comes in from the closet.
He says, ha ha. I've got you, [Bleep].
And he, like, tries to sleep in the bed.
You feel, like, a poke,
and it just stays here.
Like, they feel him near them
talking, but there's no words.
Because it's all gurbley.
It looks like intestines
or brains are coming,
like, out of their mouth or something.
It's not good.
It looks like intestines
or brains are coming,
like, out of their mouth or something.
It's not good.
Mm.
It's really hard, I can't...
Communicate because their
brains, literally, are scrambled.
They're not making any sense.
I don't know if he's,
like, severely mentally ill.
I can't get the thought
process out of him.
Mike told me the previous
owner died right in the house.
So I reached out to one of
his neighbors who knew him
pretty well to see what
he could tell me about him.
Your neighbors across the street were
telling me about the previous owner,
and that you knew him?
Yeah. I used to call him old Wild Bill.
I understand he died in
the house. Is that right?
Yeah, there was a... there was a
woman there, she would cut the lawn,
and she'd run errands for him,
and she had a key to the house.
She hadn't heard from him in like two
or three days, and she opened up the...
The door there and found he had
passed away inside the house.
Okay. Now, I was told... and
I don't know how true it is...
That he had a mean side
to him. Is that true?
Well, he could be. Yeah, if he
did a little bit of drinking there,
he could get about half
mean and that, but uh...
There was one time there the
kids had a swing in there,
and they're smoking cigarettes and that.
He come out there just bellowing and
that and chased them down the road.
Okay.
But after his wife passed away and
that, I think he started drinking more.
And I think he got a little
bit more cantankerous and that.
So, let me ask you something. How
did bill feel about his house itself?
Well, they kept that place immaculate
there, his yard looked like a golf course.
Inside the house,
everything was real nice.
And very particular about the way
everything was and that, I know if uh...
Anybody was in there and they was
messing with his tools, or anything,
he'd probably roll right over in his
grave, I believe that with all my heart.
- You do?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Can you describe him at all?
This person's white, male.
I feel like his body is frail.
He's, like, very shattered.
It's very weird. I don't know.
The guy could have been on drugs, and it's
almost like it's a lost cause or something.
This person is here most
of the time in this room.
Now that I know there was a death
fairly recently in Kathy's house.
I need to dig deeper into the property's
history to see what else I can uncover.
Searching through the archives, I discover
that a little girl named Loretta Eschenweck
died from a tragic accident
inside Kathy's home in 1936.
But the death certificate
doesn't explain how it happened.
I've managed to track
down the victim's nephew.
And he says he can
tell me what happened.
I understand your grandparents actually
lived in the house that I'm investigating.
Yes, they did.
Do you have any idea how long
your family owned that house?
Uh, from 1931 to 1974.
Okay, there was a tragedy there
where a little girl got killed.
- Loretta.
- What can you tell me about that?
It was my Aunt. She was 4 years old.
I have a picture here of
Loretta and my Grandmother.
She was playing when my
Grandmother was doing the laundry,
and then she fell into the
hot water the laundry was in.
That poor kid. I mean,
she must have suffered.
I think that she probably passed
from either, you know, infection...
Or something that related back to it.
She was an only child.
Right. She was the only
child. And they were young,
just starting out their family,
and then the devastation.
And then it took them quite
a few years to get over it.
But the memory was never lost of her.
I've traced the deed to this
property as far back as it will go,
but the history goes back even further.
I'm meeting with a local author who's
written a lot about the Flint area,
and he says Kathy's property used to
be filled with tragedy and warfare.
Turns out, the property I'm investigating
used to be Native American land.
Pretty horrific stuff went on there.
What can you tell me about it?
Well, this was the land of
the Saginaw Chippewa tribe.
They were a very fierce,
very warlike tribe.
The United States government
was terrified of these guys.
Most of the Saginaw Chippewa warriors
were very much aligned with the British.
Who were coming out of Canada to
fight the Americans in the War of 1812.
This is a picture of
United States troops.
Okay, so, what happened with
them during the War of 1812?
The Native Americans
would take hostages.
They would capture soldiers in
battle, swoop down on a settlement,
and literally ransom them back to
white representatives for money.
So, let me ask you a question
about the American soldiers.
When they were POWs, what
were they treated like?
It would have been a very, very
tough thing to be a prisoner.
The winter season would have
been very, very difficult.
Food would have been at a premium.
There are accounts of people
being tortured to death.
There's, like, a lot
of dead men over there.
And there's, like, at
least ten white men.
And they're all a mess,
and it's very, very muddy.
It's really weird, because
they really don't have anything.
Their clothes are just kind of tattered.
They have long, gray, wool coats on.
I think a lot of them are sick.
They haven't had, like,
proper meals in a long time.
They're just, like, pretty miserable.
I just think they're trying to get home.
So, what happens to my client's
property after the war's over?
After the war ends, the
Indians are left high and dry.
Now the British are
gone. They need money.
And the only other way
they had to get money
is to sell land to The United States.
And at that point, they're relying
very heavily on a fur trader,
who the Indians have known well now for
about 10, 12 years, and that's this guy.
And who's this?
That's Jacob Smith.
They think he's a friend.
They literally turn to Smith
for advice but the government is
paying him to influence the
Indians to sign a treaty in 1819.
They do. What Smith also manages to do,
is to secure land for his kids in
a very, very questionable manner.
And he does it by having Indian names for
his kids written into the treaty language.
The land you're
investigating is Nondashemau.
The Smith heirs claim that Maria
Stockton, Jacob Smith's youngest daughter.
That she is Nondashemau,
that that's her Chippewa name,
that her father's friends had given her.
The property was written
into the U.S. law for her.
So it sounds like he
basically tricked them.
He did. He manipulated things to have,
land granted to his
white kids in that treaty.
There were several entities
that stood out during my walk.
But what has me the most concerned,
is the demonic Creature
that's able to change shape.
And what I saw was this young female...
Light-brown hair, kind of pulled back.
She's kneeling down.
And there's a child sitting facing her.
On the wall, I would like there
to be the outline of just a shadow.
Is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations.
We're prepared to reveal
our findings to our clients,
and each other for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to
meet Mike and Kathy.
They live here with their five children.
We've done a lot of investigations,
but I've never heard the stuff
that they're going through.
They're actually afraid for their lives,
and they feel like we're their last hope.
That being said, I'm gonna ask Amy to
tell us a little bit about her walk.
So, I'm outside in the front
yard, and I saw these 10 men.
They were all white.
All of them were wearing, like,
torn and tattered long, gray coats.
They didn't have food.
I mean, they were a mess,
and they were very ill.
That's interesting.
During the War of 1812, the
land that your property sits on,
used to belong to the
Chippewa Saginaw Indian tribes.
During the war, they had sided with
the British, and they'd go out on raids.
And they would kidnap American
soldiers and civilians.
The historian I had spoke
to said that these guys lived
under the worst conditions
when they were hostages.
Oh.
Now, when you mentioned gray coats...
Take a look at that.
You see the uniform colors
on the American soldiers?
Oh, wow.
Now, there's an interesting
character in this whole thing.
A guy by the name of Jacob Smith...
Who used to be a fur
trader with the Indians.
Now, they trusted Smith, so he convinced
the Native Americans to sign a treaty.
With The United States government
for the land, but he tricked them.
Your property, he took from the Indians.
He did this by giving
his kids Indian names,
listing them as owners of
sections of land in the treaty.
Take a look. This is
where your house is.
He gave the property
the name Nondashemau.
The Chippewa Indians, they
thought it was their land.
It actually was there for his daughter.
Wow.
As far as I'm concerned, he
really screwed the Indians.
Whoa.
When I came into the house...
I saw an individual
jump out of the closet.
And this was in the Master Bedroom.
God.
He laughed, and then he
said, I've got you, [Bleep].
He tries to climb
into the bed and sleep.
Oh.
He was ripping covers off the bed.
You okay?
That happens.
Several times, I've felt the
blankets being pulled off...
And being grabbed...
Sexually.
You've been shook, too, right?
Yeah, it felt like somebody just...
Grabbed a hold like this on my shoulder.
And shook me right awake.
Wow.
What I did get was that he was white.
And that he was on some kind
of substance, maybe drugs.
And his body was very
frail when he died.
That's interesting you say that.
The man that lived in your house before
you guys bought it was this guy named Bill.
I talked to your neighbor about
him, who he was close with.
Said he was cantankerous and half mean.
Back in the '90s, his wife passed away,
and from that time, he took a downward
spiral, started drinking heavily.
Eventually, he wound up in a wheelchair.
He did die in the house.
I got his death certificate here.
He died of basically pneumonia
and respiratory failure.
He was found after like
three days in the house.
Some of that information you had.
The odd part is, when they
bought the house, they bought...
- Most of the furniture with it.
- Oh.
And they're actually
sleeping on Bill's mattress.
Yes.
- So...
- Oh, wow.
I mean, I don't know if this
is the guy you saw, but...
It's very possible.
Would them keeping his
furniture make things worse?
Yeah, that's probably not a good thing.
Beds hold a lot of...
Residual energy.
I'm not gonna be
settled until it's gone.
So, what else is going
on with this walk?
I felt like some of the
living in the house...
Are trying to communicate with the dead.
I wasn't upset by this, and
usually I get really pissed.
But I really felt like
these people were honestly
just trying to figure
out what's going on.
Tell her about how you've
been trying to communicate.
A paranormal team came in, and
they've done EVPs and pictures, but...
It's unsuccessful so far.
They've even done an
exorcism on me thinking that,
maybe something was attached to me.
It's very, very rare
that an individual...
Is uh, possessed.
- So it could have made it worse?
- Oh, yeah.
When they're not done
properly, all hell breaks loose.
The other thing that I got was uh...
About a living person at the
location, and this person is a female.
I felt like she was the caretaker,
always taking care of everyone.
But nothing she does is working,
and she feels like everything,
including her life, is falling apart.
She hasn't been sleeping...
exhaustion, beat up.
She's a mess.
And she has had thoughts of
possibly burning down the house.
And feels very guilty because...
She wants to leave...
But she knows she can't.
It's a constant struggle, daily.
Trying to keep the kids safe.
I haven't slept in years.
Watching your family get harmed by
something that you can't control...
It makes you feel like you're not
a good parent, you're not anything.
And the house burning...
that's all I wish about.
Every time I leave...
I just pray that it burns down.
Yeah, I'll lose everything,
but I'll gain my sanity.
Never thought it was gonna
get this bad, you know?
Somebody in this house is gonna
get either hurt or get killed.
What else you see?
So, there's one entity...
That's actually interacting with the
family, and it's extremely powerful.
And pretty much all of the
problems is generated by this thing.
And most people would
see it as a dark mass.
It's something that
you would not mess with.
Its main area is the garage.
And I saw it aggressively
moving objects.
It's very physical.
Why don't you tell Amy
about what happens in there?
I had a piece of concrete thrown
at me and hit me right in the back.
And a one-inch wrench thrown at me.
I want to show you something.
I had interviewed Zach, one of Kathy's
boys, and he showed me these pictures.
Now, I don't know if you can see
what's scratched into his chest.
It spells "leave".
Oh, yeah.
And he swore to me he
didn't do it to himself.
Wow.
Could this thing do that?
You know, I wouldn't discount
that as being a possibility.
Because it is an advanced entity,
so it can go into your mind
and it can project your fears.
It knows what scares you.
When I first encountered it,
it was like a huge spider.
I saw this headless man
come into the room one night.
And it told me to get out.
Interesting.
Well, I had the sketch artist sketch,
what I felt was the most
disturbing scene that I came across.
Take a look at that.
Who's the kid?
God.
Mikey.
I had the sketch artist sketch the most
disturbing scene that I came across.
Take a look at that.
Who's the kid?
God.
Mikey.
- He's the youngest, by the way.
- Okay.
- And he's, what, 5?
- 5.
She's the one I called the babysitter.
And you see who she really is.
She has this child entranced...
And feeling safe, but
it's not a real girl.
It's the entity.
He's constantly playing with somebody,
and he'll wake up in the middle
of the night, he's laughing.
I mean, hysterically laughing.
I knew it was a small child
that was being manipulated.
By this thing.
If it's able to do these
things, what's the next step?
What is it?
I mean, is it a human?
Is it not a human?
It took me a while to figure out,
but there was someone at some
point on that property who...
Was into dark magic.
And wanted revenge.
This individual conjured up
this entity, this demon thing.
- It's a Demon, then?
- Yeah.
That is what I would call a Demon.
It might have been kind of...
Activated again by...
Some of the investigations.
It's definitely attaching and
interacting with the family now.
It sought out living people
to begin gaining more power.
It's making people fight in the house.
And when I say fight, I mean fight.
Like, I'm talking screaming,
physical fighting, yelling.
And what it wants is for all of
you to turn against each other.
I call it kind of like a bloodbath,
because your blood boils. You just want...
Oh, God.
You want to hurt the person.
And it's just over the stupidest things.
But once you go off the
property, you can feel the relief.
Well, Kathy and Mike, this has been
a pretty tough night for you guys.
But now at least you know what the
hell has been tormenting your family.
The big question is, can you
stay in this house safely?
I can't answer that, so I'm
gonna turn that over to Amy.
I believe the best
thing you could do for,
yourselves and your
children is to relocate.
It's not too often that
this is the advice Amy gives,
but for her to give it, it must
mean you got a serious problem.
I'm leaving.
Gonna just turn my back on the
property and go away. I'm sorry.
You know, I got to protect my family.
Um... if they do decide to stay and
can't afford to move, what can they do?
It's a lot of things that would
need to be done simultaneously.
There is definitely PTSD here, okay?
And that's something that needs
to be addressed through counseling.
So you need to go and see
someone who is a psychologist,
or a psychiatrist who is
specially trained in PTSD.
The other thing that's going
on while that's happening,
is that a Catholic priest must
do an exorcism of the property.
And must counsel the dead man, and then
remove him from the location, as well.
- Would that get rid of the demon?
- Yes.
Why is it easier for them to just move
than to try to save the house and do that?
In this situation, you have a
family that is in dire straits.
Mm hmm.
You have individuals at the
location who are extremely open.
This is an emergency.
And I don't think that
you, at this time...
Need to be burdened
with all of that, too.
I'd feel much better
by getting out of there.
I mean, I'm not gonna
ruin what we have...
And our family for just a house.
It's tough, but it's a relief.
I know what steps I have to
take to see the happiness again.
I've seen so much sadness and
hate and blackness for so long.
I want to see the light again.
I wish I had better
news for Kathy and Mike,
but this demon has become so powerful...
That the only way to ensure
their family remains safe,
is to get as far away from
this property as possible.