My God.
Tonight on Dead Files Revisited...
He wants to slit my throat.
A second look at some of Amy and
Steve's most terrifying cases.
That's no way to live.
New information...
I actually started
thinking that I was nuts.
Startling revelations.
Why are you picking on
my kids? Come after me.
First...
A return to Egg Harbor, New Jersey...
The kids are completely freaked out.
Where a savage monster...
It scared the living crap out of me.
Unleashes hell.
His goal is vengeance.
Then we travel back
to Carmel, New York...
I turned around, and...
whoom!... I got tossed.
Where a local restaurant...
I see pools of blood.
Possesses a deadly threat.
That person's gonna die.
Did they listen to Amy?
Are you gonna take her advice?
Or are they cursed for life?
Spirits be gone. Leave this family.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing's, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people.
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her?
It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were
ghosts in this house.
When the call came in from a young
couple in Egg Harbor, New Jersey,
they were at the end of their rope.
They said ghosts were taking over,
and they were convinced something in
the house was making their daughter sick.
And even I didn't know
at that time that things
were a whole lot worse
than they had imagined.
All right, Jess, so, tell
me about what's going on.
The kids are starting to
see things... shadow figures.
My husband is completely freaked out.
And it's just escalating.
It's one thing for me that my
husband would be experiencing things.
But once the kids started to, like,
see things, it became more alarming.
Now, the kids... what's
going on with them?
My son... he will not go
into his room for any reason.
He doesn't sleep in there, nothing.
He just says he just doesn't like it, like
there's just someone in there with him.
What about the other kids?
My daughter... she's been sick for
over two years, and nobody knows why.
It's heartbreaking, and
that's why we called you guys.
I felt, like, this huge...
Being behind me.
And I thought it was
a big shadow person.
I've been battling shadow
people my entire life,
so I'm always on edge
when I think I see one.
But when I looked, I knew
that it was just a guy.
But I could only breathe easy for a second
before that man gave me a vicious warning.
He, wants to...
Slit my throat.
I had a dream that there was
a kid standing in my closet.
I followed him out of the
bedroom, into the kitchen.
He stopped at the basement door, went
like this for me to follow him, so I did.
I woke up from my dream. I
was standing on the landing.
Like, I physically got out of bed
and followed this kid in my sleep.
With all of the activity in
the house, I was losing my mind
because for the first five years, no
one else had experienced it besides me.
And then when my husband
finally started to see things,
it validated my
experiences because I knew,
there was something legitimately
going on in the house.
It's got to be tough for
you to sleep in here, then.
Yes. And there was a time where, for
a straight year, I slept on the couch.
- That's no way to live.
- No.
What are you looking at?
They kind of look like
little, tiny jellyfishes.
With, like, the long tentacles.
They're on the ceiling.
They're always moving.
They're always around.
They're trying to organize
themselves to become a being.
To this day, even I can't believe
I saw those strange creatures.
But despite my doubts, I couldn't
deny their heinous intentions.
What sort of things
can they do to people?
They are aggravating.
They would cause stress,
a sense of unease.
Insomnia.
Are they dangerous?
Yes, they are.
The instant I met Jessee's husband,
I thought I had him pegged as a
tough guy, but he threw me for a loop.
For a husband to admit he's
more scared than his wife,
something screwed-up
had to be in that house.
We were coming back from a
barbecue, walking up to the house.
We came up on the front porch,
and I seen a shadowy figure
appear through the curtain.
- Okay.
- It scared the living crap out of me.
Now, you don't look like you scare easy.
It scared me enough where
I had to call my 4'9 wife
to come up to the front
porch and go inside the house.
Really?
Nobody wants to believe that
you have ghosts or spirits or,
anything in your house.
So I really didn't want to
believe what Jessee had to say.
But when I had finally
seen something for myself,
it really freaked me out because I
really thought somebody was in my house.
Was this the first time
you saw something like that?
Actually, two nights ago, I had a dream.
And in that dream, in the corner of the
bedroom, there was a black shadowy figure.
And it just kind of went for me,
and I woke up at the same time.
I had the chills from head to toe.
There's a sickness here.
It just keeps feeling like I'm getting
punched in the stomach by this male...
Who initially I thought
was a shadow person.
It's like, get the **** out.
Like, get out of here. Get out of here.
Get out of here. Get out of here.
The dead man who
threatened to cut my throat
did everything in his power
to get me out of that house.
Looking back, I think he didn't
want me figuring out his cruel plan.
He feels like he was
ripped off and betrayed.
And the crawly things in the room...
I know he wants them to be
here, and he wants them to...
Come together and form a being.
Are you talking about
the jellyfish creatures?
Yes.
And they're not good, these things.
They're not. He's not.
Next...
Sounds like he got screwed over.
Deception leads to revenge.
They're cursed, really. They're cursed.
And in our second investigation...
I took off like a bat out of hell.
A vengeful spirit releases her wrath.
She really hates living people.
It didn't take long to track down
the previous owner of
Jessee and Fred's house.
The time that woman had
spent there was heartbreaking.
And by the end of our interview,
I couldn't help but feel her pain.
So, Linda, I understand you grew
up in the house I'm investigating.
Yes.
It was my mother, my father,
my brother, Louis, and myself.
Okay.
Now, you had mentioned on the
phone there was some tragedy
at home when you were living there.
- What happened?
- My brother had died.
He had committed suicide.
He had hung himself...
- In the basement.
- Geez.
- How old was he?
- 14.
It was 1970.
- Who found him?
- My mother. She found him there.
And she yelled and asked
me to bring a knife down...
Because she had to cut him down.
Geez.
How did your father deal with that?
After that, everything went downhill.
He said he was hearing voices
and there was people in his house.
He was diagnosed with psychosis.
When your father died, how old was he?
87.
He was like an empty shell.
The man I knew... he
just... he wasn't there.
There is, like, this old man
that's bopping around, too.
He's like 80.
And he wanders mostly...
He's confused.
When I see a dead person, it can
be at any given point in their life.
Typically, they have control over this.
But this old man had somehow become
a prisoner of his mentally ill state.
He does have moments of clarity where...
He knows that there's people here.
But then he gets even more confused.
There is activity in the
closet because he goes in there.
They look all cute and
harmless, and then they're crazy.
My talk with Linda moved me.
That house was clearly marked with tragedy,
and the more I dug, the worse it got.
After speaking to a local genealogist,
it seemed like every family associated
with that property ended up suffering.
So, Bob, what were you able to find out?
I was able to take the
title back to the mid-1850s.
When a group of wealthy
German financiers...
Acquired 38,000 acres of land.
And wanted to develop a town.
So, who wound up settling on the land?
There were two brothers...
an Ignatz and Louis Roesch.
They were German immigrants who came over
here expecting the land of opportunity.
Okay, so, what did they
find when they got here?
A little stark reality. I think
it was woods and mesquites.
They were met with very
difficult conditions.
Louis had a total of six
children, three of which died.
If they would have had the hospitals
and the proper medical attention,
they could have done
something different.
- Sounds like he got screwed over.
- Yes.
I can't imagine this is the life he
dreamt of when he left his home country.
Okay.
This man who I thought
was a shadow person...
There was something with money
and him and even his family.
I don't know.
Do you have any idea when this was?
Probably, like, 1850s.
I don't even know if it's
in this freaking country.
He felt betrayed, he felt...
Double-crossed.
Every time I encountered that man,
I would get a clearer picture of
why he wanted to torture the living.
But the extremes he
took were so dangerous,
it seemed like he didn't care that he
was also putting himself in harm's way.
Why would he haunt?
And be trying to get revenge?
They're cursed, really. They're cursed.
Yes.
Up next...
And is it safe for your
children in this house?
What happened after the investigation?
I felt like I was gonna hyperventilate
because I had no idea
what was in my house.
Spirits be gone.
You are not wanted here.
Pass through. You are over.
This is Fred and Jessee.
The night of the
reveal, I was so nervous.
I felt like I was gonna hyperventilate
because I had no idea what she
was gonna tell me was in my house.
What's most disturbing is
they got three small children,
and two of them are
starting to have experiences.
When I walked in the house, I felt
illnesses were in the living room.
Then when I went in the pink
room, I felt it really strongly.
That's my daughter's room.
She's been sick for two years now.
And they just couldn't find
anything wrong with her.
I don't want to think that something
in our home would hurt my child.
And it's not that I don't believe Amy.
It's just I don't want to believe that.
What else did you see?
I saw an old man in the house.
He's just, like, confused,
his favorite spot...
Is in the closet in the back bedroom.
He hides in there.
That's my son's room.
He's 6. He's never slept
a full night in his bed.
Wow.
It validates everything he says to me.
Well, there was a guy that
lived here for 51 years.
His name was Louis Brunk.
At the end, he
psychologically wasn't right.
And he would say, there's people here.
They're bothering me,
they're talking to me.
I did a sketch of a man I think
you're going to want to see.
He's probably about 80...
Very sick, very, very frail.
You guys tell me.
Wow.
That's crazy.
I think it's him.
When we first saw the picture of Louis.
It was heartbreaking because he just
looks so sad, and he looks hopeless.
And it also validated why we always just
got a bad feeling from all of the closets.
His 14-year-old son hung
himself in the basement here.
My God.
That's who I saw in my dream.
The second I saw that picture, I
knew immediately that it was him.
As a mother, it affected me
more because I could never
fathom the idea of something like that
happening to one of my own children.
And then not being able to pass over.
When I got here, behind me...
Was what I initially thought...
Was a shadow person.
And then I realized that it
was just a male who was hiding.
This guy is very capable
of inflicting pain.
He was from another country.
And he felt...
Like...
He had been double-crossed.
And he became extremely vengeful.
The guy Amy was describing
sounded just like Louis Roesch,
a German immigrant who got
screwed over in a land deal.
Basically, he was betrayed by
the people he gave his money to.
Our findings matched up perfectly,
but the next thing Amy found was
definitely out of my realm of expertise.
When I went into the Master Bedroom.
What I saw in there was these...
Things on the ceiling.
And they had, like,
little kind of tentacles.
And they become very,
very active at night.
They're shattered aspects of the
people who lived and died here.
It's kind of hard to visualize
what I'm talking about so,
the sketch artist did draw it.
Take a look at that.
My God.
Does it remind you of a dream you had?
That's exactly where it
was. That whole shape.
Absolutely, To the T.,
that's how I felt afterwards.
Exact placement.
When I seen the sketch, I was so
tripped out, it was unbelievable.
I'm like, man, this is real.
This guy Louis, the one from Germany...
Wants these things to become an entity.
So he'd get more powerful.
He would be able to control them
and also feed off of their energy.
Honestly, I don't even
know what to do with this.
What he did was he
actually cursed this land.
But when he did this curse,
he actually cursed himself.
He can't get out.
But since he can't get out,
he's gonna continue to create
problems or illness or misery.
If you're gonna pick on somebody,
why are you picking on my daughter?
Why are you picking on
my kids? Come after me.
It pissed me off. It was bad.
The pressing question is,
is it safe for you to raise
your children in this house?
You have a lot of dead
around this location.
What I feel needs to
be done here is to...
Contact a local Wiccan.
Wiccans are, like, a natural witch.
Will the Wiccan take
care of the bad Louis,
this fractured stuff,
and our poor guy here?
Yes.
And it'll protect them from his...
Vengeful curse.
Are you gonna take her advice?
Fred was immediately ready to
bring the Wiccan into the house.
I, on the other hand,
was a little hesitant.
It didn't go with our religion.
I mean, it really upset a
lot of people in my family...
That we're Catholic and we don't
believe in what was presented to us.
But if that's what Amy
told me, I was doing it.
Spirits be gone.
You are not wanted here.
Leave this family.
Leave this home. This is not your house.
When she came in, I was really hoping
that, this is it. This is the end.
Death has become of
you. You need to relieve.
It's a very surreal feeling to have a
Wiccan in the middle of your living room...
Pass through. You are over.
And burning Sage around
your entire house...
Guardians of the East,
bless us with your presence.
And blessing the backyard
and the whole property.
Help us bless this house
and rid it of evil spirits.
Since the Wiccan has been here,
everything is calmer and it's quieter.
And we haven't had any more experiences.
My children are feeling much better.
They've all started to
sleep in their own rooms.
And my daughter's health is
great, and she's doing great.
I am still a little bit leery
that there's something lurking
because it just seems
too good to be true.
Although I'm hopeful that
the curse has been lifted,
I completely understand
Jessee's apprehension.
After what she's been through,
it'll take time for her to
finally feel safe in her own home.
When I got the call from Anthony,
the bouncer at Smalley's Inn in
Carmel, New York, he sounded terrified.
He'd had some rough
paranormal encounters,
and the owner, Tony,
wasn't doing much about it.
Looking back, I'm not only shocked
at what Amy and I uncovered,
but blown away by how it all turned out for
the two tough guys at the center of it all.
What's going on here?
A lot of things are happening here.
I've seen apparitions.
I've seen things getting
pushed off a table.
I've been shoved from behind.
- You're kidding.
- Swear to God.
I hate to say that
I'm scared, but, yeah.
I grew up in the streets of the Bronx,
and I had a gun pointed at my head,
but it's when you can't see the
stuff that will drive you crazy.
You don't want to walk through
the door to come to work.
When somebody says a place
is haunted, people say,
get out of here. You're
imagining it. You're a lunatic.
I honestly started
thinking that I was nuts,
but meeting Steve, it was like
going back to the block again.
And I knew he wouldn't think that
I was lying and that I'm not nuts.
So this is actually hurting your income.
Yes, I need to support
my wife and three kids.
I can't afford to lose this job.
Before I arrived at the location,
I was already feeling on edge.
I saw...
This female, and I've seen her before.
At home, she was, like,
white and transparent.
She's here.
That dead woman had visited
me days before my walk,
and as soon as I saw her
there, I knew I was in danger.
She really hates me.
She seems to cause...
Death.
Whoom! I got tossed.
- Next...
- She's happy causing chaos.
A dark presence lurks underground.
She really hates living people.
I see pools of blood.
When the bouncer at Smalley's Inn
started telling me about
his paranormal encounters.
My first instinct was to tell him to get
the hell out of there and never come back.
But he needed that job.
And the case was just getting started.
All right, so, what
happened to you down here?
I came down here, and a woman
that was very, like, proper,
whispered something in my ear.
I turned around, and...
whoom!... I got tossed.
I mean, God, I'm a big guy.
Yeah, I mean, I go 210. You got
to be at least 275, 280, right?
Easy. Easy.
This thing threw me like
I was light as a feather.
Any time I go into the
basement, I feel nervous.
That it's gonna happen again to
me... that I'm gonna get thrown again.
Describe the way the woman looked.
She was dressed like an 1800s
look, and I could see through her.
What did you do?
I took off like a bat out of hell.
Wow.
She cries.
Really nasty.
She is...
What...
People would call a Banshee.
Seeing a Banshee is a rare
and terrifying encounter.
To look one in the eye
can be an omen of death.
So when I caught a glimpse,
I thought I was in trouble.
She's happy causing chaos.
She really hates living people.
It's really strange.
I think she's here.
Where?
Downstairs.
Well, what else have you see down here?
I've seen a male apparition,
and the same ****
I came down here to get some
liquor, and I almost bumped into him.
Like, I thought it was a customer.
Can you describe the guy to me?
Yes. Curly white hair, jacket...
Ruffles in the shirt.
And I'm ready to pop him.
I'm ready to smash this guy.
And he went that way. I went after him.
Nothing.
Gone.
If that happened to me, I don't know if I
could even come back down in the basement.
Well, I don't.
And there goes my pay, and there
goes putting food on the table.
There's a man in uniform down here.
What kind of uniform?
He's wearing, like, a poufy
outfit with a rifle, with a...
Can cut... kill you.
Like a knife on the end?
But I don't feel good about it.
It feels like maybe the
basement's his area or something.
The amount of activity in that
basement was out of control.
And whenever that many dominant
entities gather in one place,
the living are in serious trouble.
He follows people. He
likes to intimidate.
It's all, like, sneak
attacks, though, for him.
He gives off panic and confusion.
Makes me feel...
Scared.
Anthony said he wasn't the only one
frightened to work at the restaurant.
So I decided the only way to find
out how bad things really were...
Was to go straight to the top.
People have gotten
tugged on their sleeves,
pulled on their aprons,
tapped on the shoulder.
Whenever I'm hiring staff members,
I have to tell them that
the place is haunted, and...
"Are you okay with that"?
And a lot of them will
want to come to work and,
they're usually the ones that
leave because they had an incident.
People are quitting
on me left and right.
A girl, she noticed a soldier
standing there looking at her.
So, did she describe what she saw?
A blue uniform with a yellow stripe
going down the side of the pants.
So a Civil War or an older army uniform.
Yes.
The girl quit that night.
I just got, like,
this really angry male.
Very intimidating.
I don't know. He came up behind me
and was, like, trying to grab my back.
It feels like this soldier guy...
Or Captain, whatever he is, is hiding.
Do you know where he went?
No.
It feels very claustrophobic, like
you can't see your way out to escape.
He had a mortuary underneath the Inn.
Next...
And, like, someone's digging
a bullet out of somebody.
Amy unearths a dark secret.
It's gross and dirty and disgusting.
According to our clients,
Smalley's Inn was a hotbed of
violent paranormal activity.
But nothing they gave me
translated into a solid lead.
So I found someone who
could tell me about the man
whose name was written
all over the building.
As you know, I'm doing the
investigation on Smalley's Inn.
James Smalley
bought the building in 1852.
And he turned it into an inn,
a tavern, and a restaurant.
Okay.
By all accounts, he was quite
active in the community...
Town Supervisor, Sheriff,
Treasurer, Assemblyman.
He even recruited
soldiers for The Civil War.
So, did James Smalley have a family?
Yes.
His first wife was named
Harriett, but she died in 1850.
And then he married
Harriet's sister, Emily.
Do we know when he died?
He died in 1867 in the building itself.
He was about 54.
One morning, he woke up, had a
heart attack, and that was it.
I also get this guy.
I don't know if he worked
here or owned the place,
but he was very much in charge
and was here all the time.
And he also is more, like, residual.
But he died here.
When I encounter a residual haunting,
it's rarely a cause for concern.
Instead of being interactive, it's more
like watching a scene from an old movie...
In this case, a very
sad, heartbreaking movie.
And how did he die?
I think he had a heart attack.
When Linda told me about John
Smalley's involvement in The Civil War,
a light went off.
An ex-employee at the restaurant claimed
she'd seen a ghost in a Civil War uniform.
With that in mind, I found a military
expert to see if any of this tied together.
I learned that James Smalley was
pretty active during The Civil War.
He was extremely
active in The Civil War.
He handled the draft boards, got the
young people from the County to enlist.
Okay, so his role was to actually
get the men to go off and fight.
Yes.
Did Smalley actually serve in the war?
He was too old to serve in the war.
So, Rich, did he serve any other way?
Yes, he did.
He actually had a mortuary
underneath the Inn.
Now, that was in the basement?
Yes.
Soldiers that died of their wounds
in hospitals who were shipped home
for burial were put up temporarily
in his Morgue beneath the Inn.
Okay.
Again, just getting this,
like, loud... people yelling.
This is a long time ago.
It is weird, though, because
I do see, like, pools of blood.
- Where?
- On the floor.
The blood on the floor is, like, an
indicator of how many people died here.
As if that restaurant
couldn't have gotten any worse,
now blood was streaming towards my feet.
But unlike other cases where
it's from a senseless killing,
that blood was caused by something else.
And someone's talking
about something medical.
What do you mean?
I'm seeing tables here.
There's a lot of people
here, and there's...
My God!
They're bringing in these men.
People are freaking out,
and they've been injured.
And, like, someone's digging
a bullet out of somebody.
It's gross and dirty and disgusting.
Coming up next...
She's there.
The danger becomes real.
She hates all living
people. She's pissed off.
But did they listen to Amy?
I was looking to get out of
Carmel as fast as possible.
Anthony here works
Security for the restaurant.
He's a tough kid.
But he's pretty frightened by some of
the things that have happened to him here.
The night that I met Amy, I was nervous
because she sees dead
people, for Christ's sake.
But I was praying to God that
she actually did find something...
That I'm not a lunatic and that I
don't need to go to a mental hospital.
Tony owns the place.
He's concerned about maybe losing
customers because of what's going on here.
So, with that, Amy will start
and tell us about her walk.
Well, there was something I
encountered before the walk.
I was at home, and the female showed up.
And I get here...
And she's there.
And she wants me dead, and...
So you're saying she's here.
Yeah.
- Geez.
- And I'm like, okay.
She hates all living
people. She's pissed off.
And I could see through
her, which is really weird.
Have you ever heard of a Banshee?
I've heard the term.
A Banshee is, like...
A Grim Reaper.
If somebody sees them,
that person's gonna die.
If somebody hears them, someone close
to that person is going to die very soon.
And she'll go around the
area. It's not just here.
She's affecting other
locations around here.
So that's good. I could take this
woman to my house with my kids, right?
Yes, you can.
I was nervous as all hell, because
I could bring it home to my children.
And that's the only
thing in this whole world
that I really care about, is my babies.
You know, I was looking to get
out of Carmel as fast as possible.
Well, actually, I sketched her.
My God.
It's not really like a sketch
I've seen you do before.
Well, she was transparent.
The woman I saw
downstairs was transparent.
I could see through her.
I went nuts when I saw that sketch because
that's the woman I saw in the basement.
I wanted to run out of there like
I was Secretariat at the Belmont.
It was that scary.
Her eyes were just all white.
You're almost, like, describing a witch.
That's a scary-looking picture.
When I first saw the sketch it was,
like something you would
see in a horror movie.
And it was all kind of
hitting me at the point where,
I was afraid to look over
my shoulder, thinking that...
This Banshee was gonna
be sitting behind me.
What else did you see on your walk?
I encountered a big
guy who had dark hair.
And I got that he was
an owner of this place.
And he had a heart attack.
- You saw that?
- Yeah.
And then I saw these
men were brought in.
They were bloody, messed
up. The room was disgusting.
It sounds like one of the original
owners, who this place is named after...
James Smalley.
He died of what they called
a sudden morning heart attack.
During The Civil War, the
basement acted as the Morgue
for the soldiers that were
getting ready for burial.
Now, his first wife died, and he
wound up marrying her sister, Emily.
I heard and seen this lady.
You saw her?
I saw her downstairs.
One of the reasons we're here...
He was in the basement,
and he got shoved.
I got flung like it was nothing.
Well, I felt, when I saw
this photo, that it was her.
I breathed a sigh of relief because now
I knew we weren't
dealing with a Banshee.
It was only a projection
created by that woman.
But that didn't make
her any less dangerous.
Well, Anthony, Tony, there's
obviously stuff going on here.
The question is, is it
safe for you to be here?
She is your first priority to deal with.
And it's not gonna be easy.
Find a priest, and you need
a medium at the same time.
The medium is basically...
Going to ask her to leave.
The priest is gonna do a blessing.
And that's going to
help with him to leave.
Well, are you guys gonna
listen to Amy's advice?
After the investigation, I didn't
come back here for a month or two.
I still didn't think it
was safe to work here.
After Amy had left, paranormal
activity did increase.
But so did business.
So I can't complain.
I need this job to support
my three kids and my wife.
I need to pay my bills, but
I cut back my hours big-time.
I only work fridays now.
And it's because I'm not gonna
have myself thrown downstairs.
These ghosts have become,
like, our trademark here.
And people know us as the
haunted restaurant in Carmel.
So do I want to get rid of them?
No.
Cheers.
Tony's one of my best friends,
but does he care about his
business more than our friendship?
Sure, he does.
It's a restaurant.
This is his livelihood.
People will come up to me and tell
me I have to get rid of the ghosts
because something bad's gonna happen.
I'm worried about people's
safety when they come in here.
These ghosts are here for a reason.
They were here before us.
This is their territory.
And they're gonna lash out,
and they're gonna harm somebody.
Until that time, I'm gonna do it my way.
I'm disappointed in Tony for
deciding that making money
is more important than his
staff and customers' safety.
And that Anthony continues to put
himself at risk because he needs the job.
I warned Tony that he was
dealing with something dangerous,
and my guess is that one
day, I'll hear from him again.