Tonight on Dead Files Revisited...
Unhealthy attachment to the dead.
A second look at some of Amy and
Steve's most terrifying cases.
He shoots him in the head.
New information...
I didn't know where else to turn.
Startling revelations.
I really wanted to see
what Amy was made of.
First, a return to
Rock Island, Illinois...
And there's people under the trees.
Where an army of dead...
I feel like I'm always being watched.
Invade a family home.
You scared to be at home?
Then...
So, he's dead.
We travel back to Key West, Florida...
I don't have an explanation for it.
To a house where lost souls...
He was tortured and burnt.
Torment the clients.
Why are these people still
staying in this house?
Did they listen to Amy...
Are you gonna follow Amy's advice?
Or continue to live in fear?
All bad dead and bad guides must leave.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing's, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people.
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi. I'm a retired
New York City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her?
It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were
ghosts in this house.
I'll never forget the case
in Rock Island, Illinois.
For our client, Mellissa,
life was a living hell.
Paranormal activity
had taken over her home.
And her daughter, Madison,
couldn't handle it.
And when our investigation exposed
that they weren't the only ones in
the family suffering I'd wondered
if they'd ever be the same again.
So, Mellissa, I understand
that you and your 4 year
old daughter are having
problems in the house.
- Yes.
- Okay. Who else lives here?
My husband, Mike, and our
7 year old son, Nathan.
We're seeing apparitions, shadows.
Our daughter, Madison... we
want her to not be afraid.
We want her to have a normal childhood.
At first, I thought it was just
typical, kids having imaginary friends.
But then it became apparent that it
wasn't an imaginary friends of hers.
She was terrified.
I was like, okay, I
need to protect my kids.
So I need to do something about this.
She wakes up in the middle of the night,
crying, just blood-curdling screams.
I don't like being in here by myself.
So I don't really blame her for not
wanting to be in here by herself at night.
On the drive to the location, I
sensed an evil presence waiting for me.
But when I came face-to-face
with him for the first time,
I knew the only way to make it through
this walk was to keep my guard up.
There's, like, people under the trees.
There's also this other
really creepy dude.
He wears a cloak.
He works with these people
in the trees, though.
They're, like, underlings for him.
The cloaked man had amassed a
seemingly endless army of the dead,
and his plan for them was clear.
He wants to get rid of living people.
So, what's going on in here?
I feel like I'm being watched down here.
And it's like when I go up the
stairs to go back upstairs...
It's almost like if you were
being chased up the stairs,
how you want to hurry
up and get to the top.
That's how I feel.
I've had these experiences
most of my life,
and I was never really afraid of it.
But that feeling of something
standing there, just watching me.
It gave me the chills.
Now, when did things
kind of pick up here?
When we moved in, I was pregnant with
my son Noah, and Nathan was about 2.
And I noticed...
Um...
A shadow in the basement.
Okay, so, your son Noah.
You didn't mention Noah.
Yeah, I was pregnant with
Noah when we bought the house.
He passed pretty much right
away after he was born.
I'm sorry to hear that.
There's two people here who are mediums.
One of them is extremely developed.
It might be a child.
This living person is
very attracted to death.
I think there's family members
that this person's held onto.
Unhealthy attachment to the dead.
For someone with abilities,
emotions are a really powerful tool.
But if they're not in control of those
emotions, the impact can be serious.
Yeah, and stuff happens in here...
Poltergeist **** you know?
Do you have any idea
who it's coming from?
- I want to say a female.
- Okay.
The living person doesn't know how to
release their **** emotions properly.
Anything that could be dangerous?
Yes.
Mellissa's focus was primarily
on herself and her daughter.
But her husband, Mike, pointed
me in a different direction.
What about your son?
He's never really
complained of anything before
except for not wanting
to go in the basement.
I don't know if that was
because of anything that
was happening that he
didn't want to talk about.
- If he's seeing something.
- Right, right.
I don't know how to fix that.
So, I decided to talk to the other child
and find out what he
wasn't telling his parents.
So, Nathan, I was talking
to mom and she told me that
you've been experiencing
some stuff in the house here?
Have you had any experiences?
Explain that to me.
I was in my bed, looking at the closet.
I saw, like, a gray
shadow running across it.
It was kind of a person shadow.
All right. So, did that scare you?
It scared me a lot.
Just tried not to think
of it and have a nightmare.
Okay. Did you tell anybody about it?
No, I haven't yet.
It was nice to share my
information with Steve.
Because I got to tell
him about what I saw.
It was the first time I've
ever told someone because,
I was scared to tell my mom and dad.
So, anything else happen?
I felt someone trying
to pull me downstairs.
Down in the basement?
How?
Like, grabbing onto my shirt.
When I heard that Nathan was feeling
and hearing and seeing
the same things I was.
I was completely shocked, because he
had never said anything to me before.
Are you scared to be at home?
Yes.
The ones that are coming in
here, they can get kind of nasty.
They more look like shadows, but
they, like, are up against the walls.
Is there anything else these
people can do to the living?
You see them out of the corner
of your eye, but you feel them.
What will these things eventually do?
Well, they can kill.
Next...
He's burying bodies.
A betrayal ends in tragedy.
They lost everything.
And in our second investigation...
I know it's a dead person.
The fate of the dead...
Get out, get out, get out of my house!
Rests in the hands of the living.
Get out!
Our clients in Rock
Island mentioned that
their land used to be owned
by a notorious gangster.
Whenever the mob's involved, it's a
safe bet that something shady went down.
But after talking to a local author,
it was worse than I had expected.
This is John Looney.
He met a woman named Nora O'Connor.
They got married, and they
had two daughters and a son.
Okay.
But about 1903, his wife dies.
And he spiraled downward
into this life of crime.
He was involved in gambling,
moonshine, prostitution.
This is Looney from sort
of the height of his power.
How powerful did this guy get?
Well, he basically controlled the town.
People were very afraid of him.
Okay. Now, I assume
he was a violent man.
Well, we know that a lot
of people died, and...
Looney had people on his payroll who
were, you know, basically paid hit men.
There's, like, a family out there...
You know, like, a mother, a father,
I think like two or three kids.
But their father...
he's kind of freaky...
Kind of creepy-looking, too...
Dressed all in black.
I'm getting something about...
Dirty dealings.
At first, the man in black was giving
off an eerie vibe and not much else.
But that feeling quickly changed as soon
as he revealed his crueler, darker side.
I just got a nasty headache.
And someone's yelling about a gunshot.
I do feel like there's
a hole in my head.
****
There's, like, blood and then confusion.
Like, I don't know if they lived.
Do we know if he ever buried
any bodies on the property?
He had, you know, this large piece
of land with nobody living around it.
The opportunity existed.
He's, like, burying bodies.
I keep seeing these
bodies all over the place.
He's, like, digging them and just
throwing them in the ground, you know?
He was evil.
He definitely was not
involved in good things.
Continuing my research,
I learned that Mellissa's property used
to belong to a Native American tribe.
Before I got into this line of work,
I would have said that the
chance of connecting that
to the client's house
would have been slim.
But now that I've got a better
understanding of how Amy operates,
I know that I've got
to follow every lead.
Well, the last tribe of Indians to inhabit
that area were the Sauk Nation of Indians.
And they were here from about 1735.
Okay, so, what happened
with the Indians there?
They lost their land to the
American government in 1804.
But only about 1/3 of the tribe refused
to leave the land of their ancestors.
But one of their spokesmen
was a man named Keokuk...
Who was very friendly to the Americans.
He was able to convince his own people,
that there was no point in
fighting the American government.
And it to just move as they were told.
What about the people that didn't
support him, how did they feel?
Well, they felt that he was a
coward, a traitor to their nation.
So, the people that sided with Keokuk,
did they prosper with the deal he made?
Well, no, they were
removed over into Iowa
and told that they
could live there forever.
But within 10 years of
this promise, they're gone.
- They lost everything?
- They lost everything.
I'm seeing this leader guy
again, who's wearing a cloak.
And he says that
everybody who's come since
has just **** everything
up and destroyed it.
He feels justified as far
as wreaking havoc on people.
As I watched the cloaked man
plan his attack on the home,
I started to realize that he planned
to wipe out more than just the living.
What does he do?
Basically whatever needs to be done,
but he sends his people in to do it.
What do you mean?
The people that he puts in the trees...
Were from his time, like 17-something.
When he sends people into the
house, why is he doing that?
That's him trying to
get rid of this building.
Next...
That's pretty scary.
Did the clients follow Amy's advice?
I didn't know where else to turn.
My spirit helpers, I'm
here to help these people.
There are spirits here
who are hurting them.
Please release them.
Mike and Mellissa have
been here about five years.
Mellissa's had experiences
from the minute they came here.
Going into the reveal,
we knew Amy was gonna be
able to give us some answers.
But I never thought she'd
be able to answer so much.
They have two beautiful children,
so they're concerned if their kids
can live here in a safe environment.
One of the first people that
I encountered was a male.
I did get that while he was
alive, he was particularly evil,
and he definitely was not
involved in anything good.
John Looney was a gangster that
owned this property back in the 1920s.
He was supposedly very ruthless...
Got convicted of murder.
He was suspected in
many, many more deaths.
Looks like him, yeah.
Knowing who this man was and his history
and the fact that he's in my
house made me very uncomfortable.
It gave me the chills.
What else did you see?
Well, then I saw something out back.
Under the trees are all these people.
And their leader was this man
who, he was wearing a dark cloak.
He just made a big mistake.
And now that he's dead, he does an
incredible job of watching his territories.
There was a tribe of Indians called the
Sauk Nation that inhabited your land.
There was an Indian by the name of
Keokuk, and when the white men came...
He basically sold out the whole Indian
nation here and had them displaced.
What this person wants
is the house to be gone.
He'll send other people to,
like, take care of business.
What scared me the most was
Keokuk, because he's so powerful.
If he's able to kind of trap
all these other people here,
who knows what he can
do to me or my family?
Now, did you see any of those
people inside this house?
I went down to the basement,
I saw some of the specific dead people that
I think were sent to destroy your house.
I actually saw somebody
doing laundry, a female.
This was a living person, and one
of them was crawling on the floor...
And was actually trying to
grab the person's pant leg.
Yeah, there's something
about that laundry room.
I feel like I'm always being watched.
You said you saw a living
woman? That's what you saw?
Well, I sketched it.
She's gray.
Her legs are kind of bent sideways.
Wow.
That's pretty scary.
Once they pulled out the sketch and
I saw how scared it made my husband.
It was like the people that are trapped
here are reaching out for my help.
And I really wanted to
help these people move on.
So I was hoping that Amy would be
able to give me the tools to do that.
I did get that there was someone
here who brings in the dead.
And the other thing was getting that there
was a child who's extremely open here.
And very well developed,
which is very interesting.
When I went into their bedroom,
the dead lined up and greeted me.
It had the bunk beds, I think.
That's Nathan's room.
I think your daughter has
something going on too, but...
Right now, he is way more
advanced than your daughter.
So, when Amy started talking about
the child in the house
that was a sensitive.
I immediately figured she
was talking about Madison.
Since she's the one that had been
having the experiences that I knew about.
I was just shocked that she
was talking about Nathan.
So, the last thing was a little
bit of poltergeist going on here.
I felt that the adult
medium won't let go.
Specifically to the family and friends.
That sound like you?
We had another son named Noah.
Okay.
And he actually passed
away shortly after birth.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I've had other people tell me that...
I haven't grieved properly...
For Noah...
The fact that Amy touched on something
so personal just blew my mind.
There's no way she could have known that
I had been struggling to deal with that.
And made me feel horrible that,
I'm contributing to the chaos
that's going on in the house.
Well, Mellissa, I know
tonight was pretty rough.
But the big question is your children.
- Right.
- Is it safe for them to be raised here?
So, the first thing you need
to do is grief counseling.
This is going to allow
you to let go of the dead
and to process emotions
in a beneficial way.
For Nathan, every night
before he goes to bed,
have him state that he
only allows the good dead
and guides to stand by him and help him.
So, will that get Looney out of here?
Yes.
So, the last thing is
you can go to the tribe...
That Keokuk is from and ask them
to do a ceremony in your backyard.
To release him and the
people that he's imprisoned.
But are you gonna follow Amy's advice?
When Amy told me everything I
had to do to fix the situation,
it was a lot of stuff to do, but I was
really anxious to get started on it.
But we ran into some issues
getting Keokuk to leave.
The Sauk tribe believes
that this is his land.
He was here first. So they
weren't willing to help.
I didn't know where else to turn.
My spirit helpers, I'm
here to help these people.
So, Amy told me that I
could contact a local Shaman,
to help clear the land.
There are spirits here
who are hurting them.
Please release them.
First, he went through the home
and told the people that
are stuck here to move on.
Please help make this house
a safer place for them.
And then he went outside and was
doing a chant, asking Keokuk to leave.
Help me. Work through me.
So we may help these people,
rid themselves of this person
who is there and should not be.
Who has come to this house uninvited.
I felt that this was it.
We were gonna finally get rid of Keokuk,
and I was gonna actually get my home back.
Help us to help this family
rid them of this unwanted guest.
Please work through me to help them.
Amy told me to enroll
in grief counseling,
and that's been helping me a lot.
His name was Noah, and I had
him right before I had Madison,
and he only lived for a couple of hours.
Nathan's doing his special prayer
every night to keep the evil away.
I'll allow only the good dead and the
good guides to stand by and help me.
All bad dead and bad guides must leave.
When I say the prayer, it
makes me feel really nice.
I feel protected, also.
While my kids aren't seeing
things anymore, I still am.
I'm hoping that by continuing
the grief counseling...
I am able to get to the point where
I don't see these ghosts anymore.
While I understand Mellissa's concerns
about her future, I'm not worried.
So far, she's managed to overcome
every challenge that's come her way.
And that determination will be the driving
force that keeps evil out of her home.
Early on in my time working with Amy,
we investigated a home down in Key West,
Florida, that was swarming with activity.
Now, at this point, I was still coming to
grips on how this paranormal thing works.
But by the end, my eyes had
opened up just a little bit wider.
Ever since I moved in,
I felt someone was here.
I knew that I wasn't alone.
Okay.
I feel cold spots everywhere,
but I don't see anything.
I don't hear anything, really.
It just felt like someone else was in
the room, but you couldn't see them.
I know it's a dead person.
I'm here in Key West. In
summertime, it's very hot and humid.
And with on AC on, I'd be freezing
and I'd have to put on layers
of clothes just to keep warm.
It's just like, what is going
on? What do I do to fix this?
Type of thing.
You thought to yourself that that
chill was a being of some sort.
- Yes.
- Okay.
And you feel them, and it's
almost like they're right on you.
Before I arrived at the location,
I was already feeling concerned.
The dead in the home were
hesitant to talk to me.
Because what was waiting
behind the front door...
Was chaos.
I saw, like, two graves.
There was time between these two deaths.
I feel like they knew each other.
One of them, he's
wearing a hat sometimes.
And then the other guy, he was burnt.
It was, like, in a violent
rage, and it was like a betrayal.
Kind of got off on people fighting.
- Next...
- It's like they were on a mission.
The dead stalk the living.
He likes to hurt people.
Key West, Florida, has a rich
history in all things paranormal.
And the home we investigated
there was no exception.
Some strange experiences were making our
client, Colette, terrified in her own home.
And she was worried that the house itself
wasn't the only source of the problem.
Well, basically, my partner, Glenn,
sees things throughout the house.
He sees things?
Yes. And Glenn sees all this activity...
people walking through the house.
He'll say, Colette, I can't
believe you don't see these people.
We'll be sitting here on the
couch and Glenn would say,
there they go right now. Don't
you see these people walking by?
They'll be up and down
through this hallway.
And I'm going, no, I don't
see it. I don't see anything.
I don't know how these
things work, to be honest.
It'd be nice to know what's
going on in this house.
There's people...
Two main people.
There's a male.
He wanted to hurt somebody.
As I watched the burned man spew his
hatred towards the man in the hat.
It was becoming apparent they
had an intense rivalry in life
that had now carried over into death.
There's more out here.
He's had, like, something
that really bothered him.
Like, a lot of anger.
Got to get rid of that.
Colette had some obvious
anxiety about her home.
But her partner, on the other
hand, was a different story.
When it comes to the dead,
nothing seemed to faze this guy.
But what he saw would end up being
a crucial part of the investigation.
Hi, Glenn.
You've seen some things in the
house that Colette hasn't seen.
Can you go into an
explanation of what you saw?
Well, I've seen one
primary figure many times.
And every once in a while,
there were other individuals.
Since I was 2 years old, I
have been able to see spirits.
And it never scared me.
I was never threatened.
They did their thing. I did my thing.
I let them live. They let me live.
- So, you know it's a male.
- Yeah.
And it wasn't particularly friendly.
Could you pick him out of a lineup?
Yeah. Without a doubt.
I think he's about 5'10 or 5'11.
I saw white-colored slacks
and a light-colored shirt.
Seeing spirits is not an unusual
occurrence for me, but this was different.
I saw him so vividly, I
could smell his cologne.
This man could build things and
make things or tear them down.
And he tore this down, and
that gives him satisfaction.
He feels good about that.
Can you describe him?
There was kind of like
a white day outfit.
A white linen shirt and a...
Pair of white linen pants.
The person is 5'10...
Maybe hazel eyes.
And a hat sometimes.
Actually, kind of round.
And a ribbon around
it... like, a straw hat.
I could sense that the man in the
hat was the type who demanded control.
His demeanor was generally calm, but
his actions towards people were twisted.
There's some kind of conflict here.
Somebody's arguing.
He kind of got off on people fighting.
He likes to hurt people.
He was not a good guy.
They walked through the light, back and
forth, back and forth, back and forth.
The frequency of activity
with the spirits...
Was just many times a day.
Two or three dozen,
four dozen, five dozen.
It went on all day
long and all night long.
Did they look like they
were looking for something,
or was it just they
were walking through?
It's like they were on
a mission, so to speak.
- Okay.
- I don't have an explanation for it.
He shoots him in the head.
Next...
He is in a lot of pain.
And he was...
Tortured.
A bitter rivalry ends in bloodshed.
Did he see it coming?
No. No.
Digging through the records,
I uncovered a connection between a
prominent event in Key West history,
and the man who built Colette's home.
But until I sat down with
the city's top historian,
I had no clue this case would be filled
with so many deadly twists and turns.
The one interesting thing that
happened on Whitehead Street...
Back in the 1920s...
Was a murder of a man, Manuel Cabeza.
He was living with a mixed-race woman.
Which the locals and
particularly the Ku Klux Klan...
Disapproved of.
He was tortured.
And he was burnt.
He is in a lot of pain and...
Was very panicked over what happened
to him, very stressed out, very hurt.
They essentially poured hot tar
on him and stuck feathers on him.
- Literally tarred and feathered him?
- Literally tarred and feathered him.
- Did he see it coming?
- No. No.
The Klan had left Manuel Cabeza
for dead, but he didn't die.
In fact, he came back with a vengeance,
and his target was their leader.
After that, he, of
course, wanted revenge,
because he's the tough guy and he
has to live up to his reputation.
He's fascinated, fixated on something.
Got to take care of this problem.
So, the head of the
Klan was William Decker.
Now I had something big,
because William Decker was the
man who built Colette's house.
So, Decker was driving
down Duval Street.
He's in the shadows. He's
waiting. He's watching.
It doesn't really matter
what the consequences are.
And Manuel Cabeza jumped
on the running board
and he shot Decker in
the back of the head.
This man killed someone?
Obviously killing Decker in
cold blood didn't sit right
with the police or the Klan and
Manuel Cabeza's time was running out.
And of course Manuel Cabeza,
he's locked up in the County Jail.
So that night, the Ku Klux Klan,
they surrounded the building.
The scenario, the Sheriff said,
is that he was overpowered.
In the middle of the
night, he was sleeping...
And...
They put a bag on his head.
The KKK first went in and beat this man.
- Really?
- Yeah.
They have ropes, like,
with the throat, and...
Like, not being able
to breathe very well.
And they hung him up the pole.
The torture ended in killing him.
So, he's dead.
The man in the hat had a
deep connection with the house
and had no intentions of leaving.
And if the clients were going
to protect themselves from him,
I felt they needed to see his face.
Remember his eyebrows?
They're not thick. They're not thin.
And there is a slight arch to them.
Were they big eyes, or were they thin?
Slightly almond.
He has, like, a sad mouth.
This goes down, and they were not full.
A little bit of a line here.
You remember what he had
on, what he was wearing?
He did wear a hat. It had a round brim.
Sort of like a straw hat.
And it did have a band,
and it was white and blue.
Yeah, that's him.
Coming up next...
It is really... it's really, really bad.
Secrets come to light.
The guy that built your
house was the head of the KKK.
And what happened
after the investigation?
I want him out. I'm done.
Get out, get out, get out of my house!
Amy, Colette owns the home and,
probably from the minute she got
here, she felt a powerful energy.
Glenn, on the other hand,
has actually seen apparitions.
I was anxious to meet Amy
because I really wanted to
see her and measure her
eyeball-to-eyeball, face-to-face.
To see what she was made of
and if she was really for real.
Initially, I saw a man with a hat on.
And he seemed very agitated.
I mean, he was just,
frankly, out of control.
Glenn has actually seen a man.
He can distinctly recall
the man's features.
I could see things.
The guy... I could see him
going up and down the hall.
Amy, what else happened
during your walk?
I went into the house, and I saw a man.
And he was talking
about how these men...
They put a bag over his head,
and then they tortured him.
And he looked burned.
It was really... it's
really, really bad.
That was one of those moments
where a light bulb went off.
And I knew that Amy and
I had found the same guy.
There was a man by the
name of Manuel Cabeza.
Manuel was living with...
A biracial female named Angela, who...
The KKK in Key West was
not very happy about it.
Went and grabbed him out of his apartment,
and they actually put hot tar on the guy,
and they feathered him.
The next day, Manuel has a gun,
decides to go out and get some revenge.
William Decker was actually the head
of the Ku Klux Klan here in Key West.
Manuel pumps a bullet into his
chest and one through his head.
Manuel killed Decker.
I felt like Decker got what he deserved.
Had he tarred and feathered me,
I'd have killed him in a heartbeat.
I'd have scalped him, cut
his head off right there.
Cops show up, and he
was taken to the jail.
Short time later, the KKK wind up
getting into the jail cell somehow.
The burnt man was
talking about these men.
And that there was a hierarchy to this.
Then they drag him to another location
and they lynch him from a telephone pole.
Just the fact that these two men
were murdered just so brutally.
And the thought of their energies
being in my house all the time,
all hours of the day...
That was my big fear.
More history about Mr. Decker.
William Decker built this home.
How do you feel about the fact
that the guy that built your house
was the head of the KKK in Key West?
Horrible.
I think the main thing I didn't like
was the fact that Decker built my house.
And he was the head of the KKK.
That was just shocking
to me... just shocking.
Now, what I try to do
when I work with Amy,
is I try to bring in a
sketch artist for her.
He look familiar at all?
That's him. That's the
gentleman that I saw.
I'm gonna show you a
picture of Mr. Decker.
That is the gentleman in the
hallway, walking up and down.
When Glenn said, this is
the man I've been seeing,
chills went down my spine.
Just made it even more real.
It's pretty creepy.
Wow. Okay.
This, to me, definitely looks
like the person I encountered.
Amy, why are these people
still staying in this house?
They're both kind of in denial about the
parts that they played in what happened.
So one is, you know, the eternal victim.
And the other one, he thinks
he was completely right.
And I think that that's hindering them
from being able to take the next step.
So, that violence or
just the way they died,
does that energy hang in
this house or this area?
I think you're asking
Amy if you're safe here.
Amy said that I needed
to protect myself.
And there's a lot of energies out
there and they're not all good energies.
Especially around here.
In order to protect myself,
I regularly cleanse the home.
By burning Sage around the
property and spraying...
Herbal liquids.
All negative energy, out.
Get out of my house.
Get out!
My regular cleansing helps,
but they keep coming back.
Colette tries to practice cleansing
home and property or whatever.
And to sum it up, I think it's B.S.
The spirits are still in this
house. I still see Decker.
There are times when I hear the floors
creak and I look up and there's Decker.
I just want Decker to leave. I don't
know why he keeps hanging around.
I want him out.
I want him out of the house. I'm done.
Get out, get out, get
out of my house, Decker!
Get out!
Get out of my house, Decker. Out!
Spirits...
Either they are around you
or they are not around you.
They are there or they are not there,
and you can't do anything about it.
This is just part of life,
and that's part of my life...
My whole life, all my life.
The measures Colette has taken
to protect herself and her home.
Should keep the activity at a minimum.
But it seems the dead are always
going to find their way to Glenn.
I'm hopeful that he and Colette
will work together to find a balance.