I wouldn't want to mess with this woman.
She's very powerful.
The last owner killed all
three of her husbands.
It hurts so much.
I thought I was going to die.
It absolutely terrified me.
And it's almost like a butchering.
In the name of Jesus, you go.
Vicious.
They're burning them alive.
Something bad's going to happen.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's panic.
And it's almost like a butchering.
I see dead people.
They all died horribly.
I speak to dead people.
Get out of here.
And they speak to me.
Vicious.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
It doesn't matter where you are.
I'll find you.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
This guy's a real piece of work.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I feel like I live in a house of Hell.
It's my job to reveal them.
This is not good.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
I want my life back.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Is he trying to kill her?
Or time to get out.
Oh, my god.
This is going to kill us.
This is the first time
Amy and I are doing an
investigation overseas together.
We're in Jamaica,
a Caribbean Island just south of Cuba.
Now, the reason we're here is
I got a call from a young expat
who took over the family business.
It's a historic plantation
house in Montego Bay.
He says the activity is out of control.
His employees are scared,
guests are running out
of the place screaming,
and now even his kids are affected.
He says if we can't help him,
he's gonna pack his things and leave.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area of any leading information.
Photographs and artwork
can influence her findings,
so it's important that I
cover or remove them all.
When I'm finished,
the location will be
ready for tonight's walk.
There's this man.
He was treated like a dog. He had a chain.
Lots of, uh, blood.
They were setting people on fire.
They're burning them alive.
You know, pretty [Bleep] brutal [Bleep]
Well, Michael,
this is an incredible building
with spectacular views.
But I assume you guys don't live here
because it looks like it's set up as,
like a museum.
You're exactly right. It's a museum.
But it, first,
it was a sugarcane plantation.
Okay.
And eventually,
my father bought this place in the mid-'60s
and then started restoring
this Rose Hall Great House.
What kind of shape was the place
in when your father took over?
Well, when my father took over,
nobody had lived here for,
I believe, over 60 years.
You'd never know it was the same building.
How long have you been running this place?
For close to three years now.
Before that, I was in banking.
And I worked in finance,
actually, in New York City.
It had been a 50-year, you know,
passion project for my father.
And it was very important
for me to uphold that legacy.
Now, Michael, what kind of things
are we talking about that
people are experiencing?
It really runs the gamut from seeing things
to hearing things
to actually feeling as
if they've been touched
to, in the worst case,
feeling as if they've been pushed.
But for me, you know, the final straw
was my daughter had had an experience.
She was very scared
and had a hard time being
around here after that.
What about yourself, any experiences?
Yes.
When I would go up the staircase
and start going the rounds to the bedrooms,
I felt as if there was a presence there,
that somebody was on my back.
But really, the reason why I called you
was I was really worried about the guests,
the employees who are
here on a regular basis,
and I'm worried about my kids.
Now, has the activity always been bad?
Activity didn't pick up till we
started doing the night tour.
When did the night tour start?
The night tour started about two years ago.
Okay, so, now,
what kind of tours are we talking about?
It's for the most part historical.
Okay, so these people
- aren't coming in here ghost hunting?
- No.
Okay, so, what kind of history
are you covering on this tour?
The last mistress of the
house was Annie Palmer,
who supposedly had, within 12 years,
killed three husbands and countless slaves
and was finally murdered at the house.
And she's actually buried
over on the property,
right over there.
There's this woman.
And she's very well-groomed.
She's so, like, an authority,
like a powerful person.
She's very in control.
I would want to mess with this woman.
Something is going on
that is making her very
stressed out and angry.
She definitely is present here.
So, Mrs. Rollins,
it's good to meet with you.
Likewise.
So, I was talking to your son.
And it sounds like you
got some problems here.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, so, I'm curious.
What actually drew you guys to this place?
Well, my husband came for a vacation,
and what really impressed
him the most were the people.
There's just a joie de vivre,
a laughter, a joy about them.
But when Michael came
and brought his family,
I began to think, you know,
"Maybe we should relook at this."
Well, your 8-year-old granddaughter
seems to have had an experience.
Yes. I was shocked.
Now, what about yourself?
Well, you can be here at night
and have the hackles raise
on the back of your neck.
And, I mean, I was on a tour.
There were clanging of chains.
There were things that were going on
that absolutely terrified me.
Okay, so, now, after that happened,
did employees come to you with stories?
Oh, they certainly did. They said, you know,
"The shutters banged,
but they were secured,"
or, "floor creaking, floorboards,"
all kinds of noises, all kinds of things.
And I would not have
thought I was open to it,
but I'm starting to pay
a little more attention.
There was a man here.
I think he went crazy.
This guy causes issues with,
like, living people,
you know, has, like, tantrums.
He'll, like,
run into the wall and the door on purpose.
I'd say this man is the
cause of hundreds of deaths.
And it goes back in his family,
like he comes from a line of monsters.
Vicious.
Very vicious man.
Very vicious.
So, Katherine, I was talking to Daddy,
and he told me that you had
an experience that scared you.
Yeah.
Is that right?
Mm-hmm.
Can you tell me what happened?
Well, we were doing the party
for the opening of the play
that we talk about what happened
when Annie Palmer was alive.
Okay.
And I saw somebody up in
the top of the window.
And she had red lipstick with
black markings over her eyes.
It couldn't have been somebody
that was in the building?
Mnh-mnh.
Just some people at the front bottom.
Okay, but not up here.
Yeah. Not on the top floor.
Now, are you afraid of the building?
Yeah.
I'm never alone when I'm in here.
There's another lady.
She went nuts.
She went crazy.
She is seen... a lot.
And people, male, female,
kids, will see her around.
Like,
it's always like she's moving along the wall.
She's always, like, slithering.
She's kind of spooking me out a little bit.
After meeting with Michael and his family,
I started talking to the
employees of Rose Hall.
It shook.
And Mrs. Rollins wasn't kidding.
Everyone had experiences to share.
My back was to the door.
And the door slammed.
One that really caught my attention
came from a housekeeper named Becken.
A few weeks ago,
right down there, the dungeon,
I go to turn off that light over there.
And then I feel like somebody
holding me around the waist.
I say, "In the name of Jesus, you go."
Now, Becken,
you're sure it couldn't have been
one of the other employees
playing games with you
and grabbing you and then running away?
No, nobody was around.
So,
do you think whatever's here is dangerous?
Yeah.
Crazy Lady makes her whole being felt.
She doesn't just touch them.
She wants to engulf them...
and make them feel her.
She makes you very, very nauseous.
It hurts so much.
How long have you worked here?
I've been here for almost three years.
Have you ever had actual experiences?
I have many experiences.
- You have?
- Yes.
Okay, tell me about them.
We have a lady that plays Annie.
So she stands in Annie Palmer's room,
at her window, looking out at the guests.
There was another lady beside her
in a nice silhouette, white dress.
But there was no face.
Okay.
Now, is she solid like the actor,
or was she, like, misty?
Yeah, she's misty.
She's ghost-like. Yeah.
Okay.
She mimics everything that our Annie does.
You mean, like, her movements?
Yes.
So, what else have you seen?
I saw a gentleman.
- He was black.
- Okay.
And he had some wounds on his skin.
What kind of wounds are we talking about,
like a burn, a stabbing?
Like, a whip wound. Yes.
Okay, so you're assuming that
he was a slave at some point.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Oh, he followed me downstairs.
And I saw six slaves.
I saw one coming from out the dining room,
one from out the morning room,
one from outside,
one from the ballroom.
So they were all coming towards me,
and I couldn't move.
The only thing,
the one that came downstairs with me,
he held my hand.
Okay.
He held on my hands.
And he said, "Come with me."
Now, I've been doing this a long time.
I've heard a lot of stories.
But this slave story you're
telling me is pretty out there.
I know when it's real from when it's not.
Did you take it as something dangerous,
or did you take it as...
I thought I was going to die.
A lot of the dead here, they're pissed.
The things that these dead
people do to the living
could be kind of justifiable
because I think a lot of these people
might have been tortured and kidnapped.
This was done by the people from here.
The dead... may have these guardians.
What are the guardians?
I don't know. They're these big things.
I mean, I'd say they're 10, 12 feet tall.
They have long legs.
They're on all fours.
Honestly, I've never seen anything like that.
Ever, ever, ever.
How many are there?
There's about six or seven of them.
It's like a [Bleep] wall of defense.
But they said something like,
"Stand back," or, "Don't come near here."
They're guarding the dead.
I think that people would have experiences
with them over the years.
They're very powerful and dangerous.
Do you know if this might affect
people that just work here?
It would just destroy them.
Michael, his mom,
and everyone that works at Rose Hall
has really bought into
this Annie Palmer legend.
You know? It's an incredible story.
So I reached out to an author
who has written about the property.
He's out on the island doing research
and agreed to meet me and
separate fact from fiction.
So, Ben, the reason I asked
you to help me out on this case
is I know you're an expert on this stuff.
And I got told this story by my client
that I don't know if
there's any truth to it.
Said there was a woman named
Annie Palmer who lived here.
She killed three of her husbands,
as well as countless slaves.
And to top it off,
they say she's buried right here.
Is any of it true?
Almost none of that's true.
Really?
Essentially,
the Annie Palmer that people talk about,
the one that's supposedly
buried here and that lived here,
it was a composite of two different women
who lived almost a century apart.
Okay, so, who's the first woman?
Well, the very first one was
a woman named Rosa Kelly.
The most interesting thing is
that she had four husbands,
and three of them died
here on this property.
She was on her fourth husband when she died.
Okay,
so what happened to the previous husbands?
The very first one is named Henry Fanning.
He was married to her in 1746,
and he died within six months.
Okay. Do we know how he died?
He died young. We don't know exactly how.
You know, this is the tropics.
This is, you know, the 1700s.
People drop dead of malaria,
all sorts of different things.
Okay, so,
people dying young wasn't uncommon.
Exactly. Exactly.
What about the second husband? Who was he?
A man named George Ash.
And how long does that marriage last?
That marriage lasted two years,
until he himself dies.
Now, what about the third husband?
The third husband was named Norwood Witter,
and he died 12 years after they married.
Now, how do we know she
didn't murder these people?
Well, there's no record that she did.
All right.
So in-between her husbands,
who's running the plantation?
She was.
This is the 1700s.
I mean, this had to be some woman
to take care of a plantation this big.
Mm-hmm.
You can see how some of the stories
might have come about her
being very strong-willed,
you know, and an important person.
Is it possible she's buried here, Rosa?
No. That's not possible.
Why is that?
Because we know where she was buried.
We have record.
She's buried in St. James' Parish,
which isn't too far from here.
Okay,
so the records show that she died in 1790.
How old was she by then?
72.
So this is not her?
There may be somebody buried here,
but it ain't her.
This lady is way back.
I want to go back to, like...
just like, 1700s?
I'm seeing the powerful, angry woman again.
And this time,
she's telling me about her life.
She's very wealthy,
and she's very in control
and very powerful person,
which is weird because she's a female
and this is a long time ago.
But, like,
I feel like she owns like everything.
She's had her share of enemies,
let me tell you,
who have tried to kill her.
So, you said the legend of this Annie Palmer
is a combination of two women.
All right, so, we got the first woman.
What about the second one?
The second one was actually
named Annie Palmer.
Okay, so there was an Annie Palmer.
There was an Annie Palmer,
but there's nothing,
No part of that biography fits her.
The only connection is to her name.
So anything that the legend
says has nothing to do
with the real Annie Palmer.
Essentially, yeah.
All right, so, what do we know about her?
Okay, so this is an image of Annie Palmer.
Now, this is her or we think it's her?
It's said to be of her.
We don't know.
It's a painting from that time.
We know that she was originally English.
She moved here in 1820.
We know that her parents died
when she was fairly young.
Beyond that, she seems to have had
a relatively uneventful upbringing.
Okay, so, what happens with her?
Her husband died in 1827.
Three years later,
she lost the title to the property.
That was basically a year
before the slave rebellion.
After she lost the plantation,
she moved to another part of the island,
and she died in 1846.
- And how old was she?
- 34.
- Okay. Was she murdered?
- No.
As far as we know, natural causes.
Is it possible she's in here?
No, that's not possible.
And how do we know that?
Because we know where she was buried.
We have record of that.
Okay.
So, she's in the same place...
Yup... as Rosa.
Yup. They're both in the same cemetery.
Essentially, none of the stories
of cruelty and sadism and black magic,
all the bad things that
people talk about her,
had no relation to the real Annie Palmer.
Okay.
This crazy lady.
She's pretty important.
It's like she's 1860s.
She had a lot of losses,
starting really early.
This woman,
she went crazy because he father died.
Very attached, very attached to her father.
Very attached.
She seems... very not stable right now.
Lots of darkness.
A lot of darkness here.
Ben mentioned a bloody slave
rebellion in Montego Bay.
I'm heading over to meet
with a local professor
who says the fighting came really close
to the property I'm investigating.
So, Nicole, you told me on the phone
that the slave rebellion
was the most important
and violent event that took
place in Jamaican history.
It was certainly one of the most important.
On December 27, 1831,
this emancipation war started.
This emancipation war would see
60,000 enslaved Africans take arms
against the colonial overlords,
namely the white plantation masters.
Okay, so what kind of a
battle are we talking about?
What would we have seen?
This was a guerrilla fight.
Okay.
But it was also armed combat.
Occasionally, the fields were put on fire.
So, Nicole, let me ask you a question,
as far as the property I'm investigating.
How close did this whole uprising get to it?
Palmyra Plantation,
which was about two miles away, was burnt.
So it was probably likely
that the enslaved Africans,
as well as the white management,
if they couldn't see it,
they could at least smell what was going on.
So, how long does this rebellion last?
It was actually 10 days.
I'm sure a lot of people
got killed on both sides.
Not quite.
You see, over 500 people we killed,
and 14 of these individuals were white.
Okay, so what did the plantation owners do
after they stopped the rebellion?
This was actually one of the
most heart-rending part of it.
You see, innocent persons of color
could easily be rounded up.
312 were judicially executed.
Several enslaved Africans
were shot on the spot.
In fact, they executed so many people
that the bodies would pile up.
Eventually, slavery was abolished.
When did that happen here?
The emancipation bill was passed.
By August 1, 1834, slavery ended.
I'm seeing a lot of different things here.
Like, first I'm feeling, like,
all of this panic and distress.
Someone's bleeding, bleeding, cut, stabbed.
It feels more like a stab, right here.
Right here.
This is a male, young male.
Tongue ripped out.
There's a lot of [Bleep] horrible things
being done to people.
Now that I know the
truth about Annie Palmer
and the bloody slave rebellion,
I need to see if there's anything else
that could help my case.
So I'm at the local library.
Searching for old records,
I find a deadly rampage
involving a man named Rudolph Franklin.
It turns out,
he lived on Rose Hall property.
I'm heading over to meet a
local Rastafarian activist
who knows all about this deadly shoot-out.
He told me the information he's
got will be critical to my case.
Mr. Ras Karbi, I appreciate you meeting me.
Saw an article during my research
about a shoot-out between
Rastafarians and police
that was pretty deadly.
When I looked at the research,
everything came back to Rose Hall
and the property I'm investigating.
So I wanted to find out from you,
if you knew exactly what happened.
What actually took place was this guy,
Rudolph Franklin,
who used to live on the Rose Hall property
and he was a worker there.
And he's gotten some land
that he claimed that his father's given him.
So there was a dispute because
they want him off the land.
Right, Rastas weren't welcome.
Now, did he have any paperwork
documenting that he owned that property?
Most Jamaicans didn't have paperwork
that they owned any property.
So, now, what happens in 1961,
when the cops do eventually...?
In 1961, a dispute developed.
Rudolph Franklin had his machete, okay?
He was on his property.
And they told him to drop his machete.
He perhaps refused to drop the machete,
so he was shot.
And they left him to die in the grass.
So, he survived the shooting.
He decided to come back
with a personal grudge
or a personal revenge.
So he got some friends together.
So, they went to the gas station.
Gas station's set on fire. Cops came.
And there was a big clash
between Franklin and his
men and the policemen.
You know, what was the outcome
of this whole, big mess?
By the time it was over,
eight people got killed.
One was... Franklin himself got killed.
Two friends that he brought there,
two policemen got shot.
One that was assisting the police
also got hacked to death by Franklin's men.
And two other bystanders.
So there's two people.
They're both lying on the ground.
It's dark out.
There's a fire that's burning.
And there's a man who...
is standing over them.
And it's almost like a butchering,
like you would butcher an animal,
like he's being gutted.
I saw several dead people during my walk,
but the bizarre creatures
guarding the dead outside
pose the biggest threat.
There were several trees,
and there were these things
that were probably like 10 or 12 feet tall.
Like a fly with no head.
- And no face?
- No face.
It was dark... very, very dark.
Is this what you saw?
Yes, that's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our findings
to each other and our
clients for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to meet Michael.
Now, Michael gave up a banking
job in New York a few years ago
to come here and run this historic place,
but he got a lot more than he bargained for.
This is his mom, Mrs. Rollins.
Back in 1965,
her husband purchased this place.
This is what it looked like
when they purchased it.
They spent years restoring
it to what it is today.
And this is Janique.
She's an employee of Rose Hall.
And she's had more than her
fair share of experiences.
Now, Michael's the one that called us in.
Activity's gotten really bad,
and he wants to make sure
he can continue on with the family legacy.
So now that Amy knows a little
bit about what's going on,
I'm gonna have her describe
what she saw on her walk.
When I arrived, there was a lot
of chaos that was happening.
I immediately encountered a
male who is bound by his leg,
and he was telling me how he
had been here for a long time.
But he was someone who was
treated really like an animal.
Then, right after him,
I saw people were lined
up and then set on fire.
Then they were just kind
of scattered and running,
while they are engulfed in flames.
I think that this happened a very,
very long time ago.
That's pretty easy to explain.
I mean, this place was a slave
plantation back in the 1700s.
At its peak, it had 500 slaves
that lived, died, and were buried here.
Now, you saw a lot of violence and a fire.
Yeah.
Now,
it kind of sounds like you're talking about
the slave rebellion that took
place on December 27, 1831.
Now, the slaves burnt down the plantation
and took up arms to fight for their freedom.
Battle lasted 10 days.
Slaves were crushed.
221 died during that 10-day battle.
Only 14 of those 221 were white.
Now, afterwards, the whites that
were here were out for blood.
They wind up rounding up any blacks
they could find on the streets,
threw them in jail, tried them,
and 312 were executed.
Even though the whites won that battle,
they lost the war
because slavery was abolished in 1834 here.
Now, Janique,
you had experiences with slaves.
Yeah.
Explain to Amy what you encountered.
So, I went upstairs,
and I was cleaning the commode.
And there was a gentlemen behind me.
You know, he's black.
He had wounds on his skin,
and he grabbed my hand.
And he was saying, "Come with me."
After a few minutes or so,
there was a gentleman
coming from all corners of the house,
about four of them, all slaves.
It seems all wounded.
I was afraid that I might
have died or something.
So, what else happened on your walk?
I encountered this one guy.
This is his favorite area.
He was very angry, a very forceful person.
This guy causes issues with,
like, living people.
You know? Has, like, tantrums.
He'll, like,
run into the wall and the door on purpose.
You've had a lot of people
telling you they hear footsteps?
I've had people telling me
that they'll be on the second floor.
And they'll hear things downstairs.
There's a lot of activity,
a lot of movement,
and all of that without people really here.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, that's how he operates.
So, what else did you see?
There were two women that
I encountered on my walk.
The first one was extremely old,
very, very wealthy.
She is from probably 1600s, 1700s.
She was someone who was a decision-maker
and could implement power,
and from my knowledge,
as a woman at that time,
that didn't happen.
She was in control.
Now, you've heard stories for years,
right, Mrs. Rollins,
about people seeing an
apparition of a woman.
Yes.
Michael, you had told me your
daughter saw an apparition.
Was it upstairs?
Yeah, upstairs in the far bedroom,
in the far corner.
Which would be?
- Annie's room.
- Right.
Now's probably a good time to tell Amy
about the legend of Annie Palmer
that everybody at this
table believes is true
and everybody in town does,
including my cab driver.
Supposedly, she was a tyrannical
and sadistic slave owner
who ruled with an iron fist.
She murdered three of her husbands,
as well as countless slaves.
Apparently, she's also buried
right here on the property.
But, Amy, this is only the legend.
I did my own research,
and I'll tell you about it in a minute.
Michael,
tell Amy about the Annie Palmer tours
you run at night.
As of close to two years ago,
we started doing tours at night.
People started hearing things,
feeling as if a presence was there.
They've actually been touched.
And then, in the most extreme cases,
people felt as if they were pushed.
Are you doing reenactments?
Yeah, there are aspects of reenactments.
Are you doing any of...
the bad stuff that happened?
I mean, we designed the night tour
so that we could bring a story to life.
We never dreamt the
spirits would do it for us.
Now,
who was the second woman you saw?
The other woman that I met, who was younger,
from around 1860,
her family... extremely wealthy.
She was very well-taken-care-of.
She had definite father issues.
I do think that people
see her on the staircase.
I think they would see her along the walls.
She does like to be felt.
So she'll literally put
her whole physical self
around a person.
Now, I think I can clear this stuff up.
I talked to an expert who
wrote about Rose Hall.
He says the legend of Annie
Palmer is mostly false.
That legend may be the
combination of two women
that lived on this property
at two different times.
The first woman, Rosa Palmer,
came here in 1746.
Now, Rosa had four husbands,
and three of them died
right here on this property.
There's no indication that
any of them were murdered.
She was also a very strong woman
because she had to run the
plantation in-between husbands.
So, this is another aspect
of what you said about the first woman.
When she married her fourth husband,
they built this house,
and that's who he named it after.
Her name was Rosa. They named it Rose Hall.
Rosa Palmer died right
here in Rose Hall in 1790,
at the age of 72, but she's not buried here.
Now, right here I have the
burial records for Rosa Palmer.
She's buried at the St. James Church,
about nine miles from you.
Now, the second woman...
she was actually named Annie Palmer,
but the similarities end there.
According to the author I spoke to,
this is supposed to be the only
known image of Annie Palmer.
You said she had daddy issues.
Her father died young.
She moved here in 1820.
Her husband dies in 1827.
Now, in 1846,
Annie Palmer died sick and broke
on another part of the
island at the age of 34.
Now, is that her buried outside there? No.
I mean, I have another doc that says
she's buried in the same
church cemetery as Rosa.
I'm just shocked.
It's a lot of information.
The story's overwhelming.
You can't change a legend.
Let me ask you a question.
You saw the two women, right?
Yes.
Does this look like who you might've seen?
It does look similar
to the needy lady.
Obviously, there's a huge mystery here.
And I don't think that anyone is
going to resolve this mystery.
But from Steve's research that he presented,
I need to just go with my gut.
I think that this very strong,
independent woman
is possibly Rosa Palmer.
I think the male that's here is probably
one of her former husbands
that she may have killed.
As for the younger female that
I encountered, this female,
possibly Annie Palmer because
she had father issues,
and she is extraordinarily needy.
Well,
I think we need to really take a close look
at doing as much as we can
in order to not provoke something
that has the ability to be awful.
One of the things that
I find very concerning
is what I encountered in the backyard.
And the interesting thing was
that there were guardians of the dead.
These things said to me to stay
back and not to come there.
They're about 12 feet tall,
black body, bizarre arms and legs.
They're very odd-looking.
So I did do a sketch of what I saw.
I'm dying to see what
these things look like.
Well, you weren't kidding
when you said this is weird.
This is what you got in your backyard,
just so you know.
Oh.
They're horrific.
They're capable, really,
of anything, including death.
This is what you got in your backyard,
just so you know.
Oh.
They're horrific.
They're capable, really,
of anything, including death.
So,
what do we need to do to make it all stop?
The guardians... they're making sure
that nothing bad happens to the
dead that were unjustly killed.
And if these dead people feel threatened,
they would reach out to these guardians
and allow them to protect them.
All right, well, I got to ask,
I mean, you think his nighttime shows here
are causing a problem?
Yeah, that's what I'm saying
is I'm nervous about that.
Well, that makes me nervous, so...
The picture that you just showed.
Well, Michael,
you're a successful guy,
and I'm sure you got that way
by tackling problems head on.
And right now there's a problem here.
So the big question is,
can you keep your father's legacy alive
while ensuring the safety of
your employees, your guests,
and your family?
For that answer,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy
and see what she can tell us.
As far as the dead are concerned,
I do believe that some of the reenactments
probably need to cease.
It is causing them stress.
So I think that that needs to be curtailed.
So we want to make them
as comfortable as possible
until they're able to go on.
But as far as the guardians are concerned,
offerings need to be made.
Maybe once a month,
bringing flowers and putting them out there.
While you're doing this,
all you're saying is,
"I respect what you're doing. Thank you."
That's it.
Now, what do they do
about the two women you saw?
Rosa Palmer, with her three husbands,
bring in a medium to talk to her and say,
you know,
"Look, let's do this nice.
"I can help you.
I can help guide you to
move on and this and this."
I hope that goes well.
All right, so now what about the
second one with daddy issues?
Okay, so that person,
who could possibly be Annie Palmer,
I think that she actually will
be the easiest person to go.
She is looking for love.
And I think that a medium
who could connect with her
would be able to talk to her,
communicate with her
and let her know that it's okay
and that she'll be reunited with
those that she's looking for
and has always been looking for and lost.
The male is honestly going to be
the most difficult person to remove.
In order to remove him,
you would need to have a
priest come and do an exorcism.
He is not budging.
But I always thought an exorcism
was the removal of the devil from a person.
An exorcism can be done
when a dead person is
refusing to leave.
He's going to have be forcefully,
unfortunately, removed.
Now, to keep your father's
legacy alive and to respect it,
are you gonna at least do
what Amy tells you to do?
We need to do that to protect people
who are visiting at our invitation
and our family and Dad's legacy.
So if that's what it takes to
keep Rose Hall Great House,
safe and alive... Then I think
of course we'll do that.
I think, we don't have choice.
Presenting offering to these creatures
shouldn't be taken lightly,
as they pose a very serious danger.
But I believe if Michael and
his mother follow my advice,
the dead will be set free,
and his family's legacy
can continue safely for
generations to come.