These tricksters are awful... awful, awful.
I saw three shadow figures
here at the foot of the bed.
They're making them see things,
hear things, feel things.
She found him hanging from the rafters.
Something just goes "Boom!"
This is some bizarre [bleep]
you guys are talking about.
I don't know what to trust.
He's making me crazy.
Something bad's going to happen.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's panic.
And it's almost like a butchering.
I see dead people.
They all died horribly.
I speak to dead people.
Get out of here.
And they speak to me.
Vicious.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
It doesn't matter where you are.
I'll find you.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
This guy's a real piece of work.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I feel like I live in a house of Hell.
It's my job to reveal them.
This is not good.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end...
I want my life back.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Is he trying to kill her?
Or time to get out.
Oh, my god.
This is going to kill us.
I'm in the rural town of Independence,
Oregon.
It's about an hour south of Portland.
I got called in by a guy named Terry,
who sounded really desperate on the phone.
He says the activity in
his farmhouse is so bad,
it's destroying his health
and his relationship.
He says if we can't help him,
he doesn't think he's
gonna last another year.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the house
of anything that might
influence her findings.
Photos need to be removed...
and personal items covered.
When I'm finished,
the location will be
ready for tonight's walk.
Okay. Okay.
I had a really hard time opening.
The thing was, was that there were,
like, these tricksters.
They are treacherous... thieves and liars.
They're creating illusions,
and they are going into people's dreams.
What the [bleep]
They're having bad, horrible dreams.
This is not good.
Terry, I'm glad I'm here,
'cause when we spoke on the phone,
you sounded pretty desperate.
What exactly is going on in the house?
Oh, gosh. We hear voices.
There's full-body apparitions.
I've been chased down the hallway.
I just feel like something's here
trying to suck the life out of me.
Wow.
So, who exactly lives in the house?
Me, my partner, Bobby,
and my grandson, Ashton.
I think it's now starting
after my grandson.
All right.
So, how long have you been living here?
We've been here four years.
What made you come here?
With my parents being elderly,
Bobby and I decided
that it would probably be
best if we moved down here
to help take care of
the farm and my parents.
Okay. So, did you grow up in this house?
No. This house has been moved here.
We had an old farmhouse over
there that I grew up in.
Okay.
Things have progressively gotten
worse over this last year.
I've been attacked in my bed.
I'm getting no sleep... none.
I get very irritable
when my anxiety goes up.
I know on the phone, when we spoke,
it seems like your
relationship's a little strained
because of this stuff that's going on.
It is a little strained.
I don't want to be bothered.
I just kind of want to be alone,
and that's not me at all.
Now, what about your grandson?
He is so scared,
he won't go to the bath alone.
He doesn't want to sleep alone.
I'm sorry.
I don't know how to protect my family.
Yeah.
I am at my wits' end.
What the hell?
There's a man...
Oh, a living dude.
He's just, like, barreling through here
and yelling and screaming.
And he's got brown hair.
Kind of got a round face,
kind of a roundish face.
Kind of, like, always a mess.
How old?
Probably in his early 40s.
Okay.
Not a happy person.
Okay, now I'm seeing a bunch of [bleep]
I think there's a [bleep] telepath here
who is inadvertently
manipulating their environment.
How?
Like, the living people here
are seeing things that aren't really there.
He's making me crazy.
One of my very first
really scary experiences
happened here.
I used to have a mirror
that hung in my bedroom at
the end of this hallway,
and I was coming through one afternoon
with a load of towels from the laundry,
and I just got this overwhelming feeling
that somebody was behind me.
And as I happened to
look up down the hallway
and into that mirror,
I saw an old man behind me,
I would say probably in his 70s.
He was kind of see-through,
more of, like, a gray thing,
and he was coming behind
me down the hallway.
I ran and slammed the
bedroom door behind me.
Could it have been an intruder
or anything like that?
No.
I open the door back up...
There's nothing here.
Interesting. Okay,
so what else is going on in this hallway?
I hear women's voices
out in the living room.
It's like a murmuring.
You just kind of hear...
That's annoying.
Very.
How many people would you think it is?
Probably three to four.
Do you go investigate?
Yes, I usually get up.
There have been times I've
been kind of confrontational.
And what have you said?
"Get out of my house."
And what happens?
It makes it worse.
They're bullying me.
I never had circles under my eyes
until I came back here
and moved into this house.
Okay.
Oh, boy.
These, like, trickster things...
there's a lot of them... a lot of them.
How many?
50?
But I don't know if I'm...
seeing the truth.
These tricksters are incredibly
good at distorting reality.
Between them and the telepathy,
the living must be going insane.
They'll feed into the
person's paranoias and fears.
They can reach in and pull out past traumas
and make it a fresh issue for them,
and they, like, overanalyze it
and analyze it and analyze it,
talking, talking, talking,
and it's like feeding it
more and more and more.
One night,
I woke up and I saw three shadow figures
down here at the foot of the bed
that I would say were
probably about this tall
and looked like black blobs...
kind of human shape.
I freaked out, jumped up out of bed,
and I ran out.
I was scared to death.
You're sure there's no shadows
coming in from outside?
Those are block-out curtains,
and they're closed.
Huh.
Actually, after we had called you,
the other night,
I got attacked in my bed again.
I was watching TV.
I rolled over to grab
the remote, and again,
there was a large shadow
figure standing over me,
leaning in the bed.
I started swinging.
I thought maybe somebody
had broken into the house.
And it just disappeared.
When you said you were desperate,
you weren't kidding.
No. It feels like I'm being tortured.
I feel sick... horrible,
horrible [bleep] sick in here.
Awful, awful, awful.
These tricksters,
they are causing their own mayhem here.
Are you okay?
They're [bleep] with me.
Real physical. Okay [bleep]
Ah. Come on. Come on.
They come. They come. They come.
And they do. They surround...
They do... They do it...
They'll surround any bed
that has a living person in them at night.
They're like this big, and they're black...
you know, black humanoid figures.
And they all are standing together.
They come in the front door.
They crawl out of the closets.
They're attracted to the
negativity in this house.
They're having a good time feeding this.
It's not like they're like,
"I'm gonna kill this person,
but if something happens, great.
That would be [bleep] entertaining."
They're like, "Yeah, let's keep this going.
Let's do this!"
Terry mentioned to me
about his short tempers, his mood swings.
Have you noticed what he's talking about?
Yeah.
In the beginning,
when we first got together,
he was so lovable and just happy.
Just watching somebody go downhill,
you don't want to see it.
And there's a couple of times
where I've actually, like,
wanted to just walk away.
Okay.
Now, what about yourself?
What have you experienced?
I have seen something that
actually terrifies me.
Okay.
It's a little shadow figure.
It's probably about 2 feet tall,
about up to your knee,
and it peeks around the corner at you.
It's got kind of like a troll-
or gremlin-looking shape to it,
with pointed ears.
You don't think it's any kind of
an animal or anything like that?
You sure of that?
It's too big to be any kind of rodent.
Okay.
And you would have heard it
if it was some animal, huh?
Yeah. There's no sound to it.
Is there anything else going on?
I saw this little fawn
actually hop through the
back window in the bedroom,
and it went through the bedroom
and then took off down the hallway.
You're talking about a baby deer?
Yeah.
This is some bizarre [bleep]
you guys are talking about.
I haven't heard this
much stuff in one house.
I thought I was going crazy at one point.
- Were you boozing?
- No. I don't drink.
You don't drink? All right. Any drugs?
Nope.
I have no idea what that could have been.
You can see why I thought
I was going crazy.
I'm having a lot of issues
trying to figure out what
is really going on here.
But these tricksters...
They are causing issues.
Like, there's infinite possibilities
of how they can manipulate the living
into making them, you know,
behave in a certain way
or, you know, see things,
hear things, feel things.
They're causing, you know, fighting.
They'll pit people against
each other so they'll fight.
They'll cause a lot of arguments and anger.
One person will hear the
other person talking to them,
but it's not them.
They manipulate dreams.
They are making it a very negative,
volatile situation.
And they are really feeding at night.
So, Ashton, I talked to Grandpa,
and he's worried about you.
He wanted me to talk to you.
How old are you, exactly?
7.
7? Okay.
Do you see anything in the
house that frightens you?
Tell me about that.
I saw something come through the closet...
the closet in that room.
It was like red eyes,
and it was like a demon or something.
And it came on my side of the bed,
and I felt something
tickling me right here.
Are you afraid to stay here?
You are?
Why are you afraid? Tell me.
Because I see stuff moving in
the hallway and the bathroom.
What are you seeing?
All night, I see, like, a tall man.
I stay up almost all night.
The little trickster dudes
are different in here.
They're more active in here
as far as what they do.
Here, they're more aggressive.
They're, like, jumping on the bed
like they're having a good time,
barking and growling.
And I see, like...
I see somebody's in there.
Somebody's in the bed.
And they're trying to relax.
They're seeing, like...
Like, um...
Uh, like, all this movement, like lights...
and, like, you know, black,
streaky things and lights
and, like, all this chaos.
And they're just like, "Oh, man.
This is really bad."
Terry and Bobby have no clue
about the history of their house,
so I pulled the property deed
and asked a local historian that I know
to look through some of the names.
Turns out the original property owner
was publicly disgraced
and had to leave Independence in shame.
Well, Diane,
I appreciate you helping me out.
So, what can you tell me
about this guy Alva Shaw,
who originally owned my clients' property?
He was born in New York about 1819,
and he came to Oregon in 1844.
Okay. So, what did he do when he got here?
He was appointed by the governor
to be the superintendent
of the state penitentiary in Portland.
Okay, I mean,
that's a pretty prestigious job
and powerful job.
- He's got to have a lot of connections.
- He did.
How'd it work out?
Of the 154 prisoners
that were sent to the
prison during his term,
44 of them escaped,
and only 13 were recaptured.
So 1/3 of his prisoners escaped?
Yes. He was blamed for that.
Okay.
As soon as I walk outside,
it's like a haze has been lifted off of me,
and I'm able to see clearly again,
and there's someone here,
watching my every move.
I think that he's a dead man...
a very powerful man.
I think he had a lot of power
that was placed upon him,
a lot of strength, a lot of determination,
a lot of authority, and I think that's why
he's so capable of manifesting this way.
Do you know when he's from?
80 to 100 years ago?
Okay.
Do people experience him in any way?
I would assume so,
'cause he does have a
thing with the tricksters.
You know,
the only thing I could possibly say
is that he would be some kind of leader.
Now, you mentioned this
guy had a bad go of things.
- What are we talking about?
- He did.
He had a very bad go of things,
starting in August 1866.
First thing that happened is
his mother died... Hannah Shaw.
Okay.
She died on August 12th,
and she was 71 years old.
And she was buried on your clients'
property.
- She's buried on the property?
- Yes.
Eight days after his mom dies,
he hands in his resignation
as superintendent,
effective at the end of the month.
So, did his mom dying have
anything to do with him resigning?
You know, it's possible.
With just four days left in
his term would come the event
that would drive him out
of Independence forever.
On August 27th, he's taken hostage
with two of his employees by nine prisoners
and were going to use them as shields
to get out of the prison.
And as they're marching,
seeing that something needed to be done,
Shaw grabs ahold of a fence,
and it breaks the momentum of the escape,
and the guards are able
to shoot at the prisoners.
That's a pretty ballsy move on his part.
It was, and one of the prisoners is killed,
and eight of them escape,
although five are recaptured.
The hostage standoff was big news.
Here's an article about it that
was in the local newspaper.
All right.
So, it sounds like this guy
finally did something right.
The public didn't see it that way.
In this editorial,
they blame him for the escape.
They say that he was too liberal,
that he left the shackles off the prisoners
when he should have left them on,
that he didn't have adequate security.
And after the escape,
he feels like he's a
pariah in the community,
and he sells the property that he has left,
and he moves to California.
Now, how old was he when he died?
He was about 64.
So, what does he die of?
We don't know.
The obituary just says
that he died of an illness
that lasted 13 hours.
Oh. Okay.
Do you know how he died?
It wasn't the way he expected or wanted.
I think he would have liked
to go out in a blaze of glory.
He's really affecting a large area,
you know?
I don't think it's just that house.
I think he does go into homes,
and I think he spies a lot.
He might be attracted to that
negativity of the living.
But I do feel like he has ill intent here.
So far, I know the previous
owner of my clients' property
was run out of town and died
from a mysterious illness.
But I need to see
if there's anything else
that could help my case.
Searching through old records,
I find a deadly fight between two neighbors
right next to Terry and Bobby's property.
I want to know more about this deadly feud,
so I've reached out to
a local police sheriff
to look into it for me,
and he told me that this
was a controversial case
and that it tore the community apart.
Well, Sheriff Wolfe,
thanks for meeting with me
and helping me out with the case.
The reason I got ahold of you is
because of this article I
came across about a homicide
that happened very close to my clients'
property.
This was a neighborhood
feud between two gentlemen,
O.P. Beardsley and T.L. Perryman.
And in 1886,
we ended up with the first violent attack,
and it was Perryman that ended up
attacking Beardsley with a monkey wrench
and caused a pretty
significant gash to him.
And then, in 1888,
Beardsley is walking with a cane,
and Perryman comes across
him and attacks him
and actually breaks several of his ribs,
puts a big gash on his head,
and dislocates an eye.
Now, do we have any idea
what the hell they were
fighting about to begin with?
No one really seems to know.
They just had a real
dislike for each other.
All right, so, now we got this guy Perryman
giving Beardsley two beatings already...
bad beatings, it sounds like.
Yes, very bad.
But, according to the article,
Perryman is the victim of the homicide,
so what happened?
Well, March 14th of 1889...
Okay.
Perryman comes out
and does a staredown with Beardsley,
who is working on a fence
with some other folks.
Thinking he might have
another beating coming,
Beardsley ends up going to the house...
Okay... and he gets a gun.
Beardsley goes back outside,
and Beardsley shoots him.
Just like that? There's no altercation?
Just shoots him in the street.
And, apparently, was shot
once in the heart and once in the back.
Oh, geez. Okay.
So, what happens next?
Oh, he turned himself in to the sheriff.
Did it go to trial?
Yes, it did.
He was found not guilty and acquitted.
How's this guy not guilty
when he shoots a guy down in cold blood?
A jury of his peers must have felt
that he was defending himself.
I'm feeling, like, an impact...
in my back.
Uh...
And it's like a wall,
like something just goes "Boom!"
It was daytime.
It was the middle of the day.
He's probably in his late 30s or early 40s.
And it totally shocks him... like,
totally out of the blue.
Terry mentioned that his
house was physically picked up
and moved at one point.
So I checked into it, and he's right.
It was moved about 18 miles from here.
I've reached out to an old friend of mine,
Jeff Davis, who's an author,
and he said he's got information
that will definitely help my case.
All right, so, this is the property
that the house I'm
investigating was moved from?
Yes, it was built here and then moved
about 17 or 18 miles to
where you first saw it.
You had mentioned on the phone
that the original owner of this land
had an interesting story.
Well, the original landowner
is a man named John Johnson.
And there's his photo.
And he settled here originally in 1845.
And here's his house.
So, what happens to this guy?
He had tragedy after tragedy
for a period of about 15 years.
Within hours of arriving on the property,
his father died of pneumonia.
Okay. So his father dies.
- Yes.
- What else happened?
And then in 1857,
his 5-year-old nephew,
Persis, died of meningitis.
And then three months later,
in January of 1858,
his father-in-law, James Taylor, died,
and he lived right next door.
1865, one of his other nephews,
James, died of diphtheria.
What a horrible death.
- Yeah.
- All right.
So, now he's got all these
family members dying.
Well, that's not all.
On July 9, 1877, it was about 6:00 A.M.,
and his wife called him.
See, she was in the house,
and he was out in the barn, doing chores.
And so he didn't come,
and so she went into the barn to find him,
and that's when she found him
actually hanging from the rafters.
Why? For what reason?
I don't know.
The family didn't know, either.
Okay. So, 1877, he kills himself.
How old is he at this point? He was 61.
Now, let me ask you a question.
Are any of them buried on the property?
They're all buried here.
Definitely a broken neck.
Oh, this is bad.
This is not done well.
It's a male... old.
Uh...
I'd say he's, like, in his 60s.
He's white.
I think... I don't know...
it might have been an accident.
An accidental hanging?
Um...
Because it's so badly done.
I saw several entities during my walk,
but the group of tricksters
surrounding a living person
had me the most concerned.
They were probably about 3 or 4 feet tall.
They had large heads, they're pitch-black,
and they were all around the bed,
staring at the person.
Is this what you saw?
Yes, this is what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our findings
to each other and our
clients for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to meet Terry,
and this is his partner, Bobby.
They live here with Terry's
7- year-old grandson, Ashton.
Okay.
Now, we've been doing investigations
for quite a time now, but these guys have
some of the wildest
stories I've ever heard.
They called us in
'cause they can't take it anymore.
It's affecting their relationship,
Terry's health,
and, most importantly,
it's affecting Ashton.
How long have you lived here?
About four years.
Four years. When did the activity start?
When we moved in.
This was a very unusual walk.
I've actually never encountered
anything quite like this.
When I went into the house,
I actually couldn't trust
anything I was seeing,
anything I was hearing,
anything I was feeling.
It was insane, really. It was insane.
I'm gonna back up, though,
and I'm gonna talk about
what I got outside first.
I walked up the driveway,
and there was this older man...
probably in his 60s.
He was outside,
and he was getting down from something,
and he hung himself.
But it was horribly done
and extremely painful.
I can't believe she actually
saw something like this,
because it didn't happen here.
Their house was actually moved here... Oh.
From about 18 miles away.
Okay.
This guy John Johnson lived on the property
that the house came from.
This is the farmland where he lived.
Settled in 1851.
Now, this guy had bad luck
from the minute he got there.
His father died of pneumonia
within hours of getting to the property,
and then he lost a nephew,
his father-in-law,
then another nephew.
So, on July 9, 1877,
he goes out into the barn.
His wife goes to find
him, and he's hanging.
He committed suicide.
So, the guy you saw,
you said, was in his 60s.
This guy Johnson died at the age of 61.
Now, I was able to locate a photo of him.
Oh, my.
What's the matter?
I've seen him.
That's the old man from the hallway.
I was in my house one day,
and I just happened to
glance up in the mirror,
and behind me...
It looked just like him.
And it looked like he was coming after me.
I ran down the hallway and
slammed the door behind me,
it scared me so bad.
Does this guy look familiar to you at all?
Oh, yeah.
I'm a little creeped out
knowing that he came from another property.
I didn't even think anything
like that could be possible.
Yes, it is.
The dead can form all sorts of attachments.
Wow.
When I went into the house,
the first thing that I
saw was this living male.
And he seemed very angry and upset,
and he was kind of yelling and screaming,
very emotional,
and I saw that he had brown
hair and he was in his 40s.
It's me.
Yeah, I'm kind of confrontational
with the ghosts.
When I can't get any sleep,
I get up and I yell at them.
Okay.
The other thing that I got...
There is somebody at the
location with abilities.
And their dominant ability is telepathy.
The telepath can manipulate
the minds of those around them
into perceiving what they're perceiving.
So,
there's only two guys living in this place.
Which one of these two is the telepath?
Well, right away, when I sat down...
and you know I did not know their names...
I wrote this down. Oh, geez. Look at that.
Yeah.
She put your first initial down.
Wow.
I've always kind of felt
like maybe I was sensitive
or had some weird type of power.
I would say my moods are contagious.
Sure explains a lot, don't it?
It makes sense.
We also have these other
things that are here,
and what I'll call them is the tricksters.
Typically, a trickster is associated
with Native American tribes,
but they're all over the world.
But that's not what's going on here.
This is where it gets very unusual.
There's about 50 of them.
These guys are causing all kinds of chaos.
They like to feed off of
negative environments.
They're about like 3 or 4 feet tall,
shiny... very shiny... black,
like, glistening.
Well, they've seen them.
One of the many things that
these guys experience here.
Yeah.
I had an experience...
three of them at the foot of my bed.
Oh, yes.
I jumped out of the bed,
I ran through them,
and got out into the hallway.
I am awakened every night by these things.
Wow. Okay.
The thing about the bed is,
when I was in that middle room,
I actually did see them getting
and having a good time...
That's where I always see them.
And jumping on the bed,
and they were having a blast.
Here, they're more aggressive.
They're, like, jumping on the bed
like they're having a good time,
barking and growling.
And that's where Ashton sleeps.
One night, I heard him scream
in the middle of the night,
and he came running out, and he swore
there was red eyes in the
closet staring right at him,
that they were coming at him.
He's scared to death.
These things can manipulate what you see,
and, you know, most often,
they'll actually appear as
animals and things like that.
Tell her.
I was laying in bed one night,
and I saw a little fawn
actually hop through the window,
and it hopped in front of the bed
and then just booked it down the hallway.
Okay.
It's really bad.
The other thing was,
these guys are going to draw
from you any kind of negativity
because that's gonna feed them,
so these things will bring up
these done and over issues,
like past traumas
or bad things that have
happened in a person's life.
They'll, like, trigger that,
and then you're thinking
about it and thinking about it
and talking about it and talking about it,
and it's just feeding it and feeding it.
Do you know what I'm saying?
I think
about that all the time.
I don't tell anybody that.
It just makes you feel like no
matter how much good you do,
you'll never make up
for every bad thing you've
ever done in your life.
But when I'm not here,
I never think it.
Sometimes I stay long at
school so I don't have to.
He thinks I don't want to come home.
I don't want to...
I want something to think
about that's different.
I told nobody about that.
I'm sorry.
So, everything she's saying
is making sense to both of you guys?
So, I did have a sketch done
of what I saw in the master bedroom.
Ooh.
Oh, my God.
So, I did have a sketch done
of what I saw in the master bedroom.
Ooh.
Oh, my God.
And this is where I see them,
is around the bottom corner of my bed.
No wonder I'm not getting any sleep.
Are they, like, physically capable
of pulling the covers off of me?
Yes.
Oh, no.
These tricksters have a leader.
I saw him outside.
When he was alive,
he was a very strong, powerful man,
and he did have a lot of
power placed upon him.
He was in charge of a lot of people.
He was from probably, I think,
about 80 to 100 years ago.
He was extremely pissed
off about the way he died
because he didn't want to die that way.
He should have died, like,
in a blaze of glory.
Okay, so, this guy was powerful
and was in charge of a lot of people?
Yes.
So, the original owner of
the property you're on now
was this guy Alva Shaw.
He was very well-connected.
Matter of fact, he was so well-connected,
he was appointed by the governor in 1864
to be the superintendent of the
state penitentiary in Portland.
Problem was, he wasn't good at it.
When he was running the penitentiary,
44 prisoners escaped.
Only 13 were ever recaptured.
So, on August 27, 1866,
eight prisoners take him hostage.
He was able to break away,
but a bunch of them escaped.
Only five were recaptured.
The next morning,
he wakes up to an editorial
calling him a disgrace
and that he doesn't know
how to run a prison
and he caused this whole thing to happen.
Now, this is him at a younger age.
Now, he died in 1880 at the age of 64
after a 13-hour illness.
He just died.
So, he didn't definitely
go out in a blaze of glory.
That's for sure.
I don't know if this is the person or not.
I really don't.
This is so overwhelming.
I never expected this much.
I mean, I knew there was a lot going on,
but wow.
So, guys, you know why
you've been fighting.
You know why your moods have been changing.
You know why you're
hearing and seeing things.
But the big question is,
are you gonna be able to raise
Ashton here in a safe place?
For that answer,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
A lot of things have to be
attacked at the same time
to get a good, good result.
So, the first thing is the dead guy,
the leader...
He needs to go.
So, what I would like
to see happen with him
is a physical medium to come in,
talk to him,
and get him to leave.
But, at the same time,
you also need to have a shaman come in,
and what I want that person to do
is to set up a perimeter
around your property,
and I mean big.
Like, all the way around, okay?
This is gonna push these tricksters out.
So, once that's done,
you have to deal with your abilities.
Start keeping a daily journal.
And what I want you to do is
to write up any and all issues
that create strong emotions within you.
Once a week,
I want you to take all those pages
that you've written all this stuff in
and burn it and just get rid of that.
Put it away and out from you.
Now, I spoke to Ashton. He's 7 years old.
He really doesn't understand
what's going on here,
but he's scared.
How long do you think before
he'll maybe feel better
about things in the house?
He'll feel a lot better
once the shaman's moved
all of the tricksters
off the property.
So, are you guys gonna take Amy's advice?
Every step of the way.
We're gonna get it taken care of.
I want them out of my house.
Now it's payback.
They're gonna pay.
They're gonna go.
I really hope Terry
and Bobby follow my advice
and deal with the tricksters
terrorizing their family.
With the help of a medium and a shaman,
they should be able to
free themselves of the evil
surrounding their home.