Something happened to these people.
Something quick, something fast.
Somebody grabbed my ankles
and dragged me out the bottom of the bed.
Somebody's physical here.
You just can't rest in this house.
Most of the problem is upstairs.
We're gonna try to fix this, okay?
This place is bad. Bad.
Yeah,
there's a lot of crazy [bleep] going on.
Something bad's going to happen.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's panic.
And it's almost like a butchering.
I see dead people.
They all died horribly.
I speak to dead people.
Get out of here.
And they speak to me.
Vicious.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
It doesn't matter where you are.
I'll find you.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
This guy's a real piece of work.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I feel like I live in a house of Hell.
It's my job to reveal them.
This is not good.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end...
I want my life back.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Is he trying to kill her?
Or time to get out.
Oh, my God.
This is going to kill us.
I'm out here in Pittsburgh,
Pennsylvania.
Amy and I got called in
by a woman named Lisa.
Now, this is a hardworking,
salt-of-the-earth, sweet woman.
She's also scared out of her mind.
Told me the activity in her house
is so violent and out of control,
she's barely getting any sleep.
And now whatever's in the house
is attacking her grandchildren,
and that's where she draws the line.
She says we're her last hope and
she's praying that we can help.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the house of
any leading information.
Family photos and personal items
can influence her findings,
so it's important that I
cover or remove them all.
When I'm done, the location will
be ready for tonight's walk.
There's a lot of people...
dead people...
and they're cognizant, conscious entities.
They seem agitated when
I try to talk to them.
This one guy wears, like, a bowler hat.
He kind of is a troublemaker.
He's an instigator for
the dead and the living.
Lisa, I'm glad to be here.
You sounded really upset on the phone.
Now that I'm here,
tell me what the hell's going on.
I'm being attacked,
my granddaughter's being attacked,
and my daughter is being attacked, as well.
I know something's here,
and we need your help,
and that's why I called.
What kind of things are we talking about?
We're hearing walking,
doors slamming upstairs,
opening and closing constantly,
and I'm being touched.
Our household is being turned upside down,
and, you know,
my kids don't even want to come in here.
When they do visit,
they don't want to stay long.
Okay, so, let me ask you a question.
When you moved here,
was there somebody else living here?
When we first moved here,
it was an empty lot,
and they just built the homes in 2006.
That changes my investigation a lot.
Who exactly is living here with you?
My daughter Tamiera and
my granddaughter Kayla
and my ex-husband.
- Your ex-husband?
- Yes.
Are you guys in the same bed?
No. He sleeps in the spare room,
and lately,
he started sleeping on the couch.
We've spoken to him about it to
ask him if he's seen anything,
and he just says, you know,
"I don't want to talk about it."
All we do is argue.
I truly believe it's the house
that's causing all of this.
Now, Lisa, a lot of couples break up.
What makes you think it's paranormal?
Well, we've been together for 36 years,
and his attitude that he has now,
since we moved in this house,
has changed dramatically.
What are you hoping we could do for you?
Help me find out what's
going on in this house
so we can have some peace of mind
and be able to sleep in here.
I just want my family back.
Mm. There's panic... stress, panic, panic.
Bad. Bad.
These people who live here are very open,
and they are being extremely
influenced by the dead,
which instigator guy loves
because he can do whatever
the [bleep] he wants.
There's, uh... a woman,
maybe more, screaming upstairs.
They're freaking out.
And the other person in the
house is in [bleep] denial.
This instigator guy
is very focused on this
person who is in denial.
He [bleep] them all the [bleep] time,
and the person who is in denial knows this.
But it's real nasty.
Okay, so, what's going on in here?
We hear the refrigerator
opening and closing constantly,
and no one's in here.
Okay, so...
Like that?
Just like that.
Now, I've seen a dog actually
open and close a refrigerator.
- You got animals?
- We don't have any animals.
- Okay, so, you got no animals in the house.
- None.
What about your ex-husband? Did he hear it?
Yes, he's heard it,
and I'll say, "Did you hear it?"
"Yeah. It could be the wind,
or it could be," you know...
Okay, so he's just being a stubborn man.
Yes, exactly. Yes.
Would he talk to me?
He says no.
He's adamant about that.
He just will refuse.
Okay.
There's, like,
a lot of stuff going on up here.
Instigator guy can do a lot.
He can open and close doors,
and I think living people,
if they're kind of sensitive,
would kind of feel this,
and they're like, "Aah! That's freaky."
He thinks it's funny.
But it's something really evil.
So, why'd you bring me into this room?
I've seen an old lady in the closet,
in my closet right there.
She looked to be in her 80s.
She had gray in her hair,
and her hair looked like it was curly.
She had almost like a witch nose.
- Long?
- It was long. Yeah.
And she kind of looked sinister.
How the hell do you go to sleep
knowing there's a head in your closet?
I take sleeping pills to
help me sleep at night.
Are you sure that the stuff you're taking
is not giving you...?
I know without a doubt it's not those.
I don't know how you're
even dealing with that,
but what else is going on in here?
I, um,
was on my back in the middle of the bed,
and I was being touched.
Um...
My breasts were being touched,
and I saw this shadow figure get off of me.
I looked to my left,
and I saw this gentleman
standing to the left,
facing the window, and he was well-dressed,
and he smiled at me,
and I just lost it, Steve.
I just started cursing him.
Then he just disappeared after that.
I know it's hard to talk about. It is.
It's really hard to sleep
in this room at night.
It's really hard to be in this house.
- You weren't just touched.
- Yeah.
You were physically assaulted sexually.
Just can't rest...
We can't rest in this house.
You've got to be going out of your mind
thinking about your granddaughter
and your daughter being here, as well.
Yes. And that's my biggest worry.
Are you afraid that maybe
something's happening with them?
Something already has.
This person's not [bleep] sleeping.
The living person's afraid of this dead guy,
and the instigator,
he really comes on full force.
He does creepy stuff sometimes, you know.
Explain that more. What do you mean?
One thing I see is, like,
a shadow going up the wall,
going up the ceiling.
He's done things like go onto the bed.
I see grabbing.
Not a good area.
So, Tamiera, I was talking to Mom
about the activity in the house.
Mm-hmm.
Now, you live here with your
8- year-old daughter, Makayla.
- Makayla, yes.
- Okay.
- And she's autistic?
- She's autistic.
Okay.
Here's a picture of her.
- This is her?
- This is her.
- Oh, she's cute.
- Thank you.
She won't sleep nowhere else.
Okay, so, she stays in bed with you?
- All the time, yeah.
- What about you?
Any experiences that you can share with me?
Yeah. I seen an old lady.
Okay, your mom mentioned an old lady.
Which one are you seeing?
She's hunched over.
She got salt-and-pepper hair.
Okay.
She's very, like, in her 80s-looking.
- She got wrinkles.
- Okay.
So, when you see her,
does she recog... Does she see you?
Yeah. And what does she do?
I feel like somebody's stroking my hair.
Okay, is it, like, a gentle touch, though?
Yeah, like a motherly love touch.
But then, when I roll over
to see if it's my daughter,
she will have her back towards me,
facing this way.
- So it's not her.
There are a couple of dead people
that are hanging around
because these people are
so easy to be influenced.
I think it's a female.
The only thing I can see in her
aging is her hair turns white.
Kind of a witchy look,
like her nose and chin
kind of witchy-looking.
Do you know if the living would
have any interactions with her?
Yes, I do believe they would.
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
Ow!
Mm!
What happened?
I got pinched.
The older woman is being
physical to a living male here.
She won't leave him alone, really.
She's always, like,
pinching, prodding, poking.
She doesn't like him at all.
Like, he feels stalked.
She feels like she's
protecting a living female
from this living male.
I think dead lady feels like
this dude shouldn't be here
'cause he's no good for this living lady.
Yeah, she hates him a lot.
Let me ask you another question.
I was talking to Mom.
She's had some physical
things happen to her.
Yeah.
What about you?
I was in bed asleep.
My daughter wasn't home at the time.
She was with her dad, and, um...
I felt like somebody grabbed my ankles
and dragged me out the bottom of the bed,
and I hit this right here.
Okay.
Look.
You okay?
Oh, honey. All right.
Okay. You all right?
I
hate talking about that.
You okay?
I'm right here with you.
Nothing's gonna happen while I'm here, okay?
Okay.
My heart's beating fast.
I feel like... I don't know.
I feel like I'm going crazy sometimes
dealing with this, you know?
Like, why is it happening to me?
That's how you feel. Like...
Right.
How often is this physical
stuff happening to you?
I'm seeing another dead person,
and he's very distinguished-looking.
He comes in here because, um, he wants help,
and he wants to leave.
He does feel trapped here.
Why does he come here?
'Cause I think one of
the person has abilities.
He's inducing [bleep] panic attacks
because he's super-forceful at night
'cause that's when he
can get to this person.
I think that they do see him,
um, and I think they hear him,
and, you know,
I do see him getting physical.
And I think this person, like, sees him,
like, you know, shaking the bed.
Instigator guy wants to be friends
with this distinguished guy,
you know, and the other guy's like,
"Would you just leave
because I want to [bleep] leave," you know.
Even though, at times,
I think they've seen both,
like, at once.
So, yeah,
there's a lot of crazy [bleep] going on.
How are you dealing with this?
I'm trying to deal with it,
and I think the reason why
I haven't given up and left
is because of my mom.
I don't want to leave her here by herself.
Okay.
You know, and at the same time,
I'm worried about my little girl
'cause, you know, she see things, too.
She screams out, "Monster."
I don't know what else to do.
Like, I'm so afraid of being
in this house at nighttime
or even in the daytime.
You mean alone?
Yeah.
Like, I'll sit in the car when people leave
'cause I...
Aww, honey. Come here.
It's okay.
You know what? We're gonna try to fix this
so you don't have to sit
in your car no more, okay?
Okay.
It's frustrating, too,
because I don't want it
to mess with my daughter.
The second I get to a new location,
I start making a bunch of calls.
I reach out to cops and historians
to help me out with my case.
So, I just got a call
back from a genealogist
who says one of the first
owners of Lisa's property
has a story I'm definitely
gonna want to know about.
Elissa, you mentioned this guy Edward Cappe
had a tough go of things
when he lived on my client's property
in a house that's no longer there.
Edward was born in 1843 in Ohio
and came with his family to Pittsburgh.
And then he joined his father
in the printing business.
Then he met Sadie,
the love of his life, and marries her.
And they move on to the
property you're investigating
in about 1872.
You mentioned on the phone
there was a lot of tragedy
involving Edward Cappe and his family.
What did you mean?
He had lost four out of his
seven children and his wife.
His second-born daughter, Ida,
died in 1875 of scarlet fever.
This is Ida's death record.
Then we have Harry,
who dies at age 9 months.
And he dies of summer complaint,
which is a colloquial term
for salmonella contamination
through breast milk.
And then, nine years later,
Dalton is born but dies at 5 weeks old.
And he dies of malnutrition.
How did Sadie take all this?
I don't think she took it very well.
She was only 41 when she
passed of uterine cancer.
This is Sadie's death certificate from 1893.
- She also died on the property?
- Yes.
So, then, his namesake, Edward Jr.,
dies in 1920 as a young man
due to a blood disorder.
Oh, geez.
So, Elissa, at this point,
this guy's been through a lot.
What happens to him?
He dies in 1922 of stomach cancer.
I found his will,
and there's something very interesting.
The estate owed $707,
so he dies broke, dependent on his children.
You weren't kidding about a tragedy.
I mean, he loses four of his kids,
his wife, then dies broke.
The distinguished dude...
Something with the newspapers
and stuff with him.
I think it was the business
he was involved with.
He was always traveling or
living in different places.
He would have money,
and then he wouldn't have money.
Like, he feels like people are after him.
I think he's here because he wants help.
So, he wants to get moved on.
He doesn't think he's doing anything bad.
So far,
I know one of the original
owners of my client's property
suffered one crushing
tragedy after another...
losing his wife, four children,
and all of his money.
But I need to see if there's something else.
Searching through old records,
I find the death
of a 14-year-old right
on my client's property.
I'm on my way to meet with an archivist
who did some digging
on this 14-year-old kid's
death on Lisa's property.
Turns out that's only half the story.
She says after the kid died,
his dad went on a downward spiral
and got hooked up with an infamous con man.
Well, Joseph Sulzner moved onto the property
with his wife, Elonora,
and their four children.
He owned a butcher shop, and then, in 1890,
the same year he moved onto the property,
he was appointed a meat inspector
by the U.S. government.
The kid... What happens to him?
Well, in 1893, his eldest son, Christian,
contracted typhoid fever,
and here's his death record.
Now, you mentioned on the phone
that after this guy's kid died
he got hooked up with some con man?
What did you mean by that?
What was going on?
Well, he got involved with James Larson,
a medical quack.
A quack? Why do you call him a quack?
Well, he wasn't an actual doctor.
Before he even met Sulzner,
he was arrested in St. Louis and fined $250
for practicing medicine without a license.
So, now,
why did Sulzner even hook up with this guy?
What was the story?
He had a fall at work and
ended up hurting himself
and developing rheumatism from that injury.
By 1919, it all catches up to him.
He's paralyzed and bedridden,
and he spends the next three
years of his life like that.
And in 1922, he dies of cerebral hemorrhage.
What about his wife?
Well, she ends up spending
the next six years of her life
alone,
and she dies in 1928 of a stroke.
Okay, so, if I got this right,
this poor woman loses her son, who was 14,
and her husband loses it
and winds up hanging around
with this quack doctor,
then she has to take care of him
because he's bedridden for three years.
He dies, and then she's alone for six
and then winds up dying from a stroke.
It sounds like she's the biggest
victim in this whole mess.
The old lady,
she's very upset, very angry.
I think she lost her family?
The old woman who tortures
the living man in denial
likes to hang out down here.
She's angry that I'm here,
but I'm starting to see
what she was like in life.
She's talking about the meat.
Yeah, she's showing me just how...
I guess how it was,
and she's showing me putting
slabs of meat down here.
This is weird.
All I know is that she literally
is, like, in love with this house.
She loves this house.
I think she was very lonely.
I feel bad.
I, like, see her, like,
talking to walls and stuff.
I don't know if she was
mentally ill or she went crazy.
Lisa's house sits right across
the street from train tracks.
Believe me, you can hear it.
Now, to cover all my bases,
I reached out to a train
expert to look into it for me.
I wasn't expecting much,
but he just called me back, and he said
he found three deadly
accidents on those tracks.
So, professor, you mentioned on the phone
that you found a lot of accidents
regarding train tracks right
across from my client's house.
From the opening in 1883,
there was constant death,
constant injuries at this place.
The rail roads were always
considered to be very hazardous.
So, what about the first one you found?
James Gattie, 1891.
He's on the train tracks taking a shortcut,
gets off the tracks when a train's coming,
and then is surprised by another train,
which will take his life.
Geez.
What are the other ones you found?
Well, there's one in 1905,
which is a catastrophe.
It involves over 100 men.
They're waiting for the train
that usually takes them to work.
Okay.
But they're on the tracks waiting for it.
All right, so, what happened?
So, it's early in the morning, very foggy,
and another train is coming behind them.
In a matter of seconds,
they start pushing out on each other.
Of course,
some people don't get off the tracks.
It strikes them.
There is three killed and two wounded.
All right, so, let's go out here.
So many people are hanging
out on the [bleep] lawn.
And there's a lot.
Do you know who these people are?
No, I don't know yet. Um...
I would probably put them at, like, um...
between 1900 up to like 1920.
Okay.
A lot of them work together.
They know each other's families.
I'm trying to understand, like,
why are they all together, you know.
Usually when they're all together like that,
they all died together, but...
Okay, so,
that's two pretty bad accidents so far.
What else did you find?
It's a very sad story, very tragic story.
It's going to happen in
1913 around Christmastime.
There's a young couple, John and Dorothy,
and they're coming back from church,
and they decide to cut across the tracks.
And suddenly,
he saw the train barreling
down on him and Dorothy.
He decides to sacrifice himself.
He pushes her out of the way,
and he's struck.
Ah.
His arms are broken and skull is fractured.
Wow.
So, we got five deaths and a lot of injuries
associated with my client's property
with these train tracks.
I mean, that's a lot.
Yes.
But that's just what's in headline news.
I could show you where
a brakeman was killed,
a flagman was killed.
There's plenty of deaths that go unreported.
It was pretty much a death trap.
I'm trying to figure out their deal.
Um... something about church with them.
Going to church,
but something happened to these people.
Something quick, something fast.
There's some kind of walkway here.
Some kind of walkway that they're following.
But I feel like everything should move back.
Like,
I feel like everybody take a step back,
and I don't know why.
During my walk, I saw dozens of dead people,
but what has me the most concerned
is the living person being
tortured in the master bedroom.
At the end of the bed is a dead guy.
He's agitated.
And then there's another
dead guy who's under the bed,
shoving his knees up into the mattress.
Okay.
Is this what you saw?
Yes, that's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our
findings to each other
and our clients for the first time.
Amy, I'd like to meet you Lisa.
This is her daughter Tamiera.
Now, obviously, we're not in their house.
The reason for that is Lisa's ex-husband,
who lives with them,
didn't want us around all of a sudden,
and he's not happy about the investigation.
But these guys know they got a problem...
a serious problem.
The activity's bad in their house,
and it gets worse by the day.
They called us in 'cause they want to know
if it's gonna be safe
for them to live there.
Right now, I'm gonna have Amy tell
us a little bit about her walk
and see what she uncovered.
I went into the house.
I felt a lot of stress and panic,
a lot of anxiety.
I did get that there are people in the house
who are very open to the dead there.
I heard,
um... a word right after I walked in,
and the word was "denial."
And, um...
This is associated with a
particular person in the house.
They've had experiences,
but they are just, like,
completely denying it
to themselves and to everybody else,
and this is causing a lot
of the yelling and fighting.
It's obvious who she's talking about, Lisa.
Yeah. My ex-husband.
Yeah, when we talk to him
about what we've experienced in the house,
he sometimes just ignore us,
and it's really gotten worse.
The arguing and the anger, that's constant.
You said people in the house are open?
Tamiera's got an 8-year-old
daughter named Makayla.
I have a picture of her.
She's a beautiful little kid.
This is Makayla. Now, Kayla's also autistic.
Would that make her more open to the dead?
She refuses to be in the house by herself,
and when we are in the room,
she will point to certain corners,
saying, "Monster."
It tears me up because
I don't know what to do.
Okay, baby. It's okay.
She's my baby. I love her to death.
It's frustrating.
It really is.
There's three main conscious entities
that hang out in the house.
One of them is a female.
She kind of has, like,
a witchy kind of look,
so, like, a bigger nose and chin.
- You know what I'm saying?
- Yes.
And as soon as I hit the top of the stairs,
to the left, there's a room.
That's her ex-husband's room.
I went in there.
And she was telling me how
much she hated this male.
I think dead lady feels like
this dude shouldn't be here
'cause he's no good for this living lady.
She hates him a lot.
Well, obviously,
the woman she's talking about...
Is the old lady.
Is the old lady you've
seen and you have seen.
Yeah.
Describe her.
In my closet, I saw this old lady,
just her face, looking at me.
It was, like, smiling at me,
but it was real wide.
You could actually see her teeth.
Now,
who do you think this woman might've been
when she was alive?
She was talking about how
attached she is to the property,
and then,
when I went down into the basement,
she was going on and on and on
about how she used to
store her meat down there.
She was indicating that
her entire family died.
I think she died alone.
Now, you mentioned something
in the beginning about meat
and how this lady was
attached to the property.
What you said kind of makes sense
because, in 1890,
a woman moved onto the property
and lived in a different house
with her husband and her son.
Her name was Elonora Sulzner.
Her husband, Joseph, owned a butcher shop
- right around the corner.
- Oh, okay.
And later on became the meat
inspector for the state.
Interesting.
Now, you mentioned she lost her family.
Now, she did lose her son at the age of 14.
He died from typhoid.
His name was Christian, and he died in 1893.
Now, right after that happened, the husband,
he had gotten hurt in an accident at work,
and he developed rheumatism.
And this guy wound up being bedridden
for the last three years of his life.
Now, in 1922, he dies.
Here's his death certificate.
Now, Elonora lived alone for six years
until she finally died
from a stroke in 1928.
So, does that sound like
the woman you ran into?
Yeah.
So, the next person that I met was a guy
who I kind of called the
distinguished gentleman.
His whole thing is that he wants
help and he wants to leave.
You guys are so open in this house,
he's keyed in on that.
So, one of the things that I saw him doing
was trying to get, you know,
the living's attention.
Not only is he trying to reach you guys,
but other people are trying to interfere
with that... dead people...
and so this pisses him off even more,
and then he gets really agitated,
and he starts acting out a little bit,
and so what he'll do is scream and yell.
He will sometimes cause
or create panic attacks.
You had that look on your face
when she said panic attack.
Because I feel like that a lot.
As soon as I walk in, I'm like...
"Ma,
I can't feel my heart speeding up."
And then it kind of, like...
You know how you feel your
heart kind of skip a beat?
- Yeah.
- That's how it feels.
And he wants them to move him on?
Well, you know who he really
would like to have him move on
is your ex.
My dad?
Mm-hmm.
Wants her father to move him on?
Wait. Huh?
So now you're telling me that
he's probably got abilities.
- Oh, wow.
- I knew it.
Okay, so, now, the guy that you saw
you said was distinguished, well-mannered...
Yes, yes.
Who was he in life? Any idea at all?
He was traveling a lot, like for work,
and then he was showing me how,
like, sometimes
he would be really wealthy and
sometimes he'd be really poor,
like it was always fluctuating for him.
I think that his work was something around
or to do with newspapers.
You said this guy was a traveler,
had something to do with newspapers
and that, at points of his life,
he had money,
then didn't have money, had money.
The only guy that comes to mind
on the research on the property
is this guy Edward Cappe.
He came here from Ohio in the 1840s.
He wound up operating a printing press
for a local publishing company.
Now, right after he moved
onto your property in 1872,
things took a turn for him.
Everybody started dying.
I got death records here for
his wife and four kids that died
during the time he was on your property.
Now, in 1922, he died of stomach cancer.
Now, you said this guy had
money but that he lost it.
I was able to track down this guy's will.
When you look at it,
he actually died owing $700.
He died broke.
Is it possible this could be the guy?
It's possible.
I mean, the newspaper thing is interesting.
Now, that's two people.
You said there were three.
So who's the third one?
Yeah, the third guy is...
I called him the instigator.
He does have a bowler hat on.
I saw him inside actually
messing with the living
and, like,
really just trying to start [bleep]
And his thing, too, is, like,
he really likes the drama,
so, you know, he wants to see the fighting
and the yelling and all this.
Some of the things that the
instigator guy likes to do
is he does like to make a lot of noise.
Um, he will go under the bed and grab.
I can't stand him.
Now, you pretty much nailed everything
these guys are experiencing.
Tell her what happened.
I was sleeping,
and I had my daughter with me,
and I felt like somebody grabbed my ankles
and just pulled me to the
bottom of the headboard.
And the other thing is she was touched
in an inappropriate manner.
I was asleep, and I just... Something...
It felt like something woke me up,
and I just felt myself being touched.
To my right,
this dark figure got off the bed,
and then it disappeared.
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
So, I had a sketch done
of a scene that I witnessed in the bedroom,
and both of the dead guys were in there,
the distinguished guy and the instigator.
Oh, geez. Take a look at this.
I can't leave you.
This is there. I can't leave you.
So, I had a sketch done
of a scene that I witnessed in the bedroom,
and both of the dead guys were in there,
the distinguished guy and the instigator.
Oh, geez. Take a look at this.
Oh, gosh.
I can't leave you.
This is there. I can't leave you.
It's okay, baby.
That's why Amy and Steve
is here to help us.
So, Lisa, when we first met,
you said you wanted your old life back.
Yes. But now you know what took it away.
The big question here is what
can you do to fight back?
This way you, your daughter,
and your granddaughter
can live there safely.
For that, I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
What you're going to do is
you're going to find a medium.
The first thing that they
need to do when they come over
is move the old lady on.
The medium's objective is going to be
reuniting this woman with
her dead 14-year-old son.
So you think it's Elonora Sulzner?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Okay.
Once that's done,
the medium's gonna be working
on moving the distinguished gentleman on,
and when she does that,
it'll go very quickly.
- Because he's looking to go.
- Yes.
Okay.
Then you have the instigator guy.
He's going to put up a fight,
but the medium will be able to
force him out of your house.
After everyone's been moved on,
I want you to take this tar-water
and put this at every entrance,
including the windows and doors.
This will keep all of the dead out forever,
okay?
Yes.
I got a question for you.
Your ex-husband, how's he gonna react
to you having to bring in a medium?
Um, I'm gonna find out.
He's stubborn. He's not going to do it.
Then he'll have to deal with it.
- Yeah.
- I'll probably move
because I don't want to
deal with it anymore.
So, let's say her ex-husband
stays there and they leave.
Have fun.
If he stays there,
I would not ever go to that
house and visit him, ever,
because you'd be walking
into a [bleep] storm.
Literally, all the focus
would just be completely
and utterly on him.
Last night, I straight-up called him...
I was like, "You're selfish."
He is selfish.
"Because, you know,
this is happening to your granddaughter
and you don't even care."
You know, Lisa, normally I would ask you
are you gonna take Amy's advice,
but in this particular case with you,
it's not that simple.
No.
But are you at least gonna, you know, try
to talk to your ex-husband about this?
Yes, definitely, I will. I will.
Are you gonna help her, Tamiera?
Yeah.
Removing the dead is extremely important
if Lisa and her family ever
want to find any peace.
I can only hope her husband realizes this
and allows a medium to come in
and deal with the evil that's
terrorizing this family.