They're just messing with her...
touching her and manhandling her.
I've seen... we call it the shadow man.
He definitely pushes the living away.
I've got a bone-chilling fear
for the safety of our kids.
This room is bad, bad.
I feel like there's evil in here.
Why the is he torturing this girl?
Something bad's going to happen.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's panic.
And it's almost like a butchering.
I see dead people.
They all died horribly.
I speak to dead people.
Get out of here.
And they speak to me.
Vicious.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
It doesn't matter where you are.
I'll find you.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
This guy's a real piece of work.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I feel like I live in a house of Hell.
It's my job to reveal them.
This is not good.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end...
I want my life back.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Is he trying to kill her?
Or time to get out.
Oh, my God.
This is going to kill us.
I'm down here in Macon, Georgia.
Amy and I got called in
by a guy named Jeff.
He says his entire
family's being terrorized
by activity in the house,
but he's most concerned
about his youngest daughter,
who's being physically attacked
and can barely sleep at night.
Now, he's a man of faith,
and he tried prayer,
but it seems to be getting worse.
He told me we were his last hope.
Before Amy arrives,
I look for anything that
can influence her findings.
Family photos and other personal items
need to be covered or removed.
When I'm finished,
the location will be
ready for tonight's walk.
Coming up, my body wanted to run...
like an instinct, you know,
when you're being hunted.
I definitely get that
there's a lot of chaos
going on around here.
It's extremely distracting.
I feel extremely ill...
really bad... and very painful.
It's bad.
When we spoke on the phone,
it sounded like you were at your wits' end.
Last couple of years,
it's been hell to live here.
What are you and your family going through?
We're talking about anywhere
from footsteps to shadow figures...
Okay.
To hitting, scratching.
Who all lives in the house?
It's myself, my wife,
Tami, Jessica, my child,
and my son, Hunter.
You mentioned that you
were really concerned
about your youngest daughter.
Correct.
We've just always been
real protective of her,
and she seems to be the one
that mostly gets attacked.
And, of course,
she's coming downstairs to us, crying.
There's no way for me to protect her.
All you can do is hold her and
tell her it'll be all right,
although you don't know.
That would drive me crazy.
It hurts.
The house looks pretty new.
How long have you guys been here?
We've been here 23 years... '91.
We built the house.
Did you guys have experiences
from the beginning?
Just mischievous stuff...
nothing alarming, nothing frightening.
Okay, so why are you calling us now?
About a year and a half ago,
it started getting ugly.
Have you guys tried anything
to try to stop what's happening here?
A lot of prayer, a lot of shared prayer.
Nothing's helped.
I can't physically protect my family.
I need help.
So, there's this older man here.
He's talking about two bedrooms...
two bedrooms that are important here.
There's a male and a
female in these two rooms
that are having the problems.
But then there's this other guy who's,
like, younger.
The younger guy is accusing
him of being abusive.
There's a relationship there.
I'm thinking father/son
or grandfather/grandson.
There's a lot of anger and tension here,
and it's a lot between these two men.
It's completely unhealthy.
It's very, very stressful.
You know, you can really feel it.
So, why'd you bring me
into the living room?
This is where most of my
stuff has taken place.
Like what?
Me and my son came in the other afternoon.
We were walking through the living room.
The fireplace pokers started doing this,
shaking all about.
Did it stop?
It stopped.
We came back, walked back and forth,
jumped all around in the room.
It doesn't move.
So we didn't do that.
You guys didn't have a
violent storm or anything,
with hard thunder, or anything like that?
No, no.
Anything else like that ever happen?
- We came in from church one Sunday...
- Okay.
The whole family together.
This sofa's pulled out from the wall.
The other sofa behind me is
pulled out from the wall.
The recliner is turned around,
facing the window.
And you definitely weren't broken into,
and nothing was breached?
Nothing moved.
Nothing but those three items were moved.
Hm.
As far as in here,
I'm seeing movement issues.
I am seeing leaving a room, and it's...
something's set up...
say the balls are set up
a certain way coming back
and everything's...
scattered.
But I don't know who
the [bleep] is doing it.
Nobody's copping to it.
So, Tami,
I was talking to your husband, Jeff,
about stuff that's going on in the house.
Curious how you're handling things.
You know, it's just day to day.
I've got just a bone-chilling fear
for the safety of our kids at this point.
And, Tami, when I talked to Jeff,
he seemed to think that whatever's here's
kind of picking on Jessica.
Is that accurate?
Oh, I would definitely agree with that.
There's a lot more activity with Jessica
that's a lot more physical.
That's got to kill you, as a mom.
It breaks my heart.
You're constantly scared.
You don't know what's gonna
happen next to your children.
Now, what about yourself?
What about your experiences?
Have you had any?
I was sleeping on my
side of the bed one night
and felt someone sit on
the side of the bed,
and it was, like, someone heavy.
I mean, you could feel the mattress go down
to the point that it
pulled the covers tight
on the bottom part of my leg.
And you're sure it wasn't a dream?
Positive it wasn't a dream.
- Anything else?
- Yes.
There is a presence in
this corner periodically.
It's always in the corner,
by the gun cabinet.
And you immediately know
you're being watched.
What do you think this is?
I have no idea, Steve.
All I know is it's dangerous,
it's threatening,
and it seems to be getting worse.
This older man is definitely
causing people to be afraid.
If they irritate him at all,
he does creepy [bleep] to
kind of freak them out.
What does he do to them?
He'll come at night
and, like, move around like a
big spider on the floor...
on all fours.
But they're seeing, like,
this dark thing, you know,
moving around the floor and the room,
going under the bed,
and this freaks people out.
Or stand in the corner and watch people.
It is creepy, and people do see,
like, this black thing in the corner.
Do you know what this old
man wants with the living?
He wants to control them
like he controlled the
people when he was alive.
So, Hunter,
I was talking to your parents,
and they were telling me
you're having a pretty tough time here.
Yeah.
I feel very unwanted in the house.
Okay. What are you going through?
I see... we call it the shadow man.
I've seen it, you know,
20-plus times, easy.
And it's most of the time
right in between those windows right there.
Is it possible that it's a shadow
reflected from outside at all?
I keep my blinds down.
They're blackout blinds.
You can't see through them.
Really?
I know your sister's
going through some stuff.
You and her discuss this.
I try to keep it to myself, honestly.
She's already on edge.
You know, I've had probably
up to 10 calls from her...
"Hey, are you in the house?"
"No, I'm not even at the house."
She said, "I'm the only one home.
There's somebody in the house."
It's definitely attracted to her,
for some reason,
and I don't know why.
I think the two bedrooms
the old man was talking about...
they're upstairs.
Mmm, there's a male here,
and there's some kind of
bonding between this person
and the female in the other room.
There's something about the windows.
Uh... I didn't like the windows.
The female...
This room is, like, bad, bad.
So, Jessica,
I was talking to Mom, Dad,
and your brother, Hunter,
and it seems like whatever's
here is kind of targeting you.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, what are some of the
things that are happening?
Well, a lot of times,
my drawers open by themselves.
They just open, all of them.
They're almost to the point
where they're falling out of the dresser.
- That far out?
- Yes.
Is there anything else
moving around in the room.
Well, I've actually seen
what I thought was a man in my room.
It was in front of my bed,
and it was actually going
through my paperwork
on my table.
I heard the paper shuffling,
so that's why I woke up.
I called out to him, and he didn't answer,
so I turned to turn on the light,
and I came back, and the papers were moved.
They were open,
when originally they were closed.
Okay.
How are you sleeping at night?
I do have nightmares all the time,
and I sleepwalk.
Give me an example of what you're dreaming.
I'd be outside.
The sky was red,
and everything had almost a red tint.
Okay.
People would be dancing.
And then everyone would stop
and just turn their head
like they were looking at something.
But then I'd wake up,
so I never saw what they were looking at.
Okay.
This female... she has horrible nightmares,
horrible [bleep] nightmares...
some she remembers, some she doesn't.
Like,
I see her waking up outside the house like,
"What the [bleep] What the [bleep]"
But I don't know if
these are just nightmares
that she's having.
When she's having these experiences,
I think there's another force here,
and it's causing a lot
of physical phenomena.
What the [bleep]
What's going on?
She does see the older man. He watches.
He calls himself "The Watcher"
when all the [bleep] going on.
Why the [bleep] is he torturing this girl?
They'll touch me.
I've been doing my hair before,
and it just grabbed it right
here and just snatched it.
And they were big fingers,
so I felt like it was more of a man.
Wow.
From that point, it only got worse.
At one point,
something actually laid down behind me.
It almost felt like it was spooning.
It had its head, like, on me.
I mean, I was terrified.
I couldn't move.
I couldn't speak.
I couldn't even cry.
And then it finally just got up,
and I heard it walk out.
And at that point, I just started crying.
Like, I bawled my eyes out.
Okay.
And I've woken up with scratches.
You guys have a cat, right?
Oh, my cat's declawed.
How often is that happening...
the scratches?
The scratches only
happened like three times.
Only three times?
You hear what you're saying?
I have a daughter 23 years old.
I couldn't imagine her coming to me
and telling me the stuff you're saying.
That would kill me.
I feel like there's evil in here.
I want it to leave.
I want our lives back.
Okay.
There's these little,
dark things, like children.
They're black.
They're around the bed
and touching her feet.
They're climbing on the bed.
They're climbing on her.
They're incapacitating
her so she can't move.
She can't yell. She can't do anything.
She's like...
Like, the air gets sucked out.
I feel uncomfortable.
I'm getting chills. Okay, I'm freaking out.
When I get to a new town,
I put my feelers out
to cops, historians, local professors.
In this case, it paid off.
I'm on my way to meet
with a local genealogist
who says all the early owners
of Jeff and Tami's property
were slave owners.
Now,
I don't know if it's gonna help my case,
but it's something I
definitely want to check out.
So, Cecil, you mentioned on the phone
that some of the early owners
of the property I'm
investigating had slaves.
That's correct.
Okay, what can you tell me about them?
Well, the earliest guy
that we have recorded
was named John Martin.
He shows up in 1830 census.
And it shows that he owned 33 slaves.
33?
33.
He was a slave trader
for the area of Macon,
as well as he was a farmer.
I guess that would explain why so many.
Yes.
Okay, so, now,
how long does he have the property?
Well,
we have record that he sold the property
in 1837 to a guy named Alexander Hunt.
Okay, so now he moves there.
Is he a slave owner, too?
The 1850 census right here shows
that Alexander has 38 slaves,
so he has a few more than John Martin did.
Wow. All right, so...
for some reason,
this property has an abundance of slaves.
Right.
Okay, there's another man down here.
He's got issues.
He is very angry.
Probably like six foot.
He's a big guy,
big, round dude... like, chubby and built.
He's, like, sweating,
and he's really angry, and hot.
He's very protective of his space.
He doesn't really want
anybody else down here.
So he definitely pushes the living away.
People would feel him like a wall, like,
coming up behind them, like,
just kind of pushing them out.
The property's then sold to Joshua Harris.
Okay, now, what about him,
as far as slaves go?
According to the records,
he only has six slaves.
Okay, so how's it go for Joshua?
Everything seems to be going pretty well
until the Civil War comes,
and in 1862,
one of his sons joins the Confederate Army.
His name's James.
Okay.
Do we have any idea how old that kid was?
James was 20.
After he was in,
just north of Atlanta, he was captured,
and he was held prisoner of war.
Joshua Harris had another son
that was just a year younger,
named Franklin.
Franklin, I would assume,
did the same thing as his brother.
No, Franklin did not join.
Why not?
I get the impression that
his dad encouraged him
and wanted him to,
but you know how sometimes children are...
no matter what you ask them to do,
they do just the opposite.
There's always a rebellious
one in the crowd.
So, now, the war ends.
What happens with Joshua and the farm?
Well,
Joshua was able to hold onto the property,
whereas many landowners were not able to.
Okay, so does he stay there,
or does he move on?
He stays there until he dies
in 1895 at the age of 85.
Okay, what happened to his son James?
James is released as a prisoner of war
when the war's over, and he comes back.
What about the son, Franklin,
that never went off to war?
Well, sometime after 1895,
after his dad's death,
Franklin and two of the sisters leave,
and we find record of
them in 1899 in Texas.
Okay,
so did Franklin inherit any of the land?
Either he wasn't left any,
or maybe he sold his part.
Okay.
I'm seeing the older and younger man again.
And they're fighting.
It's uncomfortable.
That younger guy was saying
that this older man was abusive,
physically abusive...
you know,
that he was [bleep] torturing the family.
He ruled with an iron fist.
And I heard words, which was,
"father," "landowner," "slave."
The younger man doesn't
have anything in common
with this older man.
He doesn't like him.
There's a lot of anger
and resentment there.
The older man's perspective
to the younger man,
there's a sense of disappointment.
And do you know if they have any kind
of connection to this property?
Definitely the land.
The younger man just kept
talking about the land.
He was talking about a massacre,
something about a war.
He said that there were
a lot of innocent people.
He also said something about murders.
He said the dead weren't respected here.
So far,
I've got a family being terrorized
by unexplained activity
and a property that was
home to dozens of slaves.
But I need to see if there's anything else
that will help my case.
Searching through old records,
I find a battle
that broke out between Union
and Confederate soldiers
right on my client's property.
Obviously,
I need to know more about this fight,
so I reached out to a
local Civil War expert
who says it was a bloody battle
and the information will
definitely help my case.
So, Michael,
why'd you want to meet here?
Joshua Harris,
who owned your client's property
during the American Civil War...
- Yeah?
- is buried right here.
And how close is this spot
to my client's property?
Probably 800, 900 yards.
Okay.
Now, you mentioned on the phone
that there was a bloody battle
that took place right on the property.
- Yes.
- What happened?
Steve,
I'm sure you've heard of Sherman's March.
I have.
Troops moving from Atlanta to Savannah,
wreaking havoc along the way...
tearing up rail road tracks,
stealing crops, livestock, burning barns,
things of military value.
And this is a period
etching that an artist did
depicting some of that destruction.
The Confederates knew that
Sherman was approaching,
so they sent various units out
to establish defensive positions,
one of them right here.
Okay, so what happened?
On November 20, 1864,
Sherman's cavalry came right
down this road out here.
The Confederate troops were lying in wait
in the heavily wooded area
on each side of the road
on your client's property.
Okay.
And as the first soldiers got close enough,
the Confederates charged.
Okay,
so they got attacked and ambushed here.
Yes.
And when the smoke of
battle began to dissipate,
seven Confederates lay dead.
What about the Union side...
any casualties?
The records do not tell
us that information,
but it is certainly possible,
and if we did have dead
Federal soldiers here,
most likely, the Confederates would have
interred them in a mass grave.
Steve, I think the real kicker,
for Harris in particular...
earlier in 1864, Georgia's governor
had ordered a census statewide.
He wanted to capture the
names and locations
of all male citizens
eligible to be called up
into the service of the militia.
Okay.
Guess whose name appears on that list.
Our guy, Joshua Harris.
Wow.
So I think there is a very good possibility
he was fighting on his own property.
I am seeing a lot of activity.
There's a lot of men in
both of these directions.
That group is very large.
That one's the big one.
That's a lot of men.
That's, like, you know, war.
Like, I'm definitely feeling,
you know, panic and stress,
and, you know, it's loud.
And there's... that's very sneaky.
It was very sneaky.
It was planned.
There was a lot of yelling between them.
I think that they were being hunted,
and that's why they're
freaking the [bleep] out
and trying to hide [bleep]
Then I'm getting the
[bleep] pain in my head
like a son of a [bleep]
It hurts a lot.
I encountered several dead
people during my walk,
but the dark things
surrounding a living girl's bed
had me the most concerned.
There was a thing.
It was actually standing
to the side of her.
Same body shape as the child.
It had its hand over her mouth,
and the way that the arm
and the hand looked
was not normal.
Is this what you saw?
Yes, that's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our
findings to each other
and our clients for the first time.
Amy, I'd like you to meet
two very worried parents,
Jeff and Tami.
Everybody in the house
is having experiences,
including their son, Hunter,
who I have a picture of here.
Okay.
Now, the main reason we're here
is their daughter, Jessica.
She's going through hell.
And it's killing Jeff and Tami
that they can't do nothing to help her.
And we're their last hope.
So now that Amy knows who you guys are,
I'm gonna have her tell us about her walk.
So, when I was outside,
the first thing that I
saw was a lot of chaos.
There was some kind of big battle.
There was a lot of men.
There was some general who was,
like, pacing around.
Something about a massacre,
and I could feel there's so
much stress in this area.
I think I know
what you might have seen.
I wasn't shocked to find
that there was gonna be
Civil War activity in this area,
but what I was shocked about
is that you had a battle
that took place right on your property.
Now, what happened is in 1864,
General Sherman led the
Union Army on a march.
It started it Atlanta,
and he was going through the whole state.
I got an artist's
depiction of what happened.
They destroyed everything.
Now, on November 20th of that year,
the Union Army came right
across your property here,
where they got ambushed.
But it turned out worse
for the Confederate side,
'cause they were badly outgunned.
They wound up killing
seven Confederate soldiers
right here on your land.
Wow.
Now, did you guys know about the battle?
- No.
- No idea.
We knew there was Civil
War activity around here,
but we had no idea a battle took place.
So, what else did you see?
As soon as I walked in,
I saw this older male.
He would show himself
dressed in, like,
a black cloak and black hat.
He was extremely tall, and he was angry.
The other thing he made known
was that he likes to make people feel fear.
I was actually in the master bedroom,
and he slid into the
corner and was watching,
and that's part of his thing,
is he likes to watch people a lot.
I also got him, like,
squatting down like a spider
and, like,
moving around the floor very quickly.
There's a presence in my room,
in the corner,
that I'll wake up and I know
immediately I'm being watched,
and it's interesting that you said
about him getting small
and towards the floor,
because Jeff and I have
recently talked about how
we'll go to get in the bed,
and it's almost like you're a kid
and you're afraid for your feet
to get close to the edge of the bed.
Mm-hmm.
54 years old, I'm a grown man,
and sometimes you feel like a
kid running to jump in the bed.
Mm-hmm.
I see the shadow person
usually in the middle of the floor.
It was looking through my papers,
like it was nosy.
But Hunter sees him more than I do.
Wow. Okay.
When I look into my brother's eyes,
I can tell he's scared.
I'm supposed to be the
protector of my home,
and there's nothing I can do.
Any idea who this
guy might have been
when he was living?
Most of the information I got about him
was actually through another person...
a younger man.
The younger man has a lot
of anger and resentment
towards this older man,
so I kind of got, like,
there was some kind of
family connection here,
whether this was father and son
or grandfather and grandson.
The older man,
the only thing that came from him
was his disappointment in the younger man,
which the younger man
doesn't give a [bleep] about.
He's like, "I don't care."
And I heard three words... "father,"
"landowner," "slave."
One thing you got to
know about the property...
the earliest owners all had slaves.
There was three different
owners that owned your land
that had slaves before
the Civil War broke out.
The last slave owner who lived on the land
was a guy named Joshua Harris,
who came here in 1858.
Big reason I'm thinking it's him
is because of the
relationship with his son.
This guy, Joshua Harris,
was a big supporter of the Confederacy.
It was where we lived, obviously.
Now, I have a census here
that says he was a reserve militia
for the Confederate army.
This guy was in his mid-'50s,
so that'll give you an idea
of how supportive he was.
Now, he had a son named James who was 20,
and he enlisted in the Confederate Army.
Now, he had another son,
Franklin, who was 19,
who refused to go off and fight.
Now, the genealogist I spoke
to about the Harris family
said that it probably
caused a lot of tension
within the family.
That's the only guy I can
think of that fits that bill.
Yeah.
Sounds like them.
Now,
the thing about this Joshua Harris guy...
he's actually buried right
here on the property.
Oh, my God.
You could probably throw a
rock how far he is from here.
Wow. Oh, my gosh.
Wow.
We had absolutely no
idea he was over there.
So,
when I was talking to the older man,
he showed me that there
were two rooms in the house
that were the most active,
and these were two bedrooms,
male and a female.
And when I walked upstairs,
I knew exactly the two bedrooms,
and that this was, in fact,
what he showed me.
So I went into the room where the boy was,
and a lot of the chaos in there
was the extreme amount of noise...
movement.
The window's what I got
was making the female
in the other room feel,
like, sad and isolated,
because the boy had kind of pulled away
from being so close.
Is what she's saying
making any sense to you?
She's nailing it.
That's exactly how I feel all the time.
It's like he's really distanced
himself from everybody.
Well, then I went into the other room,
and what I was seeing was
horrible nightmares...
horrible.
And I saw, like, you waking up
occasionally in strange places.
We talked about that...
how you sleepwalk.
Yeah. I know that I woke up
in my brother's room before.
Tell Amy about some of
those dreams you had.
Well, there were a bunch of people outside.
Everything just had this red...
- Glow?
- tint, yes.
And everybody was dancing,
and then they all looked
up like they saw somebody,
but when I would look,
I would just wake up.
Interesting.
It was very weird.
Hm.
So, what I saw was,
during some of these nightmares,
that there was actually
phenomena going on...
like, lights flickering,
doors opening and closing,
objects moving, things of that nature.
When I was younger, it
was just minor stuff,
like drawers pulling out.
I remember that my whole life.
Me and Hunter walked through one day,
just a couple of weeks ago,
and the fireplace pokers about fell over.
Okay.
What I was seeing was you were in the bed,
and I saw these three things
that were surrounding the bed.
And at first I thought,
"Okay, those are children,"
'cause they're little,
all-black, like black shadow,
but solid.
Then I saw that one was
actually grabbing your feet,
and the other one, up by your head,
had its hand over your mouth.
What they were doing was manhandling you,
basically incapacitating you...
holding you down,
and they were laughing at
you because you were afraid.
The other thing I saw in your room
was the old man again,
and he loves when this is going on.
He thinks it's absolutely fascinating.
And that's why he goes up
and he'll watch when this is all happening.
She's got some stuff going on.
She feels like she's being spooned in bed.
Yes.
I woke up,
and I could feel something behind me,
spooning me, and its head was,
like, right here,
and I couldn't move.
I couldn't breathe. I couldn't cry.
I couldn't turn my light on.
And it scratched me.
I've woken up with scratches on my back.
Oh, man.
You kind of gasped when you heard
that she was spooned in bed.
Well, that happened to me.
It was the second night after the walk.
I was in my bed,
and I felt someone from
behind was holding me,
and it felt very uncomfortable
and inappropriate.
And I believe it's the old man.
I think he's kind of a predator.
I've begged it to leave her alone.
I wish I could go up there
and slap the [bleep] out of it,
honestly, and make it leave.
I don't even want it to
see that I'm afraid,
'cause in a way, that means it wins.
Well, I did do a sketch of
what I saw in the bedroom.
I got to show it to you.
I've seen that.
I did do a sketch of
what I saw in the bedroom.
I got to show it to you.
I've seen that.
The reason I know I've seen that...
that's what was trying to touch me.
When I got here, I told you guys
I never know what Amy's gonna see,
and I'm sure you weren't expecting
to hear what she told us tonight.
I wasn't expecting it.
At least now you know
what you're dealing with.
The big question is how do you fix it.
For that answer, I'll turn it over to Amy.
The first thing
that I want to focus on
are the dead individuals
that you have in the house.
Obviously, the older man needs to go.
So I would like for you to bring
in an older, male medium.
I want him to have a lot of
confidence in what he does,
and I do want him to have a certain amount
of, like, gruff, I guess you would say.
This probably isn't going to
be a very pleasant situation
for the medium or this old man,
and there's probably going to
be a lot of fighting happening.
The thing with removing the older man
is that his son is going to go immediately.
Once the medium moves on
the older man and his son,
I want you to take this tar water
and put it on all of the windowsills
and all of the doorways.
This is gonna keep all of
the dead out from now on,
so you'll know there's
no dead people anymore.
But you might still have experiences.
What do you mean?
Well, I'm saying that there's
a possibility of aliens...
because that thing I
saw was not a dead thing.
It's not a demon.
It's something that was visiting
and taking you...
and your brother.
Personally,
I have a lot of issues with this,
but when I looked and did my
own research of this area,
it was something that
I couldn't not discuss.
Let me get this straight.
You're telling me she's being abducted...
her and her brother?
I'm saying it's a very large possibility.
Oh, gosh.
I don't... I wouldn't even know
how you would begin to
fight something like that.
That's a whole nother level
of what the [bleep] do you do with that.
Now,
is this something they can put a stop to,
or is it something that
they just kind of manage it?
They kind of manage it.
What I would recommend is keeping a journal
and kind of just documenting,
like, any dreams you have,
or any further experiences,
so that you have as much
recall as possible.
And it's really up to you
how you want to handle this.
It's not gonna be something
that's on a regular basis.
That would be highly unusual.
So you can live with it.
How do you feel, Jess?
I mean, you're the one
that's the main focus
of what's going on.
I didn't really want to believe
that it was something
from another dimension
or anything like that,
but I have no choice but to
believe what Amy tells me
and to do what she tells me to do.
To me, this sounds pretty simple,
as far as getting rid of
the spirits that are here
and knowing that we can
prevent any more coming in.
The other we'll just have
to tackle as a family,
as we do other things, and
we'll work through it somehow.
I honestly feel hat God gives us the tools
to do whatever we need to do.
He led us to y'all.
I wish I had better news
for Jeff and his family,
as dealing with alien
activity can be terrifying.
But I believe if they follow my advice,
they'll be able to manage it,
and with the help of a medium,
the dead will no longer
torment them in their home.