I think a lot of bad things
happened in the trees.
It's getting more violent.
I've been scratched.
I feel like I'm being watched.
Something's wrong with the kid.
It smells like rotting flesh.
When these people die,
they're stuck with this thing.
She's trying to drive her insane.
Something bad's going to happen.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's panic.
And it's almost like a butchering.
I see dead people.
They all died horribly.
I speak to dead people.
Get out of here.
And they speak to me.
Vicious.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
It doesn't matter where you are.
I'll find you.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
This guy's a real piece of work.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I feel like I live in a house of Hell.
It's my job to reveal them.
This is not good.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end...
I want my life back.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Is he trying to kill her?
Or time to get out.
Oh, my God.
This is going to kill us.
I'm down here in Covington,
Louisiana.
It's about 40 miles north of New Orleans.
I received a call from a woman
who was hysterical on the phone.
She said the activity in her
home destroyed her marriage,
and now it's going after her three kids.
When I spoke with her,
she really tugged at my heart,
and I hope we can help her out.
Before Amy arrives,
I have to make sure
the location is free from
any leading information.
Family photos, personal items, and books
have to be covered or removed.
When I'm finished,
the location will be
ready for tonight's walk.
Oh, my God.
The first thing that I got was
really extreme amounts of anger,
like deadly anger.
Uh-oh.
I think a lot of bad things
happened in the trees.
It's very brutal, savage, and dark.
So, Rhonda, I'm glad I'm here.
Listening to you on the
phone broke my heart,
how desperate you are.
It's very stressful here.
Me and my children,
they're terrified, I'm terrified.
And how old are the kids?
This is Scarlett. She's 10.
Gilby, he's 6, and Savannah, she's 8.
Are they being affected?
Yes, I think Scarlett's probably
had the most experiences.
What have you experienced?
We're hearing a lot of footsteps, voices.
We're seeing shadows,
and now it's getting more violent.
How long have you been in the house?
December of '04.
My ex-husband and I custom-built the house.
- Your ex-husband?
- Yes.
Okay. Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
Definitely think some of
the activity in this house
contributed to our divorce.
Why do you say that?
We were very much in love, very happy.
He was my soul mate.
And he was just never his regular self
after we moved here.
You saw a personality change?
Yes. And there was just other issues,
like substance abuse.
He was addicted to pain medication.
Geez. After moving here?
After moving here.
I don't mean to get nosy. I just...
The more I know,
the more I can convey to Amy.
Mm-hmm.
So you feel your husband's
personality and the mood swings
changed when he moved here with you?
What about yourself?
I definitely noticed it with myself, too.
Could be angry really easy.
I'm in pain a lot.
I started having health problems
the day after we bought the property.
It's a burning in my legs and feet,
and it's all the time.
And I've been to over 40 specialists.
They still don't know what's wrong with me
- or why it happened.
- Let me ask you a question.
As far as the investigation goes,
what are you hoping to get out of it?
I would hope that my children
and I could not be afraid,
have a normal childhood.
They shouldn't have to
live in fear like this.
This is, like, ridiculously painful.
The energy here is so
bad that it could...
Harm a sensitive.
It's strange
because it is composed of
not just the dead energy here
but also the living.
And they are absorbing this.
That's caused an illness,
I think, for the female here.
I don't know if it's
heart or if it's blood,
but there's something
physical that's manifested
as a result of this.
I see, like, restlessness.
I see panic. I see series of illnesses.
So this is something going on.
This has, like,
incapacitated this person at times.
I think there's been hospital visits.
And I'm, like, seeing this conversation,
and there's a male.
And he's just like, "Why don't"...
Like, "Why don't we just leave?"
God, I feel so sick.
So, what's going on up here?
I've been slapped up here.
You've been slapped?
- Yes.
- How?
I was over here, putting some things away,
and it felt like someone
slapped me on my butt.
Did something fall on you maybe?
No, nothing fell on me. Felt like a hand.
Okay. But did you look to see if any
of the kids were up here or anything?
Yeah, they were downstairs.
Any other physical things
happen to you up here?
Yes. This just happened recently.
I had three scratches
just appear on my arm.
Kind of looks like cat scratches, you know?
It's not.
The cat that sleeps with us is declawed.
They're still showing up here.
Oh, yeah. I can see it.
What about the kids?
Any experiences with them?
Yes, all of my children
have had similar attacks.
Okay.
Oh, God.
There's this old woman up here.
She is very grumpy.
Whoo! Ooh!
Whoo!
Talk about some [bleep] anger issues.
She hates the living people.
She just says, "I haunt them.
That's what I do."
And she says she does it very well.
I think this old woman is
focused on an adult female here.
I'm thinking she's trying
to drive her insane.
All right.
So, what's going on in the bedroom,
as far as experiences go?
One night, I was touched a lot.
My head, my face, my hair was touched.
And then I felt someone
come on the foot of the bed
and, like, sit next to me like this,
and the bed went down,
and it didn't get back up.
It just stayed like this.
- It feel like a person?
- Yes.
It felt like a person
was getting in the bed.
How big of a person?
It felt like someone my size.
I mean, this is crazy.
This is what I'm used to.
Unless you live it every day,
people just don't understand
what you go through.
There have been times that the old woman
has beat on the living woman here.
I see her standing next to a bed.
And the old woman is very big
and literally just sits on her body.
And the woman's huge,
so it's like smushing the living woman.
She's trying to drive her crazy,
hoping that she's gonna lose
her [bleep] mind, basically.
How long did you live
here before you got divorced?
About seven years.
So, Scott,
the seven years you were living here,
did you ever experience
anything you couldn't explain?
You know, like the smells
that would just constantly
come from that room...
The same smells, like rotting flesh.
Which room are we talking about?
The playroom.
Did you ever investigate it?
Oh, yeah.
The drywall was, you know, dry.
I mean, it wasn't wet.
There was no moisture anywhere.
So, there was no indication of
a decaying body or anything?
- None.
- Anything else?
No. I'm here for Rhonda
because I know how much
this is affecting her.
Whether I'm a true believer or not, I mean,
I have to take care of my
kids and her, as well.
You realize they're getting scratched?
She told me about that.
She showed me some of the marks.
Yeah, I mean, that's got to drive you crazy.
It's horrible.
I mean, how do you protect your
child when that's going on?
They shouldn't have to
kind of go through this.
So, when I was talking to Rhonda,
she basically said you
guys were soul mates.
Do you agree with that?
Oh, yeah. I have no doubt about that.
We felt like we were doing
everything the right way,
and then we moved in this house.
Things just started changing.
And the whole seven years I was here,
I was just more unhappy than
I've ever been in my life.
My behavior started becoming more...
little bit more aggressive.
So, you think you've changed
since you've been out of here?
It's a weird thing you would say that.
I don't think I've ever been
happier in my entire life.
There's this living male,
and he's just had it,
and he's very overly dramatic
and just, like, screaming at everyone.
He's just not reacting well, I think,
to everything that's going on, I guess.
He wants out.
He wants away from these people,
the living people.
I don't know why this
living man is flipping out,
but it has something to
do with the trees outside.
There's a male in this,
like, tree house thing.
There's some connection
between this dead man
and the living male at this place.
They have things in common.
I can't... can't keep talking to you
if this is gonna keep being in the way.
He likes this relationship
'cause he's felt lonely for a long time,
and he feels like this is
a kindred spirit for him.
- How old are you?
- 8.
8 years old.
Now, is this the room that you sleep in?
I would, but I don't.
You don't, huh? Where are you sleeping?
With my mom and my sister and my brother.
Okay. Why are you sleeping with mommy?
Because I don't want to sleep in my room
because I feel like I'm being watched.
Who do you think is watching you, honey?
I know it's not good.
Have you ever seen
anything or heard anything?
I saw a back of a lady's head in a bun.
Okay. Where did you see this lady's head?
In the kitchen, on a chair.
- In the kitchen?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Are you afraid of the house, honey?
Yeah.
Any place you don't like being alone in?
All of the places.
There's something here.
There's something...
Something's wrong with the kid.
Something's really wrong with her.
Mm.
Something... Something is inside the child.
I think it looks like a woman to her.
I saw something on the floor,
something like it crawled in
on the floor or something.
Then I, like, see this woman,
so I don't know if she
thinks it's a woman or not.
Sometimes she plays with it.
There's always somebody in the room,
and they're always talking,
and it's not good.
I don't know what this thing is.
I think it wants to take the kid.
So, Scarlett, I was talking to Mommy,
and she told me you were having
some experiences in the house.
- How old are you?
- 10.
Okay. And you're the oldest, right?
Yes.
You guys are going through a lot here, huh?
I've been touched and scratched.
I've been, like, grabbed.
I feel like fingers are just touching me.
Now, you said you get scratched.
How does that happen? What goes on?
It feels like somebody's scratching me,
and it burns really bad for,
like, a long time.
Maybe a minute later, I'll look down,
there's a giant scratch right there.
Has anything else happened in here?
I see apparitions.
Okay. Of what?
I've seen one of a girl.
She's wearing a long,
long, like, pink dress.
What... Did it look like it was old?
Like, old times, or does it look
like it was from recent times?
It looked like it was from old times.
Okay.
And I've seen, like, creatures in here.
What kind of creatures?
They look like people,
but they're, like,
all crouched down and scaly.
It looks a little bit more
like an alien or something.
What are they doing?
They're just staring at me.
I can tell by the look on your face,
you're really afraid of these things, huh?
Can you describe this thing now?
It can look, like, humanoid,
but it can also look like an animal.
It can change its height.
It can be standing on two feet,
or it can be like an animal, on all fours.
Always pitch-black,
and it does always have wings.
So, what would you call this?
Most people would call it, like, a demon,
but it's not... not a demon.
I think it's scarier.
I'm very confused how it's
associated or around a child.
And they can attach to people...
living people.
Like people who are
alcoholics or drug addicts.
They attach, typically,
to somebody who's in the throes of it.
When these people die,
they're stuck with this thing for,
like, eternity.
I've seen, like,
the dead people with these things,
and they look like
they're suffering greatly.
Like, they seriously, like,
better do what I say,
or people are gonna [bleep] die.
Period.
Even though Rhonda's house is new,
the property deeds go
back to the mid 1800s.
I'm on my way to meet
with a local historian
who said one of the
original owners of the land
suffered heartbreak, insanity, and death.
So, Mary, you mentioned on the phone
that the original owners of
the property I'm investigating
had a pretty tough time there,
a lot of tragedy.
Right. But before we get to that,
how did they even come to the property?
Well, Frances Bossier inherited
about 100 acres of property
from her deceased grandmother
in the Covington area,
which is where your
client's house is located.
This is the land patent,
showing her receiving the property.
Okay. Now, who'd she come here with?
She came here with her husband, Joseph.
So I've got to assume back in the 1850s,
at some point,
the husband would've got the
property turned over to his name.
Correct.
She did turn over her assets to him.
But she thought that he
was being very reckless
with his investments,
so she actually sued him
to gain control of her property and funds.
We've actually been able to
find copies of the lawsuit.
Okay, so what happens?
Well, she actually won,
and he had to pay her her money back,
and she maintained control
of all of her property,
which was unheard of for that time period.
But he must have been very reckless.
Okay. So they were married when
they went to court on this.
Did it break them up after that?
No, it didn't.
Okay. Now, you mentioned on the phone
there was a lot of tragedy
with this family.
And I'm assuming it wasn't the court case.
No, unfortunately, in 1853,
their oldest daughter, Fanny,
drowned in an accident right
here in Lake Pontchartrain.
So I would assume,
between the court case against each other
and now they lose a kid,
it had to be tough on their marriage.
Of course.
Okay.
The old woman who beats
on the living woman here,
this is her house.
She wants the house back.
She doesn't want the living here.
I think she was wealthy.
What I see from her past is
a very dysfunctional family.
I don't think she had a very good life.
So somebody was tugging on me.
Okay. She's a little kid.
Kind of feel like she might have drowned...
but, like, in an outside water,
like, in, like,
a creek or lake or something.
You aren't kidding when you said
there was tragedy with this family.
Right, and, actually, that's not it.
There was something else.
In 1859, Joseph Bossier got involved
with a man named J.M. Vernon.
And he was his business partner,
and, like all of Bossier's
business dealings, it went sour.
J.M. Vernon was a newspaper editor,
so to get Bossier back,
he actually wrote some nasty
things about him in the paper.
Okay. So, what does this guy
Bossier do about this slander?
Well, he actually went to find Vernon
in a New Orleans courthouse.
Okay. And he brought a gun,
and he drew his gun,
but Vernon was a faster draw.
Vernon shot Bossier four times
in the hands, face, ribs, and mouth.
Okay. Does he die?
12 days later, he died,
leaving Frances a widow.
Huh.
This guy who hangs out in this tree
[bleep] there's a really bad
pain associated with him.
And then I am feeling like
something hit me here.
I got to just kind of let this go
'cause it's really kind of
messing me up a little bit.
I'm trying to learn more
about the man in the tree
who's attached himself to
a living male in the house,
but all I'm getting is intense
pain in the back of my head.
And then I hear a gunshot
right next to my ear,
and that's how he died.
I don't know if it's self-inflicted
or if he was shot in the head.
God [bleep]
This [bleep] hurts.
I can't even concentrate.
This guy Joseph Bossier
sounds like a real loose cannon,
and I want to know if
there's more to his story.
But I've actually managed
to track down one of his descendants
who says his life was so wild,
it could be made into a movie.
So, Rene, the reason I contacted you
was I did an interview about
the first owners of the property
I'm investigating,
and Joseph Bossier came up.
Now, you're related to him.
I am.
I am his fifth great-granddaughter.
- This is him?
- That's him.
So eventually he winds up with
the property I'm investigating.
But before that, what do you know about him?
Well, he was in the Navy when he was 11.
He got kicked out because
he stole something.
Then he was in the Army when he turned 12.
I don't know why he was
discharged from the Army
- at age 12.
- Okay.
Then he became a mercenary for
several different countries...
France, Russia, Spain, Britain, Egypt.
Wow.
I bet even his time overseas
wasn't gonna be a quiet one.
No. In the British Navy, as a mercenary,
he was accused of drowning a crew member.
Then he built a ship.
- He did?
- Yeah.
He played pirate.
Pirate?
Where did he do that?
Right out here in New Orleans.
When you say he played pirate,
did he actually rob people?
No.
He would see other ships out in the Gulf,
and he would know that
they were his friends.
Okay.
So he would raise the skull and crossbones,
and he would board their ship.
So, he was just out in
the water, playing...
Except for one time.
What happened?
Well, he thought it was his
friend when he boarded the ship,
but it wasn't who he thought it was.
Him and his crew member got beaten
within an inch of their life.
Wow.
- Does he ever get charged with anything?
- No.
He ends up suing the captain
for damages to his health and reputation.
Okay.
This guy was really something else.
There's something with military here.
Something.
This guy who hangs out in a tree,
he was in the military.
Yeah. He got twisted in the head.
Yeah, he did. He got real [bleep] up.
He's saying to me that, you know,
a lot of things that he
did was due to his head,
being, you know, messed up.
Do you know when this is from?
This is...
You know, he's not denying that
a part of him didn't like it.
You know, a part of him liked it,
but he's saying,
"I saw a lot of horrible things,
and it ruined me.
It ruined me."
So far, I know the original
owner of my client's land
was a reckless mercenary
who wound up murdered.
But I need to see if there's anything
else that could help my case.
Searching through old records,
I find a man named Frank Lenel,
who killed himself.
But the reasons are unclear.
So I've asked a local
archivist to meet me here.
He says the tragedies this man
suffered could help my case.
So, Bill,
I found that article about this guy Lenel
that killed himself.
Do you know how he came
about being on the property?
Frank married Louisa Schultz in 1858.
And a year later, her father died,
and she inherited hundreds
of acres of property.
And the house was on that property.
Okay. So, now, the article said it was 1880
when he killed himself.
So, what happens before that? I mean...
He and Louisa had about six children,
and then, unfortunately, in 1871, she died.
She was 36 years old.
Okay. So she's young when she died.
Do we know what she died of?
No, we weren't able to find that.
Then, the next year,
he remarries a woman by the
name of Elizabeth Davis.
That was in 1872.
The area was building up quite a bit.
And because of the trains coming
in and the population expansion,
he decided, as an entrepreneur,
to open a hotel,
which he was able to do in 1880.
That's the same year he kills himself.
Correct.
Now, you would think opening up
a hotel would be a good thing.
You would think so,
but three months before he opened the hotel,
his second wife died of unknown causes.
She was 43 years old.
Wow.
Did he live long enough
to see the hotel open?
Well, he did open the hotel successfully,
and it was a month later
that he killed himself.
In fact, he was found in the woods
about a mile and a quarter from the hotel.
And at the coroner's inquest,
they determined
that he had shot himself with
a pistol through the chin,
into the brain.
Okay.
During my walk,
I saw a dead man in the trees.
I'm meeting with a sketch artist
to draw him as he appeared in life.
He was in his 40s.
He mouth is kind of feminine-looking,
and his hair is slicked back.
Next, I describe the disturbing scene
I witnessed in a little girl's room.
There was a dead woman.
And behind the child, there was this thing.
And it has wings, like,
almost encasing his body.
Amy, is this what you saw?
Yes, that's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our
findings to each other
and our clients for the first time.
Now, Amy,
I want you to meet Rhonda and Scott.
Rhonda lives in the house with
her three beautiful young kids.
Scott is their father
and Rhonda's ex-husband.
He lived in the house for a while,
and you've been out for
about three years now?
But he's a skeptic,
and Rhonda wanted him here
just so he could know the
hell that she's going through
with the kids.
Now, you asked me to not
hold the reveal in the house.
And that's the first time
you've ever done that,
so I'm curious as to why.
Well, there's a lot going on there.
And I personally felt that
I was physically in danger.
During my walk, there was this man
who was up in a tree,
and what he was doing,
basically, was watching people.
It was disturbing.
He was saying that he had attached himself
to a male in the house,
that he felt like this person
was a kindred spirit to him
and that he really enjoyed this
because he had been lonely for so long.
Now, these guys built the house in 2004,
and Scott's the only guy
that lived in the house.
Mm-hmm.
Now, I got to ask you a question.
If this guy attached himself to Scott,
let's say,
would it change his behavior?
It's possible.
The whole time
we were living there,
everything about his
personality was different.
And so was it anger?
Yes, with everybody.
My personality did
change while in the house,
and particularly toward the end there,
I mean, I was getting really aggressive.
And I think that contributed to,
probably, the final breakup.
Now, did you get anything about this guy,
who he might have been when he was alive?
What I was able to get from this individual
was something about the military.
I believe he was in the military.
And what he said was that when
he went into the military,
he saw a lot of things that disturbed him.
So he admits that he got a
little messed up in the head
from this whole experience.
Then I heard the gunshot by my ear
and was obviously feeling this pain.
What he looked like, in his death state,
was a disaster.
There was a couple guys on your property,
going back with the history,
that died from gunshot wounds.
There's one guy in particular,
what she's describing makes me think of.
His name was Joseph Bossier and his wife,
Frances,
were the two first recorded
owners of the property
you guys live on.
You mentioned this guy was in the military,
right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
So now, in 1814, at the age of 11,
he joins the Navy.
Geez.
But he was discharged for theft.
1815, he joins the Army.
This time,
he was discharged for unknown reasons.
His involvement in the
military doesn't stop there.
Between the years of 1816 and 1823,
he served as a mercenary in
five different navies in Europe.
- No way.
- Yeah.
He served in France, Egypt,
Russia, Britain, and Spain.
Now, he got thrown out of the British Navy
because he was accused of
drowning another crew member.
Now, you said this guy
died from a gunshot wound.
In 1859, Bossier gets into a nasty dispute
with a business partner of his,
who was a guy named J.M. Vernon.
He was also a newspaper editor.
Now, Vernon printed some pretty nasty,
disparaging things
about Bossier,
so Bossier found out that he was
gonna be at a courthouse one day,
and he decided to go down there
and confront him about this
with a gun.
Vernon, actually, was a quicker draw
and pulled out his gun
and shot him four times...
the hand, the mouth, the
face, and the ribs.
Take a look at the guy's portrait.
That's Joseph Bossier.
So, is this who you think
you might have seen?
Well, I did a sketch of the person I saw.
Wow.
That's the sketch.
Now look at the portrait.
Looks like the same guy.
It's about as good a sketch and
a portrait as you're gonna get.
Unfortunately,
he felt that you guys were kind of similar,
which is kind of weird.
My personality and his personality
- were like kindred spirits?
- Yeah.
I got to be honest with you.
When I spoke to your ex-wife,
she made it sound like
you were pretty reckless on certain things.
Oh, yeah. I've been notorious.
As far as what?
Making decisions that just made
my life a lot more difficult
if I would have made the right decisions.
How did the rest of the walk go?
So then I went upstairs,
and I met this old lady
that she has a very strong sense
of ownership over the house.
I think at one point that
she owned the property.
But for whatever reason,
she's honed in on your house specifically.
While she was alive,
she was [bleep] about her family.
So she came from a very
dysfunctional family.
She did indicate that she was wealthy,
and I just felt, like,
a sense of isolation.
Like, I do think that she really
just pushed everybody away
because of her attitude problem.
Some of what you're
saying could be his wife
because she did come from wealth.
Now, her name was Frances Bossier.
She inherited the 100 acres
that your house sits on.
This is actually the
deed for her 100 acres.
She actually even sued to
get his name off the deed
'cause he was so reckless with money.
Surprisingly, they stayed married, though.
Interesting.
So, does the woman do
anything to the living
- that are in the house?
- Yes.
She has a very big problem with you.
She admitted that she was physical
and that she was trying
to drive you insane.
What about the physical stuff?
What are we talking about?
She said beating, like hitting.
So I thought, you know, she's beating.
I don't know. Hitting, pinching, shoving.
Well, Rhonda and her daughter
have gotten physical injuries.
They get scratches.
Okay. That's not good.
The one physical thing that
she showed me that she did
was she would literally sit on you.
Oh, my God.
I felt somebody crawl on the bed
before and, like, sit on it.
- Mm-hmm.
- And the bed went down.
Okay, okay. This is really bad.
During my walk, I got that a living woman
was getting very sick from
being exposed to the dead.
I got that it had been going on a few years
and that it had incapacitated this person
and that there had been
several hospital visits.
I've been sick every day
for almost 11 years now.
Nobody knows what happened to me,
why I'm in pain.
I'm incapacitated.
I'll be in bed for weeks at a time.
It's...
it's taken over my life and ruined it.
You got a lot going on so far.
But I know that wasn't the
finish of your walk, was it?
No.
How much more can we take?
So after I left the master bedroom,
I went down the hallway where the kids'
rooms are.
And I saw a little girl sitting
cross-legged on the floor,
talking to the dead lady.
And I tried to go in the room.
I couldn't go in the room.
And that's never happened before.
And then I saw this thing that
I have never seen with a kid.
And that really bothered me.
It can take on different forms.
You know, it can be short or tall.
It can take on an animal-like form.
The one feature that it consistently has
is these wings,
but they're not fully formed.
Well, this gave me a little bit of a chill,
which I never get.
And the only reason I got
a little chill from it
is because when I interviewed Scarlett,
she described seeing a woman
and this creepy,
scaly thing that was crouched down.
And she said it was almost like an alien
but with scales and stuff.
She ever mention that to you?
She told me she's seeing
things in the playroom
that look like aliens.
I had a sketch done of what I saw.
Just be prepared for what you're gonna see.
God.
I had a sketch done of what I saw.
Just be prepared for what you're gonna see.
God.
Gilby sees this and Scarlett.
I never want that to happen again.
Never want my children
to experience that again.
I almost get a feeling it's
like the angel of death.
Oh, no. This is no angel.
Well, it was interesting you said
"like the angel of death."
It's not death.
For lack of a better term,
I guess you would call
them demons and devils.
But they're not that.
They're worse.
And when I've seen it,
it's been with drug addicts,
alcoholics, you know, severe addictions.
So to see it with a child
was utterly bizarre.
This sucker is really evil.
They don't instigate the addiction.
It comes when the person's in
the throes of an addiction,
and it pushes them over the
edge and leads them to death.
And then it keeps their soul.
And it tortures them for eternity.
I've had a problem with drug addictions.
Well, more than likely,
you brought it into the house.
So I'm thinking,
if you got out of your addiction,
maybe he's pissed.
Mm.
He didn't get you.
And then he saw something easier.
I'm in pain a lot, so I take medicine now,
but I'm not addicted to medicine.
Okay.
The problem is,
this thing wants you to become to addicted.
Well, we've had some disturbing
and upsetting reveals before
but, honestly, nothing quite like this.
And, Rhonda, I'm so sorry that
this happened in your house.
I really am.
But now we're gonna find out
if there's anything you can do about it.
And I'm hoping Amy has an answer for you.
You do need to get a medium
and cleanse your house of
the dead that are there
and seal your property so
the dead cannot come back in.
But as far as this thing goes,
the only solution that
there is is in your hands.
It's not something that
somebody can come in
and take care of for you.
Not a lot of people get this warning,
and that's exactly what
this is is a warning.
These are the three reasons
that this needs to stop.
I mean, this thing, it kills people.
I want it away from us.
If I can change whatever's causing the pain
and then start to get healthy again,
get off the medication.
It's gonna take some work.
We've got some work to do.
You think you're gonna
be able to handle this?
Mm-hmm.
I'll get it done.
Whatever I need to do,
I'll take care of it.
I really feel for Rhonda,
as the entities terrorizing her
family present a serious danger.
But I believe if she cleanses
her house of all the dead
and never feeds this demon
what it's looking for,
she and her family should live in peace.