Then the house spit out this entity.
There was a silhouette, just all black,
- standing in the doorway.
- Ow.
Her face had been bludgeoned
till she was unrecognizable.
This thing does not
[bleep] like this person.
I need to know that my family is safe.
This person's in trouble.
It's saying, "I'm gonna make you pay."
Something bad's going to happen.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's panic.
And it's almost like a butchering.
I see dead people.
They all died horribly.
I speak to dead people.
Get out of here.
And they speak to me.
Vicious.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
It doesn't matter where you are.
I'll find you.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
This guy's a real piece of work.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I feel like I live in a house of Hell.
It's my job to reveal them.
This is not good.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end...
I want my life back.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Is he trying to kill her?
Or time to get out.
Oh, my God.
This is going to kill us.
I'm in Delaware, Ohio,
about 35 minutes north of Columbus.
I got a call from a newlywed mother of two
who just moved into her new husband's home.
You would think this would be
the happiest time of her life,
but she says she's in a living hell.
She's convinced the house is haunted
and that her and her two
kids are in serious danger.
She practically begged me
and Amy to come out here,
and I'm hoping we can help her out.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the house of
any leading information.
Once family photos,
religious and personal items
are covered or removed,
the location will be
ready for tonight's walk.
I'm having problems with this lady
'cause she feels like it's
hell for her to be here.
But I think she had money and nice things,
but her husband made
them move here to farm,
and things did not go well.
She thought that the land was bad.
Then, she says she is gonna give
him a taste of his own medicine.
Amy, you sounded
really bad on the phone
as far as the activity here.
What's happening?
Well, I moved here about four months ago,
with my two children, after I got married.
And it's escalated to the
point where it's pure hell
living here.
It's just not what I expected
from being newly married.
Did you guys buy this place together?
- What happened?
- We did not.
Phil actually purchased this house,
um, a few months
before we met a couple years ago.
Okay. So, who exactly lives in the house?
I have a picture here.
Um, this is my husband, Phil, and myself.
There is my older child, Jerrick.
He's 15.
My younger child, Matthias,
who is on the autism spectrum,
he is 10. So, Amy,
what kind of things are you
guys experiencing in the house?
We have, um, heard things.
Doors will open and close on their own.
We have seen shadows and apparitions.
And it's even escalated to the point
where people have been touched.
I need to know that my family is safe,
and I'm not sure that's the case right now.
Is everybody in the house
having the same amount of experiences?
I personally feel like I
have a lot of experiences.
My older son, Jerrick,
has had quite a bit of the
bulk of experiences, as well.
Okay. How's he handling all this?
Not very well.
He's... He's incredibly frustrated.
Um, at times, he gets angry.
Wants it to stop,
and, quite frankly, if it doesn't stop,
- he doesn't want to live here.
- Really?
I have, at times,
shouted at whatever this
is in a very loud voice.
I've just told it that my God
is a lot stronger than you.
Did it stop for a little bit?
I think I made it more angry.
I feel like it's evil
and definitely does not
want me and my kids here.
This woman is complaining
about her mother-in-law.
So, this older woman,
she hates the daughter-in-law.
She didn't take care of her family.
She didn't take pride in the family.
What I'm seeing, um,
in these rooms and stuff... mm...
doesn't look like this place.
- Okay.
- Um, she's freaking out now.
It's like she's all hyper now.
It's making me anxious.
Oh!
I saw her looking like a corpse.
This is a really,
really creepy place down here.
I don't like to come down here.
- Neither does anyone else.
- Okay.
So, why are you creeped out by it?
You constantly feel like
you're being watched.
So, right now, you have that feeling?
- Yes.
- Anything else?
Well, the... the most terrifying experience
was when I was pushed down
the stairs quite forcefully.
Okay. So, how hard did you get pushed?
Pretty hard, because, I mean, it sent me...
Here. Just hit me.
No, no. Just hit my chest.
Show me. Like that.
With both hands, or was it just one?
Yeah. I mean, it was forceful enough
to send me flying down into the wall.
- I'm scared now...
- Yeah.
'Cause I don't know if
it's gonna happen again.
There are two people running down there,
and they're yelling, and they're scared.
Yeah, they're all...
bunch of people cowering in the corner.
How many?
10 to 15.
They're all balled up,
hunched down, and like that.
I think that people would
feel uncomfortable here.
They would feel, uh, fear, uh,
but it's from these people.
Okay. So, what's going on in here?
I have seen a shadow figure
standing right beside of my bed,
looking down at me.
He was tall.
I'm gonna guess close to 6'.
Couldn't give you distinct facial features
other than he was very thin.
Was it dark in the room?
There was just enough light that...
that you could see.
Did you sleep the rest of the night?
Off and on.
I didn't sleep very well,
and I haven't really ever since.
What the [bleep]
I don't like it up here.
I don't feel good up here.
Something runs around...
something dark, fast.
Something's dripping off of it.
- Can people see it, too?
- Oh, yeah.
This is the thing that
they're encountering big-time.
They can't sleep.
They're having, like,
apparently out-of-body experiences.
It's making me nervous and panicky,
and it touches people.
They, uh... They can feel it.
It gives you, like, the chills.
Now, has anything else
happened to you up here?
Yes. In my office next door,
- I was typing at my computer.
- Okay.
And the next minute,
I was on the floor screaming,
and my son had called
911 because I had fallen.
The chair landed on top of me,
and I was unconscious briefly.
What the hell happened?
It's almost as if my chair was
flipped over with me in it,
is... is kind of how it looked and felt.
Have you ever experienced
fainting spells in the past?
Yes.
But you don't think this is that?
You think it's paranormal?
I do think it's paranormal.
I had no warning.
I didn't feel weird that day.
Everything was fine,
and it was with enough force
that I landed across the room
with my head into the wall.
I don't know that I'm so convinced
that that's paranormal,
but I think we'll figure it out.
Okay.
Have you thought about leaving?
If they're in danger... I mean,
I would move tonight if...
if I thought my kids were not safe.
This thing is here most
of the time in this room.
This woman with, like, light hair...
Like, is she being grabbed?
She can feel it.
Being grabbed in the
back of the neck, hard.
Like, I feel her neck hurts.
Like, her spine in her neck, you know?
Then, it, like, slams her forward
so she's, like, sitting,
and it just goes...
Like, all of a sudden, she's just like...
Oh, my God.
Ah.
Now, Phil, when I talked to Amy,
she was talking about
how you bought this place
before you guys even met.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
So, how long were you here
before she actually moved in?
About 21/2 years.
So, did you notice anything
unusual when you first moved in?
Honestly, I never really saw
much in those 21/2 years.
After Amy and the kids moved in, um, I...
it just... Things escalated from there.
- What happened?
- One night, I was sleeping.
And around 3:30 in the morning,
I just was restless.
And I kind of rolled over
and looked over my shoulder,
and in the doorway was a...
like, a silhouette, just all black,
standing in the doorway.
I stared at it for about five seconds.
The eyes were clear.
Everything else was black.
And, after five seconds,
I looked away, looked
back, and it was gone.
- That's when I was convinced.
- Okay.
So, have you experienced anything else?
Doors opening and closing.
I'd be downstairs,
and you would hear one of the
bedroom door's latch click.
And then, it would pause for a second.
Then, you'd hear it closed again.
And you can go up and press the doors,
and they're locked.
So, you've gone up to investigate?
- Absolutely.
- Okay.
Are you sure the kids ain't up there?
Positive.
Amy's gonna do her walk,
and she may say, "Listen,
you need to move from here."
How... How would you feel about that?
- I love the house.
- Right.
But I love my wife and kids a lot more.
This thing causes a lot of anxiety.
It's almost like, if the doors were closed,
this thing would,
like, run back and forth and,
like, slam into the door,
trying to get in.
They hear it.
It, like...
can go into people's bodies a little bit,
and it definitely takes
energy away from people.
And then, it... it makes them do things.
Like what?
Picks people for the
person to get angry at.
So it's not, like, a generalized anger.
It's specific.
Like, it plants very specific thoughts.
Like, "You're gonna get
angry at this person."
Somehow, it's associated with the house.
I see it, like, pulling things
from the past and eating it.
Jerrick, how old are you?
15.
So, I was talking to Mom and Phil.
Seems like things are pretty bad here.
Yeah, our attitudes change a lot.
I'll be just sitting down,
just having a great day.
And then, out of nowhere,
I'll just be angry
and just get angry at
the world for no reason.
And it's just... It's really weird.
Anything else?
I'm a firm believer that
there's three shadow figures
in this house... a taller one,
big, black, probably about
5'10" to, like, 6' tall,
and two shorter ones, more childlike.
Where do you see that?
You'll see it out of the
corner of your eye.
You'll see something,
like, smaller peeking around
the corner of the stairs at you.
I mean, how are you dealing with this?
I don't sleep well.
If something happens,
I'll either ignore it or...
I'm not usually really
quick to challenge it
because I don't like challenging things
that I can't fight back to,
- 'cause I can't see them.
- Anything else?
One time, I was sitting up in my room,
watching TV,
and something came over
and just slammed its hand down on my leg,
with more force than that.
What do you think is here?
I feel that whatever's in this house
doesn't really like people
who are devout Christians.
Whoo!
This thing does not
[bleep] like this person
and, like, is, like, choking them bad.
Like, holy [bleep]
Like, cannot breathe.
This is very focused, which is strange
because this thing doesn't
have one consciousness.
This person is somehow triggering something
in this thing
that's making it want to
kill this [bleep] person.
- So it could?
- Yeah.
I- I don't know how that hasn't happened.
Ooh, it's so bad.
This person's in trouble.
Phil and Amy don't have
a clue about the history
of their property,
so I reached out to
several local historians.
I just got a call back from a genealogist.
He tells me the original owners
of their land ended up broke,
alone, and insane.
Russ, you mentioned on the phone
that the original owners
of my clients' land
had a pretty tough time there
and that they actually went insane.
- Is that right?
- Yes, they did.
There were two gentlemen.
There was a prominent Pittsburgh
judge named Henry Baldwin.
And I have a picture of Baldwin here.
He inherited the property,
about 16,000 acres...
- Okay...
- in about 1807,
but he didn't want to come to Delaware.
So he hired Moses Bixby
to manage the property.
He was a local businessman
in the Delaware area.
A year later,
Henry Baldwin sold Bixby the land.
How does it go for him?
In 1816, his daughter Lucy
dies of unknown causes at the age of 27.
1821, his wife, also named Lucy...
She dies at the age of 61.
Okay.
So Bixby suffered a lot
during his time there.
But you said the two
original owners went insane.
Who went crazy first... Bixby or Baldwin?
Baldwin.
Actually,
he was appointed to Congress in 1822.
Shortly after taking his seat,
he steps down because of mental illness.
He ends up coming back to Delaware,
and he's wanting his property back.
The property that he sold to Bixby?
- Correct, yes.
- All right.
So, what does he do?
He ends up taking Bixby to court.
Bixby does win the case
because Baldwin did sell him the property.
Even though Bixby won the case,
it took a big toll on him.
Later on that year, he is declared insane,
and the state legislature
appoints guardians to keep him.
Here's an article to that effect.
Okay. So now, he's being watched
by these state guardians.
- How does it go?
- It doesn't go well.
Two years later, in 1826,
Bixby escapes the house
and runs into the Olentangy River,
and he dies a few days later of pneumonia.
And here's his obit.
All right. So, we see
how it ends for Bixby.
What about Baldwin?
It doesn't go well for him either.
He ends up dying penniless and alone
in a hotel in Philadelphia.
I think this thing makes people act funny.
So, what is this thing exactly?
It's from the house.
Over time, the house collected
all of these energies
from people.
Maybe the land was bad.
And then, this, you know,
collected that negative
energy from living people.
And then, the house, like,
spit out this, like, entity.
Like, almost like PK?
Something like that.
PK or entities created by
psychokinesis are very powerful
and can physically
influence their environment.
What's freaking me out about this one
is that it was created by the
house instead of a person,
and that's something
I've never seen before.
It's definitely getting stronger, um,
so that makes me concerned.
So far, I've got clients
that have been physically
assaulted by unseen forces
and two former property
owners who went insane.
But I've still got to see
if there's anything else
that could help my case.
Searching through old records,
I find a woman
who killed her husband
during a forced baptism
right next to Amy and Phil's property.
Heading over to meet with a local pastor
who agreed to look into this case for me.
Jason, thanks for meeting me.
I appreciate it. In all my time
on the police department
and working homicides,
I never had a case involving
a murder with baptism.
And the reason I'm interested in his death
is because it happened right
near my client's property.
So, what do you know about this guy?
William McCoy.
He joined the National Guard
right before World War I,
so it'd be 1917.
He ended up going to Europe and serving.
And while he was there,
his battalion,
or his squad,
got bombed by the Germans with gas.
And he ended up having to come back.
He was honorably discharged,
and because of the damage to his lungs,
tuberculosis sets in.
Okay. So, what happens?
He ends up actually meeting a lady,
Bertha Wilson.
This is Bertha.
And I guess they fell in love,
and they get married.
By 1925, McCoy's lungs
have deteriorated so badly
that he's being treated at
this hospital in Dayton,
and they basically send him home to die.
Okay.
And they send him, basically,
to his foster parents' house
here in Delaware.
They called in a local Grace
Methodist Episcopal pastor
to baptize him,
but he does it by pouring or sprinkling.
Bertha demands a different type of baptism.
The only way in her eyes
that he could truly know that
his soul was gonna be saved
is if he was immersed in full baptism.
She calls in this Reverend Pennell.
They pull him off of his deathbed
and immerse him in the water.
He died very soon after the immersion.
Okay.
This is his death certificate.
Now, was she ever officially charged?
No.
There's never charges filed.
Mainly, the sheriff and so forth said,
"Hey, he was gonna die in hours,
or days at the most."
Now, how did this sit
with the foster parents?
Well, I mean, they were opposed to it.
They were opposed to the immersion.
They... They didn't want that to happen.
I'm seeing the angry young woman again.
She told me it was 1910, 1915, and 1925...
were very important years for her.
She and the mother-in-law... You know,
they had issues.
They butted heads.
The daughter-in-law didn't
want to be here anymore,
and she didn't want to live that life.
I think she did, you know,
some pretty bad stuff.
She's blaming the land for her actions
and how she became.
Maybe that the land brings
out the worst in people
is kind of, I think,
what she's trying to say.
So, yeah, I think it's her husband,
and I think...
I think she killed him.
I never know how wide Amy will open,
so I look into the property and
the surrounding neighborhood.
Now, during my research,
one thing caught my eye...
a teenage kid who brutally
murdered his girlfriend
right near Amy and Phil's property.
I'm heading over to meet with
a Delaware police captain
who said that killer is now a free man.
So, Captain, the reason
I asked you to help me out is,
I found that article about
a homicide back in '53.
Involved a young girl, uh,
who was murdered less than a mile
from my clients' property.
What do you know about the
victim in the case itself?
Well, she was a former
Ohio Wesleyan student.
Her name was Cynthia Pfeil,
and she was 18 years old.
Okay.
The gentleman that
murdered her and was convicted
of her murder was a gentleman
by the name of Roy Schinagle.
What was their relationship?
They had, uh,
dated for approximately two years.
So, how does the murder take place?
- What happens?
- Well, what we know is,
on September 16, 1953,
Cynthia's lifeless body was found along
"a lonely road,"
I believe, is the way it was referred to.
Okay.
Her body showed that she had
been strangled or choked.
Her face had been
bludgeoned to such an extent
that she was unrecognizable.
Wow.
He, uh, confessed to the crime,
that he had choked her
and also bludgeoned her.
So, was she choked to death,
and then he beats her?
I mean, do we have any idea what happened?
We really don't know for sure,
but it's been surmised
that he possibly bludgeoned
her at that point
to prevent her from being recognized.
And we don't know what the motive was?
Right.
It was reported that Roy
and her had an argument.
I believe he's quoted
as referring to it as a
"silly little thing"
they argued over.
All right. So, now, what happens?
He gives the confession.
He was indicted for a
first-degree murder trial
and found guilty of second-degree murder
on October 24, 1953.
He served 10 years and was paroled.
That's extraordinary
how quick that happened.
Yes.
Mr. Schinagle is... is alive.
He's 81 years old,
and he's still living somewhere in...
in the state.
Something happened.
Um... I don't know.
I just see some chick getting beat up.
Mm.
She's just getting hit in the head.
The brunette...
The brunette gets knocked down.
She blacked out.
Doesn't even know what
[bleep] hit her, you know?
But, like, there's a male.
She knows this guy. She knows this guy.
I don't know how old they are.
I don't know.
Probably between [bleep]
I don't know, 17 to 20s.
- I don't know.
- Okay.
Feeling choked.
Like, pressure on my neck.
I hear a male voice saying,
"I'm gonna make you pay."
And then, I hear "[bleep]"
Oh, my God.
During my walk,
I saw a dead young woman
who was extremely angry.
I'm meeting with a sketch artist
to describe how she appeared in life.
She's probably about 17 years old.
Her eyes are deep-set,
and she has pretty thick eyebrows.
Next, I described a living person
being attacked by this thing.
It looks like it came out of a swamp.
It was, like,
putting its hand over the person's face.
And it was putting the other hand,
like, here.
Is this what you saw?
Yes, that's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our findings
to each other and our
clients for the first time.
Amy, I want you to meet Phil and Amy.
They're newlyweds,
but their life's been anything
but a honeymoon.
Now, Amy moved in here
about four months ago
with her two kids.
And this is a photo of
the whole family here.
- This is Jerrick, who's 15...
- Oh. Okay.
And Matthias, who is 10.
The weird thing is that until
Amy moved in here with the kids,
the place was relatively quiet.
And then, all hell broke loose.
Amy's very religious,
and her priorities in
life are God and her kids,
but she doesn't think
either one of those things
are welcome here.
So, now that Amy knows a little
bit about your family dynamics,
I'm gonna ask her to
tell us about her walk.
So, the first person that I met
was a female who was telling me
how she felt like this was
hell for her to be here.
She looked nice.
A very well-dressed, uh,
attractive woman, young.
Her husband made her come here,
and it was all, like, dirt.
Her mother-in-law was here,
and they did not get along.
The younger lady
was talking about how she was really pissed
that her husband brought her here,
that she couldn't be fancy anymore.
And then, she was saying how she was gonna,
uh, give him a taste of his own medicine.
I kind of thought that
maybe she killed him.
She gave me three very specific years...
1910, 1915, and 1925.
She said that these were
very important years for her.
I got an idea who you
might be talking about.
Now, you said the young woman
mentioned 1910, 1915, 1925.
Yes. Well,
I don't know anything about 1910 or 1915,
but 1925 is definitely significant.
That year, an incredibly strange death
took place next to your property.
In the early 1920s,
a woman from here named Bertha Wilson
married a World War I vet,
this guy, William McCoy.
McCoy winded up getting gassed
by the Germans in World War I
and developed TB from it.
In 1925, his condition got really bad.
He was sent home to basically die,
and he was sent home to his foster parents,
who lived right next door.
Because he only had days to live,
his parents
had a Methodist minister come
in and do a baptism for him...
what they call a sprinkling.
But Bertha,
she wanted her husband to be
baptized in a full submersion.
Problem was,
his foster parents were against that
because his health was so bad.
Despite the arguing between
Bertha and McCoy's parents,
on April 9, 1925,
she hired a minister to come
in and perform this baptism.
And within minutes after him
going into this tub of water,
he dies.
Now, according to the death certificate,
they say he dies from tuberculosis.
Now, I got a newspaper article here
that shows there was a coroner's inquest,
and they put the blame on
Bertha and the minister.
Bertha was never charged.
I guess they were thinking
he was gonna die anyway,
but they never charge her.
I've got a photo of her.
This is her. This is Bertha Wilson.
Huh.
Is it possible that might
be the woman you saw?
Well, I-I did have a sketch done of her.
Looks like her.
Mm-hmm. You can definitely...
Even the eyebrows and everything
kind of looks the same.
The brows, definitely.
So, this lady's in my house.
Yes.
Is it possible she's doing bad things now?
Yeah.
Well, she kept showing me horrible things
she did throughout her life.
She was a sociopath.
Anything else?
Then, I went into the basement,
and there were these two people
that ran past me down the stairs.
And finally, when I got down in there,
I saw the group of people that were,
like, hunched down.
As far as the living picking
up on this would be, you know,
these transient feelings of extreme fear,
uh, panic,
or anxiety.
You hate the basement.
Mm-hmm.
When I go down there,
I don't ever feel like I'm alone.
I feel like there's someone watching.
Did you say something before about...
At the top of the stairs,
people went past you?
- Yeah.
- Tell Amy what happened.
I was going down the stairs
and went flying completely down the stairs,
felt like I was bumped or pushed...
- Okay...
- and landed up against the wall,
and I laid there and
screamed for several minutes.
Now, with all the stuff that's
going on in the basement,
could that have caused her fall?
Actually, I think it could be the woman.
I just feel like it's something
she would be capable of.
It explains a lot of things.
See, what I don't get is,
you're very devout. Right.
This woman, in my opinion,
was a zealot, but...
I don't think that she was a good person.
It actually scares me
'cause I don't know what
else she's capable of doing.
Is she gonna start targeting my kids?
So, what else happened?
Did you stay in the basement?
No.
So, I went upstairs,
and actually, everything kind of changed.
It was not good.
There was this very bizarre
thing that I was seeing.
This thing is very physical.
One of the things I saw it doing
was moving very quickly in the hallway area
and, uh, touch on the doors,
you know, bang them.
I think that people would hear this.
It looked like it came out of a swamp
because, like,
things were hanging off of it.
It's very dark.
Um, you know, it has, like,
a head and arms and stuff,
but it's, like, different.
Well, Amy and her son Jerrick
see this shadow figure all the time.
And it does move in the hallway,
back and forth,
back and forth, back and forth.
Do you ever hear the banging on the door?
Yes. Our doors will slam.
We'll hear doorknobs rattle,
and I've seen it standing
beside my bed at night
almost, like, towering over me.
And you saw the same thing?
Yeah. I just saw...
It was just jet black.
But what scared me the most
is, you can see right through its eyes.
- Oh.
- Distinctive.
And what else can this thing do?
What I saw in the smaller bedroom,
so I'm assuming your
younger son's bedroom.
Mm-hmm.
When he's asleep
is when it has its interactions with him.
And it was putting its hand into his face.
He won't sleep in his room.
He is scared to death of his room.
Matthias is autistic, as well.
Unfortunately,
the influence of this thing is,
people being prone to anger and rage,
bursts of it.
So it'll pick a person, uh,
for you to get angry at.
You bicker now like you never did before.
- Right.
- Unfortunately, yeah.
We love each other a lot,
but we have arguments about things
that never would have
become an argument before.
Jerrick's mood has changed, right?
His personality a little bit?
He has less of a tolerance.
With his brother being autistic,
he's quick to get more irritable with him.
Okay.
Interesting.
One incident that I saw in the main...
the master bedroom,
uh, was of an encounter with a female.
I feel her neck hurts.
Like, her spine in her neck, you know?
Then, it, like, slams her.
Tell her what happened.
One second, I was writing.
The next second, I wake up on the floor.
I had been unconscious.
I had hit my head and
sustained a concussion.
But where I landed was so far
away from where I was sitting
that it wasn't like I simply passed out
and fell out of my chair.
And they did have to put
me in a cervical collar.
I was up in the air about
it being paranormal.
Yeah, I don't think you believed it.
Is that something this thing could do?
Oh, yeah. I think so, yeah.
The place where it made me really,
really nervous
was in the middle bedroom.
That's Jerrick's room.
What I felt was, like,
a hand around your throat.
It was, like, a pressure, like, on my neck
and then a pressure, like, on my chest.
I did have a sketch done of that.
Ah, geez.
I'm sorry.
I did have a sketch done of that.
Ah, geez.
I'm sorry.
Okay. Sorry.
No, don't be sorry. It's your son.
Has he ever relayed that
kind of feeling to you?
He wakes up feeling awful almost every day.
He did convey to me,
when I interviewed him that,
uh, he was sitting on the bed,
watching TV.
And it felt like a man's hand
had slapped him right across the thigh.
That would be similar...
along the lines of...
of what this thing can do.
I don't want that to happen to Jerrick.
I don't want it to happen
to anybody in this house,
but I didn't expect to
see something like that.
What does this thing want?
It has a real disdain for your son.
It definitely wants to harm him...
without a doubt.
Amy, remember when you told
me that whatever is here
is evil and doesn't want
you or the kids here?
- Yes.
- Well, unfortunately,
you were right.
Now, the big question is,
can you get rid of this thing,
protect your kids,
and live the life that you guys
want to live here as a family?
So, for that answer,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
Well, this case is cause for concern.
So, basically,
what we have is an
environment that has created
a semi-functioning PK manifestation.
What it did, seemingly,
was, over time,
the house absorbed personalities,
situations, memories,
things that it witnessed
and then, eventually, spit out an entity.
Now, usually, PKs are formed by people.
This is the first time I've
seen one formed by a house.
And the reason it's become so active
since you've moved in is your son.
I believe he has PK abilities.
I think that, because there was already
a semi-functioning PK manifestation here
and he came in,
it was the perfect storm.
And I think that he really needs help.
I knew something bad was going on here.
I knew something did not want us here.
Well, the problem is that there's not a lot
that can be done about this.
But if you take him away
from this location,
any attacks would cease.
But this thing will still exist here,
which is unfortunate.
But in the interim,
- Jerrick's not safe.
- No.
And you guys aren't safe.
Honestly, I would leave.
When a PK is formed by people,
there are things they can
do to protect themselves.
But, in this case,
when it's formed by the house,
there are only two options...
tear it down or get out.
I've already been assaulted twice, I feel.
And seeing what's happened to my son,
they're both gonna be sleeping with me
until we can figure out
a way to get out of here.
That's gonna be something
that we'll have to talk about.
No.
I'm their mom. My job's to protect them.
It's just not a chance I'm willing to take.
- Okay.
- It's just the way it is.
So, it sounds like your wife
already made up her mind.
Yeah. It's a shock.
We knew something was going on...
- Right...
- but not to this extent.
Yeah. We'll be... We'll be leaving.
Okay.
It breaks my heart
to tell Amy and Phil
that I believe they
should leave their home.
But if they don't, I fear this house
and the PK manifestation it's created
could put them and their
children in serious danger.