Yeah, they definitely
feel pain with this guy.
Come on.
It came at me so fast,
and then, like, swoosh.
There's times when she
really loses her [bleep]
Someone probably shot him.
Shot him twice. Killed him.
Oh. Somebody dies.
I tell my kids everything's fine.
But I'm not sure if I'm
telling them the truth.
They want to kill someone.
They want to kill him.
Something bad's going to happen.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's panic.
And it's almost like a butchering.
I see dead people.
They all died horribly.
I speak to dead people.
Get out of here.
And they speak to me.
Vicious.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
It doesn't matter where you are.
I'll find you.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
This guy's a real piece of work.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I feel like I live in a house of Hell.
It's my job to reveal them.
This is not good.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end...
I want my life back.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Is he trying to kill her?
Or time to get out.
Oh, my God.
This is going to kill us.
I'm out here in Albuquerque,
New Mexico.
I got called in by a woman
who sounded pretty damn
scared on the phone.
She says she's about to
take over a restaurant
that's been in her family for 40 years.
But the activity is so bad
she doesn't know if it's safe
for her and her children to be there.
She says, if Amy and I can't help her out,
she may have to close the place up.
Before Amy arrives,
I need to clear the restaurant
of anything that might
influence her findings.
Artwork, photographs
and religious icons need
to be covered or removed.
When I'm finished,
the location will be
ready for tonight's walk.
Okay.
Before I got here, I saw this location.
And there was, like, nothing,
you know, like, no buildings.
It was all, like, just land and black.
This thing, uh, came up to me.
And it pointed to the ground.
And then, I saw water trickling.
And then, the water all of a
sudden was flowing with blood.
So, Carla, I'm glad I'm here
'cause, when we spoke on the phone,
you sounded scared.
Right.
Okay. So give me a rundown
of what's going on.
We've got people hearing noises,
objects moving,
electrical problems, apparitions.
And people are being touched.
This business has been in
my family for 40 years.
I'm taking over.
My dad, this is his life's work.
And it's part of the family.
It's my whole life.
But I also want to protect my children.
I tell my kids that there's
nothing to be scared of,
everything's fine.
I'm not sure if I'm telling them the truth.
Okay. So, now, who exactly works here?
There's all of us. That's my mom. She's 82.
That's my son. He's 16.
That's me. That's my dad. He's 84.
And that's my daughter. She's 13.
My daughter particularly
has increased my concern.
She's so genuinely frightened.
Now, have you lost any, uh, staff
- because of what's going on here?
- I have.
And I've had to change
people's schedules also who...
They'll, like, refuse to close
or be alone in the restaurant at night.
I mean, I don't like to be in
here alone at night either.
I mean, how are you managing,
never mind everybody else?
What about you?
There's just days I don't want to come in.
Sometimes, I get really anxious,
particularly when I'm at work.
Now, is that something you
experience away from here?
No.
What are you hoping we can do for you?
I want you to tell me that I can stay here
and I can honor my dad's life's work
and I can be the good
daughter and the good mom.
There's a lot going on.
I mean, a lot of residual...
There's a lot of men, pandemonium.
They're drinking and partying.
They're getting crazy.
Do you think it would
affect the living here?
Oh, I think that they
would feel, uh, dizzy.
It's crowded. You feel this,
feeling claustrophobic, you know?
Very unsettled.
Uh, your stomach kind of does flip-flops
just because of all of this crazy,
uh, energy.
So, why'd you bring me behind the bar here?
This is where I feel something
breathing on my neck.
What part of your neck do you feel it on?
- Is it always on the same part?
- Mmhmm.
- That side.
- Okay.
So it's enough where it's...
it's gonna go through your hair.
- Mm-hmm.
- Really?
- Right.
- Okay.
Now, how often does this happen to you?
At least once a month.
And when it's happening,
it seems like it's forever.
Huh. Not like you got...
No vents.
Any other physical things happen here?
So my back bothers me more
here than anyplace else.
Now, what makes you think
this is paranormal?
I can have had several
days of no back pain at all
and get here and have my back start to...
to feel badly.
What if Amy tells you,
"It's not safe for you to stay here.
You really need to go"?
I feel very committed
and responsible to keeping
the business running.
But I wouldn't want my
kids to ever be harmed.
Right. And so you're kind of
stuck right in the middle.
Always.
Somebody got stabbed to death.
You know, this is, like, his area.
Oh, he doesn't feel very, very good.
It's a lot of pain.
I think that people would
have physical pain
associated with being around him,
so, like, sudden lower-back issues,
acute stomach pain.
Like, you'd be like, "Oh,"
you know, like, [bleep]
He acts out when he's depressed. Ow.
Yeah, they definitely feel
[bleep] pain with this guy.
Come on.
So, Edie, I'm really glad I
got a chance to talk to you
'cause your mom's most concerned about you.
- Yeah.
- Are you scared to be here?
Whenever I'm here, I can never just relax.
I'm always, "Was that just a shadow?"
One night, close to midnight almost,
I was just sitting in the dining
room playing a video game.
And then, all of a sudden,
I heard, like, a woman cry,
like a woman crying out in agony and pain.
Any idea how old the woman that was moaning
might have been?
Maybe kind of middle-aged.
Was anybody else in the building?
My mom was in the kitchen
closing up the back door.
Okay. Do you know if this door was locked?
Yeah.
That's strange.
Now, is anything else going on?
Well,
the scariest thing that has happened to me
is I actually got trapped in the bathroom.
- This bathroom here.
- Right there.
I go in there. I use the bathroom.
I wash my hands. I dry my hands.
Then, I try to open up the door.
And it was almost as if somebody
was pushing the door shut
as I was trying to open it.
You... you don't think
it was somebody playing
- a game on you, do you?
- No, not at all.
- How'd you get out of there?
- I kicked the door.
So, ever since then,
you've been pretty frightened
to death of this place.
Yeah. I refuse to go to the bathroom alone
at night anymore.
Okay. All right.
So, sweetie, it sounds
like you and your mom
have a pretty close relationship.
Oh, yeah. We're really close.
I'm curious how you feel about
her being here alone at night.
I don't know if something
would come actually at her.
I just don't want anything
to happen to her.
I feel anxious back here.
I just hear, like, a... a male.
He's like, "Ha ha, you stupid [bleep]"
Like, "That'll teach ya."
He seems like a stocky fella.
Kind of making me sick.
And he's got some guy,
drops him on the floor.
And he's, like, kicking him.
This guy killed this dude.
Lots of anxiety, too,
that they would feel back here,
like, heart racing.
Something is with the doors.
He's trying to keep the door closed
'cause he's always like,
"Close the [bleep] door."
He's a problem.
Obviously, he was prone to violence.
He killed someone.
He could be physically
violent towards the living.
The reason your mom called us in
is because of the fact
that she's worried about
you and your sister.
It's a family-owned business.
I mean, grandparents have
had it for over 40 years.
She eventually wants you guys to take over.
How do you feel about that?
The business has been around for 40 years.
And I'd love to keep it
around for another 40.
But I don't feel comfortable
running a business
in a building that's potentially haunted
with entities that could harm people.
Okay. Well, let me ask
you a question, then.
Are you afraid to be here?
Yes, especially at night.
That's when I'm most afraid to be here.
Okay. So, what experiences
have you had, Charley?
So I've had two experiences.
Throughout that door, into the Santos Room,
I saw a cowboy sitting at
the last seat of the bar.
And he's in a brown trench coat.
And he has, like, a cowboy hat on.
He's drinking a beer.
And I thought that was really strange
because it was, like, 8:00 in the morning.
The restaurant wasn't open yet.
And when I got through to the other side
and I looked through
the bar and the gallery,
there was nobody there.
Okay. So, it just disappeared?
Yes, it just disappeared.
You said there were two things.
What was the second one?
The second one actually
happened right behind us.
I was going through that doorway.
And as I passed through the hallway,
I looked through the
double doors to the window.
And I saw a woman floating there.
But she had no arms and no legs.
Her hair was down.
How long would you say her hair was?
Uh, it was probably about,
uh, 2... 2 feet long,
kind of down to a little
bit past her shoulders.
Did you think you were seeing things?
Basically, I had, like, an anxiety attack.
And I was crying and
traumatized, basically.
There's, like, this little woman here,
probably in her 40s.
She's chubby, short.
She's a busybody.
She seems really, um,
new to this whole thing,
like, being dead.
She's trying to interact
with this male and female.
But she says,
"They're not hearing, you know,
they're not hearing me."
She's not seeing a reaction.
Mm-hmm.
Or, at least, the reaction she wants.
So, Shirley, I was talking
to your daughter.
And, uh,
she was explaining of some of the problems
that are going on in the restaurant.
Honestly, I'm... I worry about it.
And I'm concerned about it.
Particularly, I think Edie, she is scared.
I don't want her to be afraid.
And I don't want my daughter to be afraid,
you know?
Right.
My partner, when she does these cases,
and then, at the end,
sometimes, she'll tell them,
"Listen,
you need to get the hell out of here
or close your business."
How would you feel about
something like that?
Would not want to do it.
This is the legacy for my family,
what my husband and I have
built all these many years.
And, uh, I want it for my
daughter and my grandchildren.
I would not want to go.
In the 40 years you've been here,
have you had any experiences?
Well, actually, the first 32 years,
I really didn't have any
personal experiences.
But about eight years ago, I did, yes.
Okay. So, what happened?
Late one night, I opened up that door.
The minute I stepped into this room,
a ghost lady came... I was standing there.
She came from this side of the room...
Okay.
At me so fast, and then,
like, swoosh, right passing through me.
I turned totally, totally cold,
totally, totally cold.
Can you describe her at all?
- I would say small.
- Small.
- Small, yes.
- Okay.
Was that the only experience
that you actually had here?
Uh, no.
We actually had something
strange happening in here
with the lights.
Maybe two or three of them
would just be flickering, flickering.
So I had two different electricians come.
So, what did the
electricians wind up saying?
Neither company that ever
came out ever found anything.
That little woman, she is very frustrated.
She's very angry with them
when they're not talking to her
or listening to her or whatever, you know?
She gets real worked up.
And then, I see her hair,
uh, get all, like, crazy.
Uh, so she's, like,
whipping around in a circle
and freaking out.
I think, that at those times,
maybe the living might have
some electrical issues.
And the living might notice that.
I think this is where the
little lady is mostly.
She's, like, bopping around, you know,
and, like, just in everybody's [bleep]
And I do see her getting in a rage.
Ooh, she's not happy.
She's kind of having a mental breakdown.
I didn't think it
would be hard to find history
on Carla's restaurant.
I mean, after all,
it sits right in the middle of Old Town.
Turns out, it was easier than I thought.
The first historian I reached out to
said that one of the early
owners of the property
suffered through years of debt,
regret and betrayal.
So, Julia, you mentioned on the phone
one of the first owners of the property
I'm investigating had a
lot of heartache there.
What'd you mean by that?
- Carlos and Felicitas Vigil
were married in 1910... - Okay.
And moved into the property in 1920.
She was pregnant with her third child
when they moved into the property.
About five months after they moved in,
their youngest, a little boy named Willie,
he passed away.
Okay. What was the cause?
Gastritis.
How'd it go for them after that?
Ernesto was born.
But he did pass away as well.
He was 1 year, 1 month old.
He had an infection that was
caused from bottle feeding.
And he passed away in 1922.
However, Felicitas becomes pregnant again.
Her name was Frances.
But Frances was only 2 months old
when she passed away.
Geez.
She died in April of 1924
of a bronchial pneumonia.
I'm afraid to even ask.
Did they have any more kids?
They did.
This time, the baby was stillborn.
Felicitas was so devastated
she couldn't even bring
herself to name the child.
I mean, just losing one child
alone has got to destroy you.
Destroy you.
She lost four.
Four in a row.
Not very long after the stillborn, um,
Carlos actually became ill.
And what was his problem?
Syphilis.
Turns out, Carlos was unfaithful.
Ah, so now I know what you meant
when you said about betrayal.
She actually had him committed
to the New Mexico Hospital for the Insane
until he passes away in 1927.
And when he died,
she did not claim his body.
Does she stay? Does she
decide to move away?
No, she stays.
She does, uh, start to become quite ill.
And eventually, she does have a stroke.
And she died in January of 1959.
Okay. So now, she dies in '59.
What happens to the property?
She left the property to
her surviving children.
Uh, they kept it for a few years.
But then, they sold the property.
15 years after Felicitas died,
the building became the High
Noon Restaurant and Saloon.
This angry woman,
she died fairly recently, I think,
maybe, like, a sudden heart attack
or something along those lines.
Do you know how old she was?
Uh, she looks, mm, maybe 50s or 60s.
And she's, like,
being very obsessed with her family.
Yeah, she's feeling more grateful about the
decision to do with her family in this building,
maybe leaving it to them or something.
Like, I am seeing a For Sale sign.
Mm, she's not happy.
I've already uncovered five people
who died on my client's property,
four of them children.
But I need to see if there's anything else
that can help my case.
Searching through old records,
I find a 16-year-old
who was fatally stabbed.
Turns out, he lived right across the street
from Carla's restaurant.
I need to find out a lot more
about this brutal attack
on the 16-year-old kid.
And when I want to know about a homicide,
I reach out to the cops.
I'm heading over to meet
with a local police officer
who's looking into this case for me.
Well, Officer Tixier,
thanks so much for helping me out
with this case. I appreciate it.
- My pleasure.
- So, can you do me a favor?
Before we get to the murder
of this 16-year-old kid,
what do you know about the family?
Luis Moya moved his family
onto your client's property in 1941.
And then, just a short time,
five years later,
he moves his family off
your client's property
but just directly across the street.
So, they're in the immediate area
when this homicide happens?
- Yes, sir.
- Okay.
So take me through the homicide.
So, uh, Luis Moya has a son, Freddy Moya.
Him and his friend,
they walk down the street
to a New Year's Eve party
that was being held at the armory,
basically to ring in 1951 into '52.
As they walk into the party,
they kind of separate, go their own ways.
And as the night is progressing,
a group of about 10 to 13 individuals
from the Atrisco street
gang come into the party.
And I can see where this is going already.
One of those people was Paul Garcia.
Okay.
Details are sketchy about
what exactly transpired between the two.
But what we do know is that
a lot of witnesses saw a commotion
between Paul Garcia and Freddy Moya.
Okay.
And then, they saw Freddy turn pale.
They take him out of the armory.
And that's when they realized
that he had been stabbed
pretty severely twice,
once in the back and
then once in his chest.
And that chest wound
actually severed his aorta.
- So he bled out.
- Bled out almost immediately.
Okay.
Paul Garcia confessed,
was found guilty and did 15 years for it.
Okay.
What a way to bring in the
new year for a family, huh?
Yes, sir.
I'm seeing a lot of fighting.
The guy who's got stabbed, he's back here.
Frankie, Frank.
I'm seeing the guy who got stabbed again.
But this time, he's making me
experience his painful death.
Really bad, too.
He got stabbed in the front and the back.
I'm just feeling it.
I think he feels betrayed and,
like, got murdered.
You know,
another thing stood out in my research.
The local town marshal
was hanged just down the
street from Carla's restaurant.
Now, you don't hear about law enforcement
getting the death penalty very often.
So I called a local author
who said Milton Yarberry was so hated
people lined the streets
to cheer his execution.
So, Johnny,
this story's pretty interesting to me.
So there was a town marshal
that was actually hanged
right down the block
from my client's property.
Milton Yarberry.
He's born in 1849 in Arkansas,
joins an outlaw gang,
kills a couple men in Arkansas.
And that's gonna send him
fleeing Arkansas into Texas.
Okay. So he's got a couple
murders under his belt already.
By 1879, at least four.
Wow. How does a guy
that's got at least four
bodies under his belt
wind up in Albuquerque and as a marshal?
He arrives in Albuquerque in 1880.
He's traveling with a woman named Sadie
and her 4-year-old daughter.
When he arrives here,
he's gonna befriend Perfecto Armijo,
who is the county sheriff.
Perfecto gets Yarberry the job
as Albuquerque's first town marshal.
He apparently liked the way
Yarberry knew his way around guns.
And this is Yarberry here.
That's Yarberry.
Looks like a tough piece of work.
Yeah, he does.
So, this guy doesn't know
anything about his background?
- No.
- Geez.
So now you got a killer with a badge.
How does this work out for the town?
In 1881, Sadie,
the woman he came to town with,
is apparently seeing another man,
Harry Brown.
So Yarberry comes to talk to Harry Brown.
I'm assuming he probably shot him.
Shot him twice. Killed him.
And Perfecto Armijo has
to arrest his friend.
What happens with Brown?
Well, during the trial,
it's brought out that Brown had a gun.
Yarberry pleads self-defense.
And the jury acquits him.
Within a few weeks,
he's back on the job as the town marshal.
But a few weeks after that shooting,
there's another one.
And that one's gonna get
Yarberry in serious trouble.
He's investigating a shot
that's been heard fired in town.
He sees a man running down the street.
He yells stop.
When the man doesn't stop,
Yarberry shoots him.
Again, the charge is murder.
And this time, it takes the jury 10 minutes
to find him guilty.
And Milton Yarberry is sentenced to hang.
2,000 people showed up.
They are lining the streets.
They are heckling.
They are booing him.
I'm hearing a lot of men yelling.
Uh, I think they're angry.
Um...
it seems like there's something
big happening, going down.
And they're, like, on top of buildings.
But they...
but the buildings kind of look different.
Somebody did something.
They want to kill him.
They're walking this
man through the streets.
And he did something very bad.
It's like he's on parade or something.
It was a circus.
In fact, I found this article.
Local businesses were selling tickets.
For a dollar,
you could go up to the rooftop.
So it's likely that the
business you're investigating,
people were up on that roof
watching the execution.
Wow.
But it doesn't go as planned.
Armijo found in a journal
this new method of hanging somebody.
It's called the jerk method.
And it's supposed to be a more humane way
of executing somebody.
But when he's jerked up,
his head hits the crossbeam,
and his skull is crushed.
This execution is so botched
they can't get the noose off his neck.
So he's buried with the rope still on him.
Wow.
He's white.
He's well-known.
I don't know if he was, like,
maybe some kind of lawman
or some [bleep]
He says that sometimes,
he wasn't always a lawman.
So, what the [bleep] was done to him?
But I don't know.
I think the guy gets hanged.
I saw several dead people during my walk.
But two stood out the most.
First, the killer I saw in the kitchen.
He is late 30s maybe.
He had a very Italian-looking nose.
And his eyes were closer
together than normal.
Next, I described the angry woman
trying to get the living's attention.
She was, like,
grabbing his arm, shaking him.
She has really long, black hair.
And when she gets mad,
it's kind of, like, whipping around.
Is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our findings
to each other and our
clients for the first time.
Now, Amy, in 1974,
Shirley and her husband
opened this restaurant.
It took a lot of blood, sweat and tears.
But it became a success.
Recently, they turned the High Noon over
to their daughter, Carla.
And that's kind of when
the trouble started.
Activity's gotten physical.
And Carla's two kids are
pretty scared to be here.
This is actually a photo of the two kids.
This is Charley, who's 16.
And this is Edie, who's 13.
Now, Carla's in a tough spot.
She wants to honor the family legacy
and keep the restaurant going.
But she's also a worried mom.
And she doesn't want to stay here
if it's not safe for her kids.
So now that Amy knows a little
bit about what's going on,
I'm gonna ask her to
tell us about her walk.
When I first got here,
there was this commotion going on outside.
Uh, there were a lot of men.
And they were yelling and screaming
and just kind of going nuts.
A lot of them were on the rooftops.
Then, I noticed a group of men
kind of walking down the street.
In the center of all of these men
was this one man that they
were kind of manhandling.
They hated him and wanted to kill him.
And then, I believe that he was hanged.
Wow.
I didn't really have to think
about this one too long.
There was a guy in 1883 by
the name of Milton Yarberry,
who was hanged just down the block here.
Okay.
Milton was born in Arkansas in 1849.
He started a life of crime pretty young.
By the time he got to Albuquerque in 1880,
he had already killed four men.
I actually managed to
track down a photo of him.
Wow.
Pretty intense-looking guy.
Now, somehow, this illiterate murderer
became friendly with the
local sheriff of Albuquerque.
He was Perfecto Armijo.
Perfecto made a bad decision
and made Yarberry Albuquerque's
first town marshal.
Now, Yarberry finds out that his girlfriend
was cheating on him with
this guy named Harry Brown.
So, how does he handle it?
Handles it with a gun.
Tracks him down.
And he shoots him, kills him.
He was tried for murder even
though he was the marshal.
But he was acquitted.
Now, you think he would lay
low after that happened.
He didn't.
Only a few weeks later,
he winds up, uh,
responding to a shots-fired-type call.
And he sees a guy, tells him to stop.
He's walking away.
And he shoots him three times
in the back and kills him.
He gets tried again.
This time,
he's found guilty and sentenced to hang.
Now, on February 9, 1883,
he was paraded through the
streets here in Old Town
on the way to the gallows.
Wow.
Now, you said people were drunk
and rowdy and stuff like that?
Oh, yeah.
Building owners here
wind up selling tickets
for $1 apiece for people
to actually watch the
hangings from the roof.
So, most likely, people
were cheering his execution
on your rooftop that day.
Wow.
Interesting.
So, uh, what else?
There's three different
conscious dead people here.
One of them was a female.
She was in her 40s.
I met her in the reception area.
What?
Continue talking. It's a...
Okay.
The other area that she
likes to hang out at
is that dining area.
She was short.
She had extremely long, beautiful hair.
And it was dark.
She was attempting to interact
with the living male and female,
trying to talk to them
and trying to grab them,
trying to shake them.
And she feels like they're not hearing her.
And she would get extremely upset.
When that would occur,
her hair would go up and get all crazy.
And this is how she's
expressing her frustration.
Now, the reason they
reacted the way they did
when you described her in that room
is a lot of people have seen this woman.
Lots of people.
I stepped into the dining
room very late one night.
And the minute I stepped into the room,
she just came rushing at me and went, like,
like, right through me.
I screamed. I really screamed.
Now, the funny thing is Charley,
your son, saw a similar thing.
Explain to Amy what Charley had seen.
He was walking down the back hallway
and just looked through the windows
and saw a figure, a woman in white...
- White. Hmm.
- ...in this room.
Okay.
So I had a sketch done of this woman.
And she was trying to,
um, get the attention of a particular male.
Oh, geez.
This is how she looked when you saw her?
That's upset, all right.
That's scary.
That's where I work mostly.
That's definitely the space
where so many people feel,
you know, a presence.
In my mind,
I was thinking she wanted me out of there.
She wanted me out of her space.
She wanted me out of her place.
Interesting. Okay.
Now, did you get any idea
who this woman might have been in life?
She knew that she was ill before she died.
But her actual death
came pretty sudden, uh,
something like a sudden heart attack.
She might have died recently.
She looked like she was in her 60s.
Um, there seemed to be
some issue with her family.
I did see a For Sale sign.
And she was absolutely unhappy about it.
I think that she regretted the decision
that she made about this location
and possibly leaving it to her children.
That's interesting.
That's really interesting.
There was a woman that
lived on the property here
that suffered a lot during her time here.
Felicity Vigil and her husband at the time,
Carlos,
bought this property in 1920.
After moving here, she lost four kids...
Whoa.
Within five years,
all under the age of 2.
Now, to make things worse for this woman,
her husband contracted syphilis.
Now, she didn't have it,
which only meant that he
had to be cheating on her.
But the disease damaged Carlos' brain.
And she had him committed to
the state mental hospital.
Now, he died in 1927.
I got his death certificate here.
She didn't even claim his body.
She just left it there.
Now, Amy, you mentioned this
woman suffered from a disease
and then died suddenly.
Felicitas suffered from high blood pressure
and caused her to have a stroke in 1959.
I have her death certificate here.
Now, she was here a long time, 39 years.
But she died on the property.
Now, you mentioned she had
regret about leaving this place
to her kids,
and that's exactly what she did.
She left it to her daughter and two sons.
- Okay.
- Now, just a few years
after they got the property after she died,
they sold it.
It's kind of sad when you think about that,
you know?
So she probably said, "Oh, look.
I'm leaving you this.
It's our legacy,"
kind of like the way your mother
and father are leaving you...
- Right.
- ...the restaurant, you know?
And... and here, her
kids just abandoned it.
It's sad. It's very sad.
Now, you said there were three dead people.
Who else did you see?
I encountered a male
who apparently was being
stabbed in the front
and then got him a couple
of times in the back.
I got the name Frank or Frankie with him.
He was indicating that he felt betrayed,
and he feels a lot of pain and depression.
So I felt like, around the bar area,
people would feel this kind of pain,
stomach pain,
lower-back pain.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
Tell Amy about that.
I get the back pain.
Okay.
You know,
I think I'm gonna be able to figure out
who this might be for
Amy and for you as well.
You said the name Frankie.
Yes.
The guy I'm gonna tell you about,
his name is Freddy Moya.
Now, Freddy was a kid who lived
on the property with his parents
from '41 to '46.
Then, they moved right across the street.
When Freddy was 16,
he went with a friend to
a New Year's Eve party
right down the street at the armory.
They were ringing in 1952.
Now, 13 gang members from
the Atrisco neighborhood
wind up coming into the party.
And, uh, Freddy was attacked
by one of the gang members.
He was stabbed several times
exactly where you said...
Oh, wow.
The chest and in the back.
Now, the stab wound in the
front is what killed him.
It was so bad it severed his aorta.
Then, five minutes after midnight,
he was pronounced dead.
Now, do you think this could
be the kid you ran into?
Yes.
Okay.
So we have the lady who died
and the stabbing victim.
But you said there was a third dead person.
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
- So, who was that?
The third dead person I ran
into was in the kitchen area.
And he's the one I'm most concerned about.
Immediately, I felt sick, uh, nauseous.
Um, I felt intense neck pain.
And then, I felt like hands
were on my neck squeezing.
I heard a male laughing and saying,
"You stupid [bleep] That'll teach ya."
I saw the image of one
man killing another man.
I got that he was stocky
and seemed to be in his 30s.
Because he was such a violent,
nasty person in life,
he could possibly, uh,
be violent and nasty in death.
The other thing...
He's kind of obsessed with doors.
He has to have the doors closed.
Talk about Edie with the bathroom incident.
Right. So my daughter went to the restroom.
And when she went to
open that bathroom door
to pull it open, she felt like
someone was pushing it shut
so that she couldn't leave.
It really, really scared her.
You get a good look at him?
I did. I had a sketch done.
We could put a face to maybe
some of the problems here.
He's a mean-looking guy.
I can tell you that.
Look at that.
Wait a second. Take a look at this guy.
Holy [bleep] take look at this.
Take a look at this photo.
Now take a look at this sketch.
Oh, my God.
- What do you think?
- Brows look very much alike.
You can see the resemblance, the wide nose,
the wide bridge nose.
This guy scares the crap out of me.
I had a sketch done.
We can put a face to maybe
some of the problems here.
He's a mean-looking guy.
I can tell you that.
Take a look at that.
Wow.
Wait a second. Take a look at this guy.
Holy [bleep] look at this.
Take a look at this photo.
Now take a look at this sketch.
Oh, my God.
- What do you think?
- Brows look very much alike.
You can see the resemblance, the wide nose,
the wide bridge nose.
This guy scares the crap out of me.
The sketch looks just like Yarberry,
the marshal who was hung.
Yeah. Look.
Look at the nose without the mustache.
Oh, God. His eyes are...
Right?
Now, when I laid down the
photo of Yarberry earlier,
did he look familiar to you?
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Big time.
Plus, the guy's a murder.
You said the guy was a mur...
Yeah, he is a murderer.
Died in his 30s.
He's 34 when he gets hung.
Now, I didn't mention this earlier
because I didn't think it was important.
But, um, you said the neck thing, right?
There was some kind of neck
pain that you were feeling?
Yes.
Well, he was hung by his neck, right?
Well, when they try to execute Yarberry,
it went terribly wrong.
They try to kill him using a
method called the jerk method.
And what it was,
was a system of ropes and pulleys.
And it failed.
It wind up launching his
body into the wooden beam
above the gallows and crushed his head.
Now, the rope was pulled
so tightly around his neck
they couldn't get it off.
So they had to cut it but leave
the noose intact on his neck
and buried him that way.
Oh, wow.
And he was hung just down the block here.
Well, Carla, now, we know why your kids
are so scared to be here alone.
But we haven't answered the big
question of can you stay here
and still carry on your family tradition
of having this restaurant
and one day turn it over to your kids?
Uh, for that answer,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
So what I would like you to do
is get a medium who is
also a psychotherapist.
That's your best bet.
Okay.
So the first day, when this person comes,
I would like them to speak with her,
basically giving her a session
where she can talk about
everything that went on in her life
and kind of process it.
The second day, I would like the person
to come back and assist
in her being moved on.
The third day, this person will come.
And they will initially work
with the stabbing victim.
They'll be giving that person a talking-to
and then go ahead and move the murderer on.
And on the fourth day,
the person can come back
and do a cleansing of the
building and the residual,
um, paying specific attention to that,
uh, room.
As long as you do all of these steps,
it's a huge possibility that you'll be okay.
You look a lot happier
than when I first met you.
I'm super relieved.
I entertained the thought
that maybe we were having a group delusion.
How do you feel now about
being able to tell your dad
that, "Hopefully,
I can do this for another 40 years"?
So relieved.
He built many things along the way.
But this is what remains.
And this is the part that I honor.
How does it feel to know that maybe,
one day,
that your grandson and granddaughter
may be running this place?
I would really love that.
I would feel complete in so many ways,
absolutely.
It won't be easy
removing the dead wreaking
havoc inside this restaurant.
But with the help of a
medium with special skills,
the evil here should be banished.
And Carla could keep the restaurant in
her family for generations to come.