She does not like children, whatsoever.
My son said he's seen the
floor covered with blood.
She gets him at night, for sure, for sure.
He stabs her 27 times with a screwdriver.
This guy really did a job on her.
She would torture the [bleep] out of them.
I want...
I want normalcy in our lives again.
People should not live here.
She just wants this person dead.
Something bad's going to happen.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's panic.
And it's almost like a butchering.
I see dead people.
They all died horribly.
I speak to dead people.
Get out of here.
And they speak to me.
Vicious.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
It doesn't matter where you are.
I'll find you.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
This guy's a real piece of work.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I feel like I live in a house of Hell.
It's my job to reveal them.
This is not good.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end...
I want my life back.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Is he trying to kill her?
Or time to get out.
Oh, my God.
This is going to kill us.
I'm in Delmont, Pennsylvania.
It's about 25 miles east of Pittsburgh.
I got a call from a desperate mother.
She says the activity
is so bad in the house,
she spends every night
with her three kids
sleeping in the living room.
She thinks the activity is
destroying their childhood,
and if we can't help her out,
someone's going to get hurt.
Before Amy arrives,
I clear the area of any
leading information.
Family photos and personal items
can influence her findings,
so it's important that I
cover or remove them all.
When I'm done, the location will
be ready for tonight's walk.
Wow, boy.
There's a male, definitely.
I think he did really awful things.
He had a lot of issues with women,
like any kind of involvement with women
didn't really go very well.
And then, like, someone else is saying...
You know, like... you know,
people should not live here.
It's been bad for a very long time.
So, Melissa,
on the phone you sounded pretty desperate
for myself and my partner to come out here.
What's going on?
Since day one that we moved in here,
I knew we weren't alone in this house.
And it's just progressively
just gotten worse.
My husband sleeps upstairs.
My children and myself sleep in this room.
My kids will not sleep in their rooms.
Well, that can't be great for the marriage.
Yeah. I mean, I should be able to
sleep in my room with my husband,
but I'm frightened of what
it could do to my kids.
Who exactly lives in the house?
It's my husband, me.
This is my daughter, Samone. She's 9.
This is my son, Mason,
and this is our baby, Cyrus.
Let me ask you a question
about the house itself.
Do you know any of its history or anything?
This was my husband's grandfather's house,
so we are the third generation.
I actually have a picture
of it if you want to see,
from, I believe, the 1800s.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
Okay,
so give me a run-down of what's going on.
Noises, voices,
horrible nightmares, and apparitions.
You feel like it's something threatening?
Definitely.
I think there's something very nasty here.
How well are you dealing with this?
I'm exhausted and I'm drained,
and I've had chronic health
problems for over five years
which no doctor could tell
me what was wrong with me.
It feels like my body's shutting down.
Either we're going to go
or something bad's going to happen.
I know you were desperate
for Amy and I to come here.
What would be the best outcome for you?
I want...
I want normalcy in our lives again.
It's hard. Being sick is hard.
And I do feel like this house
has a lot to do with it.
My kids can't deal with it anymore.
I can't deal with it anymore.
My husband can't deal with it anymore.
It's just, like,
I'd rather just pack up and go,
and just to start over, you know?
- We're here to try to fix that.
- I know.
I was feeling so desperate and hopeless.
I mean, and I'm ready to fight it,
whatever it is.
This guy, like,
as far as his interaction with women,
is a problem here, you know?
He's a real creepy creep.
He's, like,
kind of on your back all the time
stalking, following, watching, watching.
Are they aware of it at all?
I think so.
Like, going through ladies' stuff,
underwear,
you know,
watching them get dressed or undressed.
It's a feeling of, like,
I'm going to the bathroom.
I'm being watched.
Like, skeevy, skeevy perv-o.
Why'd you bring me in this room?
Uh, this is the room we all sleep in.
It's no way for anybody to live.
No, not when we have a
big house with rooms.
So, I'm curious about yourself.
What experiences have you had?
When I was walking through
the second floor hallway upstairs
a very large black shadow
moved right in front of the door
when I was trying to cross through.
I ran out into the hallway
and there was nothing there, nobody there.
Is it possible that the shadow
did come in from outside?
No, 'cause it was up in that hallway,
there's no windows or anything.
- Was anybody in the house with you?
- No.
It scared me to death, you know? It did.
So, anything else going on?
My son just woke up the other day
and had a big bruise on his side.
I wake up with bruises.
I mean, my daughter's woken
up with scratches on her.
And that's in this so-called
safe room you're in.
Mm-hmm.
Could that be as a result
of tossing and turning?
No, I mean, everyone's on a soft,
cushy surface
and away from each other.
Are you afraid there's
something attacking you, guys?
It's crossed my mind.
Because if that's the case,
then it takes it to a whole 'nother level.
I see two women...
an older one and a younger one.
The younger one's angry with me.
Dead guy is yelling,
and he says she's a spiteful little [bleep]
Who doesn't know her place
and doesn't know manners,
and she needs to be regulated?
She does not like children whatsoever.
She doesn't look at them
like they're human.
And I think that's a big problem
if there's any children in this house.
She would literally torture
the [bleep] out of them.
So, Jimmy,
I was talking to your wife about
a lot of things that your
kids are going through.
She also told me that
the house has been in
your family a long time.
- Yeah.
- Do you know how long?
Since, uh, 1952, I believe.
Did you spend time here as a kid.
Yes, I spent a lot of time here.
Here's a picture of when
I was, I believe, 5
with my grandfather.
We were fishing down here at the creek,
and I caught a 17-inch rainbow trout.
- So you had good memories.
- Oh, yeah.
Your kids aren't having
the nice times that you had, though.
No, my kids are afraid to
go anywhere in the house.
From what they said,
I can't blame them either, you know?
Right.
You know any history about the house?
My grandmother died in the house.
From what I've been told,
is she had bone cancer.
She committed suicide.
In the house?
In the room next to us, and that's where...
Right here?
That's where Mason and Samone
both have their dreams about
where they swear they've
seen things in there.
My son, multiple times,
has said he's seen the
floor covered with blood.
It's just tough.
It's just things that kids shouldn't,
you know, even talk about.
And that's why I agreed to all this.
Have you had experiences?
I was sleeping and next thing you know
I woke up, like bouncing, you know...
like it felt like
I got picked up to the ceiling and dropped.
I come straight out of the room.
My wife said I was white as a ghost.
Strangest thing I've ever had happen to me.
- Do you suffer from seizures?
- No.
- Nothing like that?
Were you drinking heavy that night
or anything like that?
No.
That's the main reason that I said
to contact you guys,
is because there's no normalcy here at all.
You know,
kids shouldn't have to feel this way
or go through this stuff.
Yeah.
They should be allowed to just be kids.
There's a lot of anger.
There's a person yelling and screaming.
Um, I saw the dead guy
doing stuff to a living guy.
I actually see him touching a living male.
I don't think that
the living male appreciates this.
So I'm seeing yelling...
yelling and screaming.
Like, "Stop! I've had it!
Stop! Leave me alone!
Go away! Stop!"
I was talking to Mommy earlier,
and she was saying that
you and your brother
were having a tough time.
Yeah.
Are you guys all sleeping
downstairs together?
Yeah.
Now,
can you tell me about some of the things
that are making you afraid?
Well,
I heard my door and dresser drawers slam
and, um, this was when I was laying down
getting ready to go to bed.
Okay, is that part of the reason, you know,
you sleep downstairs with Mom?
No. I've seen mists in corners of the room.
Okay, what kind of mist?
Like, blackish that you can see through.
Okay. Can you describe how it's shaped?
It's shaped, like, usually in a circle.
But sometimes it's in, like, weird shapes.
Okay.
Mommy mentioned something about
you guys having bad dreams.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
What's going on with that?
Well, I have dreams about...
people chasing me in the house.
They're usually grown-ups.
Okay.
And it's usually a man,
but sometimes it's a woman.
Do they say anything to you, honey?
Mm-hmm.
They say "I'm going to kill you."
The younger lady,
she really hates kids.
Absolutely despises them.
Like, the energy she puts out is monstrous.
And these kids can feel that.
You know what I mean?
It's weird too, because the older lady
is really the one kind of ratting her out.
Okay.
I see her, like, as a darkness.
Um, it's like the night.
She gets them at night, for sure, for sure.
Um...
She's in here a lot.
She comes in there a lot.
She likes that doorway a lot.
I see her sleeping in the bed.
I think that this person,
they used to be cuddled or caressed
and then it got bad.
It got frightening,
like clutched, being clutched.
Cold, icy hands.
Really bad. Really bad.
So I was talking to Mommy earlier today.
She told me that you and your sister
are pretty scared.
Yeah.
There any reason why that you can tell me?
That's kind of scary.
Okay.
Is there anything else that scares you?
I saw, like,
a white shadow coming down the stairs.
Do you remember what it looked like?
It looked like... I don't know.
It was the shape of a... a man.
Okay.
So was that the only thing that scared you?
No.
I hear sounds a lot.
Like, rattling and banging.
It's coming from Mom's dressing room.
- From Mom's dressing room?
- Yeah.
Okay, it sounds like
that kind of scares you then, huh?
Yeah.
I'll only go up here, like, sometimes
when my mom's up here.
- Okay.
- If nobody's up here,
I won't go up here, especially at night.
Especially at night, okay.
We're gonna try and fix things,
me and my partner.
And then you can come here all by yourself
and just have a good time in your bedroom.
That sound like a plan?
Mm-hmm.
There's a little boy.
I don't know, maybe 8?
Okay.
And the younger woman,
she's like this silhouette
rushing back and forth between the rooms.
It's like... like there's a weird noise
like she's moaning or
screaming or something.
These kids, they're both, you know,
seeing this and hearing this.
But I don't feel the clutching in here,
the touching from her to this person.
It's more like smothering,
much smothering in here.
Much smothering.
There's a weird relationship
between her and that person in that room.
But, here, she just wants this person dead.
Jimmy doesn't know a lot about
his grandmother's suicide in the house,
but he said I could reach
out to some of his relatives.
Turns out his aunt, the victim's daughter,
was there minutes after
her mom shot herself.
So, Kathy,
you grew up in that house, right?
Yes.
Did you ever experience
anything in the house
- that you couldn't explain.
- I haven't.
- You haven't?
- No.
Okay. Now, your mom.
What kind of woman was she?
Um, Mom was the best.
There was never anything, in my world,
she did wrong, ever.
I have a picture of my mom.
This was in the mid-to-late '50s.
It was actually taken in
the living room there.
Now, I understand your mom had gotten ill,
is that correct?
My mother got bone cancer.
She was diagnosed with
it about 1981 or 1982,
somewhere like that.
My grandmother died of bone cancer,
and I remember how painful that was.
Very terrible.
Just said, "Well, runs in the family.
I guess it's my turn."
And here's a picture of her
shortly before she died.
I know it's gonna be tough to talk about,
but can you take me through
what happened the day your mom passed?
The day mom died, um, I was working.
I got a phone call from my dad.
He says, "come quick, Mom's shot."
Got here as quick as I can,
come into the house,
and went upstairs, and
found her in her bed.
- And with a gunshot wound?
- Yes.
And seeing where the gunshot wound was,
it went right through the brain stem.
- She was gone.
- Okay.
Yeah. I know.
I'm sorry, honey.
After all these years.
It doesn't matter.
You could be 80 years old
and you'll still think about it.
Mm-hmm.
You all right?
It's the older woman.
She was sick, a lot.
I'm trying to figure out
what exactly she had.
She was, like,
very confused about where she was,
what was happening, what's going on.
Very, very dizzy.
I do think the living would feel this...
Passing out, fainting.
Somebody got it in the head.
Ah
Now that I know Jimmy's grandmother
committed suicide in the house,
I need to see if there's anything else
that could help my investigation.
Searching through old records,
I find a strange story.
It involves a woman who lived
right by my clients' property
who got married
only to have her husband kill himself
a couple of days later.
I called the local historian
to look into this weird suicide for me.
She called me back and said
there's a lot more to this story
that will definitely help my case.
So, Tracy,
before we get to this weird suicide,
uh, you mentioned on the phone
there was some interesting
stuff about his widow.
What can you tell me?
Her name is Mattie Waugaman,
and she lived a few doors down
from the property you're investigating.
Her family had a very
successful tavern in Delmont.
So she would have been
a child of privilege in the area.
All right. Did she do anything,
or did she live off the parents' money?
She was a seamstress,
but she had bigger plans.
She wanted to make her own money
and not live off of her dad's money.
So she got involved in
the Westmoreland County home scandal.
What's that all about?
She's in these rich homes,
selling dresses,
making things for these ladies,
and she's seeing some
things that maybe she wants.
So probably took things here and there.
She ever get charged?
She did not, and she did
not serve any time.
Okay, so now,
I saw in the article I came across
- that she got married at 35.
- Mmhmm.
I mean, which seems kind of late
for that time period.
Well, Mattie was a rebel.
She got married late,
and she had a child out of wedlock in 1873,
and she named him Everett.
So I could imagine in 1873,
having a kid out of wedlock's
got to be a big to-do.
Oh, absolutely.
I mean,
even in the 1970s it was a big scandal.
So just imagine the shame
that was brought on her in that small town.
So possibly
'cause it was a scandalous thing,
nobody wanted to marry this girl.
Well, in April of 1884,
she goes,
and she meets this guy in Greensburg,
- this J.R. Taylor.
- Okay.
And she married him within the day,
shocked friends and family.
What do you... wait... wait a minute.
She got married the same
day she met the guy?
- Same day she met him.
- Wow.
What happened?
Just a couple days later,
he wrote four suicide notes.
And in those suicide notes,
he expressed how sorry he
was that he had no money
and he could not support his new bride.
Only possession he had of
value was a gold piece,
and he wrote in the suicide letter
to leave it to Mattie,
a woman that he only knew for a few days.
Then, after he wrote those notes,
he went and took a lethal dose of morphine
and was found the next morning.
"From the Alter to the Grave."
That says it all right there, huh?
The younger lady,
she was all about money,
money, money, money.
Her parents may have had some money.
Um, I'm seeing, like, gold.
I would put her not much further than 1918.
She might have had two
relationships with two men,
uh, that didn't end well.
She was, like, a control freak.
She was kind of demented.
Another thing caught my attention.
Back in 1970,
just down the block from
Jimmy and Melissa's house,
a guy broke in and murdered a woman
right in front of her 6-year-old kid.
I'm heading over to meet
with the county sheriff,
who said it was one of
the most brutal crimes
in the city's history.
So, Sheriff Held, this homicide
I asked you to look into for me,
it was pretty brutal.
Yeah, It was one of the most
notorious in Delmont's history.
So, what were you able to find out
about the victim in this case?
Her name's Harriet Thomas.
She was a 52-year-old white female.
She lived across the
street and one house over
from, your client's property.
All right, so,
what do we know about our perp in this case?
His name is Johnny Fostar.
He was 25 years old at
the time of the murder.
He lived across the street
but one house in the opposite direction
from the victim.
And we have a picture of him too.
Got into trouble at a very young age.
- First arrest was at 12.
- Okay.
And it started out just petty crimes...
you know, theft,
breaking into houses, and stealing.
He was once investigated for
breaking into a neighbor's home
and observing her while she slept
and actually touched her and woke her up.
- He's a creeper?
- Yes.
- Peeping Tom maybe.
- Right.
He could be referred to as.
The pervy guy, I
would kind of put him,
like, in the '70s, like
1970s or '60s maybe.
I'm trying to get a read on the creepy guy
who watches the living here.
He doesn't want me to see anything,
but I'm getting quick glimpses
of what he was like in life.
He's weird.
Like, stalker.
He was some kind of sexual offender.
All right, so how's this homicide go down?
On February 28th, 1970,
he broke into Harriet Thomas' house.
Apparently, he was mixing alcohol
with 15 Benzodiazepine pills.
- Very strong narcotics.
- Yes.
There's a struggle with her,
and he stabs her 27 times
with a screwdriver
in front of her 6-year-old son.
And I have the coroner's report here.
Okay.
So she's stabbed in the
chest with a screwdriver.
This guy really did a job on her.
He was actually convicted in this courtroom
right here on December 7th, 1970.
So now, what did he get convicted of?
He got convicted of murder
and got sentenced to life
in prison without parole.
And we have a, uh... we have a photo here
that is a Department of Corrections photo.
Okay, so now, this guy's 25
at the time of the homicide in '70.
Plausibly,
he could still be alive in jail, right?
Oh, no. He died in 2003 of lung cancer
at the age of 57.
Good. He deserved it.
Something about fif... The number 15
has something to do with this male.
I do see blood on his hands
when he's talking about this.
He's older. He's probably in his 50s.
He's got, like, that kind of hairstyle.
It's longer, you know, swept over.
He occasionally has a mustache.
You would never think he was a weirdo.
Like, he looks like a nice,
little middle-aged,
you know, family man or something.
I saw several dead people during my walk.
But the angry woman
tormenting a living child
had me the most concerned.
She's young.
Pretty thin.
She had dark hair.
There was a kid in the bed.
And this lady,
she was smothering this child.
Is this what you saw?
Yes. That's what I saw.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations,
we're ready to reveal our findings
to each other and our
clients for the first time.
Now, Amy, when you talked to
Jimmy and Melissa here, um,
it doesn't take but a couple of seconds
to realize how much they love their kids.
I have a photo here of the family.
This is their oldest daughter,
Samone, who's 9.
This is Mason, who's 7.
And this is Cyrus, who is now what, 20...
- 22 months.
Now, they're the reason we're here.
Melissa thinks they're in danger.
Even though that house
has been in Jimmy's family
for three generations,
if we can't help them,
he's ready to pack up and leave.
So now that Amy knows a
little bit about your family
and what's going on here,
I'm gonna ask her to describe her walk.
When I got here,
there were several dead
people roaming about.
But first I want to discuss
the male that's in the living room area.
Okay.
And, um,
he seemed to be kind of a sexual deviant.
I actually saw him going through ladies'
underwear.
He likes to watch people get undressed.
He also likes to caress or touch people.
That doesn't surprise me,
'cause I always feel
like I'm being watched,
and it's weird because when I'm
getting a shower or anything,
it's like I shut the door,
and then I still feel like
there's a camera or something on me.
You know what I mean?
Like, I'm not alone in there.
I did actually see him in
the upstairs master bedroom,
and he was touching a male.
What I saw was
this male feeling something
strange happening,
and kind of being like,
you know, "I'm sick and tired of this.
It's got to stop."
It's funny you mentioned upstairs because,
I mean,
things are so bad in the house
that Melissa and the kids
sleep down here in the living room.
Okay.
Do me a favor.
Tell Amy about the incident with the bed.
Yeah.
I felt like I was picked up,
picked up to the ceiling and dropped.
And he's not someone who scares easily.
When he came out, he was white as a ghost,
and I knew something was wrong.
I had no clue.
Now,
I did come across a perv in my research,
but I need to know a little
bit more about this guy
if you've got anything.
I got that he was from the '60s or '70s.
The number 15 was important.
He was talking about women in his life
and how that never went well.
Obviously, he had sexual problems.
So then I saw him looking
in a mirror in a bathroom,
and he had his hands up,
and there was blood all over his hands.
Well, a lot of things you're saying
reminds me of a guy named Johnny Fostar.
He grew up a couple doors down from here.
I got a photo of him here.
Now, this guy was a neighborhood criminal.
- Oh.
- He stole a lot from everybody.
He was a thief.
Now, most of these crimes
took place during the '60s.
Now, in 1968,
he got caught breaking into a woman's house
and watching her sleep,
and she woke up when he touched her.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, Lord.
- You mentioned about blood on his hands...
- Uh-huh.
- ...and the number 15.
On the night of February 28th, 1970,
uh, Johnny here wound up taking 15 pills,
- very strong narcotics...
- Oh.
Mixed with booze,
and he breaks into a woman's house
right across the street from you
by the name of Harriet Thomas.
She was a 52-year-old female.
Harriet gets attacked by Johnny.
He stabs her 27 times in the chest
- with a screwdriver...
- Oh, my God.
- ...In front of her 6-year-old kid.
- Whoa.
- Oh, my God.
I actually got the coroner's report.
Stab wound of chest with a screwdriver.
Oh, my goodness.
My God.
He was convicted and
sentenced to life in prison.
He wound up dying in
prison at the age of 57.
- I got a photo of him just before he died.
- Oh, hmm.
Now, is it possible this
could be the guy you saw?
Yeah. I think that's the guy.
I wish I could just meet him,
and I wish I could just
do something [bleep]
Could this be who lifted Jimmy?
Oh, I don't think so.
There's someone worse.
I met two women in here.
Um, but the first one I'm going to discuss
is the older woman.
She doesn't really interact
with living people.
Um, I know that she got sick here.
She felt ill here.
I got her sickness a lot upstairs...
Dizziness, pain.
I got that there was some mental confusion
with her, uh, death,
and then the worst part,
there was an impact to her head.
You okay, Jimmy?
What?
This is a little bit of
a delicate situation.
Um,
you mentioned the woman you saw was sick.
Back in the 1980s, Jimmy's
grandmother Helen
was diagnosed with bone cancer.
Oh.
Um, she suffered a great deal.
It might've been a problem
with the medication.
- She was disoriented.
- Yes. Okay.
So, um...
back in 1989,
Jimmy's grandmother wound
up committing suicide
by shooting herself in the head upstairs.
She was just a good woman, you know?
She was, like, a... like,
a saint, you know?
I actually have a picture
of your grandmother.
This is not too long before she passed.
They didn't tell me she was sick.
Wow.
The important thing is for Jimmy to know,
is his grandmother here?
I...Yeah.
The good news is
I think she's here watching over you guys.
She was really helpful as far as...
Oh, okay.
You know, telling me bad things
that other dead people
were doing, you know?
Okay.
I mean, I was hoping this wasn't the case,
that your grandmother wasn't here,
but it sounds like at
least she's trying to help.
She's protecting.
Yeah.
There's one other thing I want to bring up,
and this involves one of the kids.
It's Mason, who's 7, right?
- Yeah.
You know what, Jimmy?
You explain it to her better.
It's your son, about what he sees in...
He says he sees blood on the floor
in the same room that my grandmother died.
Okay.
And he's pretty dead set on it.
Well, you do have a dead person here
who would prefer the children
have negative experiences.
That's what I thought.
So the person that I think
is the biggest threat here
is this younger dead woman.
She seems to be from a very long time ago.
I put her at about 25 years of age.
I think her parents had some money
because her fixation in life
was very much focused on money and image.
And she had two relationships
with two different men
that did not end well.
I got one woman in the
research that came up
that actually only lived a
couple doors down from here.
This woman named Mattie Waugaman
lived down here in the late 1800s.
Her parents owned a tavern in town
and were part of Delmont's high society.
Now, you mentioned the woman
you saw is obsessed with money.
Uh, this woman, Mattie,
was caught up in a pretty big scandal.
She was accused of stealing things
from wealthy people's homes,
but she was never charged.
Interesting.
But what really got my attention
was what you said about the
bad relationships with men.
- Um...
- Mm-hmm.
This woman had disastrous
relationships with two men.
- Hmm.
- 1873, she had a kid out of wedlock,
- which is pretty unheard of back then.
- Back then, yeah, of course.
So when she had the baby,
it was a huge scandal.
About 11 years later,
she wound up having a second
disastrous relationship
with a man, a guy named J.R. Taylor.
She met him and married him the same day.
- Oh.
- Oh, nice.
Three days later,
this guy J.R. Taylor committed suicide
with an overdose of morphine.
- Wow.
- I actually have an article here from it.
Now, in the suicide letter,
he basically said that he
didn't have enough money
to support his new wife,
and he left her the only
thing he had of value,
the gold piece.
So you got to wonder what
kind of a woman that was
that had this guy so wrapped up in one day.
Mm.
Now, when Mattie died in 1905,
she was buried in the
cemetery right up the street.
- Oh, my God.
- Okay.
Now, does this sound like
possibly who you ran into?
Sounds about right.
I feel, obviously,
that she has some mental issues.
The biggest problem was that
she really despises children.
She doesn't even see them as human.
When I saw her upstairs,
she's like this monstrous,
like, being up there.
And there's this energy
that's just horrendous.
She knows exactly what
to do to torture someone.
I see her sleeping in the bed,
like, clutched, being clutched.
Cold, icy hands.
Really bad.
I saw her racing back and
forth through that door
as, like, a silhouetted figure
between the two children's bedrooms.
Now you know why the kids sleep downstairs.
My daughter woke up screaming
that somebody was in her room
opening and slamming her drawers.
- Mm-hmm.
- I mean, she was terrified.
Mason had an incident where he saw
white mist coming up the stairs.
Yeah. He said it was a white mist.
It looked like a human shape.
Okay.
And they wake up with bruises.
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, my God.
- And scratches.
- Yeah.
Wow.
Now, could this be this...
- this woman?
- Yeah. Yeah.
To think that something is...
is attacking my kids,
that's enraging.
Yeah, kids can't grow up like this.
So I had a sketch done of something
that she would like to do, um, to your son.
As a parent, I don't even want to
put this down in front of you,
but, you know...
Oh, my God.
She's lucky I can't see her.
I carry a gun on me.
She's lucky she's not living.
I had a sketch done of something
that she would like to do, um, to your son.
As a parent, I don't even want to
put this down in front of you,
but, you know...
Oh, my God.
She's lucky I can't see her.
I carry a gun on me.
She's lucky she's not living.
So she's trying to smother him?
Mm-hmm.
Mason breathes real heavy.
You can hear him...
It sounds like he's
having problems breathing.
Okay.
She does a weird thing
with her hands and fingers
over his mouth, so that does worry me.
This wicked, little [bleep] needs to go.
What's her endgame?
As far as your son is concerned,
like, she would like to kill him.
I mean, that's her... her goal.
Is she even capable of doing
that to this kid, God forbid?
I think it's a possibility.
So... so that does worry me.
I'd burn it to the ground
if it meant for my family to be happy.
It's just... I mean,
the house does mean a lot to me,
but it doesn't mean nowhere even close
to what my children and my wife mean to me.
Right.
So guys, it's been a rough night,
and I'm really sorry about that,
especially about your grandma.
Um, but you two are fighters,
and now you know what's
going after your kids.
Now the thing is, how do we get
rid of the bad dead in the house
so you guys can live a normal life
and raise your kids here
in a comfortable manner?
For that answer,
I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
Uh,
the first thing is to find a male medium.
And this person,
on the first day they're here,
is to deal with the male that's here.
So the medium's job here is
to get him out of your house
and to banish him from the house.
And then the second day, actually,
I would like for him, the male medium,
to give you a reading
because there are things
that your grandmother needs to talk about.
Once the reading is finished,
she'll be ready to move on.
Okay. Now, what about the lunatic woman?
Uh, the last thing that you guys do
is to have a Voodoo priestess come.
This is something that terrifies her.
So I think that she feels like
that's going to put her in a place
where she kind of knows she belongs.
She's pretty terrified.
Good.
This little [bleep]...
she could get hit by a bus tomorrow
and I wouldn't care, you know what I mean?
So, Jimmy, it's got to make you feel good
that you can keep the house
that's been in your family
for three generations.
Of course. Yes.
You gonna take Amy's advice?
Absolutely. Absolutely.
She's gone.
I'm really concerned for Melissa and Jimmy,
as the dead terrorizing their family
present a serious danger.
But with the help of a medium
and a Voodoo priestess,
they'll be able to rid their home
of the evil surrounding it
and live a peaceful life.