I feel like he comes up from the grave.
Tonight on
"Dead Files Revisited"...
They look like little demons.
a second look
at some of Amy and Steve's
most terrifying cases.
I heard it scared the out of you.
New information...
It feels like impending doom.
startling revelations.
We were living in the
house with these demons.
First...
I don't believe they were ever alive.
demons invade an Ohio home...
And it came right at me...
"Foof," right through me.
Where hell unleashes a fury...
I thought I was just losing my mind.
that hungers for souls.
Those demons... they
can take your soul.
Then...
He shot up from the ground.
this Pennsylvania
home is under attack...
"It doesn't matter where you are.
I'll find you. I'll find you."
and the dead wage a war...
I see a black mist, and
it just goes "Whoosh."
while the
living fight for survival.
This entity haunts me.
Can these terrors be stopped...
It needs to end.
and innocent lives be saved?
Mighty Mother, let the
divine light descend!
Something bad's going to happen.
My name is Amy Allan.
There's panic.
And it's almost like a butchering.
I see dead people.
They all died horribly.
I speak to dead people.
Get out of here.
And they speak to me.
Vicious.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
It doesn't matter where
you are. I'll find you.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
This guy's a real piece of work.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I feel like I live in a house of hell.
It's my job to reveal them.
This is not good.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end...
I want my life back.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Is he trying to kill her?
Or time to get out.
My God.
This is going to kill us.
Some cases stick
with me more than others,
and the one we investigated
in Toledo, Ohio,
was a tough one for me to shake.
This family unit was being destroyed,
and one of the victims was a small child.
They turned to us for help and hope,
and I badly wanted to give them both.
We've had a couple of episodes
where we've been burned,
we've been scratched,
we've been pushed, we've been shoved.
I live in constant fear here.
Who do you live here with?
I live here with my partner, Leslie,
my daughter, Maggie,
and my 2-year-old
grandson, Nathan.
It seems like it got
worse after he was born.
- Is he being affected by this?
- He is.
We were sitting in the
living room, watching TV.
He was sitting on the
floor, playing with his toys,
and we seen him literally
lift up off the ground
and was shoved a good foot and a half.
As a grandma, I'd do anything
to protect my grandchild,
but a force that I
couldn't reckon with...
I knew that there was nothing
in my power that I could do,
and it was breaking my heart.
I fear greatly for him,
and I feel like we can't
protect him, either.
What the hell?
As soon as I stepped
through the front door,
I could tell this place was
filled with something evil.
It was clear to me whoever
lived here was at risk
and this walk was going
to be a very dangerous one.
There's a male here who
knows how it used to be
and is disturbed.
He's pissed.
The head pain is so bad.
There was an older
gentleman I seen in here,
wearing kind of like a suit.
Grayish hair.
He startles me at first, but
he doesn't seem threatening.
Okay, what time period
do you think he's from?
I would say early 1900s.
The fact that Angie
had seen this entity so clearly
she could actually pinpoint
the time period he was from
was extremely helpful to the investigation.
But what she described
next, I didn't see coming.
I seen one other one.
This one bothers me
'cause it really scared me.
It was a man, but he didn't look human.
He was in the mirror.
He had two horns off the top of his head.
Big teeth.
I would say at least 6 foot.
And I seen him kind of let out a growl,
and it came right at me...
"Foof," right through me,
and I immediately broke out into tears.
I've never been
afraid in my own home.
I thought I was just losing my mind.
I ran back to my room, woke up my partner,
and said, "Something's
going on around here,
and we need to get to the bottom of it."
I felt like I was gonna faint.
I was sick to my stomach.
- That had to scare the out of you.
- It did.
All I can tell you, Steve,
it was the scariest thing
I've ever seen in my life.
I'm telling you, what
Angie described was horrifying.
But she wasn't alone.
This was another one of
those mind-blowing cases
where during her walk, Amy
saw the same exact thing,
in even more horrific detail.
There's something here.
And it came in through the front door.
These things, they look
like, little demons.
They kind of have, like, bat faces.
They have, like, pointed
ears, big eyes, sharp teeth.
Kind of centered on this female.
I was extremely worried
about Angie's well-being.
And talking to her teenage daughter
made me even more concerned.
- Now, this is your son's room.
- Yes.
Apparently, your mom
said she actually saw him
get picked up and kind of thrown or pushed.
Yeah. It has happened.
I felt like I
could tell Steve anything.
I really believed that
he was here to help us
and that it was his goal
to make sure he took care
of everything in the house
so everyone here would be
safe, especially Nathan.
He was playing in his room.
I was cleaning up, and I
heard him hit the ground,
and when I came into his
room, he was flat on his back,
and his face was bloodshot red.
I know his cries, and it was definitely
something I've never heard before.
This was... he wanted to get out of here.
Something scared him.
Those demons... they're
getting too out of hand.
That's what this older dude was saying.
This is the moment where I figured out
why the older man was so upset.
These creatures were attacking
the living and the dead.
And he says, "I can't handle that.
I can't get involved in that."
He can't fight anymore
because they're gonna get him.
They can take your soul.
Angie mentioned
that everyone in the house
had a paranormal experience,
so I was expecting more of the same
from her partner, Leslie.
But after talking to her, it became clear
that whatever was in that house
had a problem with religion.
My cross on my neck got ripped off
and thrown across the floor.
It was strange.
- Strange? It's a little bit scary.
- Yeah.
- Was anybody else home?
- No.
There's the battle
between the living and these things.
Do you know what these things are?
I don't believe they were ever alive.
They're kept out.
They can be kept at bay because
they respond to religion.
I guess you would call them,
like, some kind of demons.
Next...
She actually used
electroshock therapy on him.
Madness drives the dead...
This guy's sick for a long time.
to torture the living.
And in our second investigation...
I feel like I live in a house of hell.
A suburban home becomes a deathtrap.
You can't escape.
I never know what pulling the deed
to someone's property is gonna lead to.
In this case, I came to find out
the previous owner was
a bit of a local legend
before his life came to a tragic end.
I called on a retired detective
who knew all about this story.
Clarence Brown was
17 at the time in 1930.
And he got this idea
about counterfeiting bills.
Now, was he operating out of
the house I'm investigating?
Yes, he did.
The older male,
I feel him very much
involved with the structure.
There was no denying
that those demons wanted
control of this house
and would do anything to get it.
But the older man I picked
up on in the living room
wasn't backing down from their threats.
Do you know anything about
what he was like in life?
I would say that he was a...
no bull kind of guy.
I would guess that he might
have been, like, a boss,
because he's very much
like, "This is what's goin'.
This is what we're doing
This is what's happening."
Who was all involved? Was
it just this guy Clarence?
Well, no.
Clarence and Sherman,
his dad, and his brother,
and two other associates.
Okay, so, he basically ran it.
Yes, he did.
I think he was also trying
to give warnings about what's going on.
Like, I see him talking to somebody,
trying to explain things to them.
Eventually, he got caught.
They were busted in 1935.
But when it came to trial,
according to this article here,
Clarence took the heat
for the entire family
and got a 3½-year sentence,
and he did about 2½ years.
Look, I can't condone
what this guy Clarence was doing,
but to take the rap for the whole thing
is a stand-up move.
Unfortunately, getting busted
was just the beginning of his troubles.
Okay, does he go back to
counterfeiting? What's he do?
No, he gave up the counterfeiting,
moved back into your client's house.
Things went real bad in 1948 initially,
when his mother died.
It hit him pretty hard.
***
This guy is sick.
Do you know how he died?
Something with his head.
He was developing a real paranoia.
He had pretty much
alienated his wife and sons.
He had a lot of pain in
his head. That's all I know.
It got so bad
that she actually used
electroshock therapy on him,
He was sick for a long time. I know that.
She eventually had him committed
to a mental institution,
where he spent the last
26 years of his life...
dying at age 83.
Coming up...
That's the thing that I see.
What happened after the investigation?
I order you,
by the Lord Jesus Christ,
to leave this home.
Exit immediately.
Do not return.
Amy, I'd like you to meet
the three ladies that live in this house.
The main reason we're here
is for Maggie's
2- year-old son, Nathan.
Aww.
My reveal with Amy and Steve
was extremely overwhelming.
Part of me was hoping that
she would find something
just so I didn't feel
like I was going crazy.
But another part of me was a little scared
of what she was gonna find.
I did meet an older male.
This individual has been trying
to warn you for some time.
He's been trying to communicate
to you through dreams.
- You told me about the old man, right?
- Right.
I often see him tinkering around.
We call him Clarence.
We don't know if that's his real name.
I started to have...
extreme pain in my head,
and I knew that it was coming from him.
Well, I'll tell you a story
about a guy that lived in this house.
His name was Clarence.
Really?
Clarence Brown.
My God.
You didn't know that?
Clarence, he decided, "You know what?
"I'm gonna start up a
counterfeiting business."
Right in the basement here,
they were printing up money.
So, it's 1935. The FBI busts him.
They arrested everybody...
his father, his brother.
He said, "No, no. It was all on me.
He took the hit,
So, he gets out of jail and
moves back into this house,
He starts getting mentally unstable.
His wife tried
everything...
in and out of doctors,
electroshock therapy.
1971, she had him committed
into a mental hospital.
He laid there for 26 years
till he died... in 1997.
That's him right there.
When Steve showed
me the picture of Clarence,
I knew right away that
was the guy I'd be seeg.
It was like, "My God, that's him."
It was crazy.
- So, you never knew the name Clarence?
- I didn't.
You're not bull me,
right? I'm not bull you.
Nowhere.
I'm blown away myself.
The older man was telling
me that he had been fighting,
for quite some time, a particular entity,
but now there's more,
and he can't contend with them any further.
They're very strange-looking.
They have bat faces. They
have the pointed ears.
I do not think that these
things were ever alive.
I think they're inherently evil.
One thing I noticed was someone was saying
some type of religious statement,
and it did make them
back... back up.
I would say that these things
are some kind of demons.
It made me sick to my stomach,
knowing that we were living
in the house with these demons.
Also, the closet where I
saw most of these things
was in the smaller room upstairs.
That's my son's room.
Is it possible that he's seen them?
Yes.
I did do a sketch of what I saw.
Geez.
That's the thing that I see.
It's all right, baby.
When I seen that
sketch, it really upset me.
There's just been a lot of times
where Nathan has woken
up crying in his room,
and I always just linked
them to bad dreams.
Now I feel like it was
probably something more.
All the things that
have happened to your son,
that would have been from these things?
Yes.
What do we do?
That's what we need to know.
The first thing that needs
to be done immediately
is the contact of a
priest or a demonologist...
someone who can perform an exorcism
on the home and the property
that is just to be directed
towards the demonic entities.
You gonna go through that?
After the investigation,
the activity around here really amped up.
It just seemed to get crazy around here.
The footsteps
got way more frequent.
The banging got way louder.
I felt like I was locking myself
in my room almost every night.
Heavenly Father,
I ask that you can place
a hedge of protection around this home
to keep out any evil spirits that are here.
We took Amy's advice
and found a demonologist
to come into our home and do an exorcism.
Heavenly Father,
we ask for a hedge of
protection upon this home.
Humbly ask this in Jesus' name.
The demonologist went through
the house with anointing oil,
and he performed an exorcism
on each and every room, window, and door.
I now renounce
all past use of this property
for false religions, occult practices,
spiritualistic healings, and such.
The next thing he did
was he went around with an incense burner,
putting up a wall of protection
against anything evil
that was remaining here.
Any demonic spirits,
any evil spirts that may
be inhabiting this home,
I order you, by the Lord Jesus Christ,
to leave this home.
Exit immediately.
Do not return.
Heavenly Father,
I ask for your guidance and
your protection upon Angie
and that you can deliver her from all evil.
In Jesus' name.
And after that,
he blessed all four of us,
and he blessed the home, as well.
Heavenly Father, I ask that
you can bless this home.
Deliver them from evil.
In Jesus' name.
Amen.
I definitely
feel like the demonologist
get rid of the demonic
entities that were here.
Soon after the priest left,
I really noticed a big difference.
The home was peaceful.
For once, in eight or nine years,
it was actually peaceful.
Demons are one of
the most difficult entities
to get rid of,
but I'm confident that the steps
Maggie and her family have taken
will keep the evil out
and make their home a
safer place to raise Nathan.
The case we looked
into in Hanover, Pennsylvania,
was really troubling for me.
We had a woman being physically assaulted
by something in her house.
Needless to say, I'm outraged
when I hear about a woman
being physically attacked,
and by the end of our investigation,
it was clear that Amy and
I got there just in time.
I want my home back.
I feel like I live in a house of hell.
What's going on?
I'm seeing apparitions.
I'm seeing shadow figures.
I'm being bit, scratched.
Geez.
How long you living here?
Seven years.
Okay, and you live
here with your husband.
Yes... Tom.
Okay, so, seven years
this has being going on,
or has it progressively gotten worse?
It has progressively gotten worse.
Tom and I are
attacked daily in our home.
It's nonstop.
I could be just sitting
here, and all of a sudden,
I'm just feeling this encroachment.
Like, you can feel them coming.
It feels like impending doom.
I've got to the point
where I won't even sleep upstairs anymore.
I don't even sleep with my own husband.
Where are you sleeping?
I'm sleeping in the spare bedroom.
Is it easier for you to sleep there?
No. I have no safe haven.
No matter where I go in this
house, I can't find relief.
This case pose some
real challenges for me
From the moment I stepped
foot on this property,
it was clear there was an entity
that was extremely hostile towards women.
I had a strong feeling
it would come after me.
There's something here.
But I don't know what it is.
Overwhelming panic, overwhelming fear,
and got to get away.
This is a living woman?
Yes.
Moving from room to room to room to room.
And the thing...
this thing's saying,
"You're mine. You can't escape."
And I hear a deep male voice.
I feel like he
comes up from the grave.
He was alive. He was a living person once.
This is...
it's very creepy.
It's very... this
is creepy.
This shadow man... he
shot up from the ground.
***
evil strikes.
He holds her down,
and he's telling her, "I've got you."
As Deanna led me from room to room,
it was obvious there
was no place in her house
where she felt safe.
But what was going on in her spare bedroom
was even more disturbing.
As I was asleep, I just felt this stroking.
And then, when I opened my eyes to look,
there was this woman in
period dress, late 1800s.
So, if you saw a sketch or a photo of her,
would you recognize her?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Anything else going on in here?
- Yes.
When I wake up,
this is what I have on me
in the middle of my back.
Is there anything else that
you are experiencing here?
Yes, I have this one particular dream
that just keeps reoccurring.
This shadow
man...
he shot up from the ground, just "Pfoom!"
And then I opened my eyes,
like, "Deanna, it's a dream.
"Get out of this. It's a dream. Wake up."
And when I woke up,
he was standing at the side of the bed,
looking at me.
Seeing this entity
is the worst experience
that I've had in
this household...
the one that haunts me in my sleep.
He was about 7 foot tall, red eyes.
He had, like, a hat.
And as soon as you saw
him, you know it's evil.
She thinks they're
dreams, but they're not dreams.
She's awake.
He holds her down, and he's telling her,
"I smell you. I taste you. I've got you."
He comes to the side of the bed.
He's always, like, over
her, hovering over her.
He manipulates how he's seen.
He has a hat
A black hat.
It's giving me chills down my back.
But it really is very disturbing.
I was coming up the steps,
and then I felt two hands just, like that.
- So that hard?
- That hard.
I was shoved.
I believe that there
was an evil entity present
that pushed me down the steps.
There's nothing you can
do to protect yourself.
There's just nothing you can do.
You must be frightened
every time you got to
come up these stairs, then.
Yeah.
It feels like somebody's
literally going like,
"You're not coming up here.
No, you don't."
Like, I just feel that coming
down the stairs towards me.
What I felt on the stairwell
was one of the more powerful
forces I've ever encountered.
It clearly did not want me
entering that upstairs bedroom.
And once I stepped
inside, I understood why.
It's almost like a seducing,
like, soothing.
And he can destroy you.
Having spoken with Deanna,
I couldn't wait to hear what
her husband, Tom, had to say.
This guy's a pharmacist, but
what came out of his mouth
was not what you'd expect to hear
from someone who has a
scientific background.
Are you a skeptic at all?
Certain things, I can't find
a reason for or an answer for.
I have physically seen
scratches on Deanna's
back that I cannot explain
and some bruises on her.
As the man of the house, you
do feel kind of powerless,
'cause you don't know
what you are up against.
It's not like you can just
call 911 and take care of it,
'cause you don't know
what you're dealing with.
Okay, but you've had some
experiences, is that right?
Yes.
I hear footsteps. I don't see anything.
Where'd you hear the footsteps?
It sounded like they
were walking on the roof
when we were in the bedroom.
And when we're in the family room,
it sounds like they're going
up and down the steps here
to the basement and to the bedroom.
Do you ever think somebody's
breaking into the house?
I don't think that, 'cause
I do have a security system.
I hate it down here.
I hate it.
It's a short man.
He's angry, this one.
He's, like, always angry.
I feel like he's gonna attack me,
like he's gonna beat the out of me.
Deanna and I were
sitting at the kitchen table,
and it wasn't long, I said,
"Hey, I feel a burn on my arm."
And I had a long-sleeve shirt
on, rolled up the sleeve,
and I had a single scratch mark across it.
And coming out, like, right in this area,
there was, like, a black
mist coming out of the wall.
What is this thing?
I see a black mist.
This is the angry guy from the basement,
And it just goes "Whoosh" at the person.
He has hostility toward women.
Yep.
I feel like he's capable
of harming someone.
Next...
He was pretty ruthless.
An entity hungers for victims.
He hates them. He hates them.
At this point, our investigation
read like something in
the police blotter...
"Woman attacked in her
sleep, assailant unknown."
I needed more.
I started digging into the
history of Deanna's property,
and I found out it was
once owned by a violent man,
who settled disputes with a gun.
The original settler
was a man named John Digges.
He was granted 10,000 acres of land.
This whole 10,000 acres
was called Digges' Choice.
Where on this map would
my clients' house be?
Right here.
Okay.
He had a fairly sizable
plantation that he farmed,
but he also wanted to
sell the rest of the land
and make as much money
as he could off of it.
The problem was, there were other settlers
that were coming in along
the edges of this property
instead of buying land from him.
He didn't like that very much.
He and his sons would go out with guns
- and try to run them off.
- Wow.
He was pretty ruthless
with the way he enforced it.
I'm seeing this guy when he was alive.
Older man.
He had this power to
control their destinies,
and that's what he's still doing.
My...
And he says, "I can smell it.
I can smell it, and I can taste it on him."
Smell what?
Fear.
He hates them. He hates them.
So, I found evidence
of a ruthless landowner
who would shoot first
and ask questions later.
And if that weren't bad enough,
I also found out about
a woman named Lydia Small
who once lived there,
and she lost four kids to drownings.
This place was a deathtrap.
The drownings of her
four children were just the start.
In 1907, she had a son.
His name was John Jacob,
and he died of what was at
the time called convulsions.
And then sadly, shortly thereafter,
she lost her husband, as well.
So now, after all this
tragedy with this woman,
what ended up happening to her?
Well, on April 18th of 1939,
Lydia herself passed away.
She just wore out after
dealing with the loss
and the hardship that she'd
suffered all those years.
Her body just eventually gave out.
There's a woman that's,
like, really losing it,
like, losing her
She's just always, like, crying.
And then I see a casket coming out.
And then I see this woman...
Just a mess.
I picked up on a woman
who suffered loss after loss after loss.
She was just surrounded by death.
It might explain
why this property felt
like it was one giant grave,
just waiting to bury its next victim.
I think there's a lot
of things that happened
one right after the other here.
I think she gets sick.
She wastes away, but I don't know
if that's, like, from her emotional loss,
because I feel this extreme anger
and this extreme sadness.
Next...
This house is extremely unsafe for women.
The shocking reveal.
He just came up with such a force
and just went "Vroom!"
clients confront their demons.
Is he trying to kill her?
Yes.
Who will prevail
... The living or the dead?
Let the divine light descend!
Amy, I'd like you
to meet Deanna and Tom.
They've been living
through hell, basically.
In the last few years,
it's gotten real physical.
My heart was just racing,
my hands are sweating.
I'm thinking, "My
gosh. It's finally here."
So I was very nervous and very apprehensive
about meeting Amy and
what she was gonna tell us.
One of the things that I got
was dead women who were suffering.
But the one that stood out the most to me
was freaking out, crying.
And then the door opened,
and a casket came out of the front door.
Whoever that person was who died,
it was extremely sudden.
In the end, she became sick
from not dealing with this death.
Now, you see a woman, right?
Yes.
This woman is, just like you said,
very sickly.
So, do you think this is the woman you saw?
I don't know, but I did do a sketch.
Wow.
That's her.
That's who I see.
It's overwhelming for
me that Amy saw this woman.
But to have somebody see what I saw,
it makes me feel better,
that it's not in my head, that it's real.
There was a woman that
lived on your property line.
Her name was Lydia Small.
This is a stack of articles
regarding her loss in life.
She lived here?
She lived on the property line.
Turns out, she lost four
children to drowning accidents,
three of them in the same quarry.
My gosh.
It was amazing.
Steve validated everything
Amy said about Lydia Small.
Now, the whole tragedy with
Lydia and what she went through,
I think the whole thing
just took a toll on her
and her body just
deteriorated down to nothing.
It's pretty sad.
Anything else go on?
There's this individual I met
on the first floor... a male...
and I was scared.
He really hates women.
And when I started going
up to the room upstairs,
I felt someone pushing me back,
being like, "No, you
are not coming up here."
Well, that's one of the
big reasons we're here.
Deanna, tell Amy what happened to you.
One night, I was going
up the steps to go to bed,
and he just came up with such a force,
and just went "Vroom!" Wow.
She actually moved into
the downstairs bedroom...
Yes...'cause she's afraid
to go upstairs and go to sleep.
Really?
Because I did see a woman
who was going from bedroom to bedroom,
trying to get away from him,
and one of the things that
I heard him saying to her
was, "I've got you. You're
mine. There's no escape."
In that bedroom, I was having a dream,
And then, when I opened up my eyes,
he's standing right there.
And he told me that nobody
can help me now... I was his.
I did do a sketch of what I saw.
Amy, that's him.
That's him.
My God, Tom.
That's the man I told you about.
I just felt
like I couldn't breathe.
It was very bad.
It's just horrible.
But she got it just right.
Now, she wakes up in the morning,
she's got bruises, scratches.
Wow.
Now, is this thing capable of causing this?
Sure. Yes. Yes.
Do you know anything about
him or who he might be or...
Yeah. He was absolutely
in a power position.
He did terrible things throughout his life.
He is attached to the property.
The original guy that
owned the place...
his name was John Digges.
So, he was a powerful guy and ruthless,
you know, in the way he did his business.
Yeah, that is interesting. Okay.
So, what does he want?
His one main goal is to
go after the women here.
Is he trying to kill her?
Yes.
When Amy told me that
this house is unsafe for women,
I was overwhelmed.
How do you stop this?
What do I got to do? What can I do?
Because it needs to end.
A male witch who's also a medium
needs to be called in here.
And he needs to call all
of the dead women to him.
And then he is going to
summon the evil dead male.
You cannot be here.
They are going to put him
where he needs to be forever,
where he can do no more
harm to anyone ever again.
Are you gonna take Amy's advice?
Ever since Amy and Steve have left,
the activity here has been off the charts.
It's just been horrible.
And I think it knows what it's up against,
and it doesn't want that,
and it's been taking it out on Tom and I.
Deanna and I took Amy's advice
and found a local male witch medium
and to have him come into the house
and cleanse it, go through the ritual.
And Deanna and I could not be present.
He started at the
top floor of the house
and cleansed each room
with sage and frankincense.
The purpose of the ritual
was to push all the entities into one room,
which was the living room,
and that's where he set up his altar,
so he could deal with the
evil entities in that one spot.
I call now upon the spirits of this house.
Those who wish to leave and
move on to the other side,
move into the light and into
the arms of those who love you.
He gave the entities a
chance to go out on their own,
and the ones that
did not choose that...
he sent them out with his ritual.
For about me flames the pentagram.
Within me shines the six-rayed star.
Above me, the glory of God.
The supreme banishing ritual
puts a giant star at
each of the four corners,
which is set to protect the house.
Virgo, Isis, Mighty Mother,
Scorpio, Apophis, Destroyer.
In addition to that, it actually
summons the four archangels
to watch over the house, as well.
Let the divine light descend!
This temple is duly closed.
After the male witch medium left,
I do notice that in my own
bedroom, where I was attacked,
that room used to be ice-cold,
and it felt so much better,
and that one particular
room felt a lot warmer.
Our hope is that we can not live in fear,
that we can be at peace,
that we can just have a
home like everybody else,
and go on with our lives.
Deanna and Tom made a good choice
by bringing in a strong,
masculine witch medium.
The fact that they are already experiencing
a change in their home is a
good sign the ritual worked.
I believe if they remain vigilant,
they should be able to stay in their home
and live in peace and tranquility.