Makes people kind of **** crazy here.
Tonight on
"Dead Files Revisited"...
She's so scared.
a second look
at some of Amy and Steve's
most terrifying cases.
Now, apparently, he went nuts.
New information.
When Amy said there was
a devil, I was floored.
Startling revelations.
I was stuck in that room. I was panicking.
First...
It's climbing the ceilings
and climbing the walls.
we travel
back to a Michigan home...
I have nightmares.
Where a deadly force is unleashed.
I will have bruises on my thighs.
From the depths of hell.
You would call it the devil.
Then...
So he wants to kill women, really.
At a California hotel...
He definitely strangled his victim.
a fascination with the dead...
Don't leave, don't leave, don't leave.
threatens the living.
There's just some presence
here, and it's not a good thing.
Can this
frightened business owner...
That's why I never say I own the
place. I say the place owns me.
Break free of her obsession...
That scares me. It sounds like
you want to stay here forever.
before it's too late?
I call upon the divine energy
to enter in this sacred space.
Something bad's going to happen
My name is Amy Allan.
There's panic.
And it's almost like a butchering.
I see dead people.
They all died horribly.
I speak to dead people.
Get out of here.
And they speak to me.
Vicious.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
It doesn't matter where
you are. I'll find you.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide detective.
This guy's a real piece of work.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
I feel like I live in a house of hell.
It's my job to reveal them.
This is not good.
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end...
I want my life back.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
Is he trying to kill her?
Or time to get out.
My God.
This is going to kill us.
I've seen and heard
a lot of strange things
in the years I've been working with Amy.
But the terror described by the
homeowners in Leslie, Michigan,
was right up there.
This poor family was being ripped apart,
and I wanted Amy and I
to do whatever we could
to keep them together.
We've seen apparitions.
We hear footsteps. Then
the last couple years,
it has become extremely physical.
I contacted Steve and Amy
because our daughter came to us
and showed us some severe
scratches that she had received.
And at that point, I knew things were,
you know, getting out of control.
If you can't see something,
then how do you stop it from happening?
Boy.
It did not take me long to realize
that the people who lived here
were surrounded by a
very powerful, evil force.
The living
people here...
It feels like they're,
like, weighted, weighted down
because there's too much...
death here.
It's not...
It's not good.
Okay, so, what's going on in here?
I have physically been
attacked in this room.
I receive scratches.
I actually have a picture
that I took last week.
Geez.
There's a woman.
Living. She has long hair, brown.
She's so scared.
She can't breathe, man.
Is there anything else going on?
I will hear footsteps
coming down the stairs,
and a shadow will appear
walking down the stairways
over there to our basement.
I would describe it like
a man, but as a black mass.
I know it's taller than I am.
There's a really big shadow person here.
It doesn't even have a face.
Really...
big.
I don't like it.
I- I don't think it's good.
It's, like, crawling oddly down the hall.
And it's climbing the ceilings
and climbing the walls...
trying to make me
follow it up the stairs.
Michelle's entire demeanor changed
the moment we stepped foot in her bedroom.
And when she described
what was going on in there,
I understood why.
I have repeated nightmares.
And when I wake up from these dreams,
I will have bruises on my thighs
in the shape of fingerprints.
I wake up scared to death.
It just reminds me of the times
when I was sexually assaulted as a child.
I wasn't aware of that. Okay.
I was chased around by a babysitter
who would strip naked,
and physically assault me, so...
I don't like it
at all, and I do want it to stop.
Okay?
I told myself not to cry.
It's not easy to talk about.
I felt like I could
trust Steve and open up to him.
And I shared some very vulnerable things
that I've never shared with other people,
but I was willing to do that
because I did want to find answers.
This guy ever get arrested for this?
No, he did not.
He committed suicide as a teenager.
Okay. All right.
I'm sorry.
I know. It's gonna be all right.
You'll be okay.
This woman again...
Something happened to her.
What?
I don't know. Like, she was
physically abused or something.
I was feeling the living
woman's fear and panic
throughout the house,
and it was very intense and uncomfortable.
There's, like, this creepy guy.
And this woman
in particular...
She's aware that he does bad things.
I think he killed himself,
and I think he would like to
make others kill themselves.
He's very disturbed.
His endgame is death.
Next...
a dark force descends.
Makes people kind of **** crazy here.
And fear closes in.
Get inside the living dude's head.
What does he tell him to do? Kill himself.
And in our
second investigation...
I never say I own the
place. The place owns me.
A vengeful spirit's motives are exposed.
I do believe that this
male was a serial killer.
What struck me about this case
was that every single family
member said they were attacked.
And what happened to
Michelle's husband, Daniel,
I got to admit, I didn't see coming.
I put my circular saw down to my right.
And at that point, I looked,
and the saw had levitated.
It went through my tennis shoes
and cut off my three middle toes.
You're joking. No, sir.
I mean, I've had friends that
have hurt themselves pretty bad,
and they never want to admit
that they made a mistake.
You know, I'd tell you if I made a mistake.
I've looked at it a million times.
I didn't place the saw down on my own foot.
You set it down?
Because I'm very cognizant of this place
and how people have gotten hurt here.
This creepy guy...
I just want to make them bleed.
This entity was very devious.
He wanted to toy with people
and mess with their minds.
He creeps.
He's a creeper.
I see him, like, coming
up behind a living dude,
and then his head is,
like, right here, you know?
Gets inside the living dude's head.
He tells him what to do.
What does he tell him to do?
I think kill himself, you know?
I could see that
this family was suffering,
and even though Michelle was convinced
her injuries were caused by the paranormal,
I still had to rule out that
they weren't self-inflicted.
So, I have a client.
She's actually waking up with
the bruising from an attack.
What would I, as an investigator, look for
in a person to see if they're
that type of personality
to do that to themselves?
They have a hard time with their emotions.
They like a lot of attention
directed towards them.
Yeah, that doesn't describe this woman.
- She's the total opposite.
- Okay.
Could those dreams possibly cause bruises?
There's no clinical
evidence that I'm aware of
that bruising and scratches
just manifest themselves.
This is that weird
**** creature thing...
crawling oddly down the hall.
Like, I don't know what this
**** thing is, really.
This creature in front of me was pure evil,
and that's when I realized it
was manipulating the creeper guy
to do its bidding and torment the living.
- Does it interact physically?
- Yes.
It makes people kind of **** crazy.
Turns out Michelle and her family
weren't the only residents
in that house to suffer.
During my research, I
discovered that the property
was once owned by two brothers
who had a miserable time there.
Lafayette Peek and his wife, Harriet,
purchased the property in the 1860s.
And along with his brother, Theodore,
they ran an apple orchard.
In addition to Lafayette's
children dying, his brother,
Theodore, and his wife,
Sally, also had five children,
and they lost three of
those children, as well.
He definitely had a mental
breakdown of some sort.
He was wandering through the streets.
He was shouting and screaming
and disturbing the neighbors.
His daughter filed a
petition with the court,
asking him to be declared insane
and committed to the
Kalamazoo State Hospital
for treatment.
Well, that's kind of a
sad story for this guy.
Unfortunately, that's not where it ends.
I also located several other neighbors
who had various forms of mental illness.
That's odd.
So it wasn't...
You know mental illness
can run in families, but...
It seems to have run in this neighborhood.
This person feels crazy.
This house, it's caused
people to go insane.
Wow.
Something's wrong with
these **** people, man.
This place is, like, insane.
Coming up...
Just pitch-black and huge.
What happened after the investigation.
Into the black candle you shall go!
I clear you now from this home!
Amy, I'd like you to
meet Dan and Michelle.
This is their home.
Now, things are pretty bad here
When Amy came, I knew she was going to find
something in my house.
But what it was, I did not have a clue.
One of the things
that also seemed to be a
constant throughout the walk
was the feeling of people thinking
that they're going crazy.
Sometimes, I felt like I was going crazy
because of the physical attacks I received.
So, during my research of
the property, it turns out
there's a long history of mental illness
associated with the land here.
Back in the 1860s, the original owners
of your property
were two brothers...
Lafayette and Theodore Peek.
Both brothers had five kids.
Both brothers lost three kids.
But it got a little bit worse for Theodore.
Apparently,
he went nuts...
walking up and down the
streets, talking to himself,
to the point where his daughter
tried to have him committed.
The thing is, there's been other cases
of neighbors in the area going crazy, too.
I saw a woman with long, brown hair,
and she was panicking.
I could feel her fear.
She felt extremely overwhelmed.
Somebody that's living?
This is a living person, yes.
I really knew it was
me. There was no doubt in my mind.
There had been times when things
that are happening in this home
definitely have
gotten to me...
because you feel like you're going crazy.
One of the other things that
I got was this female was,
at some point in her
life, abused by a male.
I'm sorry, sweetie. I didn't want to
have to bring it up at the table.
You know, could you just share with her
what happened when you were a kid?
When I was a little girl, I
was left with a male babysitter
who sexually abused me
on several occasions.
And he has since committed suicide.
Why'd you have that big reaction like that?
I ran into a person in the basement,
and I referred to him as "The Creeper."
He did not die that long ago,
and I did get that he killed himself.
I did do a sketch.
Take a look.
I knew immediately
that it was the babysitter
who attacked me as a child.
For her to hit on that, I
knew that Amy's for real.
And I've woken up with fingerprints,
bruises on my thighs.
And I get scratched.
My daughter, she has woken up with...
Similar bruises.
My goodness.
And they're unexplainable.
This is Michelle with
some scratches on her chest area.
The creeper guy, he
had very bad intentions.
He's trying to plant harmful thoughts,
wanting the males in the
household to commit suicide...
which is very concerning.
He'll never be successful.
But there is something else that's here.
The first time I saw it
was when I was about to go up the stairs,
and it was just pitch-black and huge.
Take a look.
Sorry, it's really not a good situation.
We see a shadow every night
come across the stairwell
to the basement...
and it is completely dark.
You cannot see through it.
This thing is extremely old...
never been human.
And it's been wreaking
havoc around this area
for quite some time.
It's caused people to go insane.
Could that explain what
happened to the Peeks
that lived on this property at some point?
Absolutely, yes.
From a Christian standpoint,
you would call it the devil.
When Amy said
there was a devil in my house,
I was floored.
It was just sickening and overwhelming.
There are many of them all over the world.
And they are much more
powerful than demons.
Whatever it is that
scares you, whatever it is
that will harm you,
it's going to provide it.
You have the devil.
You have the creeper.
You would have to hit
everything simultaneously.
So I would recommend a Wiccan
do a clearing and a banishment.
You would have the minister do a blessing.
I would also recommend therapy for you.
What are you gonna do?
Since Amy and
Steve came, I started therapy.
But the activity actually escalated.
Purify, bless, and
protect this sacred home!
We found a local
Wiccan to come in and help us
and perform a banishment on
the evil entities in our home,
and to do a cleansing.
I remove all negative
energy, frequencies, vibrations
that do not serve this sacred vessel.
Into the earth you go.
He then scraped
our auras with an athame,
which peeled off the bad energy
and sent them back to the earth.
I remove all negative energy
off this sacred vessel.
He also performed another
ritual that didn't involve us
that was for our home
and the land we live on.
I call upon the divine energy
to enter in this sacred space.
And I cast this circle big and bright.
I cast it now, this magical rite.
He started in the center of our
home and worked his way outward,
spreading light to surround and push out
around the area we live
in and to protect us.
With water and salt, I
consecrate this sacred space.
As I light this golden candle's flame,
I invoke Lord Shiva into this domain.
Aid us in destroying all darkness
and turning it to light.
As I light this black candle's flame,
all negative energy in
this home becomes contained.
Into the black candle you shall go.
I clear you now from this home!
The minister came
into our home after the Wiccan
to help seal and bless the home.
Protect this family.
Great spirit, please bring
an angel to bring happiness.
When the minister saged my husband and I,
that helped ground us, as she stated,
while she went through the ritual.
And the feeling was very positive.
She went through the
house and did her own cleansing.
And she actually posted
an angel by every window.
Great spirit, please send one
of your angels to protect, guide.
Thank you, great spirit, for
bringing this angel to help.
I feel like the energy
in the home is much better.
I'm definitely looking forward
to making new, happy
memories in our home now.
I feel like as long as we keep the attitude
that we're gonna do what we need
to do to keep our home cleansed,
that it will stay that way.
Demons are always
difficult to clear from a home,
and I think that Michelle and
Dan will have to stay vigilant
to keep it away.
I'm glad they're following my advice,
and if they stay on top of
it, I think they should be able
to life in their home
in peace and tranquility.
Our case in Santa Paula, California,
was one for the books.
Our client Rosanna was obsessed
with hanging on to the hotel she owned,
even though her family
didn't want her to be there,
and it was tearing them apart.
In the end, this investigation
felt more like an intervention.
10 years ago, I came here
and I saw this building that was beautiful.
But it was in such
disrepair, I told my husband,
let's do something about this building.
This building needs help."
So, I convinced my family.
It was my idea, my project.
And my family really resents that.
I became obsessed.
Geez.
When I first
walked into this place,
I sort of surrendered to the
energy that was happening,
not knowing what it entailed.
I feel really sick.
Like, I can't, like, breathe.
I think there's something in the air.
Boy.
There's a lot of commotion here.
From the beginning, I
noticed something strange.
As expected, the dead in this hotel
had extremely strong
ties to the past...
but also to someone in the present.
And those types of connections
can be very difficult to break.
This is not good.
Next...
There's a lot of commotion here.
horrors buried in the past...
Apparently, he had notches on his gun
for the amount of people he killed.
Still haunt the present.
And I thought, "My God."
What kind of experiences
are people having in here?
We get people that wake up
in the middle of the night
saying that they can't
sleep here because they feel
that their bodies are
being pulled to the floor.
There are people who hear
their names being whispered,
like, "Steve."
Wow.
Everybody's, like, ready to snap.
My husband does not
feel the attraction to this place
like I do.
He pretty much resents
the fact that I was so
in love with this place
and that I took our family
in for this experience.
There's something
here that I don't like.
It's kind of making me anxious.
Like, that kind of
rock-in-your-stomach feeling.
There was so much scattered
energy inside this hotel.
Like, all of the entities were
screaming at me the same time,
trying to be heard.
It was overwhelming and very threatening.
Like, the fear is just disgusting.
Like, I'm stressed out.
I feel very stressed out.
I feel like something
bad's going to happen.
It was clear Rosanna
had totally fallen in love
with that old hotel.
But when she told me about what
happened on the third floor,
it made me wonder
why she didn't pack up
her bags a long time ago.
My husband and I went on a trip.
And when we were on this
trip, we got the call from hell
saying that, "Your building is on fire
and we don't know if we're
gonna be able to save it."
Wow.
It was just growing all over.
It was right above this area.
Anybody get hurt?
Nobody got hurt, thank God.
If that isn't a sign to
cut your losses and get out,
I don't know what is.
But Rosanna wasn't going anywhere.
In fact, she used the
insurance money she got
to rebuild the place.
Someone's yelling.
People running. There's people running.
There was something like a
fire or something because,
um... they're all trying
to get out as quickly as possible.
Have you ever had an actual
paranormal experience?
Well, I was gonna use the restroom.
And it was in an area that was isolated.
And as I closed the door,
I noticed that the
doorknob... it moved.
Then the doorknob fell to the floor.
And I thought, "My God."
I started hitting the
door and yelling for help.
Now, how long were you
stuck? About a half an hour.
They found me just devastated,
just... just sobbing.
I was panicking because I was
in a room inside of a room,
and nobody knew where I was.
And that's why I never say I own the place.
I say the place owns me.
And you really believe that.
Okay.
I see this guy
walking down the hallway.
He wears all black.
Yeah.
**** me.
Yeah, he doesn't like...
he doesn't like women, for sure.
This dead man followed me
everywhere I went on the third floor.
It was becoming very clear
that he didn't want me there.
Yeah. The guy in the black is bad.
He's always been bad.
It seemed like nothing was
gonna get Rosanna to leave this place.
And when I spoke to her husband, Tom,
he didn't mince words
about the tension it caused.
Well, Tom, I was talking to your wife.
She has become obsessed with this place.
Would you agree with that?
Yeah, it's one of the
few things that she says
that I'll agree with completely.
I'm surprised she admitted that.
Her attachment to the
place is a little spooky.
I just feel like Rosanna's
becoming more and more attached
to this hotel. I'm not nearly as attached.
In fact, I'm a little repelled
by the environment here.
One of the doors to an
upstairs room was locked.
And this was a room
that was not supposed to
be occupied by any guest.
The door was locked from inside.
We're concerned. We're thinking
there's a guy in the room.
He's not supposed to be
there. He's a stranger.
What's going on there?
I remove the door.
And I look around.
Nobody's in the closet,
nobody's in the bathroom,
and the windows were
locked from the inside.
There's just some presence
here, and it's not a good thing.
And that, I find genuinely scary.
The guy in the
black, he's very physical.
Yeah, I think this is him
because I feel that same...
weight, that same fear.
The more time I spent on the third floor,
the more hostile this entity became.
It was like he was hiding something
he didn't want me to discover.
He doesn't like it when people are in here.
What does he do?
He makes it, like, weird...
like, loud and disturbing and shocking.
"Just get them out."
He's constantly touching
me, so I don't like that.
Next...
Everybody was scared to death of him.
Amy confronts a cold-blooded killer.
Definitely strangled his victims.
Occasionally, he'd have to shoot them.
The Glen Tavern Inn
was built in the early 1900s,
right in the heart of old town Santa Paula.
I found a local historian
who told me this location had
a very dark and violent past.
There had been a shooting,
which had been initiated
by this outlaw Joe Dye,
who challenged a man for
having an affair with his wife.
The man's name was Herman Haines.
Joe Dye shot Herman Haines in 1886.
So, what kind of guy was Joe Dye?
He was a known outlaw.
He was known to be very
mean and very violent
and a high temper.
Everybody was scared to death of him.
He even had notches on his
gun as the number of victims.
He had several victims?
Yes.
The guy in the black is not good.
I think he's from way
back, like 18-something.
Traveled all the time.
I saw a lot of entities on this walk,
but I sensed that this one posed
the most danger to the living.
I think he killed prostitutes, mainly.
He definitely strangled his victims.
Occasionally, he'd have to shoot them.
As if a trigger-happy
outlaw wasn't bad enough,
I found out that one of
California's worst disasters
took place right in this town.
A 185-foot dam broke
open, killing hundreds.
I spoke to an author
who gave me a bird's-eye
view of what happened.
On the night of March 12, 1928,
it was just a few minutes before midnight,
the St. Francis Dam burst,
and it released 12.4
billion gallons of water.
The flood wave was 140 feet high.
What kind of a body count we talking about?
The official body count was about 500.
Where I'm investigating, Glen Tavern Inn,
was that affected by this?
The first floor received damage.
It was on high enough ground.
So, the Glen Tavern Inn
became a refuge for families
that lost their homes,
that were trying to locate
the bodies of their loved ones.
Okay.
Something about the carpet was wet.
And the floor was wet.
There's a lot of arguing over this.
What's going on here?
Next...
I do believe that this
male was a serial killer.
The shocking reveal.
Apparently, he had notches on his gun
for the amount of people he killed.
Clients face
the terrifying truth.
In the middle of the night,
I would just burst out crying.
Will their nightmare ever end?
You need to leave.
Well, Amy, I'd like
you to meet Tom and Rosanna.
Rosanna's gotten obsessed with this place.
The activity's bad here,
and it's tearing their family apart.
So, Rosanna wants to know
if it's safe to stay here,
while the rest of the family
wants you to talk her into leaving.
I was watching Amy across the
table, and she was hard to read.
I found that a little mysterious,
and it made me all the more interested
in finding out what it was she had to say.
When I was on the second floor,
and I kind of felt like
a fire had taken place.
I was seeing all the people running,
but I didn't feel like anybody died.
We had a fire in 2005,
and it was on the second and third floor.
It was a serious fire,
but nobody was injured.
Okay.
I actually have a photo
of the actual fire when it was happening.
Wow!
The other thing that I got
was when I walked into the lobby.
I saw the carpets were
wet. There was water.
It seemed to be a pretty
stressful situation, so...
Back in 1928, St. Francis Dam gave way.
The Glen Tavern itself,
the only damage it received
was the first floor...
water damage.
Okay.
The rest of the town got hit really bad.
The water got as high as 140 feet,
actually swept its way through this town.
They estimate 500 died.
Now, the other thing is
everybody that survived that flood
wound up in this hotel at some point,
you know, to seek refuge.
I was really aghast
by seeing those pictures.
Just, I couldn't believe
what a tragedy that was,
and Steve brought a lot of information,
that this place had a major
role during that tragedy.
Rosanna, do me a
favor, just explain to Amy
about how obsessed you
really are with this place.
Well, I feel at
home. I love this place.
But my family, they don't like
the fact that I love it so much.
They're kind of jealous, I think.
That scares me. It sounds like
you want to stay here forever.
Some people, they'll just
be attracted to locations
where they were in previous lives.
I don't think Rosanna
was surprised to hear
she had past-life
connections to the hotel.
But I was concerned she wouldn't understand
just how much danger she was in.
The feelings that you've
had of anger and anxiety
are mostly caused by one entity,
and I met him on the third floor.
He'll do whatever it
takes to keep people out.
What I was able to get out of him
was that he is male, was a serial killer.
There's one guy that came across
that might have fit the bill.
It's a guy, Joe Dye.
Not a good guy.
Apparently, he had notches on his gun
for the amount of people he killed.
I got a photo of him.
- He's a crazy-looking guy.
- Ew!
Those eyes.
Wow.
So, he wants to kill women, really.
I do know that there is something here,
but I also feel that there's
a lot of protection...
a lot of good.
And if there is bad entities,
I'm sure that the good
ones will knock them out.
Mnh-mnh.
You have a connection here,
and, unfortunately, in this situation,
you have deceased individuals here
who have a connection with you, as well.
And they're going to try to keep you here
and manipulate you and blind you
and bring that other person that they knew
more and more to life in the present day.
This is your life now.
And you need to move
forward, not backwards.
So, what I would like you
to do is bring in mediums.
So, there's a mental medium,
a physical medium, and a psychic medium.
So, they would
do two things...
clear the residual energy from this place
and also move on as many of
the deceased people as they can.
Following that, you should really consider
selling this place and walking away.
Will they let me go?
It's about you letting them go
and letting this building go.
You've done your time.
Since the investigation,
the activity increased for me.
In the middle of the night, like at 3:30,
my computer would just start
talking, and it was closed.
The doors would just open by themselves.
Couldn't believe it.
I would just burst out crying.
We did take Amy's advice
and bring in mediums
and assess the place
and possibly even get rid
of the negative energy.
I'd be very happy if one
of the mediums told Rosanna
that she should start detaching
herself from the hotel.
We need to banish the spirits,
and we need to get rid of
the energies that are there,
because this is our space.
The first medium,
she was a mentalist,
and she went around the place.
When I walk around, I use my hands,
and then I'm pulled to particular spaces
that I want to focus on.
I feel in this town,
there's so many secrets,
and this building is no exception.
This whole thing is about
clearing the building.
I strongly believe
that there's a lot of stories
here that need to be exposed,
and those souls don't have closure.
So, when I get right over here,
it gets very hard to breathe.
I feel like I'm being suffocated.
I feel there's something around my throat.
Things just feel very uncomfortable,
and he's a bad spirit.
Definitely feels very heavy over here.
It felt like I was being choked,
I was being suffocated almost,
and it was very bad.
And then it felt a
little bit more panicked.
You're not gonna be able
to do harm to anybody,
because this is our space,
and now we want to be
here, so you need to leave.
The second medium came in
to cleanse the place where
we had a horrible fire.
All I see is sort of bits and
pieces of what happened up here.
And there's, like, a fire.
I don't know if it was,
like, a structural problem.
I feel like somebody
came out of this door...
and was, like, screaming or something.
This is so much energy.
I definitely felt that there
was a pushing of the energy up.
I'm releasing all trapped residual energy
within these walls.
Only love, light, and peace may enter.
The third medium
that came was a writer.
I am an automatic writer,
so the information that I receive
comes through my hand
in the form of writing.
There is some dark energy here.
Rose... Anna
Rosanna,
she wants to...
She wants to find me.
So, someone's coming through.
It was very shocking
that the spirits were connecting with her.
I had a very emotional reaction to it.
Behind...
behind her...
soul, crying.
I am so much...
pain, anger.
She needs to leave.
I receive information that the spirit feels
is most important for them
to hear in that moment.
Okay.
It's time to resolve...
turmoil in the family.
Yes, she... she
needs to just go.
They want you to know...
I mean, you heard it...
that there's nothing to fear.
They're safe.
The spirits are saying
you don't have to take
care of them anymore,
and that relieves something within me.
So if this place is in the right hands,
I can see myself walking away.
This was an
extremely challenging case.
Past-life connections are
not only difficult to sever,
but can also be very destructive
if you don't know how to handle them.
I hope Rosanna has seen the light
and will follow through
on letting go of the hotel
and re-engaging with her present life.