Subs created by: David Coleman.
- Tonight..
- Stop it.
On "Dead Files Revisited"..
A second look at some of Amy and
Steve's most terrifying cases..
Ooh, look.
- New information..
- It was horrifying to hear.
Startling revelations.
I was afraid of what she was gonna find.
- First..
- Stop it.
A return to Wichita, Kansas, where
a woman's violent encounters..
The veins all started popping out.
Left her family fearing for their lives.
It's weird.
And Amy sensed the
house wasn't the problem.
If this thing gets in,
you'll lose your mind.
Then..
We travel back to Santaquin, Utah..
Apparitions here follow us home.
Where a family Restaurant
held an awful secret..
They're all dead together.
And horror lurked in the shadows.
- I couldn't hardly even look at it.
- Oh, my God.
It's like a little pit of hell.
Did they follow Amy's advice?
If Amy told you you better not stay here,
you gotta get out, what would you do?
There's something down there.
My name is Amy Allan.
A lot of dead people are here.
I see dead people.
This is not good.
I speak to dead people..
He is very pissed off.
And they speak to me..
The house is angry.
But there's only way to
know if my findings are real.
He's killed people.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Dischiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide Detective..
He got shot at his house?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
Aren't you terrified being here?
It's my job to reveal 'em.
That sounds like something
out of "The Exorcist".
But Steve and I never speak..
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
It's bad.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay..
I'd like some answers.
Or time to get out.
Our investigation in Wichita
was one I'll never forget.
Our client Kristen sent me a
video that was really intense.
Look. Ewe!
I've never seen this before.
I can't stop it. It's gone crazy.
That video? Bizarre stuff.
...
I realize this was a lot
to ask of Leslie and Bobby,
but it's what needed to be done.
That was the only way they were
going to save their Restaurant,
and more importantly, release the
innocent dead that were trapped there.
- What are you gonna do?
- We'll move on to getting it blessed.
Sounds like a lot of
steps, but we'll take 'em.
Well, you guys are pretty
passionate about this Restaurant.
It sounds like you want the fight.
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
You are. You're fighting
for your life here.
Thank you again, ladies. Appreciate you.
Amy told us that we needed
to get the curse lifted.
And have the place blessed.
But it's just really scary just to
trust anybody with my Restaurant.
The activity has definitely increased.
I don't feel safe here any more.
At this point, leaving the Restaurant
to my daughter Bobby is not an option.
I'm really worried
about her safety here.
It's a shame that Leslie and Bobby didn't
keep their promise to cleanse the property.
And I'm not surprised to find
out the activity has increased.
Until they take action, I'm worried
about what could happen to them,
their employees, and their patrons.
Subs created by: David Coleman.