-  TONIGHT...
- BANG!
...ON "DEAD FILES REVISITED"...
- TERRY TOOK OVER MY BODY.
A SECOND LOOK
AT SOME OF AMY AND STEVE'S
MOST TERRIFYING CASES.
NEW INFORMATION.
EVERYTHING WAS TRUE.
STARTLING REVELATIONS.
THERE'S THINGS OUT THERE
THAT DEFY EXPLANATION.
FIRST--
A RETURN
TO VIRGINIA CITY, NEVADA,
WHERE A FRIGHTENING ENTITY...
- CREEPY.
-  THREATENED A WOMAN'S LIFE...
- I AM SCARED TO DEATH.
AND LED AMY TO PRESCRIBE
A DRASTIC CURE.
I NEVER EVEN HEARD
YOU SAY THAT WORD BEFORE.
THEN...
THERE ARE GHOSTS IN THIS HOUSE.
WE TRAVEL BACK
TO BLACKSHEAR, GEORGIA,
WHERE UNSPEAKABLE TERROR
INVADED A FAMILY'S HOME...
MY DAUGHTER SEES
A GHOST GIRL.
AND THE REVEAL...
-  THAT DROVE AMY TO THE EDGE.
- I'M SORRY.
THERE WAS A GIRL
THAT DIED HERE.
DID THEY FOLLOW
AMY'S ADVICE?
I TOLD YOU THERE WERE
GHOSTS IN THIS HOUSE.
THERE'S SOMETHING DOWN THERE.
MY NAME IS AMY ALLAN.
A LOT OF DEAD PEOPLE ARE HERE.
I SEE DEAD PEOPLE.
THIS IS NOT GOOD.
I SPEAK TO DEAD PEOPLE...
HE IS VERY PISSED OFF.
AND THEY SPEAK TO ME...
THE HOUSE IS ANGRY.
BUT THERE'S ONLY WAY TO KNOW
IF MY FINDINGS ARE REAL.
HE'S KILLED PEOPLE.
I RELY ON MY PARTNER.
I'M STEVE Di SCHIAVI.
I'M A RETIRED NEW YORK CITY
HOMICIDE DETECTIVE...
HE GOT SHOT AT HIS HOUSE?
AND I KNOW EVERY PERSON,
EVERY HOUSE HAS SECRETS.
- AREN'T YOU TERRIFIED BEING HERE?
- IT'S MY JOB TO REVEAL 'EM.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE SOMETHING
OUT OF "THE EXORCIST."
BUT STEVE AND I NEVER
SPEAK...
- WE NEVER COMMUNICATE DURING
AN INVESTIGATION. - UNTIL THE VERY END.
IT'S BAD.
AND WE UNCOVER IF IT'S SAFE
FOR YOU TO STAY...
I'D LIKE SOME ANSWERS.
OR TIME TO GET OUT.
VIRGINIA CITY, NEVADA,
JUST A HALF-HOUR OUTSIDE OF RENO
WAS LIKE STEPPING BACK
INTO THE WILD WEST.
AMY AND I WERE CALLED IN
BY A WOMAN, DEBBIE,
WHO WORKED AT A MUSEUM
CALLED THE MACKAY MANSION.
SHE WAS AFRAID
...
BUT MY HUSBAND WAS NOT.
I KNEW ROBERT WOULDN'T DO IT.
HE JUST DIDN'T THINK
HE WOULD FEEL COMFORTABLE.
I HAD CONCERNS
ABOUT GOING
TO A CATHOLIC PRIEST
AND HAVING HIM LOOK AT ME
LIKE I WAS CRAZY.
BUT OVER TIME, THE ACTIVITY
WE'VE HAD HERE IN THE HOUSE
HAS BECOME PROGRESSIVELY WORSE.
WE FINALLY DID
WHAT WE NEEDED TO DO.
WE HAD A PRIEST COME IN,
AND HE DID THE STEPS
THAT AMY HAD TALKED ABOUT.
HE GAVE A FUNERAL SPEECH
AND BASICALLY ASKED
THE PEOPLE HERE TO MOVE ON.
FOR THOSE WHO HAVE PASSED
THEIR LIFE HERE,
IT IS NOW TIME FOR YOU TO DEPART
INTO THE LIGHT.
LEAVE THOSE WHO HEREIN LIVE,
CAROL, ROBERT, AND THEIR FAMILY,
IN PEACE.
WE WISH YOU TO GO ON,
TO BE AT PEACE,
TO BE AT REST, AMEN.
NOW THAT WE HAD THE CEREMONY,
I HOPE THAT ALL THE DEAD
THAT ARE IN THIS HOUSE CAN--
CAN GO REST IN PEACE.
I'M SO GLAD
THAT CAROL AND ROBERT
FINALLY TOOK MY ADVICE.
DESPITE SO MUCH TRAGEDY
SURROUNDING THEIR HOUSE,
I'M CONFIDENT
THAT THESE BLESSINGS
WILL HELP PEARLE
AND THE OTHERS MOVE ON.