Subs created by: David Coleman.
Tonight...
Physical pain here.
On "Dead Files Revisited"...
A second look at some of Amy and
Steve's most terrifying cases.
It's kind of creepy.
New information.
Scared the hell out of me.
Startling revelations.
My fear was real.
First a return to Uriah, Alabama.
Where violent encounters...
I fell through the ceiling.
Were just the beginning.
I heard a little girl scream.
What happened after the investigation?
It was terrifying.
- Then...
- A lot of blood in my mouth.
We travel back to
Santa Fe, New Mexico...
It was haunted.
To a notorious prison overrun by evil.
Far worse than any demon.
The monster turns one
woman's world into hell...
Somebody can see into my head.
And leads to a life-changing decision.
It was a bad idea.
Did she follow Amy's advice?
I can't even look.
There's something down there.
My name is Amy Allan.
A lot of dead people are here.
I see dead people.
This is not good.
I speak to dead people...
He is very pissed off.
And they speak to me...
The house is angry.
But there's only way to
know if my findings are real.
He's killed people.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide Detective...
He got shot at his house?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
Aren't you terrified being here?
It's my job to reveal 'em.
That sounds like something
out of "The Exorcist."
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
It's bad.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I'd like some answers.
Or time to get out.
This investigation took us to a
tiny town in Alabama called Uriah.
About an hour from Mobile.
The investigation started with
a call from a woman named Robin.
She's never believed in the paranormal,
but sometimes a near-death experience
...
because then things started
happening in my house.
Hmm, boy.
So I burned it, but I
burned it in the fireplace.
- In the house.
- Oh, [Bleep].
What I'm thinking is that you brought
a little piece of this negative...
To your home.
What you need to have happen...
Is for a medicine man, to..
Come to your house...
And do...
A... Ritual cleansing.
The other thing is that you need
a cleansing ritual of your body,
because it does like to attach.
In a very physical way.
These two things need to
be happening simultaneously.
Okay?
You gonna take her advice?
I did have a medicine
man come to my home.
We walked room to room.
And we prayed.
I did not get a body cleanse.
I really didn't feel like I needed it.
I believe the devil, his minions...
They can't hurt me.
If Sandi's medicine man
performed a proper cleansing,
her home should be safer than it was.
But this thing is also
attracted to her personally.
So until she cleanses herself,
I believe she's still in danger.