Subs created by: David Coleman.
Tonight on "Dead Files Revisited"...
This is nuts.
A second look at some of Amy and
Steve's most terrifying cases.
I'm getting chills up and down my back.
New information.
We were getting to the bottom of it.
Startling revelations.
It was so weird.
First... a return to
Cedar Park, Texas...
I don't come out here at night.
Where a home was under siege.
They burned it down.
Amy exposes monsters
lurking in the trees.
- I see exactly what you just described.
- Lord.
But one question remained.
- How afraid should I be?
- What?
Then...
It was really crazy.
We travel back to Ybor City, Florida...
A lot of dead people are here.
Where a landmark hotel
hides a sinister past.
It was a ghost.
- What happened after the investigation?
- It was a lot of pressure.
And how did it change their lives?
When you see an apparition,
you will never forget it.
There's something down there.
My name is Amy Allan.
A lot of dead people are here.
I see dead people. This is not good.
I speak to dead people...
He is very pissed off.
And they speak to me...
the house is angry.
But there's only way to
know if my findings are real.
He's killed people.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide Detective...
He got shot at his house?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
Aren't you terrified being
here? It's my job to reveal 'em.
That sounds like something
out of "The Exorcist."
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
It's bad.
And we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I'd like some answers.
Or time to get out.
I've heard a lot of strange things
since I started working with Amy.
But our investigation in Cedar Park,
Texas, still makes my head spin.
We were called in by
a woman named Annie.
Who thought the activity around her
home was making her physically ill.
I'm so glad you're here.
What's going on?
...
Looking back Jack and Tessa were lucky.
There were a lot of dead
people in the basement,
and it's fortunate none
of them were dangerous.
They just needed help moving on.
You are safe, the guests are safe.
And the nurse is still working and
doing her job taking care of everybody.
That's what we want is a happy place.
After the reveal I recommended
a very strict cleansing process.
It was going to take a lot of time
to remove that many dead people.
And I can remember thinking,
I hope they take my advice.
Amy's advice was to do a cleansing
downstairs to release the spirits.
To set them free so
that they can move on.
Since then...
My father and I have not seen anything
nor has anybody that works with us.
But when you see an apparition
you will never forget it.
So I still have a little bit of
trepidation about the basement,
and I think that that
will always be there.
Hi welcome to the Don Vicente.
But I love what I do,
this is a family business.
It's such a big part of my life.
- Enjoy your stay.
- Thank you.
I can breath freely now, knowing that...
The building, our livelihood, our
lives, each other, are all safe.