Subs created by: David Coleman.
Tonight on "Dead Files Revisited"...
I was absolutely spooked.
A second look at some of Amy and
Steve's most terrifying cases.
I was scared.
New information.
There was something creepy.
Startling revelations.
This person was and is real.
First... a return to
Asbury Park, New Jersey...
You must be frightened coming down here.
Where a Restaurant hides
a dangerous entity.
It makes my hair stand up.
Very angry.
Amy exposes evil lurking in the basement.
Have you ever been so scared?
And Steve comes face-to-face
with a murderer.
Did you want to kill him?
Then we travel back to
Vancouver, Washington...
It's crazy.
Where a local theater's sinister past...
That's pretty sick.
Puts innocent children in danger.
Is it safe for those kids
to come into the theater?
But did they listen to Amy?
What do they do if it doesn't stop?
Or did they continue to live in fear?
I haven't been back since.
There's something down there.
My name is Amy Allan.
A lot of dead people are here.
I see dead people.
This is not good.
I speak to dead people...
He is very pissed off.
And they speak to me...
The house is angry.
But there's only way to know
if my findings are real.
He's killed people.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide Detective...
He got shot at his house?
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
Aren't you terrified being here?
It's my job to reveal 'em.
That sounds like something
out of "The Exorcist."
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
It's bad.
And we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I'd like some answers.
Or time to get out.
One of the first cases that Amy
and I ever worked on together
was in Asbury Park, New Jersey.
We had gotten a call from Jeffrey,
the owner of Plan B Restaurant.
Both he and his employees were
having strange experiences
...
I think he needs a stern talking-to,
because he is being a hypocrite.
He is saying he wants to be left alone...
And yet he's harassing...
People. So that needs to stop.
Then go down there as a group and be like,
"that's your space, you hang out there.
"We'll respect that, if you respect us.
If you don't respect us, then
you're gonna have to go."
But the most pressing question is,
is it safe for those kids
to come into the theater?
Amy told us it was safe
for the kids to be there.
But the Slocum House has this
dark, oppressive energy.
And we were hoping to get away from that.
So a couple of weeks after the
investigation, we decided to move.
And it was, uh...
It was kind of devastating to leave.
But we needed to feel safe.
At the new space things are looking up.
We still have a ways to go.
So far we haven't noticed
anything, but who knows?
Sometimes it's hard for
people to stay somewhere
once they learn what's really going on.
So I can understand why Rebecca
and her staff left the theater.
But that means the 7-foot-tall
man still remains.
So my advice to the next tenant is be
ready to put this guy in his place.