Subs created by: David Coleman.
There's a lot of frickin' dead people.
- How are you sleeping at night?
- I don't.
It wants to take them down
there and mutilate them.
It feels like someone's
gonna come out and get me.
- You think she's in danger?
- Yes, I do.
He had a very dark past.
This thing can possess you.
I am scared to death to
be down here right now.
There's real monsters.
She said that we'll meet them.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing is, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people...
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her? It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak.
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were
ghosts in this house.
Amy and I conduct our
investigations separately.
I interview witnesses and
research the history of a location.
While Amy communicates with
those on the other side.
At the end, we'll get together and
reveal our findings to the clients.
I'm in Garrett, Indiana, an old rail
road town just outside of Fort Wayne.
I got a call from a
young girl named Leah.
She says she desperately needs our help.
She told me that her and her new
husband just moved into their first home.
And that things got so weird so fast,
she's afraid to be in the house alone.
Before Amy arrives, I look for anything
that could influence her findings.
This house has a lot
of personal photographs,
so it's important I remove them all.
Once the location is cleared,
Amy can begin her walk.
As I approach this location, dead
people are already surrounding me.
They are warning me of
...
Make a protective boundary, but
it's going to be around the bed.
And then you're going to take this.
What is that?
It's called tar-water.
This is very, very potent
stuff, um, from New Orleans.
Tar-water dates back to Medieval times,
and is often used in voodoo practices.
It consists of pine tar, water,
and other ritualistic medicines.
Go through the house and
put one drop in each room.
What this means is that no dead
person, even the nice ones...
Are going to be able to remain.
Nothing will ever be able
to enter your house again.
I never, never use this stuff, because
I personally really like dead people.
But I feel in this case this is
something that needs to be done.
That's it. No more dead people, okay?
You gotta make me a promise that
you're gonna do what she tells you.
Absolutely. Probably
in less than 12 hours.
Okay. How you feeling
now about all this stuff?
Well, if it helps her
relax, then let's do it.
I'm glad we can get rid of those things.
I really hope Leah and
Rudy follow my advice,
and rid their home of the
entities lurking inside.
If they do, it should set the dead free
and allow them to begin a family in peace.