Subs created by: David Coleman.
There's a male who's really maniacal.
He likes walking up right behind 'em.
I feel as though I'm being watched.
I looked around, and
there was no one there.
I want it to be over.
I don't feel comfortable here.
Were their bodies ever found?
This is bad.
I'd like to have some answers.
Do you know what happened?
Everybody dies.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing is, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people...
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her? It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak.
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were
ghosts in this house.
Amy and I work
independently of one another.
I gather evidence, interview witnesses,
and sort through the
history of each location,
at the end, we come together
to reveal our findings.
I'm headed to
Parkersburg, West Virginia.
It's a small town on the Ohio River,
about an hour north of Charleston.
I received a call from
a woman named Tisha.
Her and her eight children are being
terrorized by something in their new home.
She can't afford to leave, but
she is scared to stay there.
I'm hoping Amy and I can help her out.
Looking at the photos and
artwork throughout the house,
it's clear to me that
a family lives here.
So it's important that I take my
time to remove any personal evidence,
that could influence
Amy during her walk.
What's going on?
I saw water and felt ice cold and wet.
Well, there was, like,
someone who has drowned.
...
gonna go, like, every window,
every doorway, everything
that could be an entrance.
And you let it burn there.
Why... why Sage, though?
It is thought to be a
natural cleansing agent.
To disperse residual energy.
The other thing is in each room,
you're gonna take salt, and just
filling up your palm with it,
taking a little sprinkle, throwing
it in the four corners of each room.
They're gonna all be attracted to this.
Then what you're going to do is throw
it out the front door, and that's it.
The dead people at this location
will be drawn to the salt.
When Tisha throws it outside,
this will release them.
There's a lot of people
here who want to leave.
The air will be so much
better, so much lighter.
I've always felt like there was
something here that needed my help.
And I didn't know how
to help them, so...
But promise me you guys
are gonna do what she says.
Absolutely.
- Probably tomorrow.
- Good, good.
There are several dead
people inhabiting this house.
But I think only the man in the
long black coat presents any danger.
And I believe as long as Tisha
and her family follow my advice,
everyone should remain safe.