Subs created by: David Coleman.
There's something lurking in the dark here.
Not too comfortable with
this house at night.
He loves the death.
It's really disturbing.
It makes me physically sick.
Previous owner killed
himself in that bathtub?
He sliced his throat, right at the jugular.
People are freaking the [Bleep] out.
I really don't want to be in the dark here.
- Are you okay?
- No.
It's the house of death.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing is, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people...
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her? It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth.
I want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were ghosts in this house.
Amy and I never cross paths
during our investigations.
I gather witnesses
accounts, expert opinions,
and research the history of the location.
While Amy investigates what
most people can't see.
When we're done, we meet up
and reveal our findings.
I'm in the small town of
Clinton, North Carolina.
It's about 45 minutes
outside of Fayetteville.
I got a call from a woman named Kara
who runs the art center in town.
She said that people that work for her
are seeing all kinds of weird stuff.
And Kara's worried that
whatever's going on there,
might shut down the center
that she loves so much.
Amy needs to be free from outside
influences during her walk.
So it's important that I cover all the
artwork and personal items at the location.
Once I'm done, the building will
be ready for tonight's walk.
...
He does have issues, I'm not gonna lie.
Um, but I think that if you're willing
to do this, you can help him.
And you can fix the situation here as well.
Okay.
Then what you're going to want
to do is contact a death medium.
Like me, who can come in and do a cleansing
from top to bottom, inside and out.
If this is done properly, it should get
rid of all the entities that are here.
And hopefully that can
be done fairly easily.
If not, there may have
to be another session.
Listen, are you okay? This is a lot...
a lot of pressure for you.
A little overwhelmed, I'm not gonna lie.
You know, there's a light at the
end of this tunnel, though.
If you do do this, and you're strong
enough to do it, kids could come back.
Now are you gonna be able to follow through
with all of this and help out with this?
We're definitely gonna do
what Amy has suggested.
Because we want, you know,
everything to end, and...
I'm confident that we can settle it.
I really hope that Kara and Ashley
follow through with my advice,
and release this house of all
the entities that lurk inside.
If they do, I'm confident the
staff and visitors here will be
safe from the harm that has been
inflicted on so many people.