Subs created by: David Coleman.
You hear that?
He's stalking them.
My wife was assaulted here.
It hurts.
I felt this push.
Looks like a scratch mark.
Really dangerous situation.
Within two minutes
he's dead on the street.
I see a lot of brains.
Holy [Bleep].
She was tried for first-degree murder.
She's, like, trying to reach out.
There's something very bad here.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing is, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people...
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her? It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were
ghosts in this house.
Amy and I conduct our
investigations separately.
I interview witnesses, local experts,
and dig into the history of the location.
At the end we reveal our findings to the
clients and each other for the first time.
I'm in Columbus, Ohio.
We've been called in by
this guy named Harold.
He owns a restaurant
with his wife in town,
and he says there's violent spirits
attacking his wife and his employees.
I'm hoping Amy and I
can straighten this out.
Before Amy enters a location.
I clear the area of anything
that could influence her findings.
This restaurant has a lot of
photographs and historical items.
So it's important that I cover or
remove them before Amy begins her walk.
There's too much going on.
I saw this dead lady
who's depressed, and...
I saw things moving. I saw a chair move.
...
than if it had been a shadow
person or some kind of evil entity.
With him, his main
weakness is his religion.
Using the religion is
bringing in a man of the cloth,
to do a blessing of the entire location.
That's going to keep him out.
Once you do this, there will be
no dead that can enter this place.
And no dead that remain.
Just because I am slightly worried about
him, we're going to see how things go.
If things are still happening...
Then we might have
to go for an exorcism.
It's almost empowering to feel that
- we can kick these guys out.
- Mm hmm.
I feel good that we can,
uh, protect our staff,
and we can send everyone on their way.
And... and you guys are
definitely gonna do this?
- Yeah. Oh, yes.
- Okay.
Now are you gonna be a little afraid
to go upstairs to your office tomorrow?
I'm a little creeped
out, but I'm prepared.
And there's light at the
end of the tunnel here.
Yeah, absolutely.
I really hope Elizabeth
and Harold follow my advice,
and rid their restaurant of
the entities that inhabit it.
If they don't, I fear
not only for their safety,
but their employees
and customers as well.