Subs created by: David Coleman.
He said that he'd kill me if I came here.
As I looked up, I saw a face
look out the window at me.
This little kid becomes, like, the devil.
You can see its head just...
Hanging.
He lets things in that are
really bad sometimes.
And I'm very, very concerned
for the welfare of my son.
Like, they could be standing right
next to us right now as we speak.
Oh, yeah.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing is, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people...
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her? It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it. Stop it.
We uncover if it's safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were ghosts in this house.
Amy and I conduct our
investigations separately.
I interview witnesses and uncover
dark secrets from the past.
While Amy communicates with the other side.
At the end, we come together
to reveal our findings.
I'm in the small farming
town of Belvidere, Illinois.
It's about an hour and a
half north of Chicago.
We've been called in by a woman named Judy.
She sounds hysterical.
She says weird stuff is happening
and it's tearing her family apart.
She's afraid for her son and her dad.
I'm hoping we can help her out,
because this one sounds bad.
Before Amy arrives, I clear the
area of any leading information.
This location is not only
filled with pictures,
but many unique items that
I have to cover or remove.
Once the house is cleared,
Amy can begin her walk.
So there's, like, some really
significant stuff going on here.
Right in here.
There are, like, these things.
And they're, like...
They're [Bleep ] creepy as [Bleep ].
I saw one...
Walking, um, in the yard.
And it was, like, probably 7 feet tall.
Huge, huge, and... and
they're just all over here.
Judy, you sounded really concerned
on the phone and upset.
- I mean, what's going on?
- Well, we're here at my dad's house.
About ten years ago, my
son and I moved in here,
and ever since we moved
in, we're experiencing...
A lot on this property.
So what kind of things are happening?
We've heard noises, we've seen apparitions,
and we've been physically touched.
As a concerned mom, I wanted to
get my son out of that situation,
so about three years ago, we moved
out of here about 10 miles away.
And it hasn't stopped.
Similar experiences are
happening to us over there,
and I'm very, very concerned
for the welfare of my son.
Well, Judy, let me ask you,
your father still lives here?
- He does.
- Okay, are you concerned about that?
I am concerned about him and his welfare.
While I was opening, there was,
like, this little boy who was...
Like, 5 or 6 years old maybe.
And blond hair, and he
didn't have any eyes.
He looks, like, Angelic,
but he's, uh, he's dark.
He just had this, like, really...
Bad, bad feeling about him.
What the [Bleep ] is
burrowing under the ground?
It's, like, some creepy...
Thing. Like...
This is not good, and it has something
to do with the little boy and the...
Barn.
It feels weird, creepy being back in here.
Okay.
So do me a favor why
don't you tell me about,
some of the experiences you had
while you were living here?
I've been brushed up against
the back of my legs.
My shirt kind of tugged a little bit.
I've heard whistling.
My name called.
And my ear being tugged on.
Judy, how'd you wind up staying here
so long with all this going on?
You know, Steve, I had to really try
to hold it together for my son.
Well, you're a tough woman.
I give you credit.
I had to be.
There's, like, a lot of hatred there.
With this child...
A lot of hatred.
And, like, he... he... he can interact.
He does.
He can and he does.
I don't really get what he's doing or why
a fricking 5-year-old kid would go crazy.
It's like this little kid
becomes, like, the devil.
So, Judy, why are we here?
Well, I had to feed the animals
for my dad who went out of town,
so my girlfriend came with
me, and as I looked up,
I saw a face look out the window at me,
and I immediately turned around and
ran screaming towards the house.
Okay, now can you describe him
for me as far as his features?
He had a round face, a big nose, and...
his eyes were dark.
If you had to guess an
age, what would you say?
I would say mid-30s or 40s.
The feeling I had in my stomach, it
definitely wasn't anything human.
- This was ghostly looking.
- Okay.
So I hear this voice.
It's really grumbly, like,
gravelly, like, hoarse.
He's like a... like a madman.
I don't know if he thinks
he's possessed, or...
Can you describe him more?
He's probably in his, like, late 30s.
Mm, he's thin.
He's yelling at me. He's a...
very agitated.
- What is he yelling?
- Uh, to get out.
He said that he'd kill me if I came here.
He's like a madman.
- He's yelling at me.
- What is he yelling?
Uh, to get out.
He told me that he'd
kill me if I came here.
And I said, "oh, yeah? Bring it on".
Now he's small and weak and
cowering, and, um, and he's crying.
He's, like, sad, depressed, um...
Frankie, I was talking to
your mom earlier, and, uh,
she basically told me you had
it rough growing up here.
Can you tell me about some
of the experiences you had?
There was one time I was
coming outside of the house,
and I looked up from the
porch at that window,
and I seen this figure,
moving back and forth, you know, trying to
hide, but at the same time watching us.
- Can you describe the guy?
- It was a white outlined figure.
- Did you ever see it again?
- Yes.
A few months later, uh, I seen the same
figure up in the corner over there...
And its head was actually tilted down.
I could see the rope around
its neck and its head just...
Hanging to the side.
So it looked like somebody that was hung.
Yeah.
This male, I guess he kind of
just lost his mind or something.
My head hurts oh, so bad up here.
Bad pain in my head. Bad,
bad pain in my head.
I'm feeling the agony
this man went through.
He is lost, confused, and
completely out of his mind.
He killed himself.
It happened here.
There's something with a rope.
How old were you when
this was all going on?
Around 9, 10 years old.
- How were you sleeping at night?
- I wasn't really sleeping good at all.
For a few years straight,
I had the same dream.
Of this man standing in
the yard watching me.
Describe him to me.
He wasn't that tall, had a
mask on, regular pants.
- What do you mean, had a mask on?
- It was a plain white mask.
Couldn't see his face, nothing.
- How'd you deal with that?
- It bothered me as a kid a lot.
I felt like it was supposed to,
like, mean something to me,
like I was supposed to
understand something.
But I still to this day don't understand.
Okay.
Those things, they're just all over here.
- What did it look like?
- Human-shaped.
Very broad...
Big arms.
Okay.
As I head back to the house, I have to
pass by the 7-foot-tall creatures again.
I don't know why they're here, but
I know they're hiding something.
Like, how many?
Six to ten, maybe.
They were exchanging
masks, like, white masks.
Do you think living people have seen these?
Definitely, I think they've,
like, seen 'em, and,
like, had, like, encounters with them.
And [Bleep ] freaked the [Bleep ] out.
Because they are very scary.
Well, Franco, I spoke with your daughter.
She told me she was getting
physically touched.
Your grandson is pretty much traumatized
by everything that happened here.
He's still traumatized.
I was wondering if you ever
experienced anything here.
Oh, I sure did.
In the dining room, a figure
walked in, and he looked at me,
and like he was surprised that I was here.
And this was a real tall, slender man.
He had this old jacket,
almost like a suit jacket,
but again, from way back when.
- Did you see anything else in this house?
- Just one other time.
One night I was in here watching TV,
and right to the right on the floor,
I see this little white cloud.
And then it started moving, and I could
see the shape of a head and little arms.
You're kidding.
Almost like a premature baby.
It was slowly moving around.
Wow.
The little boy thing, whatever
the [Bleep ] it is...
He likes really bad [Bleep ].
He lets things in that are
really bad sometimes.
But he seems too [Bleep ]
evil to be a 5-year-old.
Yeah, he's a liar. I
think he's tricking me.
I think he's a liar.
I don't like him, okay?
Yeah, that kind of scared me a little bit.
What happened?
It's not a real kid.
It's something really bad.
Like what?
Demons will pretend to be dead people.
What are you thinking?
That it's not a real kid.
I think that the burrowing
monster is this child...
And I think that it'll torment
the people who are living here.
Do you know if, uh,
people here see this boy?
I think so, but I don't think they
necessarily see him like I do.
Yeah, that kind of scared me a little bit.
So you're saying that he might
project himself differently to,
different people to influence
their perception of him?
Yes.
Do you know if they have
any kind of interaction?
He makes them feel sick or he makes them
hurt or something along those lines.
It feels like he can easily
travel back and forth.
With all the activity in this house,
I need to know about the previous owners.
So I went to the local library to see
what I can uncover in their records.
Digging through the archives,
I was shocked to discover that
two brothers committed suicide,
at the location I'm investigating.
The newspaper articles
didn't have many details.
So I'm headed over to meet
with a retired Belvidere cop,
who says he's got information
to help my case.
What were you able to find
out about these suicides?
Well, actually, Steve, this was
one of the most interesting
cases I've ever looked into.
Back in 1939, Thomas Smith,
a 24-year-old young man,
was quite despondent, and he ended up
having an argument with his girlfriend.
And later that evening, he
went out into the kitchen,
and took a.22 caliber pistol.
And shot himself in the heart.
I was able to come up with the
actual death certificate.
Now what about the second suicide?
Well, in 1961,
Thomas' brother Raymond,
also committed suicide
using the exact same gun,
that Thomas had shot himself
with 20 years earlier.
And I also have a copy of the
Medical Examiner's report.
He lived alone with his mother,
had no girlfriends, wasn't sick.
There was really no indication as to
why he would want to commit suicide.
This demon says he controls
the house and everyone in it.
And I get the feeling
he's about to prove it.
I think it's, uh, self-inflicted.
What do you mean?
I saw...
A noose hanging from the beams.
Raymond takes the gun
that his brother used.
He shoots himself in the same
manner, but he doesn't die.
So he looks up and sees this rope,
decides to put it around his
neck, and hang himself.
Have you ever heard of anything like that?
No. Of the 23 years, I-I never
had anything like this happen.
He says he was trying to find a way
out for a long time, long time.
I guess he kind of just
lost his mind or something.
There's a lot of blood.
I hear somebody yelling.
I hear a male yelling.
I hear a gunshot, and there's
the pain in my head.
He doesn't like this. He
doesn't like that we're up...
That we're in his... his domain.
Who's "he" that you're talking about?
The man who killed himself.
After Bill filled me in on
the details of the suicides.
Clearly I need to find out a lot
more about the Smith family,
who owned the property I'm investigating.
I've contacted a local historian who
tells me their story is a tragedy.
The Smith family settled here about 1899.
Charles Smith was the father. He
settled the area, had 13 children.
And then his oldest son
Edward took it over.
Okay.
Edward was married to a woman named Asika.
And he had ten children, and of those,
six of them died on the property.
Six? So it's more than
just the two suicides.
There were four children that died.
We had one girl died at the age
of 6 from cancer of the arm.
Another girl died from
pneumonia at the age of 4.
The third girl died at the age
of 9 months from bronchitis.
And finally, they had a
baby boy who was stillborn.
Do you know why he killed himself?
Sad, depressed.
I think a lot of his...
His, uh, family or friends
or both were killed.
Can you tell how they were killed?
It's like, everybody's eating and
it's great and it's evening, and...
Something bad, and then they're dead.
Their all bodies are...
They're all messed up. They are all bloody.
Everybody put in a hole or some [Bleep ].
And he's, uh, he's all [Bleep ] up.
I need to find out more about the Smith
family and what they went through.
So I've managed to track down a descendant
of the two brothers who killed themselves.
He says he's willing to talk to me about a
very dark chapter in his family's history.
Trevor, thanks for meeting me.
I appreciate it.
You know I'm investigating Thomas,
and Raymond's suicides on the
property that your family owned.
What is your relationship
with Raymond and Thomas?
My grandpa is Raymond and
Thomas' youngest brother.
What can you tell me about
their father, Ed Sr.?
This is my great-grandfather.
I heard he was a hardworking kind of man.
They put in long-hour days, you know?
12, 13, 14 hours.
The winters were harsh,
but he enjoyed doing it.
Because they knew they had
to provide for the family.
There's something about
this old man, grandpa.
Like, an Ed, Eddie, Edgar.
He's a farmer. Literally
the image of a farmer...
Overalls, cut-off sleeves, big rosy guy.
Anyways, he died.
He comes here still. Uh...
I got to ask you a question... how did
these suicides affect your family?
When Thomas committed suicide, they were
sad and they were heartbroken, but...
They kind of saw it happening since
him and his girlfriend broke up.
But when Ray died, nobody
was expecting that.
This is Raymond.
All in all, the family was upset,
but it kind of erased the family.
You know, kind of made them
just go all their own ways.
Trevor, I read in an article that
your great-grandmother Asika,
basically had no emotion or no
reaction when they found Raymond.
I believe myself that she was
more shell-shocked or just,
all in all just shocked about it.
That was her, and then this
is after Raymond passed away.
Within two years, three years after
Ray died, Asika passed away.
She, uh, came down with an illness,
and then she went anorexic
and she was 63 pounds.
So she took it probably the hardest.
She committed suicide, too, in a sense.
I mean, you know, she just
pretty much quite eating,
went into a bad depression,
and just took her from there.
Some woman, her heart's broken.
Nobody's gonna do anything
to make it right,
and she is not okay.
About any of this.
So she keeps skipping through time.
So I see her younger. She's happy.
It's summer.
All good things, and then she's old.
She's so sad.
And lost.
Why is she sad?
She feels, like, a huge sense of loss.
Do you know if she was here on
this property when she was living?
Yes.
A lot of bizarre activity has
taken place on Franco's property.
And Judy's worried that it's
followed her to her new home.
As much as I don't like breaking the rules.
I need to meet with Amy and
have her walk Judy's house.
Okay, I'll set it up.
There's stuff that comes
inside from out here.
There's...
People.
They've been called.
They've been asked to come
into the back of the house.
What do you mean, they've
been asked to come?
They've been invited.
So I'm assuming one of the owners
or both invited them to come here.
A lot of dead people are being
drawn to this location.
Either the people who live here are
trying to communicate with them.
Or they have abilities that are
unintentionally attracting the dead.
I feel like there are
two people that are...
Have been having experiences. And
there's so much, like, tr...
Like, these voices that are in
the air constantly talking.
My body doesn't feel comfortable here.
It's like, you know...
This annoying hum.
Is what's going on dangerous for them?
Yeah, open invitation.
They've had nasty [Bleep ] come in.
During my walk, I
encountered many entities.
I wanted to sketch the
two I saw most clearly.
First, the old woman.
She's probably in her 80s, very round face.
Very, very thin hair going
down to about here.
Her eyes are actually rather large, round,
and kind of bulbous, like, protruding.
Next, I describe the 7-foot-tall entity.
It was wearing a mask, so
it has a very oval head.
The eyes on the mask are...
are very almond-shaped.
It has a stripe.
It goes right across the eyes like that.
Amy, is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
completed our investigations.
We're ready to reveal our findings to the
clients and each other for the first time.
Amy, I want to introduce you
to three generations here.
Franco lives here.
Judy and Frankie did live here.
And things got so bad for the three of them
that Judy and Frankie actually moved out.
Big concern here is, is it
safe for Franco to stay.
And have Judy and Frankie taken
something back to where they live now,
and are they gonna be okay?
So with that, Amy will start
and tell us about her walk.
The first thing that I
got was this little...
Creature, maybe about this tall.
And, um, it would burrow into the ground.
And it felt very, very negative.
And then I saw these creature
things out in the yard.
They were, like, 7 feet tall,
abnormally long arms, muscular.
They were wearing two
different types of masks.
When I was a little kid, I would
go to bed, uh, and in the dream,
I would be looking out my
second-floor window into the yard.
And I would see just one man standing
there wouldn't do nothing, wouldn't move.
He had a mask on, and I would
have that dream constantly.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Okay, all right, I drew it.
You did a sketch of what you saw.
Wow.
Well, I think I'd be afraid if I saw
that in the middle of the night, too.
Yeah, that's...
Looks like him.
It's scary.
Are they, like, guardians or something?
Not in a good way.
I wouldn't know why you
would call that a guardian.
Okay, Amy, what else did you see?
When I came in here, I saw
this, uh, really nice guy.
Uh, he's a farmer.
Um, he lived here. I know he died here.
He comes in the barn a lot, but he's all
around, and his name was Ed or Eddie.
You're kidding.
- Ed or Eddie?
- Mm-hmm.
Do me a favor before I move
on, just tell her about...
Franco, if you can, the
guy you saw in the house.
The guy that I saw in the
house was very tall, lean.
Uh...
Very old-fashionedly dressed.
The original settler on this land
was a second-generation farmer,
by the name of Eddie Smith, Edward Smith.
And he, uh, farmed this
land for probably 70 years.
He was a nice guy, apparently.
He was... ten children.
Jeez.
Now that looks more like what I seen.
Is that...
He looked just like that. I
seen him with my own eyes.
- Do you think this could have been him?
- I mean, yeah.
It's incredible.
The other person that I saw
was right here in this barn.
He, like, was suicidal.
He just kind of snapped.
I saw an old pistol, and
then I heard a gunshot.
But I'm looking at these, and
I'm like, "he hung himself".
She almost nailed this down to 100%.
His son Raymond in 1961
committed suicide in this barn.
This is Raymond.
He committed suicide by shooting himself
in the chest with an old pistol.
Oh, my God.
- Apparently he didn't die right away...
- Oh, my God.
So he decided that he
wasn't dying fast enough.
He took a rope and then hung himself.
I know ten people personally
that have committed suicide.
And nine out of those ten,
I could see it coming.
They didn't see that with this guy.
They did not see it coming at all.
So it was pretty much a big shock.
You look upset, Judy.
Tell Amy what you saw...
That time.
My dad went out of town and I had...
He asked me to come here one evening
to take care of the animals.
I looked up, and I saw a guy look
like this out the window at me,
and I just turned around and
ran for the house screaming.
I don't think I've ever been
so petrified in my life.
Same thing kind of along the
lines with my mother...
I look up at the barn.
Just some reason made me look, you
know, and I notice this white figure
peeking its head through the window,
but at the same time trying to hide.
It was the same window.
- The same window.
- Okay.
Didn't want us to know he was
there, but he was peeking.
Well, there's a little bit of a kicker to
the whole story about the Smith family.
Raymond here had an older brother,
that committed suicide in the kitchen
of your house, with the same exact gun
- that he killed himself with.
- Oh, my God. Are you kidding me?
The same.22 caliber gun.
He shot himself in the chest area.
The same exact way he did in
the kitchen of your house.
Hmm.
I saw friends and family off to the side.
Um... and then I saw them all dead.
Really? How many?
Five or six.
The story of the Smith
family is pretty tragic.
He had ten kids. Six of
'em died, two to suicide.
He also had a 6-year-old daughter
who died of cancer of the arm...
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah, he had a 5-year-old
daughter died of pneumonia.
He had a 9-month-old
daughter died of bronchitis.
And then he had a son that was stillborn.
That explains what I saw, probably.
I was in my living room one
night, and I see this little...
White ball on the floor, and you could
tell it was, like, a preemie baby.
- Mm.
- Just kind of arms and feet moving.
You could tell the shape of a
baby, but not fully formed.
So what else did you see?
Outside over here I met, um, an older
lady, and she was really heartbroken.
And she was, like, old.
She's just so, uh, sad and lost that, um,
you know, nothing can make it better.
Who would that sound like?
- The mom, right?
- Right.
Ed Sr.'s wife was named Asika.
After Raymond killed himself, she
just went into a downward spiral.
And she wound up dying three years later.
I got a photo of her.
She was 63 pounds when she died.
Oh, my goodness.
So I sketched the sad woman.
- The woman you saw?
- Mm-hmm.
She's just sad.
Wow.
You guys tell me what you think.
So I sketched the sad woman that I saw.
Wow.
Yeah, I'd call that her.
Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, that looks like the mouth exactly.
- Yeah.
Definitely in the mouth, the nose.
- You do think this is her.
- Yeah, it's very possible.
So they're still here?
Like, they could be standing right
next to us right now as we speak?
Yes.
The other thing that I saw when I
went into the house was a child.
A 5-year-old little boy.
He was very Angelic-looking,
except he didn't have any eyes,
and there were, like, this
light coming out of his eyes.
His main area is the house,
but he can go anywhere.
He's very, very powerful.
Initially he showed me, like,
this sweet little boy.
But it... it wasn't real.
It was to gain my sympathy, to trick me.
And then when I chased him out of
the barn, he turned into the...
That little creature thing.
It dove into the ground and
was burrowing in the ground.
The child is not a child.
It's some kind of demonic presence.
And what it did to this family
was it caused two suicides.
It probably influenced them to do it.
And probably killed the girls...
The children, because they're weak, and...
Completely destroyed the family.
You were concerned about Frankie because
you feel like you were losing him,
at some point?
Yeah, I mean, he was getting
to the point where...
You know, like, nothing mattered and...
Just became distant, you know?
And I don't want that to happen.
Well, there's obviously
a lot going on here.
Two biggest questions...
Is it safe for Franco at this house,
and did this thing follow you two guys to
your new home, and are you safe there?
With that, I'm gonna turn it over to Amy,
and hopefully, she will have an answer.
In your house, you guys are getting
an influx of random people,
and things coming in the back
door and the back window.
But the good news is that your
house is a lot easier to contain.
Um, all you need to do
is bring in a holy man.
Who will have a blessing
done and a sealing done.
Okay.
But this property, your situation
is a little bit different.
You know, this thing's
been here for a long time.
It can affect people.
So you really need to not only get the
blessing and get the sealing done,
but also you need to bring in a Shaman
who will deal with the Elementals.
And seal up the property so that the...
Demonic thing can't get back in.
Elementals are entities created by nature.
The creature tormenting
this family never lived.
So a priest wouldn't be able to
get rid of it, only a Shaman.
My concern is that if you don't take
care of this, what could happen?
Ooh, it'd be bad. It'll continue.
So what... what do they do first?
It'd be great if you could do it
all at the same time, really.
Like, if you could have the Shaman here
and have the priest or the holy man.
That would be great.
You have that look on your face
like you don't believe her.
No, I've heard stories before actually
from my friend, uh, that is half Indian.
How this one family had evil spirits
and they called one of these shamans,
and got rid of all those evil
spirits that were in the house.
Okay, so you're gonna take
Amy's advice and do this?
Yes.
In your opinion,
do you think once they take care of
all this that things will get better?
I think that their home environment
will be much better, you know?
The chaos will subside.
I don't want to see what
happened to this family...
God forbid. Happen to your family.
That's why I want you to promise that
you'll at least do what you have to do,
and I can walk out of here
tonight feeling better.
You can guarantee I will be doing that.
Okay, what about you?
Yeah. I'm definitely gonna
take up what she said.
Okay.
I witnessed exactly what Frankie
saw, and the sketch proves it.
But that can be hard for
a young man to accept.
I just hope this family
keeps their promise,
because I believe their
lives could depend on it.