Subs created by: David Coleman.
Oh, yeah, this is creepy.
We've heard things. We've been touched.
He can get physical if he wants to.
My daughter talks about seeing things.
It looked like a Grim Reaper.
The death was suspicious.
He was killed instantly.
So you feel that whatever's
here wants you out?
Absolutely.
He wants to hurt people.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing is, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people.
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her? It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were ghosts in this house.
Amy and I conduct our
investigations separately.
I interview witnesses and dig
into the history of the location.
While Amy communicates with the dead.
At the end, we get together
to reveal our findings.
I'm in Wichita, Kansas, on my way to a
property owned by a husband-and-wife team.
They run a beauty salon and an
auto shop on the same property.
The husband Jeff says violent spirits
are destroying his business,
their family life, and their sanity.
Amy needs to be free from outside
influences during her walk.
So it's important that I cover
or remove all photographs,
artwork, and even religious icons.
Once I'm done, the building will
be clear for tonight's walk.
Uh, well, I'm not open at all.
I usually open to communicate with
the dead as I approach a location.
But this area has such an overwhelming
amount of death surrounding it...
That I decided to do my
opening inside the location.
This is some... some...
Some bad [Bleep] going on over in here.
Not good. Not good at all.
Yeah, this is some bad stuff.
Bad ground. Always been bad.
Will always be bad.
Bad [Bleep] is always gonna happen here.
Jeff, you sounded concerned on the phone.
Well, I am concerned.
You know, really I'm fighting
to save two businesses here.
- My wife has the salon here in front.
- Okay.
And then I have my garage here at the back.
Give me an idea what's going on.
We've heard things. We've
been touched, pushed.
We've had things misplaced
in the salon and the shop.
I'd like my kids to be able
to take over the business,
but right now I'm not even
comfortable having 'em in there.
- How old are the kids?
- Fifteen and nine.
My daughter's actually experienced things,
and you know, as a father that concerns me,
because I'm, you know, not sure if she can
handle that or understands what's going on.
How are you and your
wife handling all this?
My wife would just as soon sell the
place, where I want to keep it.
And you know, this is something that
we built over the last seven years...
And I'm not just willing
to walk away from it.
Okay. What about yourself? Have you ever
seen anything or experienced anything?
I just finished working on some vehicles...
- Okay.
- And I looked up inside,
and I saw somebody standing there.
Looked like an older gentleman, maybe.
Um, I'm guessing him to be in his
mid to late 50s with a beard.
Alright, did you go inside to search?
We did. All of us went inside.
We found out that there
was nobody in there.
There's one kinda creepy dude.
He's kinda like a greaser dude.
And he likes his area.
- What's that?
- Um...
The driveway, this whole thing...
This whole building...
His territory.
To me, he's, like, just a tough
guy, you know, just like...
"I'm... I'm tough. I'm bad.
I'm big. I'm bad".
Like, would you say that he's dangerous?
Yes.
But he's kinda [Bleep] up.
So what's going on in here?
There's a lot of things
that happen in here.
We started to notice that
tools would come up missing.
If you can't find 'em,
you can't work with 'em.
- Anything else, Jeff?
- We've heard whispering.
I remember a time I was leaned over the
back of a car, and I'm in there working.
You know, you're turning wrenches, and
you're focused on what you're doing.
And then suddenly someone
whispers in my ear.
And I know that I'm alone in the garage
at that particular point, but I stand up.
There was nothing in here.
He likes to yell. Uh, he
likes to hear his voice.
He likes to hear himself.
He's able to manifest things.
Like, it's weird.
He likes to take things and make
'em disappear and reappear...
Reappear in weird places.
That's to irritate people.
He doesn't want anybody in his space.
He hates them.
- And what's...
- Living or dead.
He just doesn't want anybody in his space.
We were just opening up for the morning,
and we heard footsteps run
right across the top of us.
We had gone up there,
couldn't find anything.
And that's when we really started to worry,
because we expected to find something.
What the hell were you
thinking when that happened?
It's disturbing. You're concerned.
You think somebody might be in here.
But then a whole new fear rushes
over you that someone's not in here.
So, Jeff, I'm assuming the guys you've got
working for you are, like, guy's guys,
- you know, tough guys and...
- Yeah.
They don't want to admit
that they're scared,
but you can see fear in somebody's eyes.
You can tell that they're not
just bothered by what happened,
but that it actually frightened them,
to the point that they don't even
want to talk about it sometimes.
Do you think that anything that's going
on in the garage could be dangerous?
If it can, you know, move tools around in a
garage, if it can do things like that...
- Right.
- It could certainly try and hurt somebody.
Right. Okay.
Does this guy interact
with the living at all?
Um, he can get physical if he wants to...
Grabbing, pushing.
- Okay.
- He likes to throw things.
Could he hurt anybody?
I think he, uh, I think he could.
He's really good at the stuff
he's already learned how to do.
He knows how to affect his environment.
Obviously this is a storage space.
Um, did you use it? I mean,
it's kinda, like, wasted.
No. My guys have reported the same thing.
None of 'em want to come back
here, you know, if they're gonna,
put something in here for storage, they
either try and leave it for me to do,
or they just come, throw it in
here, and yank the door shut.
I wish we could use it, I wish
we could do something with it,
but nobody likes to be out here.
- Why?
- You just feel a presence...
A heaviness about the area.
It's like you can't get a full
breath, you know, in your lungs.
Like you can't breathe all the way.
Like you're in high altitude or something?
Right, just like that.
Oh, yeah, this is creepy.
What is?
The thing that's in here.
Making me feel uncomfortable and scared.
Like, I felt scared in my stomach.
What thing?
Death.
This is creepy.
What is?
Um, it looked like...
Like a Grim Reaper.
But I think it's, you know, just
a regular dead person because,
I've seen death, and it doesn't...
doesn't look anything like that.
We all associate certain images with death.
And we take those images
with us when we die.
It had, like, the whole thing, like,
skeleton face and the whole...
Cloak and the sickle.
This dead man's projection is childish,
but it is still creeping me out.
Which is exactly what he wants to do.
Now I'm picking up on his
death state and feeling, um,
everything that he went through physically.
It's, like, really hurting my head.
- I just feel very, very sick.
- You gonna be all right?
I'm out of it. Like, my equilibrium's off.
Uh, disoriented.
It [Bleep] hurts, man.
So, Emily, I was talking to your
husband Jeff and he basically said,
you were ready to put the "for sale"
sign on this place and get outta here.
What's going on?
From the first time we unlocked the door
here, it's never felt like it's been ours.
- Why do you say that?
- Um, stuff moves.
People get pushed.
You hear people whispering in your ears.
Doing hair there was a container
sitting on my cabinet,
it was in the middle of the station it
flipped in the air, and landed on its side.
- What was in the can? Was it heavy?
- It was heavy, it was like a pomade.
It was bad. It was scary.
He never came back and got his hair cut.
And he was a regular for years.
Okay, so you're losing business
because of what's going on.
Absolutely. One time I said...
"Show me you're here, do something so that
I know you're here, and I'm not crazy".
And I turned to shut the door behind
me, and I saw someone standing
right in the entryway between the
kitchen and the living room.
- Who'd you see?
- I saw a man standing there.
With a shirt and jeans.
He had a goatee and gray hair.
All right, so do you feel that
whatever's here wants you out?
Absolutely.
The dead man inside the garage is so sick,
that I'm experiencing exactly what
he went through when he died.
The pain is so intense
that I have to leave.
There's a lot of stuff
coming in from outside.
I'm, like, seeing this woman who's alive.
But the dead are just, like, following her.
And then they're inside.
Why are they following her?
Uh, because she has abilities.
Do you have any idea if this Reaper
guy does follow her in here?
Yes.
Can he do anything to people here?
Cause headaches and breathing issues...
And feeling like you're gonna vomit.
Okay, so what's going on here?
My daughter talks about seeing things.
She even drew a picture of, like,
a black figure with red eyes.
And she said that's something she saw here.
- Where's the picture?
- I threw it away immediately.
- I didn't want to think about it again.
- Now what did she say it was?
It had no form, but you could tell it had
arms and legs, and it was all black.
How'd you react to it?
It made my heart stop, because I don't
want to be putting her in danger.
Emily, your daughter's 9?
Yes. I want to preserve her innocence.
I don't want her to be scared.
Okay.
The dead guy who showed himself
to me as the Grim Reaper...
Throughout his life he
seems to have some money.
Does he try to show himself to the living?
Well, he wants to, because
he has his disguises.
He likes the Grim Reaper the best.
So would people see him as
the Grim Reaper in here?
I would think that he would
come off more like...
Like just, like, a black
mass or something like that.
And he wants to...
Make other people hurt themselves.
Daniel, I was talking to Jeff,
and he mentioned that you
do work for him on and off.
He said you might have had
experiences here yourself.
Yeah, something did happen one night.
Me and Jeff were working with
a battery that overheated.
We went and set it down
and got another one.
A couple minutes later I went back to
the kitchen to get something to drink,
opened the freezer up, and the
battery was sitting in the freezer.
So where'd you lay the battery down first?
Laid the battery down on the counter
across from the refrigerator.
Jeff was with me the whole time.
And nobody else was in the house?
Nobody else was there at that time.
When that happened to me, I was
more cautious about working here.
- You don't look like you scare easy.
- I don't scare easy.
I spent nine years in the Marine corps.
But stuff that you can't
explain tends to, you know,
scare you a little bit to where you're
thinking, "what's going on here?"
The greaser dude, he likes his area.
The entities here are very territorial.
As soon as I walk to the garage, I'm
back in the greaser guy's space.
He gets pissed, you know,
if people are in his area.
So he will try to make them leave.
Do you know how?
Things will be moved, like, taken
from one place and put in another.
I think this guy is
actually Apporting [Bleep].
Apporting is the ability
to make things disappear,
and reappear in different locations.
Entities that have mastered
this can be very dangerous.
He's, like, really kind of a sociopath.
Like, he doesn't have any...
Feelings or anything like that.
I feel like...
Him, like, grabbing, like, my face.
You know, like, he would do that...
You know, like...
I'm headed over to meet
with a woman named Cheryl.
She's the former owner of the property.
She tells me her time on the
property ended in tragedy.
I've gotta find out what this is all about.
Cheryl, I got called in to
investigate your old home.
- How long did you live there?
- About five years.
What did you use the garage for?
Was it always a garage?
We did a lot of hangouts
with friends in there.
People came by every day, and
it was like they lived there.
Looks like you had a good
time, a lot of bikers.
A lot of bikers.
Uh, I gotta ask an unusual question.
The people that are living
there now are claiming
there's a lot of paranormal
activity going on.
When you lived there, did you ever
experience anything like that?
Nothing happened paranormally, but we lost
three of our dear friends within a year.
- Really?
- Right.
This is Kevin. He's in the middle.
How'd you lose Kevin?
Kevin was hit by a car on his motorcycle,
and he was killed instantly.
And then we lost Tony.
And he practically lived there.
He had a stroke, and he died.
He looks like a young guy, though.
How old was he?
Oh, he was in his late 50s.
And then we had Mark, and he passed
away, and he was a dear friend.
He had previously lived in the basement
of that house back 20 years ago.
And what did he die of?
He went to bed and didn't wake up.
I don't know what happened to him.
I mean, he went from driving a brand-new
car to just living month to month.
He had some problems and some issues.
He lived in an apartment complex that had
a lot of people that did drugs in it.
Whatever he was doing, he just
looked worse every time I saw him.
Were you surprised when
they found him dead?
No.
The greaser dude, he's tall.
He's wearing a black,
like, '50s biker jacket.
He killed himself, and he was intoxicated.
He was mad when I walked away.
As soon as I asked the
greaser guy about his death,
he gets very angry and wants
nothing to do with me.
He's not gonna talk to me again.
Cheryl had some pretty tragic stories about
the people that used to
hang out at her house.
But no deaths actually happened there.
So I'm at the Genealogical Society seeing
what I can dig up in the archives.
Turns out in 1977...
A former owner named Helen Hillman,
died on the property when she
fell down a flight of stairs.
I've asked a local reporter
to look into the accidental
death of a woman who lived on
Jeff and Emily's property.
I'm heading over to the cemetery
where the woman is buried,
to find out the rest of the story.
Well, this is actually where
Helen Hillman is buried.
She was married when she was 19 in 1917.
That's a picture of her and
William on their wedding day.
Then they moved from Arkansas to
right outside of Wichita, Kansas,
on the property that you're investigating.
And when did they move in?
1947, I believe.
Now what were you able to find out
about the circumstances of her death?
Well, according to her death certificate,
it said "massive head injury".
Even though she was 79, according to her
descendants, she was in good health.
They said that she had a zest for life.
She was active. She lived independently.
All right, so it was odd the way she died.
Yes, it was very odd.
She had lived in that house for so long,
and the distance between
the stairs and the floor,
wouldn't be enough to
kill someone, typically.
- It says "massive head injuries".
- Mm hmm.
I don't know if that fall can
cause injuries like that.
Yes, and that's why I think
the death is suspicious.
There's another person.
She's more evolved.
She's not in her death state anymore.
- She got out of that pretty quickly.
- Okay.
I think she broke her neck...
Early of mid '70s.
She was dead, like, fast.
She's not in her death state anymore.
- She got out of that pretty quickly.
- Okay.
Early of mid '70s...
That's when she died.
She was dead, like, fast.
Broke her neck.
Oh, God, it [Bleep] hurts.
This woman is making me extremely sad.
She's in so much physical
and emotional pain.
That she seems lost and confused.
And most of all scared.
She kind of, uh, runs
away from living people.
Sometimes she's reliving her life.
Ah, now I'm getting her pain.
I'm on my way to meet with a historian,
who helped me out the last
time I was in Wichita.
He dug deep into the property's history,
and he told me he uncovered some
pretty unusual information.
So, Anthony, what were you
able to find out about the
early history of the
property I'm investigating?
The interesting thing about
this piece of property,
is the number of times
that it's changed hands.
Over 30 people have owned it since
it was first purchased up until now.
Out of all these people that tend
to come and go on this property,
did anybody stand out?
Yeah, a Dr. Alfred Ray was one of the guys,
that seemed to be very, very interesting.
He was a physician who came
to this part of the country.
He brought his whole family with him,
and he purchased this property,
from the outside looking in,
we assume that he was going to
be setting up his family there.
And living on it for generations.
And yet within less than six months,
he's already sold the property and has
moved on with his whole family with him.
The reason why Dr. Ray stands out so much,
is that he was a man with business savvy.
And yet he comes to this one
particular piece of property.
He's there for six months.
And then he left it without
even developing it.
That's strange.
Bad [Bleep] is always gonna happen here.
It's like, oh, kinda bad, worse,
worse, really, really bad...
[Bleep] Terrible.
So basically it's... it's anybody
that lives here or on this land is...
Are they gonna have problems because of it?
Oh, yeah.
You know, they'll have,
uh, struggle and, uh...
You know, negative things will happen.
So I think it's just automatically gonna...
Draw negativity.
And, like, I think it makes people angry.
It makes people act in bizarre ways.
During my walk I saw a strange scene,
where a living person was leading
a trail of dead into the house.
I'm meeting with a sketch artist
to describe what I encountered.
I saw this woman at the
door about to open it.
Behind her...
Is this really tall man.
And he is wearing, like, a black cloak.
And then slightly to his right is...
The back of a man who is wearing a
cowboy hat, jeans, and cowboy boots.
Amy, is this what you saw?
Yes.
Now that Amy and I have
finished our investigations.
It's time to sit down with Jeff and his
wife Emily to reveal what we've uncovered.
This is Emily and Jeff. They're married
and actually own this property.
Jeff actually runs the garage here.
Emily runs the salon up front.
They've had a lot of experiences here.
It's affecting work.
It's affecting business. And it's
affecting their relationship.
They want to make sure it's okay for them
to stay here and if it's safe for the kids.
That being said, we'll hear a
little bit about Amy's walk.
When I started my walk, I came into
contact with this creepy male.
He is a really tall guy.
He had a leather jacket.
His hair is greased back.
He hates anybody in his space.
Because he considers the
driveway, that front area,
and this entire garage and
the back of it his space.
One night I remember this
guy looking from the back,
and as I started to go inside...
They were gone just like that.
When he gets upset, he likes to yell.
He likes to throw things.
He also does a thing called Apporting.
What the hell is Apporting?
It's a phenomena where
an object can disappear,
from one place and reappear in another.
Seemingly out of thin air.
Why don't you tell Amy about
some of your experiences here.
We definitely get things
moving here all the time.
And whatever's doing this is
moving at a great distance.
Well, I mean, he definitely has a mission.
And everything he does
is to get you to leave.
He did try to physically attack me.
So I feel like he wants to hurt
the living if he hasn't already.
We started to have a really good dialogue,
but what ended up happening was I
felt like he had killed himself.
And I said that...
And he was so,
irate that he just stormed off.
I spoke to the previous
owners of the property.
And they told me this garage
was basically a party house.
So all the bikers would come here.
There was a bar in here.
There was a pool table.
Right after they sold the property,
three of the guys that hung out
here on a continuous basis...
Died within a year.
One died in an accident, got
killed on his motorcycle.
The other guy died of a stroke.
And then the third guy
is this guy right here.
Now his name was Mark.
A lot of the friends thought
he was on a downward spiral,
and that he was in a sense killing
himself by what he was doing to himself.
He actually lived in the
basement of your salon.
Does this guy look familiar at all?
Yeah, I remember distinctly seeing this.
The look in his eyes, him looking
back at me was very similar.
Now, Emily, you saw an apparition.
Yes, between the kitchen
and the living room.
Does this look familiar at all?
Oh, yes, absolutely.
I'm scared with my kids
or my husband out here.
Would he hurt me or somebody out here,
or is he just trying to scare us?
No, he wants to hurt you.
He wants you out.
For a dead person to learn how to...
Throw objects, apport...
If you put those together,
you've got a problem.
So what else did you see on your walk?
I saw a woman up in the attic area.
She was, like, re-experiencing her life,
so sometimes she's, like, back in it.
But when she's here, she's very frightened.
She doesn't know where she
is or what's going on.
And she's terrified of the living.
- Now you said the attic?
- Yeah, up those stairs.
We opened the attic door at one point, and
it was almost like we startled someone.
And whatever it was ran
across to the corner.
And we fully expected to find someone.
So we ascended the ladder,
looking for something up there.
There was... there was
never anything there.
She's just really, really terrified.
Her death was so fast
and extremely painful.
She didn't really process it.
It was a very sharp...
Pain in the neck.
And I did get that she died in the '70s.
There's a woman, Helen Hillman,
who lived in the house that your
salon is in from 1947 to 1977.
1977 is when she died.
She fell down the steps into the basement.
- That's where they found her.
- Wow.
She died of massive head injuries.
That's her and her husband.
That's really sad, really, really sad.
So what else did you get on the walk?
I saw something really strange
in the old garage area.
What I saw was your typical Grim Reaper...
The skeleton face, the sickle,
the cloak, the whole thing.
And that's really odd,
because I've seen death,
before and death actually
does not look like that.
So as I'm looking deeper, I can feel
and tell that this is a dead person.
That it's a dead male.
That he hid in life a lot,
and now he's hiding again in death.
When I went in there, I, um...
Felt like I had been beaten up.
I couldn't breathe. My head felt
like it was going to explode.
Tell her the feeling you guys
get when you go back there.
The back side of the property,
especially by that old garage...
We feel this... this pressure.
And I would say it's like the air's
kinda sucked out of the room.
It would be like being in high altitude,
really, but there's no explanation for it.
Basically, he wants to cause
pain and to hurt people.
He's trying to stop you from breathing?
Yes.
The other thing that I saw was...
A sensitive who... who's here.
And she knowingly or unknowingly...
Lets the dead on the property
into the main house.
They just kind of follow her.
And this includes the Grim Reaper guy.
Remember the dark mist with your daughter?
Tell Amy about that.
She drew a figure that
she saw in the basement.
It was a full figure like a human,
but with red eyes and all black.
And she drew a picture of that.
I said, "oh, what's this?"
She said, "oh, mom, that's
the man in the basement".
Okay, I did do a sketch of what I saw.
As far as this individual leading
several dead people into the house.
Oh.
Is that me?
I did do a sketch of what I saw.
As far as this individual leading
several dead people into the house.
Okay.
Oh.
Is that me?
When was the first time
you had an experience?
When I was 2.
What kind of experiences have you had?
A lot.
I noticed doing hair that I
can't even touch some people,
or I feel, like, their pain, and
I start crying for no reason.
Is there a reason why
you're running from it?
It's something that if you run...
Or try to run from it...
They're gonna follow you. And it's
hereditary, it runs in families.
I see it in my daughter.
Prior owners never felt this or anything.
Nobody ever... is it because possibly
she's a sensitive that this is happening?
If they see somebody who can talk
to them who's ignoring them...
They get a little feisty.
The last thing that I got is...
Really crappy.
This land draws negativity to it.
And a lot of bad things have happened here.
When people are here, they struggle.
They go broke.
They... there's fires. There's robberies.
You know, like, it's never okay in...
in this, going way back, area.
Hmm, it's interesting you say
that, though, because...
What we're sitting on was
part of a 160-acre farm.
And it got turned over 30 times
in 80 years, which is unheard of.
There's surrounding farms...
No problems. They didn't...
families for generations.
It makes total sense to me.
Well, you've seen the results
of the investigation,
learned about the dark
history of this property.
You've seen and heard who
Amy's encountered here.
But the most important question
is, is it gonna be safe,
for you guys, your employees, customers...
Most importantly your family?
For that I'm gonna turn it over to Amy.
There's a few things that are
going to have to be done.
The first thing is dealing with the land.
The house is actually in a
good position on the land.
But once you get to the back deck, it
begins to get progressively worse.
But it gets really dark when
you hit the old garage.
That's where a line literally
needs to be drawn weekly.
And all you have to do is
draw a line with salt.
And that'll help with the whole
contamination factor of the land here.
The other thing that needs to be done is
to take care of the girl in the attic.
This is something that you
innately have the ability to do.
Get some Sage and some salt.
Go ahead and Sage the building
inside and out, including the attic.
Then taking the salt...
And drawing a line all
along the walls inside.
Tossing it around the attic,
and taking the salt all around the
outside of the building as well.
What about the Grim Reaper
and the greaser guy?
So the greaser guy and the Grim
Reaper are actually the same person.
And at some point after
death, he fractured.
Occasionally, I'll meet a dead person...
That forms an attachment.
So...
I'm going to go ahead and
take him home with me.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- He's attached to me anyway,
so I'll just take him home...
Until I reunite the
shattered aspect of him.
And then I'm able to help move him on.
The other thing I want to talk to you about
is the fact that you are a sensitive,
and your daughter is a sensitive.
And there's things that you need to do now
to make it a comfortable
environment for her.
For you, what this is...
this is gaining knowledge,
learning how to control your environment.
And your daughter's environment,
and teaching her those skills,
so she can protect herself as well.
Let me ask you a question. What about him?
How does he help her?
The main thing is for right
now is just being supportive.
It's really tough to think,
that they were experiencing more
than I was this entire time,
both my wife and my daughter.
You know, you're trying to protect 'em.
Now are you gonna be all right
doing this with your daughter,
you gonna be comfortable with it?
- Oh, yes.
- Yeah.
And you guys are gonna do this stuff?
- Yes, yes, yes, yes.
- Oh, yeah. Yeah.
The good news is you don't have to leave.
Very good news.
Thank you.