Subs created by: David Coleman.
So much has happened here.
I'm going through their
deaths... one, two, three, four.
I didn't even know if I
was gonna live through it.
I could feel them touching.
She was pushed down the stairs.
It is an excruciating death.
- And they hung them.
- They hung them.
They're bent on revenge.
Is it dangerous?
You get bad people in a bad place.
Bad things are gonna happen.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing is, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people.
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her? It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were
ghosts in this house.
Amy and I conduct our
investigations separately.
I interview witnesses, local experts,
and look for anything unusual
about the history of the location.
At the end, we meet with our
clients to reveal our findings.
I'm in downtown Seattle to
meet a woman named Darcy.
She was a big-time
skeptic of the paranormal.
Then she bought a restaurant.
Now she's seeing strange things, and she
thinks it's making her physically sick.
She's afraid of losing her
business, her health, and her sanity.
Hopefully, Amy and I can help her out.
Before Amy enters a location,
I clear it of anything that
could be leading information.
This restaurant has a lot of
photographs and historical items.
So it's important I take my
time to cover or remove them all.
Once I'm done...
Amy can begin her walk.
...
And there was no respect there.
I would like them to
have a funeral service.
Followed by a blessing.
So, if they get this funeral service
done, will this move these creatures on?
Well, it's part of the process.
So, the funeral and then the blessing.
And that will help to move them on.
Who do you think made Darcy sick, then?
I think it's the woman
in black downstairs.
I think it was her.
What kind of a risk are we talking about
with her, if she doesn't listen to you?
Well, she'd kill her.
Darcy, it sounds like
we got here just in time.
That's a lot to lay on
you guys in one night.
What are you gonna do?
We're gonna do it.
We have nothing to lose.
You have everything to gain, actually.
Gain your health back. Hopefully,
business will be better.
I really care about Darcy's
business, as well as her well-being.
So I'll do everything I can to make
sure that her business is successful.
I really hope Darcy follows my advice.
This way, all the entities in her
restaurant will be able to move on.
If she doesn't, I fear
not only for her safety,
but her employees' and
customers', as well.