Subs created by: David Coleman.
I'm seeing a female losing her mind.
There's a struggle on
whose house this is.
I see attacks every day, every day.
- We're kind of trapped.
- Then I hear "death".
Do you think there's any
foul play involved here?
It might be a poltergeist.
I feel like it's watching me.
"Mine, mine. Back the [Bleep] off".
I want to have my home back.
I encountered a poltergeist.
They're being watched.
My name is Amy Allan.
This thing likes death.
I see dead people.
This thing is, like, a monster.
I speak to dead people.
And he's pissed off now.
And they speak to me.
His head was cracked.
But there's only one way to
know if my findings are real.
This guy was murdered.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Di Schiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide Detective.
I cannot help you unless
I know the whole story.
And I know every person,
every house has secrets.
You saw her? It's my job to reveal them.
Why would you stay here?
But Steve and I never speak...
We never communicate
during an investigation.
Until the very end.
Stop it.
We uncover if it's
safe for you to stay...
I want to know the truth. I
want to know what's happening.
Or time to get out.
I told you there were
ghosts in this house.
Amy and I investigate
each case separately.
I uncover a property's history and
question the witnesses involved.
While Amy talks to the dead.
When we're done, we reveal our
findings to our client and each other.
I'm in Westminster, Colorado.
It's a sleepy little suburb
about 20 minutes north of Denver.
I received a call from a woman
named Cara, who's a single mom.
She tells me her entire family's
afraid to be in the house alone.
She does not sound good.
I'm hoping Amy and I can help her out.
Before Amy can start her walk,
I need to make sure she is free
from any outside influences.
This house is filled with photographs
of a mother and her young children,
that have to be covered or removed.
When I'm finished, Amy can begin.
I'm seeing a female freaking out...
Losing her mind.
...
She'll be taken care of, like, kind
of inadvertently through this process.
And then the last thing is
dealing with the PK manifestation,
that's, you know,
upstairs in your closet.
What you want to do is a
little bit of counseling,
just to work out those past issues.
So, you're taking it outside
of the house to a person...
- Rather than in here.
- Right.
And you're verbalizing
it out to that therapist.
Will it ever go away?
Um, no.
I mean, it, very slowly over a very
long period of time, could dissipate.
So as long as you keep
it stunted, it's great.
What about this guy John Shannon?
Till this stuff gets resolved,
are they gonna be all right?
Yes. You know your power over him.
And so you just need to start
exerting that like nobody's business.
And also tell your
children to do the same.
- So you're empowering them.
- Mm hmm.
Well, Cara, you're gonna
do what she tells you.
- Definitely, yes.
- Okay.
I truly believe the PK manifestation
poses a dangerous threat to Cara's family.
If she follows the steps I
outlined, it will slowly dissolve,
and she and her two kids can
live in their home in peace.