Kit!
- Two dollars.
- Okay.
- Mark.
- Coming.
Hey, the plate!
Sir.
Tastes good?
Are you alright?
- Here, go see a doctor.
- Thanks, Mark.
Can you read that?
What?
It's all in English.
Hi Tom, how are you?
Hi, Russ.
Hi!
- Tom, good to see you
- Long time no see
Thanks
That's heavy.
That's great. First class!
Here.
Hey! Why don't we go out
for a drink sometime, all right?
Why don't you find us some women?
We can all go out.
Tom, it was a pleasure doing
business with you.
You're good at bullshitting.
Your English has improved.
- You can even say "Of course"!
- Of course!
- Good morning.
Good morning.
- Good morning, Mark.
- That's "Brother Mark".
Mr. Yiu.
Ho, you're back.
Everything okay?
- I already checked it.
- Great.
It's easy dealing with the foreigners.
They are not all trustworthy.
You trust people too easily.
Thanks.
You must be Sing?
Take a seat.
No, thanks.
I'll stand.
Good morning,
Linda.
Rose!
Sing, you can learn a lot from Ho.
He is the most loyal.
Yes, he can teach me a lot.
Mark is a bit frivolous,
but he is loyal too.
Yes, he takes good care of me.
What's that?
Nothing, we're just talking about you.
Really?
Ho. Doesn't your brother, Kit,
graduate today?
Oh, yeah!
I forgot to get him a present.
I gotta go.
Ho, take Sing with you to Taiwan
day after tomorrow.
Give the youngster a change.
Show him the ropes.
Taiwan! It's not Chaiwan.
Have you got the guts?
I've been at this for years,
and I'm still afraid. Know why?
The drills, choppers, Taiwan gangs!
Even the beer drinking can kill you!
- Don't make fun of him.
- Okay.
So, Kit graduated...
get him a woman for a gift!
No, I won't let him go astray like us.
Hey, it's better than getting a hooker.
I want to see him get
his PhD...
...and see him get married.
See him consummate his marriage,
have a baby...
...then his life will be even harder!
They say, "One with a dirty mouth
steps on shit entering an elevator! "
You first.
I won't! Let's step in together!
Don't move. Police!
- Search!
- Yes, sir.
Don't move!
- Don't joke with me.
- Turn around.
We both have guns.
If you don't respect me,
I won't respect you.
Let's see who is not
respecting the other.
That tickles! Don't...
Enough!
Enough.
Brother, I have some good news.
I've been accepted to become
a Police Inspector. Surprised?
It'll be hard work.
You'll be the Police Commissioner
one day.
Jackie!
She's my girlfriend.
She helps take care of dad.
My big brother.
Hi.
Don't worry, dad's in good hands.
- Thank you very much.
- Don't mention it.
It's time for my audition!
A new girlfriend...
I hope this time it'll last.
That all depends on how she behaves.
You said you would go with me.
Hurry up!
I'd love to stay, but...
No need to explain,
get out of here!
Excuse me.
- Let's go.
- Hurry up!
Bye.
- Ho...
- Dad.
You should get out of the business.
Your brother has no idea
what you are doing.
I remember when you kids played
"Cops & Robbers" together.
Even when he lost...
...he still wanted to be the cop.
I don't want to see you two brothers
play this game for real.
Give it up for the sake of
your brother.
- Okay?
- Alright.
It's about time.
- Sorry, the traffic was horrible.
- A real traffic jam.
I'm Jackie.
- Give me a chance, please!
- Give her a chance!
- Careful, she's pregnant!
- Are you alright?
Sir, the traffic was awful!
- Please give her a chance?
- Okay.
Alright, go, go ahead!
Pregnant and getting
pushed like that...
Hey, panel judges.
Please listen.
Sorry.
It's all your fault! You embarrassed
me before I went on stage!
You can't help in any way!
You don't even have confidence
in yourself. How can I help?
They didn't say you failed.
You don't know it's hopeless.
Give that back to me!
Now it's really hopeless!
Have you decided?
One last job, then I'll quit.
Because of Kit?
That deal in Taiwan tomorrow,
you better not go.
If anything happens to me there,
you can take care of things here.
You will lead the Brothers
in the future.
I cannot do that.
Let Godfather Sing do it.
He looks just like Al Pacino.
Mark, stop fooling around!
Ho, we can't do it without you.
I still have much to learn from you.
You really think you can learn this?
Don't think reading gangster books
will help make you the boss.
Have you ever had a gun
pointed at your head?
No.
Twelve years ago...
Twelve years already.
For the first time, I went with Ho
to bring goods to Indonesia.
The Boss there treated us to
dinner in the night club.
I said something wrong,
displeasing the Boss...
...and there were two
guns pointing at my head.
I was forced to drink
a bottle of whiskey.
I was so scared, I pissed my pants!
Fortunately, Ho drank the whole
bottle of whiskey for me.
But, it got even worse after that.
Four guns were pointed at my head.
You know what they made me drink?
Piss!
Drank piss in a night club!
You want to learn?
That's real learning!
That's how we got through
our first job.
That's all in the past,
forget about it.
No.
I had never cried before.
That was the first time I cried.
I swore I'd never let anyone
point a gun at my head again!
How's that?
Careful!
Practice more with your sand bag.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
Disappearing as usual.
I'll be back soon.
While I'm away,
take good care of dad.
Sure.
Take care.
I will.
They're coming, move!
Hurry!
Careful, something's wrong.
- How do you know?
- Intuition.
- Mr. Sung, how are you?
- Where is Mr. Wang?
Sick. I'm his nephew.
He asked me to meet with you.
How are you?
What's wrong with him?
Mr. Sung, let's go in first.
It's nothing serious. The police
are quite alert these days...
...and it's better for him to lay low.
- Have a cup of tea.
- Thanks.
Mr. Sung, this way please.
Come in, please, have a seat.
Let's not waste any more time.
Head quarters, please run a check
on a car numbered 1086379.
Mr. Sung, you really keep your word.
When I was a kid, I admired you.
Can you believe that someone is
paying me triple to kill you?
He's crazy, who does he think I am?
Let me get your money.
The police are coming!
Hello?
Uncle...
Sung Tse Ho has killed some
of our Brothers in Taiwan.
Now, the police are after him...
...and our boss is afraid he'll talk.
You're coming with me.
I don't want to use force.
You bastard!
If you hurt my son, I'll hunt
you down till the day I die!
Run, quickly run!
What are you doing?
Don't! Don't!
No, don't!
Hello, hello?
Wrong number!
Uncle, let's go!
Uncle!
Jackie, what's happening?
Kit, watch out!
Dad, don't come out!
Dad! Dad, don't!
Dad!
Kit, you have to... forgive...
your brother...
Who betrayed me?
You?
Brother Ho, if I had betrayed you,
I wouldn't be here with you.
I don't know if I'll escape this time.
Brother Ho, what are you doing?
- Brother Ho...
- Surrendering.
You can't go, Ho! Don't go.
You shouldn't go out there.
Brother Ho, don't.
Don't go out there!
Go! Run!
- Brother Ho...
- Go!
I won't let you get caught.
Gun shots are coming from inside!
- Go!
- I don't want to!
I'm telling you to go!
Stand up and don't move!
Don't move!
Put down the gun!
Brotherhood and ethics do not seem
to exist in our world anymore.
No one is trustworthy anymore.
Little Wang really is my nephew...
...but he has betrayed me as well.
He hooked up with
a new force in Hong Kong...
...and is trying to take over
my business.
Sung Tse Ho went down
because of him.
On principle, we strictly
respect loyal friends.
And we won't forgive those
who betray us.
Hello?
Yes.
Tonight he will be at
Fung Lim Kok Restaurant.
Is there anything else
I could do to help?
Do you need some extra men?
Take care.
Thanks.
Captain!
Captain, this way.
I'm not scared.
My boss will bail me out.
Come on, drop your gun
and let's fight as equals.
Then we'll see who is stronger.
5703!
- Yes, sir, what is it?
- Nothing.
Mr. Sung, what's up?
Drug trafficking, resisting arrest,
assault.
- Not very smart.
- Take his statement.
Thanks!
How's it going? It's a lot different
on the outside, isn't it?
Need a lift?
No, thanks.
We're going different directions.
I admire you.
Your loyalty. Three years in jail
and you haven't said a word.
What's crazy is while
you were inside...
...the counterfeit money was
still being printed.
Thanks!
I've retired.
Tell your friends...
...that case three years ago isn't
closed yet. I'm not giving up.
Once a thief, it's not easy
to turn your life around.
Bye.
I won't be back.
Stop!
Kit, calm down!
Stop fighting!
Kit, stop it!
Don't let me see you again!
Are you the manager?
There's no manager here.
I'm Ken. What do you want?
Ken, Uncle Chung from Taiwan
told me to come to you.
I was doing business in Taiwan...
You were in jail,
not doing business.
Uncle Chung asked me to
give you this letter in person.
Uncle Chung never has
anything good for me.
But we are good old friends.
It's very difficult for an
ex-con to find a job.
Who wants to employ an ex-con?
No need to get depressed.
Everyone here has been a jailbird.
Some people like to adopt orphans...
...I like to take care of ex-convicts!
You see, I also have been
in prison before.
Colleagues...
...this brother has just been
released.
Take good care of him.
- He is... you are...
- Sung Tse Ho.
Brother Ho!
Oh no, just call me Ho.
What are you doing?
Trying to win favors?
Get back to work!
I'm not paying you to stand around!
- You got a driver's license?
- No.
I don't care if you get one or not.
Just stick around here for now.
- Ken, you're very kind.
- Don't worry about it.
There is no boss here.
- For your lunch.
- Thank you.
Mark.
Why did you lie to me in your letters?
Mark, even if both my
legs were broken...
...I could never make it up to you.
Idiot, I just had some bad luck,
don't worry about it.
I'm so happy to see you again!
It's been so long!
You still look good.
Mark, this is not our world anymore.
Why are you still staying here?
I've waited for you for three years.
Three years, already!
We can start over again!
Don't worry about me.
Look after your brother.
He's been following Sing everyday.
It's getting dangerous.
Anyhow, you two are real brothers.
Kit, we all know you are very
capable.
In fact, I'd like you to be promoted,
but the higher-ups don't approve.
Why?
This guy. You know him well.
We thought he had
disappeared for good.
But he was just released from jail
and is back in town.
- He's with his old brothers again.
- How does that affect me?
This is an investigation of
corruption in the police force.
And we can't have officers
with relatives in the underworld.
Now do you understand?
When I'm on duty...
...I never think of him as my brother.
Kit...
...you're off the Sing case.
I can't allow anything to ruin it.
Mr. Sung, Sing is meeting
the Thai men tonight.
Brothers, cheers!
- Mark, tell us some of your stories!
- Ho, you tell.
My Boss says the maximum price
is 18 million, no more.
Okay, okay.
Sung Tse Ho's group is outside.
Draught beer, please.
Bye.
Our Boss is over there.
Ho!
You didn't let us know you're back!
What kind of a friend are you?
We were once good brothers.
Right, Mark?
Ho, if you hadn't taken care of me,
I wouldn't be where I am today.
Don't be silly, you've worked hard.
I don't have that kind of power.
It's thanks to Mark, that the
position opened up for me.
Mark, should you ever need my help,
feel free to call me.
No more bullshit,
come on, let's drink!
You really take good care
of your brothers!
Come on, cheers!
This glass is for my leg!
Happy?
Ho, call me when you have time.
We have lots to discuss.
I'm not interested.
You will be.
I have to go now.
Sung Tse Ho!
Step outside with me.
What are you doing?
What did Sing tell you?
Just bullshit.
Don't lie to me!
Is it business or bullshit?
Really bullshit!
- Are the goods arriving soon?
- I don't know.
Where is it unloading? And when?
I don't know.
You don't know anything!
How can you be the boss?
Kit...
Don't ever call me Kit again,
call me 'Sir'!
Sir...
...I haven't been the Boss
for a long time.
Where do you work?
United Taxi Company.
A regular job?
Robbing with a taxi?
- Where do you live?
- United Taxi Company.
Someone's willing to take
in a thief like you!
You bastard! "Thief"?!
He has a name!
Just because you have a gun...
Touch me again and I'll kill you,
you cripple!
Kid, do not point a gun at my head.
If you've got the guts, kill me!
Shoot me... shoot me!
Kit...
...No...
Sir, I know I owe you a lot.
Can you give me another chance?
Give you another chance?
I'm the one who needs
another chance!
Because of you, I've lost
any chance of promotion!
Because you're a gangster!
You'd better not leave Hong Kong.
I'll be watching you!
Break time!
Thank you, Ken!
Don't thank me, I'm taking it out
from your salary!
You're so mean!
Hey, I've got a wife to support.
There's a beautiful girl staring at you.
Your girlfriend?
- Please come in!
- No, thanks!
I need your help.
Can you leave Hong Kong
for a while?
Kit is about to have
a mental breakdown.
He can't stand this pressure,
and neither can I .
I think it's best if you
go away for awhile.
I can't leave.
I need Kit to see that
I've started a new life.
Can you give me the
chance to show him?
Do you think that I don't want to...
...go skating and cycling
with him again?
I want my little brother back.
Brother Ho!
Don't stay here, go inside.
You standing here won't help.
Ho will handle his own business,
go inside!
- Who are they?
- They're not good guys.
Our boss wants to
invite you to a meeting.
I'm busy.
Show some respect,
have a little chat with the boss.
- Hello?
- Ho, Mark is here now.
Come join us and discuss business.
Sorry, I'm not interested.
Don't want to talk about business?
Let's talk about your brother then.
- Still not interested? I'm waiting.
- Okay.
Ken, I have to go out for awhile.
If you live by your principles,
you have nothing to fear.
Be strong.
Ho, this way.
It's easy to become a gangster,
but it's hard to get out.
- Ho.
- Brother Ho!
Ho, I'm so glad you're back.
- Mr. Yiu, how are you?
- Fine, thanks.
Come on... come over
and talk with Sing.
Not with you?
Talking with Sing is the same.
I'm old...
...he can make the decisions.
Sit down.
Business is good right now.
I was hoping you'd like to cooperate.
How's that?
You're still our Boss.
Mark will handle trafficking
the money.
I traffic drugs.
Earn some money for the company.
There's too many old debts,
we need you to get our money back.
Get to the point.
We need an insider at the police
department. Maybe your brother.
There's nothing better than having
one of your own on the force.
Come here, I have
something to tell you.
What if I don't accept?
Ho, I respect you, so I'm keeping
that dead fish Mark here.
Your brother knows no limits,
he follows me everyday!
If I didn't respect you,
he'd be dead already!
Sing, one is my friend,
one is my brother.
If I can promise you this,
how can I walk out this door?
I don't care if you insult me,
but don't insult my friend!
If you dare hurt my brother...
...you will live to regret it!
Mark Lee is a serious killer.
We've been after him for three years.
But there's no extradition treaty
between Hong Kong and Taiwan.
However, we may be able
to arrest the whole syndicate.
The ROC Police Dept
wanna give information...
to Interpol and to the
Hong Kong Police.
The US Police Dept has also taken action
I see!
We just got some
important information.
In two days, there'll be a whole lot of
counterfeit money brought to Taiwan.
Along with 500 kg. Of morphine.
Even though I can't break
the case myself...
...I still hope to see Mark Lee
and his gang get arrested.
Boss, Sung Tse Ho is too much,
let us finish him off!
We don't need to kill him,
we can still play with him.
Just follow the plan.
We already paid. Where do
we pick up the merchandise?
Okay, I'll write it down.
That's the address.
Let's drink!
You're back!
Have you eaten?
What are you doing?
Mr. Mok, it's Kit.
I have some information.
The Thai are delivering
the goods tomorrow.
The location and time should be...
Kit, bring in the information
tomorrow, then leave it alone.
Why?
You are not on the case!
I can't allow it!
Just give me a chance.
I've told you, the police force
won't allow it.
You do this now and...
Do you know that
today is my birthday?
Why won't you look at me?
You'll look at a vase, but not me!
This is your home,
not the Police Station!
You even forgot my birthday!
Jackie.
Happy Birthday.
I didn't forget.
Blow out your candles,
they're almost out.
- What did you wish for?
- You really want to know?
Sure.
- Promise you won't get mad?
- Just say it.
I just wished you two brothers
would reunite.
Don't be mad.
I'm not.
Don't be mad, it's my birthday.
I won't let you lose your temper.
Otherwise, I will get mad.
Smile!
I'll get the door.
What is it?
I need to speak to Kit.
Who is it?
Don't get angry!
Keep your promise, okay?
- Please, sit down.
- Thanks.
- Today is your birthday?
- Yes.
- Have some cake.
- Who told you to be nice to him?!
Kit, stop it.
Kit, I don't care how you treat me...
...I'm just here to warn you.
Sing is going to trap you at any
minute. Please, be careful.
Thanks for your concern.
Don't trust information
that comes too easily.
Usually, those clues are planted ones.
You have to be able to spot them.
Do you think I'm the same old Kit?
I just wanted to help.
- That's all.
- Help me or trick me?
Did you know your release
from jail ruined my career?
Can't you trust me just once?
Trust you?
It's because I trusted you
that my father is dead!
Jackie...
Ho.
His feelings about me
still haven't changed.
Don't give up.
Please, keep trying.
Don't let others look down on you.
How come you can't accept him?
- Can't you give him a chance?
- Dad's dead because of him!
Why are you forcing me
to accept him?
He chose the wrong road!
It's his own fault!
I'm the cop, he's the thief.
In the eyes of the law,
we're on different paths.
Police!
- What's up, Ken?
- Your brother had an accident.
- He's at Margaret Hospital. Hurry!
- Got it.
What happened to my brother?
I believe he was set up by Sing.
It was an ambush.
Is he okay?
Hey, you can't go in!
I tried to stop him from
going alone, but he insisted.
I hope you'll cooperate with us. Keep
us informed of your whereabouts.
Come on, being a hero is easy.
Just jump.
Times have changed,
if you don't cooperate with us...
...that'll be your only choice.
You can't go to the police.
You're as dirty as I am.
What's going on?
Everybody stop fighting!
This is to teach Ho a lesson.
Everyone stop fighting!
Kick his ass!
Stop!
Let's talk about it!
We've worked so hard
for a better life!
Don't throw it all away
and end up in jail again!
Stop fighting!
Stop, you bastard!
Come on, run, go!
You stay here, you bastard!
Stay here, if you got the guts!
You bastards!
Ken, it's my fault.
I didn't mean to involve you!
If you do this, you're just like them!
They beat on people
because they are weak.
If you hit them back,
you'll be back where you started.
It's so hard to change paths.
Why'd you bother?
Who is this guy?
Come on, let's pick him up.
Ken! Ho!
Come here, come look!
Mark!
Hurry, go and get the first aid kit.
Hurry!
Ken, what do we do now?
You get out of here.
Police, out of the car!
Oh, come on...
...are the police above the law?
I'll send my insurance claim to you.
Smart ass. Get out of here!
I didn't realize Hong Kong
looked so beautiful at night.
Such beauty can vanish in a blink.
Really it isn't worth it.
Ho...
...let's start all over again.
One last job and we'll leave
Hong Kong and vanish!
Mark...
You've never been afraid
of anything...
...why do you fear Sing?
Don't push me...
I can't get involved again.
What's done is done. It's over.
Not yet. Not as long as I'm alive!
There's no difference between one
more job, or ten more, or a hundred!
I let you kill Sing, then what?
I've already lost a brother...
...I don't want to lose you too.
Mark, don't you see?
I don't need your pity!
You don't owe me a thing!
I would never force a friend
to go against their will.
I have my own principles!
I can't live like this anymore!
Do you think I like to beg?
Three years like this!
This is my chance to get out!
I have to prove myself!
Not because I'm better than them...
...but to prove I can get back
what I've lost!
Look at yourself. Can you see
what you've become?
Before, people rejected you.
Now, you can't take two steps
without someone following you!
Have you ever fought for a chance?
You haven't.
No!
I don't want to be like you.
Mark!
What happened?
I want to get something back.
Stand back!
Go get the tape.
Think about this.
You won't get away.
Don't move!
Stop! Switch off!
- Go, get out of here.
- Open the door.
Thanks, Uncle Chan.
Don't let him escape!
You bastard!
You bastard! I told you
not to play with fire!
Bastard.
If Ho gives the Police that tape...
...it won't just be your head, bastard!
Our whole organization
will collapse!
Have you finished?
Bastard... bastard?!
When I was making you rich,
was I a bastard?
I'm sorry I ever trusted you!
If you don't get that tape back,
I'll kill you!
Kill me then.
Three years ago I betrayed Ho.
You think I'm scared of you?
You'll suffer the consequences!
You put me in charge.
We'll go down together!
Hello?
Hello, Ho? What the hell happened?
Mr. Yiu, I want to talk to Sing.
Sing? Hold on.
No matter what, get him
to return the tape, okay bastard?
Ho, stop fooling around.
Let's talk about this.
At 10 PM, bring $2 million to the
Temple in exchange for the tape.
Then, have a boat ready
for us at Surf Bay.
Is that all?
I want cash.
- And come in person.
- I'll be there.
So, what did Ho say, bastard?
What did he say?
What?!
- He'll meet you for dinner tonight.
- Okay, I'll be waiting.
Sung Sir.
Come in.
Sir, I've got some news.
Sung Tse Ho and the cripple
had a falling out with Sing.
They're blackmailing him.
The exchange is tonight.
- Do you know where and when?
- I'll find out.
Hello? Yes, I...
Thanks.
Sing just withdrew $2 million dollars
from the bank.
Cancel any leave!
Put everyone on alert!
Yes, sir.
Mr. Mok, let me in on the action.
You're still injured.
Why are you here?
I'm all right, it's not serious.
Go home and rest!
I'm okay. See, I can lift this chair.
You're not wanted this time!
My brother is the thief, not me!
I've always fulfilled my duties!
You know the rules!
- Your brother is involved!
- Ever since my father died...
...I've been after Sing.
I know more about this
case than anyone!
You'll bring him in yourself?
I'll bring him in myself.
I will.
You bet I'll bring him in.
Kit, be practical.
Jackie...
...I'm leaving Hong Kong tonight.
You're giving up?
You have to get this package
to Kit before nine tonight.
The contents are
very important to him.
Will you come back?
Kit, your brother is leaving tonight!
He told me to give you this.
It's important.
Kit, the tape I've enclosed...
...has the evidence you need
to nail Sing.
I've arranged a meeting
with Sing tonight at Surf Bay.
You can arrest me as well,
I don't care.
I've decided not to stay
in Hong Kong.
Kit, what are you going to do?
Arrest him.
No, you can't arrest him!
You can't!
Get off!
Kit... !
Where is Ho?
The food is already cold!
You know what to say, right?
Do you believe there's a god?
Sure, I'm a god.
A god can be human.
Anyone who controls
their own destiny is a god.
Sometimes, there's things
you can't control.
You win some, you lose some.
Don't move.
And the money?
You got the tape?
The police have it.
Don't open it!
There's a bomb inside.
Did you think it would be so easy?
Did I scare you?
You're no fun to play with.
Holy shit.
Fuck you!
After Sung Tse Ho arrived,
he and Master quarreled.
He asked Master for $2 million.
Said he's leaving from Surf Bay
tonight. Then, I heard shooting.
That's him.
- Are you sure?
- Oh, yes.
- Are you willing to testify?
- Sure.
- You're going down, you bastard.
- And you're going with me.
Get out!
- Get out!
- Move!
Get out!
Be smart, let him go!
Come out!
Don't hide!
Move!
Ho, come aboard!
You go on ahead.
You said we'd leave together.
I have some unfinished business.
I'll catch up.
Mark, get out of here!
I'll see you later.
Move!
Release him or your brother is dead!
I don't think so!
One for the other!
Go.
- Go.
- Move!
I won't let you go.
I know.
Over here!
Get over here!
This is your brother!
Take a good look at him!
Take a good look!
Whatever he's done in the past,
he's more than paid you back!
He's trying to change his life around!
Why can't you accept him?
Why?
To be brothers...
Mark!
Sing!
Miss, you can't go in.
Sung Tse Ho, you're surrounded
by the police!
You have three minutes to
come out with your hands up!
Out of bullets?
I guess I'll go surrender.
I'll be okay. You on the other hand...
You see, I have money. A few days
in court and I'll be a free man.
If you have money,
you can turn black to white.
This, I learned from you.
I pity your brother.
Because of you,
his white has become black.
And it's your fault.
Kit...
...you've done nothing wrong.
We are on different paths.
Yours is the right one.
I lost my way before...
...but I want to find my way back
if it's not too late.
Subtitles by TUO PADRE