Kit...
Kit!
- Two dollars' worth!
- OK!
- Mark!
- Coming!
Hey! Don't forget your plate...
Sir!
Taste good?
You feeling alright?
- Take this and go see a doctor...
- Thank you, Brother Mark...
You can read?
Huh?
If you can't read, don't pretend...
Hi!
Oh, hi Tom. How are you?
Hi Russ.
Hi.
Tom, good to see you.
How are things?
Ah, thanks.
That's heavy.
That's great.
First class.
Hey, why don't we go out
for a drink sometime?
Tom. It was a pleasure
doing business with you.
Very good! Your English
is getting better...
You even know "of course"...
Of course!
Good morning, Brother Mark!
Good morning, Mr. Sung!
Good morning!
- Good morning, Mr. Sung!
- Good morning!
Brother Mark, good morning!
"Brother Mark"...
I like the way that sounds!
- Mr. Yiu!
- Ho, you're back!
- Did it go OK?
- I counted it already...
- That's great.
- Those foreigners are easygoing...
Not every foreigner is
as considerate as them...
Your weakness is that
you are too easily taken in...
You're Shing? Have a seat...
No, thanks.
It's better for me to stand.
Good morning, Linda!
Like a rose...
Shing, you can learn a lot
from Brother Ho...
He's extremely loyal!
True, but I could never
be as good as Brother Ho...
Mark here is a bit silly,
but he'll always have your back...
Yes, Brother Mark
takes good care of me...
- What are you talking about?
- Nothing... Just talking about you...
Really?
Your little brother Kit graduates today...
Oh! I forgot...
I've got to get him a gift...
I should get going...
Ho...
When you go to Taiwan the day after next,
take Shing with you.
Give the kid a chance!
Taiwan! Don't go thinking
it's "Chai-wan"...
I've spent decades in this jianghu world,
but I still don't dare go there!
You want to know why? The gangsters
there use drills! And cleavers!
Just drinking the beer there can kill you!
- Quit playing tricks on him...
- Oh, OK...
You should give Kit a girl
as a graduation present...
I'm a bad guy, but I don't
want him to be like me...
Still better to have a hooker...
I want to see him get a doctorate...
Get married in a church...
Start a life, and have a baby...
You'll be as busy as a buffalo
just keeping up...
I've heard that people with dirty mouths
will step in shit getting on an elevator...
Then after you...
- You first!
- I won't...
Then we'll step in it together!
Hold it! Police!
- Spread 'em!
- Yes, sir...
- Don't move!
- This isn't funny...
Face the wall!
We both have guns...
If you don't treat me with respect,
I'll treat you the same way...
We'll see who gets less respect!
Too ticklish!
- No, don't! Please...
- You sure?
Brother...
I've got some news
sure to give you a surprise!
I passed the officer's exam!
Surprise!
Then you've got to work hard...
You've got to make
superintendent at least...
Jackie!
This is my girlfriend... When she is free
she comes by to look after Dad...
- Hi!
- My big brother!
So this is how she takes care of Dad...
- Thanks for your help...
- Don't mention it...
I've got to get to an interview...
What are you waiting for?
You should make it official with her...
First I'll see how it goes this afternoon
and let you know later...
You said you'll go with me!
Hurry up!
I really want to stay and
look after Dad, but...
No need to explain, go!
- Then I'll be going...
- Go!
Sorry...
- Let's go!
- Hurry up!
Bye bye!
- Ho!
- Dad...
You should quit...
Your brother has never known
what line of work you are in...
I remember when you two were little...
You would always play
cops and robbers together...
He always lost...
But he wanted to be a cop anyways...
Now that you are both grown, I don't
want to see you play that game again...
So do it for your brother...
OK?
OK...
That's the last one...
Excuse me... I'm sorry...
The traffic is terrible!
Yeah, the traffic is completely jammed!
- I'm Jackie...
- Sir... traffic...
- Please give me a chance...
- Give her a chance, OK?
- Are you OK? Aren't you pregnant...
- You alright?
Sir, the traffic just now is really bad...
Give her a chance, please...
OK, OK...
Great! Let's go!
- To hit a pregnant lady...
- How awful!
Hey, judges! Listen up...
Excuse me...
It was all your fault!
You made me look like a fool!
You didn't help me one bit!
When you don't have confidence
in yourself, how can I help you?
Besides, the judge didn't say
you failed, so how can you know?
Give it to me!
How can I have any hope now?
Are you sure?
Once this job is finished... I'm done...
Because of Kit?
Don't go with me to Taiwan
to make the buy...
If anything goes wrong,
you'll be here to look after things...
And you can become the new boss...
That's going too far...
Let Shing here stay...
He looks like Al Pacino...
Brother Mark, don't make fun of me...
Brother Ho, we can't
do this job without you...
I still have a lot of things
to learn from you...
You think you can learn just by watching?
Don't think you can become the boss just
by reading the gangster novels all day...
You ever had the barrel of
a gun against your head?
No, you haven't...
Twelve years ago...
Twelve years?
Brother Ho and I took some goods
to Indonesia for the first time...
Their boss invited us
to dinner at a nightclub...
I said something wrong,
and offended their boss...
Suddenly there were two guns
pressed against my head...
They told me I had to finish
a whole bottle of whiskey...
I was so scared I peed in
my pants... I really peed!
Brother Ho here saved me...
He drank all that whiskey for me...
But to not drink was even worse...
Suddenly there were four guns
against my head!
Do you know what they
asked me to drink then?
Piss!
That night in the club I drank piss!
Learning? That's what's called learning!
That was our first job together...
It's all in the past...
don't bring it up again...
I will...
I had never cried before...
But that night I bawled...
After that I swore, no one would ever
put a gun to my head again!
Strong, eh?
Whoa, careful!
You need to hit the sandbag more!
I'm leaving tomorrow...
Time for you to disappear again...
I'll be back soon...
While I am away...
Take care of Dad...
Don't worry about it...
Look after yourself...
I will...
They're coming, get ready!
Be careful... I've got a bad feeling...
- How do you know?
- Intuition...
Mr. Sung, you've made it! How are you?
Where's Wang?
He fell ill. I'm his nephew and
he asked to come in his place...
How you doing... Hi, hi...
What kind of illness he has got?
Mr. Sung, let's go inside to talk...
Actually he's not ill, he's just lying
low for now, 'til things here clear up...
- You guys have travelled all this way!
- Have some tea!
Mr. Sung, this way please!
As the boss gets older,
he gets more afraid of everything...
Please, sit...
We shouldn't waste time!
Calling headquarters, please run a check
on license number 1086379...
We feel it warrants suspicion...
Mr. Sung, you are really reliable!
Even when I was still hustling in
Hsimenting, I always looked up to you...
Now would you believe it?
Someone has offered to pay
me double to whack you...
They must be crazy to think
I'm that kind of person!
Let me get you your money...
The police are here!
Hello?
Uncle?
"The ferry boat has departed...
Thousands of miles now separate us..."
Sung has killed many of
my brothers in Taiwan...
Now he is wanted by the police...
My boss is worried that
he might rat us out...
He requests that you, sir, come with us...
I don't want to be rude, but...
You son of a bitch! If you hurt my son...
I'll never let you off!
Run! Get out of here!
What are you doing to him? No, no!
Don't try it!
Hello? Wrong number...
Run, Uncle!
Uncle!
Jackie, what's going on in there?
Kit! Be careful!
Dad, don't come out here!
Dad! Dad, don't!
Dad! Dad!
Kit... you have to...
forgive... your brother!
Who sold me out?
You?
Brother Ho, if I sold you out,
would I be here with you now?
I don't know if we can
get away this time...
Brother Ho, what are you
doing? Brother Ho...
- I'm going to surrender.
- You can't! Brother Ho!
Don't do it! What ever you do, not that!
No, Brother Ho! Don't go! Brother Ho...
Run!
- Brother Ho...
- Get out of here!
I don't want to involve a friend...
There's gun shots in the cavern!
- Go on!
- No...
I'm telling you, go!
Halt! Don't move!
Put down the gun! You hear me? Drop it!
Taiwan and Hong Kong Counterfeit
Smuggling Gangs in Shootout
Hong Kong Gang Leader Sung Tse-ho
Surrenders to Police
The code of the jianghu world
doesn't exist anymore...
There's no one left that you can trust...
That piece of trash Wang
is my own nephew...
And he still sold us out...
He joined up with a new Hong Kong gang...
They are planning to take
over my operations...
As a result, we've lost Ho to them...
According to the code, we have
absolute respect for a loyal man...
And absolute contempt for betrayal...
Hello?
OK...
He will be in Fung Lim
Restaurant tonight...
What do you think?
Is there anything else I can help with?
Do you want to take some of my men?
Take care...
Thanks...
- Chief!
- What do we have?
Chief! This way...
Hmph! I'm not scared...
My boss will get his lawyer
to come and post bail for me!
If you're such a hero,
fight me without your gun!
Then we'll see who's stronger...
5703!
- Everything OK, sir?
- Fine...
Sung, what's the charge?
Drug trafficking and attacking the police!
- You've got some balls to attack Sung!
- Take down his confession...
Thank you...
How you doing? Doesn't the air
on the outside feel different?
Let me give you a lift...
Thanks, but we're not
going the same way...
I admire you...
For your friends, you kept
your mouth shut for three years...
The funny thing is, all the time
you were on the inside...
The counterfeiting racket
just got stronger...
Thanks...
I haven't asked about the
jianghu world for a long time...
Tell your friend...
That case from three years ago
hasn't been resolved yet...
I won't let him off...
Even a criminal for a single day...
Finds it hard to live the
straight life again...
Goodbye...
I won't be back here again...
Stop the car!
Kit, cool down...
Stop fighting!
Kit, stop hitting him!
Don't let me see you again!
Manager!
There's no manager here...
I'm Uncle Kin, are you looking for me?
Uncle Chung in Taiwan asked
me to come see you...
When I was in Taiwan doing business...
Sitting in jail, you mean!
What's this about business?
Uncle Chung asked me
to give you this letter...
That Chung is really shameless!
It's a wonder we are still friends...
It's difficult for an
ex-con to get a job...
Who wants to hire a jailbird?
Don't act so glum...
All of the brothers here have
done time in prison!
Some people like to adopt orphans...
I like to take in jailbirds!
Because I, too, have done time in prison...
Everybody, this new brother
is reporting for duty...
Everyone should look after him...
He is... You are...?
Sung Tse-Ho...
Brother Ho!
No need for all that, just call me Ho...
What is this, a social gathering?
Isn't there work to be done?
I'm not paying you for doing nothing...
- Do you have a driver's license?
- No...
Whether you pass the exam or not...
You are welcome to stay here...
Uncle Kin, you are too kind...
No need to say anymore...
There's no boss here...
- Take it for lunch...
- Thank you!
Mark!
This isn't what you told me
in the letter you wrote!
Mark... even if I break both of my legs...
I can never pay you back!
You idiot... it was my own bad luck
nothing to do with you...
I'm so glad to see you again!
It's been such a long time...
You're still just as handsome...
Mark... this isn't our world anymore...
What are you still doing here?
I've waited for you for three years...
Three years!
Let's start all over again...
Don't bother with me...
Look after your little brother...
Everyday he's been tailing Shing. It's
getting more and more dangerous...
You are both my brothers...
Kit, the whole department knows
how capable you are...
I recommended your promotion...
But the upper levels wouldn't approve it...
Why?
You should be very
familiar with this guy...
Three years ago he disappeared...
He's back after being released
from prison in Taiwan...
And he's back at it with
his old partners...
What does that have to do with me?
Right now we're investigating
underworld contacts in the police force!
The worst would be that a policeman's
blood relation turned out to be a gangster!
Understand?
When I carry out my duty as a cop...
I never even consider
that I have a brother...
Kit!
I'm taking you off Boss Shing's case...
I'm afraid you will spoil
the whole thing...
Officer Sung, tonight Boss Shing
will meet up with those Thais...
Nam!
All my brothers, drain your glasses!
- Brother Mark, let us hear about some of your heroic feats!
- Brother Ho should tell them!
My boss says the highest we
will go is 18 million, no more...
- OK, OK...
- Boss, Sung Tse-Ho is outside...
Draught beer, please...
Boss, he's over there...
Brother Ho! How come you didn't let
me know that you're back?
Not too friendly of you...
I thought we were once all
good brothers, right, Brother Mark?
Brother Ho, without you
looking after me then...
I would never have what I have now!
Don't be ridiculous...
Your greatness today is
due to your own hard work...
I don't have any ability myself...
It was Mark who gave me the chance!
Mark, if you need any
help from me in the future...
Just say the word...
Don't talk shit... Let's drink...
You can really take care of your brothers!
- Raise your glass, cheers!
- Cheers!
This glass... is for my leg to drink...
Happy!
Brother Ho, come see me
when you have time...
We have a lot of things to discuss...
I'm not interested...
You will be...
Well, I'll be going...
Sung Tse-Ho!
Come with me...
- What are you doing?
- Don't move!
What did Boss Shing talk to you about?
Bullshit!
Don't try and fool me!
Which was it, business or bullshit?
Really, it was just bullshit...
Are the goods coming in
the day after tomorrow?
- I don't know...
- Where and when is the drop off?
I don't know...
How can you know nothing
and call yourself a "big brother"?
Kit!
Don't call me Kit ever again!
Address me as sir!
Sir...
I haven't been a "big brother"
for a long time...
Where do you work?
United Taxi Company...
Is that a decent business?
Driving a taxi to pull jobs?
Where do you live?
United Taxi Company...
So somebody was still
willing to take in a thief...
You brat! Why call him a thief
when you know his name?
Don't think that having a gun
makes you so great!
If you don't mind your business,
I'll shoot you down, you cripple...
Listen boy, don't point
your gun at my head...
If you've got the guts...
Then go ahead and shoot... Shoot!
Kit!
Sir, I know I owe you so much...
Give me a chance!
Give you a chance?
I beg of you to give me a chance!
Do you know that because of you...
I lost my chance at a promotion!
Because you're a gangster!
Neither of you are to leave Hong Kong...
I'll be back to look for you!
Come, come, have a cup of tea...
Thanks, Uncle Kin!
I will deduct it from your salary...
Wow, you're so cheap!
Otherwise, how can I support my family?
Oh, you're right...
There's a girl over there
staring at you... she's pretty!
Your girlfriend?
Please come in!
No...
I want to ask you for your help...
Can you leave Hong Kong for a while?
I don't want to see Kit have a breakdown...
He can't take this pressure...
...neither can I...
I think if you left for a while...
he can get a bit better...
I won't leave!
I want Kit to see...
I've turned over a new leaf...
Can you give me the chance
to prove it to him?
Don't you think I want go out
and have fun with him, too?
Ice-skating... riding bicycles...
I don't want to lose my little brother...
Brother Ho!
Don't stay here, get inside...
There's no use in staying out here...
Brother Ho can handle
this himself, get inside!
What kind of men are they?
- They're not good, for sure...
- Brother Ho, the boss wants to see you...
I'm busy...
Give me a little face...
just have a word with the boss...
Hello?
Brother Ho, Mark is with us now...
Drop by to do some business...
Sorry, I'm not interested...
You may not interested
in doing business...
What if I told you it has to
do with your little brother...
Are you interested now?
I'm waiting for you...
OK...
Uncle Kin, I have to go out for a while...
When you have principles,
there's nothing to be afraid of...
Stand your ground!
Brother Ho... this way please...
Once you have been involved
with these gangsters...
It's so hard to start over again...
- Ho!
- Brother Ho...
Ho, I'm so glad you're back!
How are you, Mr. Yiu?
Fine... thanks for asking...
Come, talk to Shing!
You mean I'm not here to talk with you?
It's the same as talking to Shing...
I've become old, and he has
taken over some of the operation...
Brother Ho, have a seat...
We are making big money now...
I really hope to work with you again...
How can we work together?
You're still our "big brother"...
Mark will handle the
counterfeit money trafficking...
And I'll manage the flow of drugs...
Together we can reap huge
profits for the company!
There are a lot of old clients we
can win back with you aboard again...
You haven't got to the point yet...
If your brother could become our
inside man on the police force...
Everything else would be settled!
What could be better than to have
someone working for us inside the police?
Come here... There's
something I want to tell you...
How about if I don't accept?
Brother Ho, it's only out of respect for you
I've kept that dead weight Mark around!
And your brother is acting recklessly,
trailing me clay in and day out...
If I didn't care about respecting you,
he would have been dead long ago!
Shing...
One is my friend...
the other is my brother...
What face would I have
left if I agreed to this?
Insulting me isn't a big deal...
But you absolutely cannot
insult my friends!
If you dare hurt a hair on my brother...
I guarantee your days will be numbered!
We've been searching for
this murderer Mark Lee...
...for more than three years now...
It's too bad there is no extradition
treaty between Hong Kong and Taiwan...
Otherwise, we could take
down their entire operation...
The ROC police department
want to give information
through Interpol to
the Hong Kong police.
The US police department
has also taken action.
I see.
Recently we received some
very important information...
In two days there will be a shipment
of counterfeit bills to Taiwan...
...along with five hundred kilos of heroin!
Though I can't break
the case this time...
I hope to see Mark and
his men brought to justice...
Boss, Sung Tse-Ho is too
shameless... Let's take him out!
It's no good to just kill him...
Why not have some fun with him?
Act according to the plan...
I've already paid you, so where
is the drop-off point?
I'll give you the address...
Be careful...
Let's go back inside...
You're back!
Did you have dinner yet?
What are you doing?
Mr. Mok, it's Kit... I've got something...
The Thais are preparing to make
the deal with Boss Shing tomorrow...
The time and location will be...
OK, turn over your clues
tomorrow when you come in...
- After that it is of no concern to you!
- Why?
This case is not your concern anymore!
I'm afraid you spoil the whole thing...
Just give me a chance, OK?
I've already explained to you, no one
person is a hero in our department...
And you continue to act like this...
Do you know that today is my birthday?
Can you look at me?
I may as well be a flowerpot...
But you'd still rather look
at that instead of me!
This is your home... not
the police station!
Jackie...
Happy birthday...
I didn't forget...
You'd better blow out the candles
before they start a fire...
- What was your wish?
- You really want to know?
Hmm, a mystery...
Promise you won't get angry...
So tell me...
I wished that you two brothers
could be reunited...
You can't get mad...
It's nothing...
You can't get mad on my birthday...
I won't let you get angry,
or else I'll get angry, too...
Smile...
I'll get it...
What is it?
I want to speak to Kit...
Who is it?
You're can't get angry...
You promised me, you won't get mad...
- Have a seat...
- OK...
- Is today your birthday?
- Yes...
Have some cake...
Why treat him so nicely?
Kit, don't be like that...
Kit... I don't care how you treat me...
I came here to speak frankly with you...
Boss Shing is preparing to set you up...
Watch yourself...
Thanks for your concern...
Don't believe what you heard
from those hoodlums...
Clues that come that easily...
are usually fake...
You think I'm still the same Kit as before?
I only want to help you,
whether you believe me or not...
You want to help me or trick me?
Since you got out of prison...
you've done nothing but get in my way!
Can you believe me just this once?
Trust you?
I don't even have a father anymore...
Kit!
Jackie!
Brother Ho!
His feelings toward me
haven't changed at all...
Don't give up... He will come around...
Don't let anyone look down on you...
Why aren't you willing to forgive him?
Let him choose a new path...
He's responsible for Dad's death!
Why are you forcing me to forgive him?
He's the one who chose
the wrong path, not me...
I'm the cop... and he's the robber...
In terms of the law, we're
going in opposite directions...
Police!
What is it, Uncle Kin?
Your brother has been hurt
and he's in surgery now...
He's at Princess Margaret Hospital,
get over there, quick!
OK!
What happened to my brother?
It appears Shing was trying
to set him up on purpose...
Is he hurt?
Hey, you can't go in there...
I tried to stop him from going
it alone, but he insisted...
I hope you can cooperate with the police
and let's know your location
It's easy to become a hero... Jump!
Circumstances have changed,
and if you don't want to cooperate...
Well, there is no other choice...
Don't even think about telling the cops...
You should know that deep
down, everyone is for sale...
Hey! What are you doing?
From now on, Sung Tse-Ho
doesn't work here!
Stop that!
Fight!
Stop it!
We can talk this out!
Everyone stop fighting!
It's not worth it to go back to jail!
Stop fighting!
Let him go!
Brother Ho...
You idiot, get out of here!
Bastard! Don't go!
You bastards!
You fuckin' bastards!
Uncle Kin, this is my fault!
I didn't want you to be involved!
If you act like this
you've got no principle!
Their guilt is what makes them fight!
If you fight back you're right back
on the old path!
Why did you work so hard to
start again? What was all that for?
Uncle Kin! Brother Ho!
Get over here and look at this!
Mark!
Stop talking and get the first aid box!
Hurry with the first aid!
Uncle Kin, what do we do?
You guys get out of here!
Police! Submit to our search!
Is that necessary, officer?
Can't you see I'm injured?
I'll send my statement to the station...
Smartass, get out of here!
I've never noticed how beautiful
Hong Kong is at night...
But such a beautiful thing...
disappears in an instant...
It's really worthless...
Brother Ho...
Let's start all over...
Let's finish this last job...
And leave beautiful Hong Kong...
- Mark...
- We were never scared of death before...
Why are we so scared of Shing now?
Don't push me...
I'll never again go down that road...
What happened before...
it is all in the past...
It not the past yet! I'm not dead yet!
Say I let you do ten
more jobs, a hundred...
Then what? Say I let you
kill Shing, then what?
I've already lost my brother...
I don't want to lose my friend, too...
Mark, snap out of it, OK?
Don't say any more!
I don't want your sympathy!
You didn't owe me anything!
I never make my friends do
something they don't want...
I have my principles...
I've never bowed before anyone!
You think I like begging?
I've had bad luck for three years,
just waiting for this one chance!
I only want to prove myself, not to
prove I'm more powerful than others!
I want everyone to know, those things I
have lost I will most definitely get back!
What do you see in yourself?
Look at yourself and tell me what you see!
We were punished when
we were bad people...
But when we become good people...
they still follow us around!
Did you fight for your chance?
You didn't!
You never did!
I don't want to be like you...
Mark!
What happened to you?
I need to take something back...
Stay where you are!
Go get me the tape...
You haven't thought this through...
You'll be in deep trouble!
Don't think about it!
Shut it down!
- You better get out of here!
- Open the door!
Thanks, Uncle Chan!
Go after him!
This all your fault, you idiot!
I told you long ago, don't play with fire!
Idiot...
If Ho hands that tape to the police,
not only will you fall to your death...
...the whole organization will collapse!
Idiot...
Are you finished?
Calling me idiot left and right...
What did you call me when
I made you money?
I regret ever using you!
If you don't get back that plate,
I'll kill you myself!
So kill me then...
Three years ago I sold Sung Tse-Ho out...
Why should I be scared of him now?
You have to pay for that!
You and I together will sit here
together and figure it out...
Hello?
Hey, Ho! Why would you
act so cruelly to me?
Mr. Yiu, I want to speak to Shing...
Shing? Wait a moment...
Without a doubt, you've got to ask
him to give back the tape...
Brother Ho, don't try to fool me...
We can work this out...
Ten o'clock tonight
Bring two million US dollars to
the temple in exchange for the tape...
...and have a boat ready for me
at West Sandy Bay...
Is it that simple?
I want cash...
Bring it yourself!
I'll be there...
What did Ho say, idiot?
Well, what did he say?
Well?
He said he wants to have
dinner with you tonight...
OK, I'll wait for him...
Come in...
Mr. Mok, I have new information...
Sung Tse-Ho and Mark the cripple
got into a fight with Boss Shing...
They are extorting money from Shing,
and the deal is going down tonight!
Do you know the time and place?
We'll have it later...
Hello? This is...
Thanks...
Two minutes ago Boss Shing
withdrew two million US dollars...
Put the entire department
on notice to receive orders!
Yes, sir!
Mr. Mok, let me take part
in the operation...
The doctors haven't released you yet,
what are you doing out of the hospital?
I'm fine... its just a flesh wound...
You're off duty for several days...
Now go home and rest!
Look, I can lift this chair no problem!
You're not a part of this operation!
My brother is the robber, not me!
I've always done things according
to code, why are you punishing me?
If you still remember the code,
then you know why!
Since my dad died three years ago,
I've trailed Shing all the time!
- You and Ho are brothers!
- I know this case better than anyone!
- Why are you still punishing me?
- Will you lock him up?
I'll lock him up myself! I will...
I'll lock him up for certain...
Kit, get real...
Who would neglect their own home?
Or throw away their memories of youth? I
Who could bear to look
at the despair of yesterday?
And take away our smiles?
Youth does not understand
the cruel world
Ruddy cheeks are soon tainted with dust
Tears long forgotten
will dampen your face
So sing your enthusiasm,
and reach out your hands
Let me embrace your dreams
Let me see your true face
Jackie...
I'm leaving Hong Kong tonight...
You're giving up just like that?
Can you give this package to Kit
before nine o'clock tonight?
The contents are very valuable to him...
Will you come back?
The rising sun awakens the morning
The luster of the land is revived
Let the breeze carry the sound
Set your life to the music
Kit, your brother is leaving tonight...
He asked me to give this
valuable package to you...
Kit, the tape I am giving you now...
...is the proof to charge
Shing for counterfeiting...
We've arranged to make a deal
tonight at West Sandy Bay...
You can put me in prison if you'd like...
Anyway, I've decided not
to stay in Hong Kong...
Kit, what are you doing?
I have to arrest him!
- No! You can't arrest him!
- Let go!
Let go!
Kit! Kit!
Where's Ho? The food is already cold...
You know what to say, right?
Do you believe in God?
Yes... I'm God...
God is a man...
Anyone who can control
his own destiny is God!
But there are times and
situations that one can't control...
You'll either win or lose...
Hold it!
Where's the money?
Where's the tape?
I gave it to the police...
Not so fast...
There's a bomb inside!
You shouldn't fuck with me...
You scared now?
Then how can we go on with the game?
Motherfucker!
After Sung Tse-Ho arrived,
he and Master began to argue...
He told Master to give him
two million US dollars...
He said he'll be setting out to sea
from West Sandy Bay tonight...
Then I heard gunshots...
That's him!
- Are you sure?
- Yes!
- Are you willing to be a witness?
I knew that a jerk like you
would try to set me up!
You will lose...
Get out!
Get out! Get out!
If you guys are smart, you'll let him go!
Come on! Over here!
Go!
Brother Ho, get in the boat!
You go ahead...
Didn't you say we would go together?
There's still something I have to do...
I'll meet you again...
Mark, start the boat!
I'll be waiting for you...
Walk!
Let him go, or we'll kill your brother!
Don't move!
Trade one for one...
Go!
Go! Walk!
I won't let you off...
I know...
Kit!
Come over here!
This is your older brother!
Look into his eyes!
Take a good look!
No matter mistakes he made in the
past, he has paid it all back to you!
He's brave enough to change...
What can't you be brave
enough to forgive him?
Why?
Be a brother...
Shing!
Miss, you can't go over there!
Sung Tse-Ho, the police
have you surrounded!
You have three minutes to put
down your weapons and come out!
No more bullets?
I'm going to give myself up...
I won't have any problems...
But you will...
I have money...
In three days, I'll walk out of
the courtroom a free man...
With money, you can change
black into white!
These things... I have learned from you...
Too bad about your brother...
Because of you he's changed
from white to black...
You've condemned him to death!
Kit...
You haven't done anything wrong...
Our paths go in different directions...
Your path... is the right one...
I took the the wrong one before...
But now I've returned to the right one...
I only hope its not too late!
The sound of light laughter
Gives me a warm feeling
You send a strong current
of happiness into me
The sound of soft whispers
As we reach the end of a long road
We finally step into the
beautiful sunshine!
Thunderous cheers erupt
Like the setting sun
radiating golden arrows
The smile from my days
with you has reappeared!
The sound of light calling
Together we raise our heads
to look at the sky
At last the brilliant blue sky
has appeared for you!
Holding you
The soft warmth of those earlier
times comes surging back
In my heart
The innocent dreams of my
youth have not been ruined
Today, I am
Standing shoulder to shoulder
with you once more
The feelings of the past
At this moment have new freshness
Once I see you
The sweetness in your eyes strikes me
My heart
Remains completely unchanged
Today, I am
Standing shoulder to shoulder
with you once more
The feelings of the past